Chapter 3

Hellhound (3)

◆

Baby Vikir.

He was lying in the darkness of the shared nursery.

There is not much you can do with the body of a child who can’t even control his body.

He just sucks on his nanny’s milk and thinks over each situation before returning.

8 years old.

He felt mana for the first time. In the world, he was a talent worthy of being called a genius, but within the Baskervilles, he was just mediocre.

15 years old.

He has accumulated 1 circle level mana. His sword was able to light up an aura, albeit faintly.

20 years old.

He started putting himself into action in earnest. He mainly took on missions such as assassination, spying, and subjugation of barbarians.

25 years old.

Is it because the ship lived more fiercely than others? Descendants of the Baskervilles had mastered swordsmanship at a level they hadn’t reached even in their thirties.

29 years old.

The limits to which an illegitimate child were clear. The direct descendants, who had lagged behind for a while, began to run ahead of him as soon as they gained practical experience, and soon disappeared so far forward that he couldn’t even see them.

30 years old.

The gates to the Pandemonium were opened and countless demons began to invade.

35 years old.

He endured the era of destruction, accumulated a lot of practical experience, and killed more monsters than anyone else.

39 years old.

He won the war for the Empire. It was a valuable victory for the humans.

40 years old.

A hunting dog that had been loyal throughout its life. But the Baskervilles did not reciprocate that loyalty. What came back was the slander and false accusation of colluding with the demons. And then it was the guillotine.

Aww-

Hatred for Hugo Le Baskerville crept in.

When Vikir gnashed his teeth, as the nanny was startled and pulled him away from herself.

“Ah, the young master goes through this sometimes.”

She put Vikir in the cradle and got up.

Now that her shift is over, it’s time to switch to another nanny.

But.

Swoop-

The nanny, who should have gone through the door as usual, looked around her and then went to the bed across from her.

“Come on, young men. Eat up.”

The nurse started breastfeeding some of the children she had nursed earlier.

The children of the Baskervilles are raised together in one room.

It is to raise all children equally.

But what mother would treat her own child and her half-brother the same?

Some mothers memorized the characteristics of their children well and would tell the nanny and ask for a longer breastfeeding sessions.

Of course, for Vikir who did not know who his mother was, so he had no choice but to set aside all expectations.

At least until you can get food and eat it with your own hands, you will have to grow up to be able to do anything quickly.

…Right then.

A something unexpected happened.

The nanny, who looked around her, approached Vikir’s cradle again.

“Ugh. Why would Madam want to bring this to Master Vikir’s cradle?”

Lady? There are few people in this family who were called ‘Lady’.

And there is even less reason for someone like that to ask for something to be brought to him.

The nurse took out a rather large box from her bosom, and she herself did not seem to know what was in it.

Dalgrak-

The nanny tilted her head a few times as she placed the box in Vikir’s cradle.

The she stormed out of her nursery with her galloping stride.

“…….”

Vikir stared at the box next to him.

Did he have any memories like this before he regressed? There was nothing.

He lifted his head with difficulty and looked out of the cradle.

Vikir’s Cradle, quite far from the other cradles.

Something doesn’t feel right

And his instincts were right.

Creepy – Creepy –

Before long, the box was squeezed and something poked out its head.

A gift for a newborn child.

Snakes.

Two black, triangular-headed snakes were exposing their thick bodies out of the box.

Bloody Mamba.

A venomous snake is also called Chilbosa because if bitten, one dies before taking seven steps.

It is a rare species that is rarely found in the world.

Vikir half-opened his mouth in amazement.

Who released this snake here?

Apparently, the nanny also left without knowing what she had unlocked.

Vikir, who was bewildered for a moment, soon grasped the situation.

‘Come to think of it, there were often cases of babies dying mysteriously in the nursery.’

There were many cases in which children who had outstanding abilities died prematurely.

In the meantime, it was a different world from him, and he thought it was just an accidental death, an assassination from an enemy, or just bad luck.

But looking at it now, the situation is not very good.

The black hand aiming for the nursery must have been reaching out from within the family.

Shhh-

Two bloody mambas are coming towards him.

Their red mouth, gleaming fangs, seemed already covered in blood.

In the event of an emergency, all the children in this nursery could be exterminated by them.

If that happens, there will be a catastrophe unprecedented in the history of the Baskervilles.

‘……Well, that’s not too bad either.’

There is no attachment to the family at all.

However, if revenge come at the cost of self harm then it is useless.

Vikir stretched out his hand.

After going through the era of destruction, he had beaten and killed countless monsters.

He had dealt with reptilian monsters, especially those in the form of snakes, many times, and of course he was well aware of their weaknesses.

He could kill them with the body of a newborn child.

…Kwak Kwak!

Vikir stretched out his two hands and grabbed a poisonous snake each.

The place he caught was right around the nape of their neck. A place where it could not reach.

Rather, the snakes that have been preemptively attacked began to struggle.

They tried to stab Vikir with sharp scales, but body body was already hardened by the protection of the River Styx, so it was impossible.

‘I don’t know about it’s teeth, but the scales won’t hurt me.’

At the same time. Vikir operated his mana.

His body, which had been empty since he was born, was filled with mana.

It was the result of drinking the water of the River Styx to its limit.

…Pod!

His fists began to emit a twinkle of light.

It is a state that the babies in the nursery gathered here will be able to reach in the next 8 years.

That’s what Vikir did when he was less than eight months old.

Tsutsutsutsutsu……

The bodies of the two venomous snakes stiffened.

It was when a weaker creature faced a predator.

The two venomous snakes froze with their scales stiff, as if they felt unprecedented fear from the child in front of them.

Before long, Vikir’s mana-infused hands ferociously twisted the necks of the two venomous snakes.

…Wood deok!

The hide and the flesh beneath it are intact, but the bones supporting them broke.

The two venomous snakes each opened their mouths.

The pressure caused her two eyeballs to protrude and her tongue to stick out.

The two venomous snakes, whose necks were broken, shuddered at that moment and died.

Deadly venom dripped from the tips of the exposed fangs.

Next day.

All the guardian knights in the family gathered in the common childcare room at the screams of the nanny who came to work first.

Vikir, smiling brightly, held two venomous snakes with broken necks in his hands.

The Guardian Knights who saw that it was the bloody mamba, the notorious venom of the ‘Le Rogue’ Mountains, were literally surprised to the point that they didn’t belive their eyes.

Even though it was a dead snake, it was still a great disaster that such a monster was found in a nursery.

Within a few minutes, this was transmitted to Hugo, who was in the main castle, and he ran straight to the Fang castle.

Afterwards, all the nannies who worked the night shift were tortured and executed, and a really strict guard was set up in the nursery.

The culprit who released the poisonous snake was never found.

But only one person.

“…….”

A young hound dog, silently, saw through it all.

A legendary child who, since he was born, crossed the cradle of swords in the shortest time, dived in the River Styx for the longest time, and strangled two poisonous snakes in the cradle.

Vikir Van Baskerville.

He just waited quietly, lying in the cradle.

For the moment to repay his debt, the time for revenge.

…….

And eight years have passed since then.

Chapter 6

The Baskerville Dog (3)

◆

John Barrymore.

He is a butler who has been loyal to the Baskerville family for as many as four generations.

“My lord. I will give you a daily report.”

And in front of Barrymore, a middle-aged man.

A sharp nose bridge, a thick beard, and cold eyes.

The Sword Master, the Sword Master, and the Seven Pillars of National Salvation.

‘Hugo Le Baskerville’, the most famous swordsman of Baskerville, was looking at Barrymore with an expressionless face.

“This is the first report. Regarding the battle with the ‘House of Morgue’ in the ruby mines of Red Cane Mountain…….”

The Morgue family, famous for their magic, is one of the seven greatest families along with the Baskervilles.

The Baskervilles were recently having a territorial dispute with the Morgue family, over the ruby mines in the west, which subtly straddled the ends of each other’s domains.

Eventually, Hugo’s mouth opened.

“We will have an opportunity to discuss that soon. Morgue will come first.”

Hugo’s folded his hands.

Barrymore continued to report.

Hugo looked mostly nonchalant, he listened to his report without much interest.

Occasional frowning to express irritation was the only response.

Advertisement

At that time.

There was a report that Hugo showed a change in expression for the first time.

“……Because Master Vikir is ranked number one in the handwriting of this midterm evaluation of early childhood.”

Hearing Barrymore’s words, Hugo gently stroked his chin.

It was Hugo’s habit when he was satisfied, Barrymore knew this from experience.

It’s rare for Hugo to remember the name of a child in the family, so Barrymore’s expression brightened too.

Soon after, Hugo asked.

“Butler. When is the practical test for children?”

“Not long. It starts in five days. Most of the Guardian Knights of Fang Castle have already gone on a trip to prepare.”

“Then the Fang castle must have been empty.”

At that, Barrymore’s expression lifted slightly.

“Even so, the next news I want to report is about Fang Castle, Lord.”

“Did something happen?”

“That…… There are good things and there are bad things.”

“Listen to the good stuff first.”

When Hugo showed interest, Barrymore’s voice picked up a little more force.

“It is said that there was a phenomenon where two suns rose in the sky above Fang Castle.”

“Two suns?”

Hearing that, Hugo’s eyes widened slightly.

The Baskervilles tend to believed in superstitions.

“Is this an auspicious sign?”

“First of all, since the sun has risen two times, isn’t it? There is also a rumor among the Gasols that a little sun was born to assist the children.”

“……Hmm. Couldn’t someone have been playing around with mana?”

“At the time, all those skilled enough to play such pranks were on the trip to prepare for the practical exams for the youngsters.”

“Well, then that’s not a bad sign. Another sun.”

Hugo quietly nodded his head.

Originally, the rising of two suns, namely Chae-un, has been considered an auspicious sign.

“When such things appear clouds rise, good things always happen to the family. I don’t know what might happen in the Fang castle.”

Then Barrymore’s expression darkened.

“That is…… Something happened.”

“Is that the bad news I told you about? Tell me.”

At Hugo’s words, Barrymore continued his report with a calm complexion.

“There was a big fight between the young boys.”

At those words, Hugo’s expression changed completely.

“A big fight? How many died?”

“……No one died, but Master Highbro’s teeth were all damaged, Master Middlebro’s jawbone was caved in, and Master Lowbro’s right index finger was amputated. Of course, now everyone has been treated and restored to his original health.”

“Then it’s a small quarrel. Siblings naturally grow up fighting each other.”

Hugo seemed relieved and leaned back in his chair.

Then he murmured as he flipped through the reports on the triplets.

“Since we’re the only ones that are close to each other, there’s no way we could have fought with each other, right?”

“You’re right. There was friction with another young boy.”

“They are foolish. If the person is older than them, they would definitely be stronger. Even mere bastards will judge whether they are stronger or weaker before attacking you.”

Hugo clicked his tongue, and Barrymore corrected him.

“That is…… The boy who made them like that is younger.”

“What? He’s younger? So you’re saying the whole class of 8-year-olds jumped on them?”

“No. It is only one.”

At those words, Hugo’s eyes lit up again.

And in Barrymore’s report that followed, they got even more excited.

“The 1st place in the written test I mentioned earlier, Master Vikir, was the perpetrator.”

Vikir van Baskerville. 8 years old this year.

He received a call from the family head and headed for the family room that was hidden in the depths of the mansion.

When he opened the door and came in, he could see the large stature of Hugo Le Baskerville.

“Sit down.”

Even though he didn’t show any particular aura, the momentum radiating from him was heavy.

Vikir moved carefully so as not to reveal the mana hidden in his body.

‘I’m confident in hiding mana.’

The warriors who had passed through the confrontation with the demons and the long era of destruction were well versed in hiding their mana.

The way to completely hide mana like this was unknown right now.

It wasn’t a matter of strength, it was a matter of skill.

But even that has some limits, and if you have a stronger mana here, you will inevitably stand out in Hugo’s eyes.

‘I’ll have to find a way to show myself sooner or later.’

Vikir sat down on the small chair in front of him, thinking about this and that.

Hugo opened his mouth.

“You’ve grown a lot while I couldn’t see you.”

Hearing this, Vikir was a little surprised.

His voice, which was always forged like a blade and seemed like it would be cut just by hearing it, is rather dull today.

And the dialogue itself was also strange.

‘Pigs are huge, but why do they always look so small and messy every time I see them?’

Before returning, Hugo, used to say it all the time.

While watching the growth of the livestock, he gave the gaze of an impatient butcher who couldn’t sell it quickly, but today he is sending a strangely warm gaze.

It was as if he was expecting something.

“Hello, Patriarch.”

Vikir greeted me brightly like a child.

However, Hugo, who is called by the title of ‘Patriarch’, found it odd.

“My Patriarch? Okay. Not even the head of the household.”

He thought about something for a while, then changed the topic as if it was over.

He said, “I heard you crippled triplets in your senior class of 9 years old.”

“I know that they received appropriate treatment afterwards.”

“I’m not talking about physical disabilities.”

Hugo frowned.

“Isn’t their mind crippled?”

“…….”

“Since that day, I heard that they eat separately, sleep separately, and do not mix words properly. The three of them were excellent at teamwork passing the exam at the same time, but now they have completely fallen apart.”

Would that be all? These days, all three of them were scared of Vikir.

A dog that has lost its fighting spirit is useless in eternity.

But Vikir didn’t bother to say that.

But he’s just making a bold statement.

“Wouldn’t it be heavy and useless to carry three sloppy swords at once? Rather than a master sword.”

Hugo’s eyes widen at those words.

“……That’s right.”

He stroked his chin and looks down at the 8-year-old kid in front of him.

If you look at it, the corners of his mouth tickle.

“But don’t you think it was wrong to beat up his brothers?”

At Hugo’s words, Vikir questioned incredulously.

“Wrong? Why am I wrong?”

“What? Didn’t you make your brothers a mess?”

At Hugo’s question, Vikir tilted his head as if he couldn’t understand at all.

“Why is that wrong? I am stronger”

“……What?”

Vikir drove the question back at Hugo, who had a blank expression.

“How can a strong person do something wrong?”

Strong self-esteem. A world where weakness is sin.

Wouldn’t that be Baskerville?

Yet.

“…….”

The corners of Hugo Le Baskerville’s mouth began to twitch.

As he found the situation in front of him cute.

Chapter 7

The Baskerville Dog (4)

◆

Vikir knows Hugo’s personality well.

‘……Lizard.’

A cold-blooded human with blood so cold that he might be mistaken for a lizard.

He was a being who was only interested in the future of his family and his own actions.

He is a human who thought of everyone but himself as a tool, especially as a weapon.

Weapons basically exist to harm others, and it is unimaginable that weapons independently show mercy or hesitate.

It is also natural that the more weapons he nurtures, the better they would be at killing.

So it was quite possible that Hugo’s gaze at Vikir was gradually coloured with satisfaction.

“Do you think you are innocent?”

“Yes. Rather, my brothers were wrong.”

“What did they do wrong?”

“They were weak.”

A world where weakness is sin.

Wouldn’t that be Baskerville?

Vikir’s words ran right through this core family motto of the Baskerville.

It is not a sin for a lion to hunt a deer.

It was the providence of nature that the strong win against the weak, and insisting that it should be divided into crime and punishment is just foolishness.

It was Hugo’s teaching behind the tutors which stuck in his ears like nails during his childhood.

‘…So the older brothers bullied me first! Even if I try to whine, it’s useless.’

Before his return, Vikir explained his innocence and the sins of his brothers, as a normal child would usually do, but Hugo only expressed contempt.

…And those eyes were the same until the last moment when he knelt on the guillotine at the execution site.

Meanwhile.

Hugo Le Baskerville.

He clasped his hands together and covered his mouth.

And he said in a low, subdued voice.

“Your brothers were here before you.”

“…….”

“They forgave you.”

Vikir didn’t bother to answer.

You can tell that he has the experience of keeping Hugo’s side for a long time.

Perhaps the triplets did not give Hugo an answer to their liking, and instead annoyed him.

‘I must have been very intimidated. And what about forgiveness?’

Vikir replied in an emotionless voice.

“It’s okay if they are scared.”

“…….”

Hugo paused for a moment.

Finally, Hugo let out a faint laugh.

“Ha. That’s right. When I wanted to the successor, I had to work hard to become the successor.”

It was quite an unfamiliar sight for Hugo to talk about himself.

‘By the way, he had to become the successor? Can he say that by just working hard?’

Vikir, who was worried for a while at the first sound he heard, soon understood.

Hugo had risen to the position of head of the household by killing all of his older brothers.

‘Right. He only heard that the eldest son is unconditionally the one who inherit the family. Even the position of sucessor could be acquired.’

It was the moment when he realized the true nature of the Baskervilles again.

Hugo asked again.

“Whatever. The older brothers reached out first to forgive you. Do you still not feel guilty?”

“…….”

Vikir looked at Hugo in silence for a moment.

The warm eyes of his father, which he had never received in his previous life.

However, the already salty and cold frozen heart can never be melted with such feeble warmth.

…When was it before returning?

The last daughter of a family destroyed by the Baskervilles once visited Hugo in person.

After a long time, she became a nun and gave a Mass saying, “I forgive you.”

And Hugo, who heard the contents of the mass, said this.

“Wouldn’t forgiveness be just an excuse for the weak who have no power to take revenge?”

Excluding the honorifics, the lines are exactly the same as Hugo’s at the time.

In an instant, Hugo’s eyes widened.

“Hahahahahaha-”

The sound of laughter so loud that the windows trembled resounded throughout the room.

Hugo leaned back in his chair with a look of supreme satisfaction.

“This is how my child should be.”

It was the first time Vikir had ever seen him express his emotions to this extent towards his son.

The conversation with Hugo ended here.

“Barrymore.”

Hugo, who had summoned the butler, his face returned to the stoic face he knew before.

But the warmth of the embers still lingered in his voice.

“Give Vikir the key to the food storage.”

Hearing this, Barrymore’s eyes widened.

Children in the Baskervilles always eat the same food until they are 15 years old.

Water and Haggis.

It is a dough made by mashing together the meat and intestines of all kinds of animals and a little bit of vegetables.

The amount of food is provided in an unlimited amount and managed in a very hygienic manner, but was tasteless.

So, the children of the Baskerville family are crazy about sweets and chocolate that are sometimes given out when the children get good grades.

It is a system that inspired children at a very low price, cultivate a sense of competition, and further develop them into great members of Baskerville.

Knowing that, Hugo asked Vikir.

“Do you have any snacks you want to eat?”

Then Vikir answered with an innocent smile typical of an 8-year-old child.

“Chocolate!”

Hugo looked at him and nodded his head.

‘He must be thinking to the extent of ‘I even have a cuteness suitable for my age’.’

Barrymore also smiled.

Hugo beckoned Barrymore.

“Go to the food pantry and take out as much chocolate as you want. But, don’t be too greedy. Just carry what you can.”

“Yes, my lord.”

Barrymore took Vikir’s hand and headed for the door.

As they were leaving.

Hugo spoke up, turning his back to the door.

“Perform well at this midterm evaluation.”

It is unusual to receive such encouragement.

But what followed was even more unusual.

“……Don’t lose to direct descendants.”

At those words, Vikir’s eyes turned red.

Like two suns.

◆

“We greet, Master Vikir.”

Barrymore took Vikir to the kitchen outside the infant castle.

A few chefs followed suit, politely greeting him.

The food storage deep underground.

The cold air blew through the cracks in the stones met with the warm air from outside creating a slight mist.

Barrymore held up his hand to dissapating the mist inside of the warehouse.

It’s just a matter of managing mana, but it’s not something that makes you feel embarrassed when the old butler did it.

Vikir went inside.

The food eaten by the guardian knights in the family, family members over the age of 15, and other servants was neatly arranged.

“Candies and jellies are over here young master. If there is anything you would like to cook separately, I will ask the chefs to prepare it.”

At Barrymore’s kind invitation, Vikir shook his head.

“Just chocolate.”

At that, Barrymore looked down at Vikir with a slightly sorrowful look.

How much chocolate do you want to eat?

“When you’re over 15, you’ll be able to eat as much as you want.”

It was a sincere advice.

The chefs in the back took out the finest chocolates from the shelf while paying attention to the butler.

“This is the finest chocolate that the women of the House of Morgue who are reputed to be gourmets enjoy eating. This time, we also got a few cans from our side. It is said that the flavor becomes more intense if you add nuts from the south and honey from the west.”

But Vikir shook his head.

“I don’t need anything processed.”

“……Yes?”

Barrymore and the chefs looked puzzled, Vikir opened his mouth.

“I need coca beans. The type with a very strong flavor.”

Hearing that, Barrymore tilted her head.

The raw material of chocolate is coca beans.

However, unprocessed coca beans are bitter rather than sweet.

After hearing the chefs’ report, Barrymore spoke up.

“Ugh. If it’s beans with a strong flavor…… It is said that there is. In the past, the family lord personally led the senators in the family to subdue the barbarians on the western front of the territory and cultivated the vast jungles of the area as farmland. It is said that one grain of ‘Bloody Bean’, a local specialty, can make 100 liters of chocolate.”

“Good. Bring it.”

“How much should I bring?”

“As it is.”

At Vikir’s command, the chefs moved.

Before long, one of the chefs came with a small leather pouch in his hand.

The pouch, barely big enough for two fists, was filled with bright red beans.

It looks like more than 100 grains.

This is Bloody Bean. One bean has a consistency comparable to 100 liters of chocolate.

Vikir tried chewing a bean.

…Knock it!

Reaction comes right in the mouth.

It was astringent and bitter enough to tingle your entire tongue.

Vikir spat out the peas and nodded in satisfaction.

Barrymore nodded his head.

‘You really like chocolate.’

Anyway, Hugo told Vikir to give him as much food as he wanted, so it wouldn’t be a problem even if he took all these cocoa beans.

However, this single cacao bean is the amount that can produce 10,000 liters of chocolate.

Barrymore admired the 8-year-old’s greed and wisdom.

Maybe Vikir will gorge on his favorite chocolate for the rest of his life.

“Young master. Shall I process this and bring it to your room?”

…However.

Vikir gave an answer that made everyone wonder.

“No processing required. This is enough.”

Apparently, he didn’t want it for eating.

Chapter 10

Hounds of Hell (3)

◆

Vikir recalled.

It was just a few days ago.

Something similar to the award Hugo Le Baskerville gave in the name of getting first place in the written exam.

‘Do you have any snacks you want to eat?’

‘Chocolate!’

‘Go to the food storage and take out as much as you wants. But, don’t be too greedy. Just what you can carry.’

At that time, Vikir had been handed over the key to the food warehouse.

In the cellar following Barrymore, Vikir obtained a bag of chocolate beans.

‘In the past, the Lord personally led knights to subjugate the savages on the western front and reclaimed the vast jungles of the area as farmland. It is said that one grain of ‘bloody bean’, can make 100 liters of chocolate.’

Bloody Bean. A magical bean that boasts a rich flavor that one bean can make 100 liters of chocolate.

Vikir took out a single bloody bean from the sack he was wearing around his waist.

And he looked at the hellhound, which had been very slow while going around the water, and was now rushing towards him.

The way it was rushing towards him with its mouth wide open is as if asking for something to be thrown into its mouth.

In the eyes of Vikir, it looked like that.

…Fick!

Vikir flicked with a bean into the hellhound’s mouth.

And the effects were immediate.

…Yelp!

A hellhound swallowed something that flew into its mouth.

The guy started to stagger.

[Cahang! Crack! Yep!]

Its mouth started frothing, and sticky mucous vomit trickled down.

It started convulsing.

It heart beat quickened as if it were going to burst, and it started bleed ing from the eyes.

‘As expected.’

Vikir nodded his head.

It was a fact known to all hunters who had gone through the era of destruction.

That is the fact that canine monsters are weak to chocolate.

The substances like chocolate beans are like poison to dogs.

Even if it was a hound from hell, this was similar.

“Let’s see. Vomiting of mucus, difficulty breathing, incontinence, diarrhea, increased body temperature, increased heart rate, loss of appetite, convulsions, seizures, severe agitation…… And then death?”

Vikir grabbed a blunt shortsword.

Then, he walked after the hellhound as it staggered away into the depths of the forest.

“The blow to the stomach and heart must have come first. The liver is next.”

However, a hellhound’s stomach, heart and liver were protected by ribs that are harder than steel.

And Vikir couldn’t squeeze through the gaps with the blunt shortsword he currently had.

In that case, it is best to aim for a place that is slightly off the ribs and still weakened by the chocolate.

“……The answer is height.”

The lower abdomen, which the hellhound’s ribs can’t cover, and the kidneys, which are overworked by the toxin from the chocolate.

Vikir laid his shortsword and stabbed it hard.

His blade was blunt, so he couldn’t cut or penetrate, but it was enough to damage the muscle, and kidneys beneath.

[Kang!…]

The more the shock comes tothe kidney, the weaker the kidney and the stronger the toxins.

The hellhound dropped on the floor, slowly died

Vikir cut off the last breath of the hellhound, which had become irresistible.

Hellhounds are monsters of the canine family, and at the same time, they are monsters of the hell who roam around with the hellfire swallowed in their stomachs.

If you don’t kill it, you won’t know when it will become a threat again, like an ember reviving from the ashes.

“I’ll have to take care of it.”

Vikir raised his shortsword and completely extinguished the hellhound’s last spark of life.

Puck! Puck! Puck! Wow!

With his blunt shortsword, there was no answer other than to beat it.

Yet.

An amazing thing happened.

Tsutsutsutsutsu……

When the hellhound died, an intangible aura escaped from its corpse and settled into Vikir’s body.

What many people call “experience,” “effort,” or “karma,” “karma.”

When this mysterious and magical energy obtained by killing monsters accumulates in the body, it leads to strengthening of the body.

Vikir single-handedly defeated a high-ranking monster that children of her age could not dare imagine, and as a result, his body became even more powerful.

In addition to the blessing of the Styx River, the experience gained from killing a hellhound was added.

Vikir’s body is now impervious to any amount of poison, magic, or other physical force.

“……Hmm. Are my bones thicker now? I also seem to have grown taller.”

The shortsword in my hand became much lighter than before.

Since the weight of the sword could not suddenly decrease, it must be said that the strength of the grip has increased.

Boom- boom-

No other 8-9 year olds handle the knife as if wielding it with one hand, which is difficult to wield even with both hands.

However, there is still a long way to go before he regains his former strength.

‘At this pace, I’ll be able to recover all my strength before the coming-of-age ceremony.’

Vikir is only 8 years old now. The level is Advanced Sword Expert.

The other Baskerville would only reach it after the coming-of-age ceremony.

After the next seven years, he was more than confident enough to regain the power of his previous life.

‘Right now, if I get first place in the practical test, since there’s a reward.’

Vikir looked down at the hellhound’s corpse with a satisfied expression.

If the corpse of this monster, which is still hot, is brought to the family, it is a matter of course that it won first place in the practical evaluation.

Going out of the boundary area could be a bit of a problem, but it’s a rebuke to the guardian knights in charge and rather praise from the examinee’s point of view.

An 8-year-old kid went out of the border area that even knights struggle with, and went to the forbidden zone to catch a dangerous grade B+ monster, and that alone!

He could already picture Hugo’s expression.

…Hung!

Vikir grabbed the hellhound by the tail and began to drag it away.

The corpse of a monster is subject to gravity and different laws from the human world because its soul is held in the demon realm.

Because of that, Hellhound’s corpse was much heavier than it seemed, but Vikir’s strength was different from that of a normal 8-year-old, so it didn’t matter.

Deodeuk-deuk-woodeuk!

Vikir continued to move forward.

It was an uphill road back.

Now to go back and submit Hellhound’s corpse to the Guardian Knights.

And when he thought of the reward, a smile formed on Vikir’s lips.

Vikir was waiting for a huge reward that he would never have dared to dream of in his lifetime, a treasure that no one even knows the real value of in this day and age.

…At that time.

Vikir stopped looking around.

Grrrrr……

The cries that flowed from the depths of the sea behind them.

The howl coming from deep in the throat is getting closer.

“……Oops.”

Vikir put down the hellhound’s corpse for a moment.

I forgot.

Hellhounds are monsters that live in packs.

Yet.

Fires began to burn in the darkness of the sea of trees.

Eleven Hellhounds came and surrounded Vikir.

However.

“…….”

Vikir just grinned, unfazed in the slightest.

Rather, the hellhounds who faced that smile just shrank their bodies low and growled as if they were anxious.

Do they recognize the danger?

It seems that even those who passed through the era of destruction and passed through another round of reincarnation could not wash away the smell of blood that was deeply embedded in their souls.

Just like Bloody Mamba, the venomous snake who froze at the sight of Vikir in the cradle, it seems that the enemy and the Hellhounds of Black Mountain did not dare to act carelessly in front of Vikir, who reveals his life in earnest.

Before long, Vikir opened his mouth.

“Come on guys. There are still a lot of beans left.”

Bloody bean beans rattle at the waist.

Considering the body that became stronger after catching one hellhound, the growth rate when he could kill the hellhounds gathered here… he couldn’t even guess.

When the Vikir and the hellhounds were in such a tense confrontation.

I’m sorry……

The ferocious hellhounds suddenly curled their tails between their crotches and began to withdraw.

“……?”

Vikir was a little surprised.

A hellhound that once bares its teeth will never show its back.

But now, the hellhounds were running away in fear.

No matter how heinous the killing intent that Vikir spewed out was, he still had the body of an 8-year-old child, so it wasn’t enough to deal with all of them.

What then?

What external factors could cause these hellhounds to run away with their tails down?

Eventually, Vikir soon learned what it was.

Grrrrr……

The sound of spit and brimstone boiling.

The owner of this growl who made all hellhounds scared.

Six eyes burning in the dark.

Three heads poking out of the root hole of the sea.

“…Did something like this live here?”

A top-notch monster that makes even surprised him.

<Cerberus>

Risk level: A+

Size: 7m

Discovery Location: Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain 7th

Ridge

-Aka “Hell’s Guard Dog”

It was not interested in the ghosts who went to hell, but the ghosts who wanted to get out of hell are immediately torn to pieces by it.

It lives deep in hell, where all the evil ghosts finally head, and leads to the ultimate of monsters of the canine species.

The three-headed dog, which symbolizes hell itself, appeared.

Chapter 15

Solitary (2)

◆

Inner Library

It is a large library located deep in the Baskerville family’s main castle, and its size rivals the ranking within the Empire.

“Come to think of it, this is the first time I’ve come in and seen it myself.”

Vikir passed through the entrance guarded by several knights and entered the restricted area.

When he had presented the pass signed by Hugo himself, no one dared to stop him.

Some knights even gave a salute with a light smile.

Before long, Vikir stood in front of the passage leading to the depths of the universe.

This library, made by directly drilling a hole in the rock wall, was comparable to the mouth of a giant monster.

Books were piled up all over the place, looking down at Vikir.

“I’ll have to hurry up a bit.”

Vikir looked at his library, thinking about the time left.

His heart was in a hurry, but his steps and gaze moved slowly.

The unique feeling of old books, the smell of ink and dust.

But he didn’t feel particularly cozy.

Books discussing techniques for dealing with weapons, calculation methods for killing enemies with the shortest route, and efficient and logical killing theories.

And the library where they are tightly packed together.

Numerous swordsmen from previous generations who existed in the history of the Baskervilles are engaged in a silent war of words, remaining only in theory.

Is that why?

Rather than stepping into a library, it felt like walking through the corridors of a prison where ruthless and cold homicidal maniacs were imprisoned.

Vikir felt a stabbing gaze from the swordsmanship textbooks.

And Vikir soon got used to all of this.

Tak-tak-tak-

The sound of footsteps sinking into the abyss of the corridor.

The deeper you go into the library, the older books you can see.

‘Cutting front teeth’ swordsmanship, ‘mincing molars’ swordsmanship, ‘piercing fangs’ swordsmanship, “double-bite double tooth” swordsmanship, “hidden tooth” swordsmanship…… ,

Familiar swordsmanship textbooks, swordsmanship textbooks he wanted to learn so much in his previous life, and swordsmanship textbooks that were so powerful that he had never dared to dream were lined up neatly like teeth.

The locks to prevent theft or thieves’ access were firmly locked.

Usually, collateral and illegitimate children, no matter how much mana they have and how much experience they have in practice, it is difficult for them to learn more than 4 types of swordsmanship.

Direct descendents learn at least 5-level swordsmanship, elites among direct descendents learn 6-level swordsmanship, and elders learn 7th-level swordsmanship.

Hugo Le Baskerville has now mastered the 7th Baskerville, and the seven teeth he draws have made him one of the most powerful figures on the continent and a sword master.

As it is a rivalry with the head of the House of Morgue, known as the great wizard of the 7th circle, the inaction must be similar to some extent.

Vikir paused his steps.

In the vast library, there are a sea of books that you can’t tell which book is in which place.

In one of them, he could see the book Hugo gave him.

A bookshelf with several layers of locks on it, befitting a valuable collection.

When he matched the key Hugo gave him, the book hidden inside was revealed.

<Baskerville Carnivore, Twice-Stuck Tooth>

A book that contains noble swordsmanship that Vikir would never have dreamed of in his previous life.

Vikir picked it up and looked it over.

According to the shape of the teeth drawn by the trajectory of the knife, the methods of cutting, stabbing, blocking, crushing, cutting, and mincing are described.

And this swordsmanship manual was discussing how to draw a total of six teeth.

Naturally, Hugo must have thought it would be unreasonable for 8-year-old Vikir to memorize them in one day.

So, with a certain amount of goodwill and a certain amount of belittling, he would have allowed Vikir to read the book on meat-eating swordsmanship.

However, Vikir was a skilled swordsman who has lived 40 years and was an elite Baskerville among Baskervilles who survived even after going through the age of destruction.

Of course, he had mastered the theories of swordsmanship 1 to 4.

To the extent that he already guessed and established the theory of the 5th fang, which he had not formally learned.

The time when he was stagnant because he did not know the right way.

The formula for rising one’s status that one longed for with a burning thirst.

“……Right. After drawing the fourth tooth, I had to break the flow of mana once. That’s why I couldn’t create a fifth tooth!”

Vikir finally felt his thoughts clear up.

It took only about 3 hours to understand and memorize the knowledge he had gained.

Of course, it was thanks to the experience accumulated over and over while staying on 4 fangs for almost 20 years.

Having memorized the entire book, Vikir soon closed it.

It’s good that he figured out the way to go over to 4th fang and go to 5th and 6th fang, but in fact, that’s not the real purpose of being here today.

Vikir returned to the very beginning of the Inner Library.

It was a space that even knights who stood guard and servants who cleaned the library could pass through.

“What? Young master. Why did you come out again?”

“What have you forgotten? We will bring it to you.”

“If you are hungry, shall we bring you a meal?”

Servants come to talk kindly.

Judging from the subtle respect and fear imbued in his gaze, it seems that the rumors of this practical skills evaluation have already spread.

But Vikir shook his head.

“I’m done with my errands.”

The servants were also surprised by those words, and even the guardian knights who were standing guard were surprised.

“Already?”

“Watch a little more and then come out.”

“Do you still have a lot of time left?”

Everyone didn’t say anything, but they looked very sorry.

It must be so.

To refuse the swordsmanship textbooks that were like treasures stored deep in the Inner Library and to leave them out in a matter of hours.

It is understandable that they feel sorry for them, as these are valuable collections that are worth reading even at the risk of their lives.

Even if it was Vikir before the return, it would have been the same.

But Vikir was unconcerned.

“Before I leave, I plan to read other books as well, so stop worrying and do what you have to do.”

At the same time. Vikir headed to the shallowest floor of the Inner Library, where miscellaneous books were collected.

Some of the knights, who were shining a watchful eye, whispered while watching such a Vikir.

“If it were me, I would have read the swordsmanship textbooks in the depths. I must have memorized it like crazy.”

“He is still young and doesn’t know its full value. He would regret it for the rest of your life when you get older.”

“I have to tell the others not to worry. It’s because he is reading insignificant miscellaneous books like that.”

However, if they had seen Vikir’s expression back to them, they wouldn’t have thoughtlessly talked like that.

Vikir was rummaging through the books with a zeal.

Nobody cared about these books and they were a jumbled mess on this dusty bookshelf.

Vikir searched slowly and painstakingly.

And he was able to find what he was looking for within a few hours.

The edge of the library, a place that everyone could see, but everyone passed by without thinking.

There was an old book stuck there.

It seems that there is no preservation magic applied because it is quite dusty.

“…….”

Vikir stood for a long while, staring at the title of the book.

<Lurking Ambush>

A basic book of type 1 that even the children of the Baskervilles did not care to read.

An old book classified as a swordsmanship textbook.

But who in this world knew the value of this book?

Only Vikir, who had lived through the age of destruction, knew.

This book is the Baskerville’s greatest treasure!

Vikir pulled out the book.

It seemed to have been on the bookshelf for a very long time, and at first it did not come out well.

It wasn’t until after I pulled out and put away a few books that were blocking my way that it was pulled out and revealed to the world.

“…A lurking ambush.”

Having succeeded in extracting the book, Vikir carefully swiped it with his hand.

And he turned the page.

Pararak-

He quickly turned through the pages.

And soon, the reason why this book was classified as a miscellaneous book was revealed.

A torn page can be seen in the middle of the book.

A sparse book, as if a few pages had been knocked out.

Torn marks are evident on every important page. Of course, the contents were cut off and not connected.

Because of this, no one could understand the contents of this book, and as a result, it must have been classified as such an insignificant miscellaneous book.

But.

‘……I know.’

Vikir. He memorized what was written on the torn pages of this book.

Because the memories of participating in the ‘Operation to Recapture Torn Pages’ or ‘Operation to Restore Missing Teeth’ were still clear in his head.

At that time, the hound that crossed countless lines and collected all the pages that had been torn and lost was Vikir van Baskerville!

Chapter 16

Solitary (3)

◆

It all started by accident.

Before the regression, Vikir’s hunting party, the Hound Group, was raiding the dungeons that straddled the border between the Enemy and Black Mountain when they found a strange artifact.

It was a fragment of a swords manual.

It was a single torn page.

Realizing that what was written on it was strange, Vikir memorized it in his mind.

When he handed in the page in question, Hugo immediately realized that it contained something out of the ordinary.

Hugo searched through his entire library to find a book that matched this page.

What he eventually found was a swordsmanship book titled The Lurking Ambush.

It was an ancient book, found deep in the shallow shelves of miscellaneous books, not in the restricted area where the higher martial arts were concentrated.

The sudden discovery of this sword technique, buried in an unknown location, had set the entire Baskerville Street on fire.

“This sword art is the essence of our Baskerville.”

Hugo raves.

At first glance, the sword technique was insignificant, but with the addition of the missing pages, the system was completely redefined.

A sword that would seemingly defend itself against an enemy’s attack, then suddenly leap out and bite down on the point of death, with the sole purpose of inflicting pain on the enemy.

This sword art, which must have been written long ago by some ancestor named Baskerville, describes how to draw ten teeth.

The Baskerville Tenth Form.

Hugo, who had achieved the rank of Sword Master with only seven techniques, couldn’t help but be intrigued.

…But even with Vikir’s discovery of the missing first half, the book was still incomplete.

There were more missing pages in the second half.

The torn pages totaled seven.

Except for the one that Vikir found, the other six were lost.

Hugo spent the next several years collecting the torn pages of this “‘Lurking Ambush’”.

The Baskervilles were relentless in their pursuit.

After investing vast amounts of time and money, Hugo realized that the torn pages of the Swordsmanship Book were hidden deep within the estates of each of the seven families that supported the empire.

Naturally, Hugo set out to retrieve them one by one.

It was a project he called Operation Reclaim the Torn Pages or Operation Restore the Missing Teeth.

Vikir shook his head from side to side as he recalled the memory.

He could still smell the blood at the end of his nose.

“…It was a long, drawn-out operation.”

Hugo unleashed the dogs to retrieve the page.

Whether they knew about the torn pages or not, the resistance from the other families was fierce.

For them, it was a matter of course.

No one would look good with someone else’s hounds bursting into their courtyard.

The Baskervilles practically declared war on all the other houses.

Countless Baskerville hounds perished under the weight of it.

The number of siblings and companions I had grown up playing with had shrunk at an unbelievable rate.

The familiar faces of yesterday are nowhere to be seen in the dining hall.

The gaps left by the missing teeth were filled with new ones, which fell out just as quickly.

The one permanent tooth that didn’t fall out through all that gnashing of teeth was Vikir’s.

Vikir became a vicious right-handed black dog, fighting and fighting and fighting.

Eventually, he gathered the seven missing pages and brought them to his master.

A few fingers and toes, a pair of ears, ugly burns and cuts covering his entire body, and his lost brothers.

The reward for all this was simple and straightforward.

“Well done.”

A single word of praise from Hugo’s mouth. Why did he think it was enough at the time?

“ …It was a stupid life.”

Vikir gritted his teeth.

Before the regression, Hugo had used all the things that Vikir and the hounds had asked for to provide for himself and his two sons.

Hugo’s cultivation had risen beyond the seventh degree to the ninth, and the honor of Ironblade Baskerville had soared.

The blood of the hounds and the flesh of the dead lay beneath him.

“That will not happen in this life.”

Vikir closed his eyes and recalled the pages in his mind.

Everything that had been written on those lost pages was in his mind.

Nevertheless, the reason why the pre-regression Vikir couldn’t go beyond the fourth teeth was because he didn’t know the original.

The pages he remembered were sparse, only seven pages at most.

Without the original, they were useless.

…But not now.

In Vikir’s hands now was the original copy of the ‘Lurking Ambush’ sword technique!

Though seven pages had been torn out, the missing information was still perfectly clear in Vikir’s mind.

The experience of fighting through multiple layers of siege, sometimes with no way to keep the pages themselves intact, and carrying them in his mind, shines through.

Soon, Vikir began to read the book.

…10The first step of a decadal eclipse corresponds to a solar eclipse. The moment a sword is drawn and shows aggression in its first trajectory, all swordplay from then on has an innate limitation…

Indeed.

If an ignorant person were to read this book, it would be treated as a bunch of nonsense.

What’s the point of having 10 formulas?

But as soon as the torn pages are reconstructed and the blanks are filled in, what was once a bunch of bluster and rhetoric becomes the puzzle pieces that make up a masterpiece.

Vikir notices that the gaze of his surroundings has completely disappeared, and he moves his body accordingly.

Four teeth, honed to the limit before his regression. After that, the story begins in earnest.

The book explained how to reveal the fifth tooth, how to make the sixth tooth, how dangerous the seventh tooth was, when to reveal the eighth tooth, if the ninth tooth actually existed, and what the tenth tooth was.

Even though he didn’t have enough mana and his body was immature for an eight-year-old, he would surely be able to recreate all of these things someday.

‘…15 years old. Within it, he regains all of his pre-regression powers.’

Of course, it doesn’t end there.

After that, you will go beyond the fifth degree, to the sixth and seventh degrees, which were unattainable before the regression.

The stain of the past, the time when you were pushed aside, beaten, and ignored by your superiors because you didn’t have the aura of a Graduate, yet didn’t have the swordsmanship to match, will never have to happen again.

“I’ll start by memorizing the contents of the book.”

As soon as the memorization is finished, the book will disappear from the world forever.

Then Hugo won’t find it, and he won’t have to make nine teeth.

Pretty sweet revenge for an eight-year-old, don’t you think?

Vikir laughed, though dryly.

He still had more than twelve hours to go in the Mansang Library, no matter how little time he took.

For the children of Baskerville Street, it would not be too difficult to memorize a small book in that time.

Half a day from now.

Unaware of what she would become afterward, Vikir read the book.

And then, at exactly 11 hours and 50 minutes from now.

…Boom!

A small fire broke out in the shallowest part of the Great Library, in the section where the janitors were gathered.

No injuries. No fatalities.

Damage was minimal, with one tome burned to the ground.

It was a small enough incident that even the servants shrugged it off.

And then, at exactly 11 hours and 50 minutes from now.

…Boom!

A small fire broke out in the shallowest part of the Great Library, in the section where the janitors were gathered.

No injuries. No fatalities.

Damage was minimal, with one tome burned to the ground.

It was a small enough incident that even the servants shrugged it off.

Chapter 19

Bared Teeth (2)

◆

A rare prodigy in Baskerville.

A young warrior who became a perfect Sword Expert beginner at the age of only eight.

“Is there anything bigger than an orc?”

Vikir’s words caused the training center to heat up.

The members of House Baskerville are basically a cold people who don’t care about other people, except for one thing: when it comes to battle, they’re always interested.

That was true even for the cold-blooded Hugo.

“…Hmm.”

Hugo began to think.

Watching him, Vikir thought to himself.

“It’s better to show power in moderation.”

It wasn’t that he hadn’t thought about it.

If anything, it would be less alarming for Hugo to see his achievements at a very young age.

Showing promise at a young age would also give him an excuse to stay off Hugo’s radar.

Such as being sent to the backcountry or studying in the Imperial Capital.

‘…Or, perhaps, admission to the Academy.

The third hand was an unwelcome one, so he put it on hold, shaking his head to clear his thoughts.

It was time to focus on the here and now.

Hugo, meanwhile, was done thinking.

“Vikir has a point. You’re at the age where you need to get your hands dirty.”

It wasn’t the right thing to say to an eight-year-old, but it made sense, at least within Baskerville.

Hugo continued.

“It seems that the orcs from far away are not good enough for my son’s castle. Are there higher beasts in your family’s foraging grounds?”

You’d think they’d find a better bug in the bug bowl.

But in the Baskervilles’ collection, every single one of them is an abomination.

They’re no match for an eight-year-old.

Knowing this, no one, including Deacon Barrymore, speaks easily.

Hugo, unable to bear the silence, spoke first.

“Come to think of it, isn’t there an object that you captured as an experiment when you were exterminating the barbarians?”

“Yes, …. There is only one left.”

Deacon Barrymore answered matter-of-factly.

Hugo smirked.

“It must be weak from not being fed for so long.”

“Ha, but they’ll be just as fierce, I’m afraid, and not much of an opponent for one who’s just turned eight years old….”

“Well, if he does, the Guardian Knights will stop him, and that’s the least of the butler’s worries.”

Hugo waved his hand dismissively at Deacon Barrymore’s concern.

His deliberation was brief, his decision even shorter.

Soon, the Guardian Knights were pulling Vikir’s opponent from the depths of the cellar.

Thump, thump, thump, thump.

The earth shook faintly.

Then, a gigantic creature began to emerge, wearing a variety of heavy cuffs and restraints.

It had a short neck, two arms and legs, grotesquely twisted teeth, weighed over 400 kilograms, and stood four meters tall.

<Troll

Danger Rating: C

Size: 4 meters

Found in: Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, Ridge 2

-A cannibal with a massive physique and a vicious mind. They are mostly responsible for the disappearance of Huazhen people who enter the mountains.

Possessing inscrutable regenerative powers, they do not understand the concept of mortal wounds and never die unless their throats are completely severed.

A green-skinned giant goblin.

Sticky saliva oozes from its severed gums, torn lips, and protruding fangs.

[Grrrrr-grrrrrr!]

The troll rattled the chains and heavy lead weights around his neck, wrists, and ankles.

It looked like it had been starving for a very long time.

“….”

Vikir squinted at the troll in front of him.

Then, as soon as the troll stepped out into the center of the smoke screen. The hunt was on.

The pot.

Vikir lunged at it, short sword at the ready.

Hugo and several of the older Baskervilles looked on in amazement as he showed no sign of fear.

And then.

Boom.

The troll’s arm flailed.

Vikir ducked low, dodging the troll’s fist and digging into the blind spot in his side.

Time to deliver the killing blow!

But.

Wham!

Vikir didn’t actually stab the troll in the side.

He simply walked past him and reset his stance.

Hugo smirked.

“Good call.”

Zagoro trolls are highly regenerative, able to heal from wounds to their flanks and stomachs.

It’s a waste of energy unless you’re trying to hit them where it’s going to hurt, which is why Vikir didn’t bother trying to pick their holes.

Thud, thud, thud, thud.

The troll continued to attack Vikir.

They pounded the ground with their fists and stomped their feet.

Normally, an 8-year-old Baskerville would have been overwhelmed by the sight of these attacks, and would have made a series of mistakes, but… Vikir was different.

“It’s slow, so there’s no tension.”

An old soldier who had spent the last forty years on the battlefield. There’s no way he could lose his composure under this kind of pressure. It’s harder to hold back a yawn.

Vikir had been dodging the trolls’ attacks with a relaxed demeanor.

In fact, it was the trolls who were losing health with each rampage.

The seasoned Baskervilles watched in amazement.

“You’re trying to drain the troll’s strength? That’s amazing.”

“Is he really eight years old? I can’t believe it.”

“Heh, heh, heh, I never thought I’d see such an ahae in my family. Live long and see.”

Vikir’s judgment is always spot-on, and he follows the best route.

The troll grows increasingly unruly as he struggles with the heavy restraints.

But he is rapidly losing his reserves of health.

Its attacks became less accurate and its speed even slower. The patterns were becoming simpler and simpler.

Vikir watched the troll’s self-destructive demeanor, waiting for the one moment that would decide the game.

And then.

Grrrrr!

The troll began to lunge at him, throwing his whole body at him.

Vikir realized it was time to move out of the way and quickly jumped forward.

The body of an eight-year-old child can dodge a troll’s attacks, but it can’t kill a troll.

Not even a genius.

That was common knowledge, and Vikir knew it well.

If he unleashed his hidden powers, he might be able to kill a troll, but that would complicate matters greatly.

So Vikir had been waiting for this moment to kill the troll, to make it as easy as possible.

Quack, quack, quack!

The troll lunges, and Vikir uses the momentum to his advantage.

Vikir uses the momentum of the troll’s heavy body to thrust his blade in from the opposite direction, cutting through the tough layers of leather and muscle and severing the nerve bundles in its neck.

And then.

…Whoosh!

A faint gaseous aura emanates from the tip of Vikir’s blade.

It’s the same one that wowed everyone in the orc battle earlier.

Kiririk-

Vikir’s aura formed a distinctive tooth-like shape and flew straight for the troll’s throat.

Pow!

One sharp fang sank deep into the troll’s neck.

In the next instant, Vikir twisted his body and slipped through the gap between the troll’s sides, instantly blasting a gaping hole in the troll’s neck.

“Oooooh!”

Everyone watching gasped in amazement.

Vikir’s seasoned battlefield experience was disguised as genius here.

…But.

[Grrrrrrrr!]

The troll was not dead.

He jammed his fist into the hole in his neck and grunted as he tended to the wound.

A faint sigh escaped from the onlookers.

“Oh, no. I guess one Baskerville isn’t enough for a troll.”

“It’s definitely a little harder with a gaseous aura.”

“It’s a shame, but it’s still a monumental feat for an eight-year-old to have gotten this far.”

Baskerville 1 meal. You can’t catch a troll with one tooth.

Vikir knew that already.

True, with Beelzebub’s ability to bleed, the troll would die a natural death in time, but… there was no point in winning that way.

“That’s enough. Any more could be dangerous, so let’s stop here….”

Hugo raised his hand to stop the fight.

“Restraints.”

Vikir opened his mouth.

“Release the restraints.”

At those words, the faces of all the Baskervilles stiffened.

Unshackling a troll, at this point?

“….”

“….”

“….”

All eyes turned to Vikir and Hugo.

“….”

Even the mighty Hugo was dumbfounded.

Then, slowly, his mouth opened.

“My son, you have already proven your worth. It is the mark of a swordsman to walk away when he is satisfied.”

The tone was stern. All of the Baskervilles were surprised by Hugo’s demeanor, something they had never seen before.

But the surprise was short-lived, as Vikir’s words drew everyone’s attention back to him.

“We’re almost there, and if I don’t kill you on the next strike, I’ll end it cleanly.”

A declaration of war.

Vikir’s words startled all the Baskervilles, including Hugo.

How on earth were they going to take down this troll whose tenacity was unmatched?

“….”

Hugo fell silent. The signal to resume the battle.

[Caw! Caw! Caw!]

The trolls rampaged.

Several of the Guardian Knights stepped out of the way of the troll’s rampage, removed the cuffs and chains, and led him back out into the open.

Then. The troll, now completely free, pushed himself to his feet.

His eyes, red and bloodshot, no longer even pupils.

[He-ahhhhhh!]

With a guttural roar, the troll lunged at Vikir with all its might.

But Vikir could only stare coldly at the troll.

“How far should I show my power?”

The question had already been answered earlier in the evening.

…Pow!

The tip of Vikir’s short sword glows a little brighter than before.

Some of the veterans recognized it immediately. The density of Vikir’s aura had changed.

But there was no time to wonder about it, as Vikir continued with his next move.

Kiririk- Karak!

The tip of the blade flashed towards the charging troll. Fangs clearly visible.

The troll breaking free of its restraints, running even faster, and the force of the reaction even stronger.

And then.

…Poof!

The troll is faster and stronger than before, and the tip of the blade is thrust back into his body, faster and stronger than before.

And then.

There were two teeth sinking into the troll’s neck this time.

The first tooth ripped a hole in the troll’s neck.

And a second tooth, smaller and fainter, but clearly visible, biting ferociously into the side of the troll’s neck.

Baskerville Two-Thirds.

And Sword Expert Intermediate.

…! …! …! …! …!

All the Baskervilles, including Hugo, stand in place with their mouths agape.

…Thud!

The troll behemoth, decapitated, fell to his knees on the ground.

Chapter 21

Camus Morgue (2)

◆

Camus dropped a bombshell.

“Are you the thief who stole our ruby mine?”

The 8-year-old girl’s bold question instantly froze the room.

First, the servants of the two families stiffened on the spot.

“….”

“….”

Even the mighty Adolf Morgue stiffened in confusion.

Hugo, too, remained silent, looking somewhat dazed.

“What did I just hear?” is a thought that peeks through his poker face.

The Baskervilles’ family room is silent, as if no living thing exists.

The silence is broken once more by the camouflage.

“Give it back, Ruby Mine.”

The camouflaged creature strides forward and holds out a white palm in front of you.

Hugo, meanwhile, was still dumbfounded by the glare.

He’d never heard anyone say that to his face before, and even more so when it came from an eight-year-old.

Then. Adolf was the first to realize.

“Hey, kid, what’s with the sudden rudeness?”

“I told you earlier, Uncle, that this man stole our ruby mine.”

“Hey, hey, hey, rascal, when did I!”

“Before you got out of the carriage. Starting this month, the number of research rubies paid to me will be reduced, and it’s all because of that stupid old mustached thief.”

“This, this, this, this rascal, me, when!?”

“If you’re asking when, about an hour and forty-two minutes ago? Come on, I heard it clearly….”

The Camus gets a little sour.

At this point, Adolf felt a cold sweat break out.

He didn’t have to look away to realize it. The temperature in the room had dropped several degrees.

“…Hmm. An unfortunate mustached old man, and a thief?”

A cold voice came from the front.

Hugo turned to look at it, narrowing his eyes.

Adolf pulled out his handkerchief, covered his mouth, and coughed.

“Hmph. There seems to be a misunderstanding. I’ll be sure to clear that up later.”

“What does a puppy know? There is no need to explain to me the problem of the house education in the Morgue.”

Hugo’s words were barbed, but he seemed to have already lost his temper.

Adolf turned to the Camus, thinking it was an accusation.

“Camus, what a rude thing to say to an elderly member of a friendly neighborhood family.”

“But what my uncle said….”

“Even if the servants around you said something bad, you shouldn’t pass it on. There are many things in the rumor mill that are inflated… well, there are many things that are diminished.”

Adolf and the Camus turned to face each other.

Suddenly, Hugo was starting to get annoyed with the whole situation.

His mind flashed back to Butler Barrymore’s report the other day.

“First report. About the bloodshed with House Morgue at the ruby mines on Red Mountain….”

‘We’ll have a chance to discuss that soon enough. The Morgue will come to me first.’

The ruby mines were actually an old dispute.

On the border between Baskerville and Morgue, the so-called ‘Joint Security Zone’, there is a mine that pumps out high quality rubies.

The problem is that the mine’s entrance is above ground on Morgue’s territory, while the underground vein runs beneath Baskerville’s territory.

Due to the angle of the vein, there is only one mining route that can be accessed from the surface, and that is from the mine on Morgue’s estate.

However, mining along this vein will inevitably lead to digging beneath the Baskerville estate.

<Imaginary view of Camus mine>

As a result, the Morgue have been trying to find a way around this.

The most tried and true is to secretly dig a tunnel and mine rubies.

However, the Baskervilles’ hounds, with their keen sense of smell, picked up on the signs like ghosts and raided the Morgue’s mines.

There was bloodshed on several occasions, but nothing was ever reported in public, so relations between the two families remained good on the surface.

Even though it was boiling over on the inside.

And so it was that Adolf Morgue, who had come to discuss the friendly competition today, was actually here to talk about the ruby mines and the bloodshed.

So Hugo was prepared for that, too…..

“I want my rubies back! I can’t do my research because I don’t have enough rubies!”

Little did he know that an 8-year-old girl would be so insistent.

Hugo put his hand to his forehead at her demand.

“‘Look at you, Adolf Governor. What kind of disgrace is this on an official visit?”

“Uh-huh. Hmm. I apologize for this, my lord. But I’m afraid I’m at a loss for words, unless she’s saying something very wrong again.”

“…What?”

“It’s the right thing to say, isn’t it, though it’s crude coming from a child’s mouth.”

Hugo and Adolf’s gazes met in unison.

“….”

“….”

Hugo tried to channel the Swordmaster’s superhuman aura to pressure his intestines, but he was distracted by the Camus that had stepped directly in front of….

He tries to slow his momentum down enough to make the Camus back off.

“What do you think you’re doing to a child, the Sword Star of the Empire persecuting an eight-year-old girl?”

That’s when Adolf’s pinzan comes in.

Adolf wrapped Camus in a cloak.

And Hugo with a scowl on his face.

It’s embarrassing for an adult to argue with an 8-year-old, but this Adolf guy keeps trying to exploit her innocence for political purposes.

It was very annoying for Hugo.

Should we reignite the ruby mine issue, which we’ve been silent about?

For Baskerville, it’s a matter of pride, and for Morgue, it’s a matter of business.

In the first place, rubies are more important to the Morgue than to Baskerville, as they are used as a key ingredient in magical experiments.

Hugo is a closed-minded man who doesn’t like to interact with other families, so he just wants to keep his mind off the ruby veins.

Training hounds and navigating the black mountains with enemies was enough to give him a headache, and he didn’t want to get into trouble with a bunch of kids who wanted to play magic with a red stone that was only used for women’s jewelry.

“Give me back my ruby mine. Without the rubies from there, it’s hard for me to continue my studies.”

“Uh-huh, Camus, you’re talking about grown-ups, uh-huh, uh-huh.”

I can’t even stand to listen to the conversation between the girl named Camus and the guy named Adolf.

‘No matter how you look at it, this is a political performance….’

But since the other party is a child, I can’t say anything, and I can only boil inside.

Even if the iron-blooded swordsman, who is in a position to recognize things, asks me to stop.

…Right then.

A voice made Hugo’s ears perk up.

“Don’t they teach you not to covet what belongs to others in Morgue?”

A voice as cheerful and innocent as an 8-year-old camel.

It was 8-year-old Vikir.

Chapter 23

Camus Morgue (4)

◆

What a shocking sight.

…Hiccups!

Even Hugo Le Baskerville, the patriarch of the Iron Blade family, had hiccups.

Vikir’s actions were just as sudden.

“Aaaaah!”

Camus closed his eyes and screamed. No wonder, his arm was about to be cut off.

She was screaming and crying at a crisis she had never faced before.

Even his uncle, Adolf, had never seen her cry like this before.

“That, stop!”

Adolf unconsciously raised his mana.

The mana of a Sixth Circle Master surged out, pressuring Vikir.

But.

…Sasak.

As if he had anticipated it, Vikir immediately let go of Camus’s arm and fell backwards.

“Aaahhh! Uncle, he’s got my arm…!”

Camus cried, running to bury his face in the hem of Adolf’s cloak.

Adolf stared at Vikir in disbelief, not even angry, before turning his attention to Hugo.

“Go away, what are you doing!”

Hugo ignored Adolf’s protests. He simply tilted his head at an angle and looked down at Vikir.

“Son.”

Son, he said, and Vikir answered politely.

“Yes, father.”

“Your prank just now was a bit too much, I’m afraid.”

“I apologize. It is a common prank among the brothers of the family.”

After speaking, Vikir took the tip of the dagger in his hand and bent it.

Mmm.

The knife bent so easily. It’s a fake sword, made of rubber.

When Adolf saw it, he exclaimed in disbelief.

“No, no, no, what kind of a toy is this?”

“You’ve never seen a boy play with a toy sword before, and we Baskervillians play with them from the time they’re a year old.”

It was only at Hugo’s words, which seemed to surprise him, that Adolf opened his eyes and saw the sword in Vikir’s hand.

It was a crude rubber knife, obviously a fake, the sort of thing that even the average child in the world would play with.

My mistake was that I didn’t recognize the quality of the knife in Vikir’s momentary burst of strength.

Seeing Adolf, who was known for his meticulousness and composure, stumble in surprise gave Hugo a bit of satisfaction.

He quickly forgot his own surprise.

“Now, I’ve thought of something about the ruby mine. Maybe the Morgue will like it.”

“….”

“So let’s just get this friendly competition over with.”

Hugo’s blatant attempt to sell out.

Adolf, looking dumbfounded, tried to protest in Moorish.

“…Blah, blah, kihing, kihing. That bastard, I’m not gonna let him get away with it, you’ll see!”

Unfortunately, he didn’t have time for that as he was busy petting Camus, who was blowing his nose against his cloak and whimpering.

Thus, an important meeting between the two families was ridiculously interrupted by an eight-year-old child’s argument.

◆

‘Magic and the sword are at odds with each other in normal times, but in times of crisis they are a good complement to each other and save the country.’

In keeping with the former Emperor’s beliefs, Morgue the Mage and Baskerville the Ironblade hold an annual friendly tournament.

Children from the ages of eight to fifteen gather to test their skills against one another.

By tradition, it is the 15-year-olds who compete in the most intense and spectacular battles with swords and magic, as opposed to the 8-year-olds who compete in theory and mana sensitivity.

…But.

For this year’s friendly competition, all eyes were elsewhere.

The 8-year-old class usually gets little attention.

The two youngsters standing there were the main protagonists of the day.

Vikir van Baskerville, of the iron-blooded House Baskerville.

Camus Morgue of House Morgue, a master mage.

At the Morgue’s initiative, the eight year olds were moved to the side of the field next to the 15 year old class where the real action was taking place.

They would be fighting just like the 15-year-olds.

The contrast between the nonchalant Vikir and the venomous Camus was quite striking.

“Brace yourself, boy.”

“….”

“You’re not going to get any breaks once you’re in the ring.”

“….”

“Say something!”

“….”

“Eeh!”

Vikir could only yawn.

The more he does so, the more he stomps his foot in frustration.

Finally.

The bell rang, signaling the start of the real competition.

And with that, the match began.

“Yaaaaaah!”

A loud cheer rang out.

Camus immediately drew up his mana and charged at Vikir.

A performance that draws all of its power from the start.

It’s a great way to get a quick start, but in the long run, it’s not a good strategy because it reveals all of your cards.

However, Camus’s talent was indeed impressive.

Quadra casting!

He casts four spells at the same time, when most people can’t even cast two in a row.

Even though they were one-circle spells, Fireball, Ice Sphere, Thunder Ring, and Mud Wall, each one of them would be difficult for a 15 year old in Morgue’s household.

To perform four of them simultaneously is a talent beyond imagination!

It was indeed a genius that could only be found once in a hundred years, even in the prestigious Morgue.

Boom!

Fireballs, ice balls, and lightning bolts the size of a child’s fist hit the ground.

They actually hurt a little, but only slightly, and Vikir ducked just enough to avoid them.

“It’s pretty spectacular, but I think you’d be better off focusing on just one spell for now.”

“‘Eeh, what business is it of yours, you magical ignoramus!”

Camus was chasing after Vikir, diligently controlling his three offensive magics.

There was a hint of determination to feed him a shot no matter what.

But.

…Hook!

Vikir dodged a barrage (more like three child’s fists) of spells, and instead moved closer to the Camus.

And then.

Puck!

Vikir kicked the mud wall that was protecting Camus and shattered it.

“Huh?”

Camus swallowed hard.

It was too close to call in its offensive magic.

The base of the mud wall collapsed, and Vikir’s face came into view.

Camus felt his heart pounding in his chest.

“We’re down!”

Camus’s eyes rolled back in his head as Vikir’s flying palm blocked his vision.

Then, a searing pain shot across his forehead.

…Crack!

Bam. Camus pulled back, wiping the tears from his eyes, and looked up.

“…?”

Her forehead burned, but that was all.

Vikir didn’t do anything, just flicked his finger and made a small bump on Camus forehead.

“You, you bastard! Are you kidding me?”

“….”

“Go, go!”

Camus canceled one of the three offensive spells he had cast earlier.

Woodshed!

Mud Wall, a wall of mud was created in two layers, covering Camus.

“Haha, now there’s a double wall! You can’t get through this!”

The problem is, with the double wall, Camus herself can’t see out of it.

But.

…Puck!

The two layers of mud are as easy to break through as a sheet of paper.

It was Vikir’s hand that broke through the wall and stretched out in front of Camus face.

“Who does this hand belong to?”

The hand that broke through Camus wall and into her space.

Vikir’s fingers moved quickly while Camus was stunned and unable to find the words to answer.

“The answer is, turn off the stronger one.”

Another snap.

Another tear leaked from Camus’s eye.

He was hit again.

Swat after swat hit the exact same spot, creating a second, smaller bump.

To make matters worse, Vikir’s hand slipped away immediately after the second blow.

It wasn’t like he was delivering a killer blow, it was just a quick slap.

“Who does this thing dare to play with me-aaaaaaaaaaaah!”

Eight years old, a genius girl who’s spent her entire life growing up like a forbidden jade leaf.

Camus screamed at the top of her lungs, unable to contain her rising tantrum.

With that, she canceled all of her offensive spells and formed four walls of mud to surround herself.

“Now, how about this, no one can break through this, not even you! Ha ha!”

Camus didn’t seem to mind that his vision had gone completely dark.

In fact, he was glad that he didn’t have to show his hands rubbing his forehead and his sullen expression.

“….”

He paused for a moment, wondering if that little bastard Vikir couldn’t break through the four walls.

Camus smiled victoriously.

“Ho-ho-ho! Loser! They say you can’t even penetrate walls because you’re a dwarf dung bag! Come all the way here, you idiot!”

But still no answer.

….

Some time passed.

Trapped in the mud dome, Camus rubbed his forehead and thought to herself.

“Huh? But this won’t let me get out, will it?”

What should I do? My vision is completely blocked and I can’t see what’s going on outside.

I can’t even try to do something different, because I’m stuck with four layers of mud.

I thought, “Hmm. Maybe I can cut a hole and peek out?’”

With a little effort, Camus cut a small hole in the mud wall.

He stuck his face through the hole to look out.

…Bam!

Vikir’s hand swooped in like a ghost and delivered a third blow to the Camus forehead.

“Kaaaahhhh!”

Three lumps!

With three small lumps on the same spot on her forehead, Camus writhed in pain and anger.

She lifted her burning eyes and quickly canceled all four layers of mud walls.

As the mud wall collapsed, she could see the face of the insignificant bastard in the distance.

“I’m going to kill him! Aaahhhh!”

Camus cried. He was too angry and frustrated to think about his dignity.

So he threw away all his defensive spells and cast four offensive spells at the same time.

A firepower that would have been impossible for a fifteen year old to pull off!

Meanwhile, Vikir faced the Camus’s fury and thought.

“…What should I do?”

If you want to kill her, you can snap her neck in 0.1 seconds. But that’s not the problem right now.

Dealing with children is painful. You don’t know where to stop and where to start.

This is especially true for Vikir, who has spent his entire life on the battlefield.

He was too young to be appeased by the younger members of House Morgue.

Eventually, Vikir made a judgment call.

“Morgue’s problems are Morgue’s problems.”

It’s always cleaner to do things without getting your hands dirty.

Boom!

A quick glance to the side reveals an intense battle in progress.

A nameless fifteen year old Baskerville and a fifteen year old Morgue were engaged in a fierce battle of swordsmanship and magic.

Both are so focused that they don’t realize that someone is approaching them.

The 15 year old Morgue seems to be practicing a powerful fire explosion spell, and a loud explosion is emanating from the arena.

Swoosh-

Vikir ducked back and stood as close as he could to the border of the neighboring arena.

A very angry Camus followed closely behind him.

“Well, if there’s any more, the arbiters will step in.”

Vikir shifted slightly, and Camus followed him relentlessly, not wanting to let go.

And then.

…Boom!

An explosion. And gasps.

“Ouch! It’s Camus!”

“Oh my God, Ms. Camus!”

“No! It’s…!”

Vikir began to see the picture he wanted.

Chapter 25

Camus Morgue (6)

◆

“You said it wasn’t for me to hear, so I didn’t listen after that.”

At those words, Hugo hastily covered the corner of his mouth with his hand.

Though expressionless from the hand up, it was a… gesture that hid a smile from anyone who saw it.

Camus also stares at him with wide eyes.

“Hoo… hoo hoo hoo hoo….”

Only Adolf’s forehead is covered in blood.

He straightened his bent back to meet Vikir’s eye and looked back at Hugo.

“My lord. Will you allow me to speak with this child for a few moments?”

It was highly unusual for a delegate of House Morgue, much less a top member of the power, to take such an undue interest in a mere eight-year-old.

And Hugo didn’t have much to say in response to his opponent’s overreaction.

“What are you doing with that kid? Is the Mad Star of the Empire persecuting an eight-year-old boy?”

Hugo hadn’t forgotten what he’d heard before, and he was returning the favor.

But Adolf was stubborn.

“Hehe, isn’t this a child who may one day be my niece’s husband, and I’m asking you this as an uncle, not as the head of Morgue’s delegation?”

“Oh, uncle, it’s not like that!”

“Uh-huh, leave my nephew alone. This uncle will take care of it. We all have to see this once in a while.”

Adolf says with a stern look on his face as Camus speaks up.

He nudges Hugo with a sly glance, a nuanced way of asking him to save face.

“….”

Hugo threw up his hands, thinking that it had been a long time since he’d had to deal with the Morgue.

Do as you please.

◆

Vikir readily accepted Adolf’s request.

Adolf Morgue was an absolute powerhouse who had been difficult to deal with even before his regression. At the age of forty, he is already the acting head of the family at official events.

The chance to experience a little bit of Adolf’s power was a good one.

I’m sure Hugo thought so too, which is why he allowed me to attend.

After the annual ceremony, everyone cleared out of the ballroom.

Vikir and Adolf stood facing each other in a large field.

The observers were Hugo Le Baskerville and Camus Morgue.

They stood at a distance from each other, looking at the two men in the center of the arena.

Adolf said.

“Child of Baskerville, I am about to test your qualities, so show me all that you are.”

Vikir nodded and thought of something else.

“If I show you all of me, you’ll faint.”

What would happen if I faced him at his pre-regression peak?

Fifty percent in ambush and assassination, ten percent in hand-to-hand combat.

But I don’t have all of my pre-regression strength back, and I don’t have to fight to the best of my ability.

I just need to fulfill Adolf’s expectations in moderation.

“Let’s see what confidence can do.”

It’s said that masters can tell each other’s skill by shaking hands.

Vikir thought he’d take this opportunity to see how Morgue stacks up against the top players.

Then Adolf said.

“Child, I give you a handicap.”

He raised his hand and swung it toward the ground.

Boom!

Mud rose up from the ground and swirled around to form the shape of a jar.

Boom!

The flames from Adolf’s hand solidified the clay.

…

Next, the jar began to fill with water spontaneously.

A seemingly simple combination of earth, fire, and water, three magical elements all at once.

…Just right!

Adolf snapped his fingers, and the jar of water slowly rose into the air and landed on top of Adolf’s head.

Carrying the jar of water, Adolf looked down at Vikir and said.

“I will fight you with this jar full of water on my head. If you can get even one drop of water to flow from the jar on my head, you win.”

In other words, go for it.

Vikir gripped his short sword and took up his stance.

Adolf crossed his arms and stared at Vikir.

And then.

…Tadak!

Vikir made the first move.

Seeing Vikir charging straight at him, Camus cried out in alarm.

“Uh-uh! You can’t run straight at my uncle!”

Hearing this, Adolf looks back at Camus with a very regretful expression.

“Nephew, I don’t want you to tell him that.”

At the same time, a transparent barrier forms in front of Adolf’s eyes.

Pow!

Vikir is knocked back against the wall as he charges.

“Shield magic is best when dealing with swordsmen. Even an aura sword will be hard pressed to stop them.”

Adolf’s words were true.

Adolf, in particular, was a master of shield magic, able to create shields of various sizes, thicknesses, and shapes to suit the time and place.

Earlier, he had created a shield just the right size to cover Vikir’s torso to minimize the waste of mana.

However, Vikir is no slouch either.

…Ta-da!

Vikir used the backward bouncing momentum to close the distance, then immediately turned and moved to the side.

At the same time.

Bam! Bam!

Vikir kicked a few cobblestones in the opposite direction of his travels.

The stones flew straight toward the water jar.

“It’s not a good idea to aim for the jug.”

Without even looking in the direction the rocks were coming from, Adolf used his hands to create a shield.

He summoned another, smaller shield for the incoming Vikir.

Vikir bounced back from another blow.

Adolf opened his mouth.

“From now on, I will attack as well.”

Before he can finish his sentence, fire spears are summoned.

Fire bolts descend rapidly through the air, each one powerful enough to pierce the solid soil of the smokefield and create a deep pit.

Seeing this, Camus cried out.

“Uncle, that’s not fair, you didn’t even use that kind of magic against me!”

“You are my … nephew. Whose side are you on now?”

Adolf looked bitterly disappointed.

But Vikir was frantically dodging the flying fire spears.

“Hmm. That’s it.”

Vikir’s familiarity with Adolf’s power hadn’t changed much since then.

This level was already familiar.

‘I see how to deal with him.

The seasoned battle experience before the regression, and the innocent face of a child afterward.

The combination of the two can catch your opponent off guard and lead to unexpected results.

‘Or kill him.’

A ghastly thought crossed my mind, but… I didn’t need to make a big deal out of it.

Hugo’s eyes were on me, and I needed to get this right.

“Eeeeee!”

Vikir moved as if chased by flames.

Vikir quickly drew his sword and swung at Adolf.

But.

“Not a chance.”

Adolf’s shield blocks Vikir’s blade.

Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang!

Vikir swung his sword again, but it too was blocked by the shield.

Adolf grumbled.

“Same thing a hundred times. Your sword can’t pierce the shield.”

But Vikir did not give up.

Boom.

The sword swings.

Boom!

And it hits the shield.

Vikir kept repeating the same move, and Adolf kept blocking the sword with the same shield.

Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom!

The sword was hitting the same place over and over again without missing a beat.

Vikir’s sword flew with machine-like precision, the same trajectory repeated countless times.

At this point, even Adolf realized that something was wrong.

“…Hoh.”

Vikir’s blade was hitting the same spot on the shield over and over again.

The shield was getting worn down by the blade.

Especially since it was constantly hitting only one part, the magical fatigue level of that part was already quite high.

“Hahahaha- you’re trying to pierce the shield by hitting the same spot over and over again, what a bold idea. I can’t help but praise your concentration and swordsmanship for being able to target the same spot over and over again without missing a beat.”

However, Adolf’s eyes immediately turn cold.

“But… that’s like trying to hit a boulder with an egg, and you’re trying to do that against the durability of my shield and the durability of your sword?”

He was right.

Bam! Bam!

Vikir’s sword struck Adolf’s shield for the tenth time.

…Pow!

Vikir’s sword finally shatters and breaks.

Vikir was forced to retrieve his broken sword and step back.

Hugo stroked his chin and remained speechless, while Camus looked disappointed.

Adolf turned to Vikir, who had retreated into the distance.

“I admire your stubbornness and willingness to stick to one position, but it’s something you have to do while watching your opponent. You’re a fine young man, but you’re far from qualified to be my nephew’s husb….”

Adolf was about to end the line with an admonition.

…But.

He immediately felt the top of his head grow damp and stopped speaking.

“What is it?”

When Adolf realized that something was wrong.

Gurgling.

A trickle of water dampened his hair and began to run down his face.

“…?”

Dazed, Adolf looks up and sees a jar of water leaking from his head.

“…Boom!”

The shard of Vikir’s sword that broke and bounced off earlier had stuck into the side of the jar, causing it to leak water.

Adolf, soaked from the crown of his head to his chin and even to the nape of his neck, looked on in a daze.

Thud, thud, thud, thud.

Vikir walked up to him and said.

“You’re full to the brim.”

He was referring to the water in the jar, of course.

Chapter 26

The Graduate (1)

◆

The number of people being born in Baskerville was still high, and the number of people dying was still high.

The Styx River flowed, the current pushing back the tide.

Seven years had passed since the day of the duel of the two eight-year-olds.

◆

“This instructor can be an angel or a devil, depending on what you do!”

A short-bearded young hound was shouting in a raspy voice.

His name is Staffordshire Baskerville. Thirty-five years old. He’s a veteran knight of the Graduator class.

An outsider, a commoner, not even given the middle name of Van, let alone La, but an upstanding man who had managed to cleanse his bloodline by taking the surname of Baskerville due to his outstanding qualities and straightforward heart.

In particular, his “stabbing fang” swordsmanship is said to have reached the level of the Four Teeth Baskervilles.

Four teeth, drawn to perfection.

If he’s this good, he should be able to lead and teach the younger Baskervilles right now.

“Now, for the final exercise, practice makes perfect, as I’m sure you’re all well aware!”

Staffordshire glanced at the fifteen- and sixteen-year-old Baskervilles in front of him.

All looked tired and weary. But the chill and poison in their eyes is growing stronger and stronger.

The young Baskervilles here, all fifteen or sixteen years old, are swordsmen who have mastered the Sword Expert junior class, Baskerville One Tooth.

Staffordshire checked the trainees’ form, then turned his head again.

In the center of the training grounds that surrounded them, a huge bear stood on two paws.

Weighing in at 800 kilograms and standing three meters tall, there was something else unusual about this giant bear.

It has two sharply curved horns on top of its head.

<Oxbear>

Danger rating: A

Size: 5 meters

Found in: Ridge 7, Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain

-A very large bear with two massive horns.

A carnivorous bear, the strongest terrestrial predator, and a perfect killing machine, it is considered the strongest and pinnacle of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain 7th Ridge ecosystem.

A demonic creature with few natural enemies other than its own kind.

The bear carries two massive, curved buffalo horns on its head.

Its entire body is covered in thick muscle, fat, and bristly fur.

[Grrrr…]

The beast currently on the loose in the performance hall appears to be a sub-adult, not yet fully grown.

It’s also been in a cage for a long time, so its nutrition is not very good.

But that also means it’s aggressive and nervous.

Staffordshire swung his sword to intimidate Oxbear, while encouraging the younger Baskervilles behind him.

“Now, we just need to do what we’ve been practicing on the demon’s corpse. Last time we practiced on Oxbear’s corpse, you all know how tough his hide is, how tight his muscles are, and which parts of his body contain which entrails.”

The meek-looking Staffordshire was a different man when he stood before Oxbear.

His eyes glowed with life, and the aura emanating from the tip of his sword was like a giant’s grip.

Staffordshire exuded such a terrifying aura that it overwhelmed Oxbear, but he never attacked.

Because it’s not his place.

Next.

[Grrrrrr!]

Oxbear charged.

He charged like a buffalo with his two horns.

The young Baskervilles fight back, each according to their own preferences.

Some scattered to the left and right to dodge, while others swung their swords in front of them.

…BANG!

Those who dodge live, and those who meet head-on fall.

Staffordshire continued.

“If someone stronger than you is coming at you head-on, it’s natural to dodge. But don’t dodge by putting too much distance between you and them, but sneak around them to the side and get in a little attack.”

The young hounds’ advice continues.

The young hounds’ eyes glowed, sucking them in like water.

“Don’t be greedy and go for the kill right from the start. It’s more likely to be countered. Instead, go for the center of gravity of the body, in this case the right hind leg, so that it’s not as fast to move or react.”

The young hounds followed their handler’s instructions and repeatedly attacked the bear’s legs as it stood on its two feet.

Continuing to attack only his hind legs, Oxbear was left with a widening wound that left him with little use of one leg.

The menacing antler lunge was sealed.

By this time, the young Baskervilles had bared their teeth in earnest.

They were now hunting dogs who could take care of themselves without the guidance of the Staffordshire.

Baskerville 1 meal. More than thirty teeth bared, tearing at Oxbear’s body.

The most aggressive were the triplets, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

Quack, quack, quack!

They hunted the bear as if they were the boss.

They were the boss of the pack, physically shoving aside any cocky siblings who tried to get ahead of them, or any dumb siblings who fell behind their peers.

And then.

…Thud!

Oxbear fell to the ground.

“Well done.”

Staffordshire raised his sword and stepped toward Oxbear’s body.

Thwack!

The bear’s stomach split open, spilling guts and flesh.

After four periods of training, lunchtime came naturally.

Staffordshire impromptu distributed Oxbear’s guts and flesh to the young hounds.

Steaming red chunks of meat.

The young Baskervilles chewed and gulped down the raw, squeamish flesh.

Staffordshire said to the trainees as they ate.

“Now, eat and listen. As of this hour, three and a half years of basic training, three and a half years of practical training, are over. Congratulations on your graduation.”

Seven years of training had turned these snotty little boys into young warriors.

Everyone here was now a young prodigy who could not only load a sword with mana, but also draw a perfect set of teeth.

But Staffordshire said they were just getting started.

“Practicing with captured demons is really just a tutorial that I wouldn’t even call realistic, and now you have to create and build your own experience.”

The advice of an old hound who has seen it all is always worth heeding.

“The wild beasts of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain are not only fit and strong, but also cunning and calm in nature, unlike those that have been left in cages for a long time. Even I can’t compete with the stubborn and old individuals I sometimes see.”

That’s true of the oxbear I just killed.

Facing a full-grown wild oxbear’s horns, followed by a series of front paws and head bites, is dangerous enough for any grader.

Controlled variables, a safe environment, and set rules.

And a wild, unexplored place where you can’t survive on your training alone.

That’s where these young hounds have to go from here.

The young Baskervilles already knew that.

Staffordshire gestured to the countless scars across his face.

“You’ll have to go through the hell that lies ahead on your own. Either overcome it with the blood you were born with, or overcome it with your own experience. I have nothing more to say to you, that’s all!”

With a brief colossus salute, he relinquished his position as leader.

The young Baskervilles put down the flesh and guts they’d been tearing up for a moment.

Then they steeled themselves for the next twenty-one months of unexplored territory.

Once Staffordshire was out of sight, they gathered in small groups and began to make small talk.

“Hey, where did you get your knighthood?”

“First degree, Doberman. Two, a pit bull. And a Rottweiler.”

“Oh, none of those overlap with me. I like the Knights of the Wolfhound, then the Shepherds and the Bull Mastiffs.”

The Seven Knights of Baskerville.

Each order was created and operated for a different purpose: vigilance, search, protection, assassination, suppression, and all-out warfare.

But the best of the bunch was the Order of the Wolfhound, which symbolized the power of the house.

“I want to join the Wolfhounds.”

“But you can’t just go there because you want to, you have to be kicked out.”

“I’m going to be realistic and apply for the Dobermans. That’s practically the only place you can get in, besides the Wolfhounds.”

“If I join the Doberman Knights, I’ll have to watch the castle walls for the rest of my life, and I can’t stand that. I’d rather be a Pit Bull Knight, always on the battlefield.”

The children murmured.

And naturally, their eyes slowly began to converge on a single point.

“…But where is he going to go?”

That was the common question of all the kids here.

Even the triplets, who had been the most active in this oxbear hunt, had put down their morsels of meat and were now watching.

Vikir Van Baskerville.

A child from outside the family, rumored to be Hugo’s illegitimate son.

He hadn’t joined the oxbear hunt, but sat alone and still in a remote part of the country.

And at Vikir’s feet, a large oxbear lies dead.

A much larger one than the one that had just been killed by the combined efforts of over thirty children.

The young Baskervilles stare at Vikir, awe in their eyes.

“Is he really 15 years old like us?”

“How does he catch an oxbear by himself?”

“From what I’ve heard, he’s already a Sword Expert?”

“He’s also drawn three teeth.”

“Crazy, he can use the three Baskerville form? That makes him almost like a leader hound!”

Worship of the powerful is common in any group, but it’s even more pronounced in the Baskerville family.

But the truth is, Vikir doesn’t pay much attention to the rumors.

“Advanced Sword Expert.”

Advanced Sword Expert means that the aura at the tip of a sword has become so dense that it can pass between gas and liquid.

The children of Les Baskervilles usually reach this stage between the ages of twenty and twenty-five, but Vikir is rumored to have achieved it by the age of fifteen.

…But.

Vikir’s true hidden power was beyond that of a Graduator Intermediate.

It was a full two levels above Sword Expert, and comparable to Staffordshire, who had been his leader hound.

Moreover, considering the protection of the Styx River and the power of the demonic sword Beelzebub, his actual combat power would be even stronger than this.

If the world knew, it would be shaken to its core.

‘…Currently, I’ve mastered five Baskerville Forms. In terms of swordsmanship alone, he has already surpassed the level before the regression.’

He had never mastered a sword technique above the fourth level in his previous life.

Because of this, it would take him a little longer than he had originally planned to become a perfect Graduator Intermediate.

Meanwhile, Vikir closed his eyes and recalled the oxbear he had just killed.

It had been a close call, but the animal had been weakened by years in captivity, and he’d been able to kill it with his hidden skills.

Vikir’s mind raced as he tried to figure out how good he was now, and how much he’d lost in comparison to his pre-regression skills.

He couldn’t be bothered with the chatter of the Baskervilles’ day pups, who were just getting their teeth.

Then.

A topic of conversation caught the attention of even Vikir, who was lost in thought.

A young Baskerville had casually mentioned something.

“…So, in our line, he’s going to the Academy?”

The Academy ‘Colosseo’

An Imperial compulsory school where the Seven Houses of the Empire send their young heirs to be educated.

Due to the academy’s capacity limitations, the number of students admitted is limited to a small number from each family.

Naturally, only the most elite young people from each family are allowed to attend, which is something Vikir was interested in.

Of course, he doesn’t have the greed for fame or the desire for education that the other kids do.

“It’s a chance to get away from Hugo and improve my skills.”

Of course, there’s more to it than that. Like paying back a debt from a previous life, or gaining control of a hidden artifact.

As Vikir ponders his next move.

“Young master.”

A voice called to him from behind.

An old voice, but still strong. A warm, gentle demeanor.

Butler John Barrymore came to stand at Vikir’s side.

He was one of the few people Vikir had ever felt sorry for in his previous life, and Vikir had come to trust him.

Then Butler Barrymore leaned closer to Vikir and whispered.

“My lord wants to see you.”

Hugo Le Baskerville?

It was always unusual for him to seek out his children.

At Vikir’s puzzled look, Barrymore smirked and continued.

“I believe he has decided on your position.”

Chapter 27

The Graduate (2)

◆

It’s been a long time since I’ve been in Hugo’s office, and it still smells cold and dingy.

Dust from old books, stale cigarette smoke, stale coffee, and a faint scent of blood.

Like a seasoned hound, Vikir reads the atmosphere through scent.

Then a middle-aged man sitting behind the desk, in a swivel chair, staring out the window, turned and faced Vikir.

Hugo Le Baskerville.

The iron-blooded patriarch of House Baskerville.

His face bore a slight resemblance to the face of Hugo in Vikir’s last memory before his regression.

Suddenly. Vikir noticed a single, relatively recent scar across the bridge of Hugo’s nose.

It had been there before the regression, but Vikir had no idea how it had come to be, and his eyes lit up.

“Greetings.”

“Mm.”

Hugo answered briefly, then nodded.

Vikir continued his casual conversation in a nonchalant tone.

When Vikir asked about the scar on the bridge of his nose, Hugo shrugged it off as nothing.

“I was struck by an arrow while slaying the enemy and the barbarians of the Black Mountains.”

Vikir was a little surprised.

The mighty Hugo Le Baskerville could be wounded by an arrow.

There was no way a man of Hugo’s stature as a Swordmaster could have been struck by a blind arrow; there must have been a sniper targeting him.

Hugo smirked.

“There’s a woman who can shoot a bow.”

“Did you catch her?”

“No, I didn’t. But I did carve one of those same things into the fox thing’s face.”

A swordsman of Hugo’s caliber would have been able to scatter the aura of the blade’s tip to intercept even the most distant foe.

Hugo touched the bridge of his nose for a moment, feeling the scar across the bridge of his nose still throbbing.

He paused for a moment, then spoke.

“Anyway. Congratulations on completing your training.”

“Thank you.”

“From now on, it’s harder.”

At Hugo’s words, Vikir nodded.

As Guardian Knight Staffordshire Baskerville had told her at the end of her training, the real work begins now.

Three and a half years of basic training to learn the theory of warfare, build physical strength, and develop an eye for opposition.

Another three and a half years of practical training, including combat training against real demons and humans, and wilderness survival skills.

But the enemies they’re about to face, and the deep waters of the Black Mountains, are a hell that will negate everything they’ve learned about survival.

You can only survive if you have a good bloodline, or if you are willing to die for it.

‘For the next twenty-one months, we’ll be working with the enemy to open up the Black Mountains.

Vikir thought as he recalled his pre-regression memories.

If things had gone according to plan, he would have become an apprentice knight of the Pit Bull Knights at this point and been sent to Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, crossing countless lines of fire over the next 21 months.

He would have been thrown into the fray like a hunting dog to be used a few times and then discarded.

…But.

Hugo has a rather unexpected proposal for Vikir.

“You should be a member of the House of Representatives.”

It was a surprise indeed.

Hugo would train Vikir in the ways of the court.

Of course, the Baskervilles are a family of seasoned warriors, so being a bard doesn’t mean you can’t fight.

However, it is not uncommon for younger Baskervillians, especially those who are particularly gifted and skilled, to take the path of an unaffiliated warrior after serving as an officer.

Hugo’s nemesis and second son were on the same path.

“A man must be strong. As with the sword, so with power.”

Vikir nodded at Hugo’s words.

While the other expendables were dying on the battlefield, the elites were learning about politics and administration, both within the family and outside.

And when an elderly elite finally draws his sword and goes into battle, he’ll have the seasoned expendables to assist him.

The elite may start out a bit late, but he or she will build up his or her skills and accomplishments, and grow into an even bigger giant with the political and administrative experience he or she has learned.

‘…And only the elite can learn more than the Baskerville Five.’

This is why consumables are not taught higher level swordsmanship beyond Baskerville 5.

It’s so that the elites, who are late to the game, can catch up to the expendable hounds with little effort.

It’s the same reason why the higher-ups in the country don’t teach the people to write.

“As you say.”

Vikir bowed respectfully.

He’d meant to move away from Hugo’s side, but instead he’d grown closer.

It didn’t matter much, though, as he hadn’t yet shown much in the way of hidden skills, and this was good for Vikir in more ways than one, as it allowed him to get closer to the center of power.

Hugo explained Vikir’s new position as an MP simply.

“The House of Representatives assists the Baskervilles in the executive, legislative, and judicial branches of the House of Baskerville’s territory, as well as attracting business for the House and running the affairs of the House, in short.”

Successful House members are promoted to Senator, which allows them to deal with matters outside of the House, which is not something Vikir is currently interested in.

Drac-

Hugo opened a drawer and pulled out a few papers.

Deacon Barrymore quickly stood beside him with his seal and sigil.

“Your new position is Deputy Magistrate of the City of Underdog.”

Underdog City, Vikir knew well.

The busiest town in the vast territory ruled by the Baskervilles. No, it was more of a metropolis than a town.

The Archon is the one who oversees the legislative and judicial affairs of the city, and the Deputy Archon is responsible for assisting the Archon in various ways.

Vikir looked at his appointment letter and said.

“So it’s about making and enforcing laws.”

“Yes, and there are currently vacancies for both the Archon and Deputy Archon positions.”

There was a reason why the positions of one magistrate and several deputy magistrates were all vacant.

Originally, Underdog City’s ruler was Hugo’s second son, and the second son’s relatives who took the Baskerville surname were the deputy rulers.

But now Hugo’s second son was long gone, and the deputy magistrates who were supposed to take his place had been fired or suspended en masse for bribery.

And Hugo intends to hand over all the powers and duties of those vacant posts to Vikir.

“It’s a city that’s become a state-free zone. Can you do a good job?”

Vikir nodded.

Deputy magistracies are usually held by men in their thirties, but occasionally a prodigy, a genius among geniuses, will hold the position in their early twenties.

And it was likely that these young elites would one day take on important positions representing their families.

‘…For example, they would be admitted to the Academy.’

And after four years of studying at the academy, they would return to the family and immediately become a magistrate.

An elite course for the elite.

What Hugo proposed to Vikir was an equally unconventional appointment.

“I think you’re giving me too much power.”

“And a great deal of responsibility.”

Hugo said with a dry laugh.

“Your achievements are at least ten years ahead of the children who are considered geniuses within the family, so I will treat you accordingly.”

Treatment includes both rights and duties.

The greater the power, the heavier the duty.

Or, to put it another way, the heavier the task, the greater the power.

“I will endeavor to live up to my lord’s expectations.”

Hugo nodded wordlessly.

And then.

…The land!

A piece of paper was stamped with Hugo’s seal.

With that, Vikir became the deputy magistrate, the de facto magistrate, of a metropolitan underdog with a population of half a million.

‘This is good.

Vikir thought.

‘If I use the power of the Deputy Magistrate well, I can train my skills much more safely than if I go straight into the fray.

His hidden teeth and claws would be sharpened.

And then. Vikir opened his mouth.

“My lord.”

“…?”

Hugo looked up.

There was a glimmer of warmth in his eyes that had been absent since the end of the mission.

Vikir seized on the threadbare warmth.

“I’d like to tell you about the ruby mine in Morgue.”

Seven years ago, an eight-year-old Vikir had done something daring against Morgue’s envoys that had made Hugo’s stomach turn.

Hugo had been so pleased that he had promised Vikir a reward, though he hadn’t asked for exactly what it was.

And now, Vikir was asking for a reward for his behavior in a very clear way.

“I was wondering if I could borrow ….”

Hugo looked a little troubled at that.

“Hmmm. Yes, I did, and I made it clear then that I would reward you. You said you’d tell me if you wanted something.”

“You don’t have to listen if you don’t want to.”

Hugo’s thick eyebrows arched at that.

“It won’t be difficult.”

He nodded, then pulled another piece of paper from a drawer and stamped it with his lordship’s seal.

“I trust you won’t do anything stupid. Son.”

No matter how many times I hear him say “son,” I never get used to it.

And in truth, Vikir was more surprised by Hugo’s willingness to grant his request than by the title.

“I would never have dared to ask you for a favor before ….”

Perhaps things will go more smoothly than I thought.

◆

Stepping out of the guest room, Vikir walked down the long hallway.

Behind him, Deacon Barrymore smiled gently.

“Master.”

“Yes.”

“My lord is very fond of you.”

Vikir remained silent, not saying anything.

Then Deacon Barrymore spoke.

“I can see that you’re not going to put him in the field right away, but you’re going to give him the position of de facto ruler. Isn’t that the art of imperialism? You’re going to use him big and heavy.”

Literally, if you’re going to raise a hound to be used and discarded, you should send it out into the battlefield right now to die.

While the hounds are seasoned by their encounters with death, their would-be masters are armed with ideas and knowledge from a safe place.

And from this foothold, the hounds leap to the heights of the untouchable.

In the end, the lower life cannot overcome the higher, even if it dies and rebirths. Neither by words nor by martial arts.

It’s a bitter pill to swallow for Vikir, who is feeling it all over again.

“That’s if I do a good job as Deputy Magistrate.”

“I’m sure you’ll do just fine, Master, and if you do anything more than passably well there, you’ll be the next one to enter the Academy.”

Deacon Barrymore had noticed that Vikir was interested in the Academy as well.

…Although he couldn’t quite put his finger on why.

Meanwhile.

Vikir’s mind was racing with the policies and exploits of the famous bureaucrats he had seen and heard about before his regression.

The letter of appointment to the position of Deputy Magistrate, stamped with the seal of Hugo le Baskerville, Lord of Ironblooded Baskerville, slipped deep into the pocket of Vikir’s arm.

“You’ll have to prove yourself quickly.”

There were many ways to prove oneself and move up the ranks in a short period of time.

Vikir chose the quickest and most obvious one.

Chapter 28

Special Laws of Vikir (1)

◆

Vikir made his way to the city hall in the center of Underdog City.

He made his way across the buildings that housed the many employees, and found his office at the far end.

“The new deputy magistrate is coming today, so make sure the place is clean.”

“Who will he be?”

“I don’t care who it is, I just hope it’s someone who’s a little more hands-on.”

“Hey, what do you expect, I heard he’s fifteen.”

Employees sweep, mop, and clean throughout the building.

On a high wall hung a banner welcoming Vikir van Baskerville, the new Deputy Archon and Acting Archon.

Vikir walked nonchalantly past the workers.

He was supposed to start tomorrow, so they didn’t pay much attention to him.

“Is this your kid, did the staff bring him here?”

“Honey, you’re not supposed to be here.”

“It’s temporarily closed because the High King is coming tomorrow.”

“You can go out there and play, there’s a playground outside for the staff kids.”

A few employees blocked Vikir’s path.

“Move over.”

When Vikir sees the letter of appointment in his hand, he ducks his head in confusion.

“…, You’re early for work, Mr. President.”

The staff falls flat on their faces, looking as if they’ve seen a ghost.

Vikir walks into the office and sits down in the overstuffed chair.

His first order, as soon as he assumed his position as de facto ruler, was order number one.

“Colonize the liquor and the women.”

◆

Baskerville, Chihuahua.

For ten years now, he’d been the clerk of the town hall here, and he felt a sinking feeling in his stomach.

“I can’t believe I’ve been drinking since day one.”

And he’s only 15 years old.

After all of his predecessors were suspended for bribery, it’s hard not to feel sick to the stomach when a new kid comes in and starts getting promiscuous.

‘What an asshole, and in a sacred workplace, too!

Chihuahua Baskerville rubbed his forehead with his hand.

He was from outside the clan and had been given the surname Baskerville in recognition of his administrative prowess.

Although he had to settle for the title of secretary because he didn’t have a middle name of “Les” or “La” or “Van,” he was working hard.

“Man, I’ve got a lot of work to do, and then some rascal comes rolling in and says…. At least I had some hope that Baskerville was from the inside.”

I hadn’t gotten my hopes up when the 15-year-old kid said he was coming, but now they were dashed.

Even now, the sound of clinking glasses, giggling women, and singing clowns could be heard outside the window.

Baskerville, the Chihuahua, twitched his goatee nervously and threw down his filing cabinet.

“Yeah, damn it, it takes a damned underdog cigar to wake me up and just…!?”

But he couldn’t get his complaint out.

Creak-

The door to his office opened, revealing a boy.

Vikir Van Baskerville. The new Archon.

He was finally officially in the office.

“You’re the head of the office.”

The Chihuahua Baskerville gave Vikir a mock polite look.

“Yes, sir. I’m Chihuahua Baskerville.”

“You don’t have a middle name.”

The Chihuahua’s expression hardened slightly at Vikir’s words.

To not even have a middle name for a half-breed or illegitimate child was to be from outside the family.

Usually, those brought in from the outside were indentured servants within the Baskervilles for three years before being given the Baskerville surname and formally admitted into the family, which was exactly what Staffordshire and Chihuahua had done.

Strictly speaking, they are not blood relatives, but users.

The new deputies would always use this as a way to discriminate against the newcomers.

So Chihuahua had to put up with the bitterness of this atmosphere.

But.

“Good.”

Vikir’s assessment came as a surprise.

As the Chihuahua’s eyes widened, Vikir recalled a memory from the past.

“Chihuahua Baskerville, yes, I recognize the name.”

He’s a skinny guy, and his goatee gives him the image of a lowly ganeshin, but he’s surprisingly kind-hearted.

And because he was an outsider, he faced a lot of discrimination, and his accomplishments were often labeled as those of a ruler or deputy ruler.

This was something that Vikir identified with.

Vikir also doesn’t trust his own family members, and outsiders with proven credentials are much more trustworthy.

“I took a quick look at your bio on the way in. You’re from Underdog City, right?”

“Yes? Yes, yes, I’m a native, born and raised here.”

“Then you know the lay of the land better than I, a newcomer to the city.”

“…That’s right.”

The Chihuahua hesitated to answer, then realized he shouldn’t have.

He knew from experience that this would be followed by a string of “If you know so much, why don’t you do it?”, “If you’re so good, why are you working for me?”, “How dare you try to boss me around?”, “Why don’t you just do it all?”, and so on.

But once again, Vikir’s answer was unexpected.

“I know the hard work of the people who actually run on the field, and I have no intention of interfering with their principles, customs, or styles.”

The Chihuahua went blank at that.

He hadn’t expected to hear these words from someone from within the family.

Naturally, he was expecting a sense of privilege and to tear down all the old customs as bad.

“Well, at least you don’t seem to be a carcinogenic character.”

If it didn’t do any good, at least it wouldn’t do any harm.

While the Chihuahua breathed a sigh of relief, Vikir flipped through the papers on his desk.

Parallax.

The sound of the papers being flipped, and the Chihuahua didn’t expect Vikir to be looking at them.

But to his surprise, Vikir was looking at all of them carefully.

And then. Closing the papers, Vikir said.

“I don’t see anything wrong with the legislative system, but there are a lot of oddities in the judicial system.”

“What? You’ve seen all that, the bird?”

Chihuahua asked in amazement. The papers here are hundreds of pages long.

But Vikir already knew a lot about the Underdog City.

It was one of the more prominent cities in the pre-Reversion spy and planting operations.

“There are illegal gambling houses, brothels, slave auctions, and all sorts of private banking going on in the territory. The underground economy of Underdog City is probably quite substantial.”

The Chihuahua’s eyes narrowed.

Vikir continued.

“Perhaps these are the factors that led to the departure of the previous deputy magistrates. It will not be easy to break the cycle without some sort of compromise.”

“….”

“Aye. What do you think, you underdog native?”

Vikir asks outright, and the Chihuahua can only twitch his lips.

Not only has Vikir grasped all these documents and gotten to the heart of Underdog City’s core issues, but he’s also consulted with her on the most important issues without looking down on her as a subordinate from the outside.

And he came to me on his first day, even a day in advance!

At this sudden turn of events, which defied common sense, the Chihuahua could only stammer, unable to answer.

Vikir smirks.

“It’s actually quite easy to take down an underground economy, you just have to get to the heart of the matter, hidden amongst the dotty remnants of lawlessness.”

In a previous life, Vikir had a long history of battling illegal organizations in the underdog city.

As a result, he knew almost everything about who was committing what crimes and where they were hiding.

He even knew the locations and identities of the bureaucrats who were taking bribes.

‘It’s worth it,’ I thought, ‘to look through the black books left over from the pre-Regression busting of the illegal organizations.

It’s the job of a deputy magistrate to make and enforce laws.

Vikir got right to work.

“I honor all the laws that have come before. I’m just adding one new law to them.”

“A new law?”

“Yes. It won’t be very long, a few lines at most.”

Vikir’s eyes lit up.

“Within a week, we will have dried up the seeds of Underdog City’s underground economy.”

Short and bold, he finished and floated off to the Academy.

There was a war on crime to come, and some laws that would be necessary.

“And to create and enforce these laws, we need a rationale.”

Hearing Vikir murmur, the Chihuahua felt herself slowly being drawn into the strange aura the boy exuded.

She couldn’t help but ask.

“What’s the point? Why do you want to fight lawlessness…?”

“I’m still young, and above all, am I not a rookie who will be joining the force tomorrow?”

Vikir looked back at the Chihuahua and smirked.

“Isn’t the least you could do is give me a ‘warning’?”

“…?”

The Chihuahua shakes his head, unable to understand Vikir’s words.

But Vikir doesn’t bother to explain further.

Instead, he strokes his chin as he looks out the window of the ruler’s office and down at the bar.

Pour, drink. The gathering to welcome the new Deputy Archon, Vikir, is already large.

In fact, the party was going strong even without him.

And Vikir, who should be the center of attention, is sitting in the high council chambers right now, planning tomorrow’s events.

“…Yes. You gotta shit to catch shit flies.”

Vikir’s voice, muttering in a low voice, had an edge to it that didn’t belong to a 15-year-old.

And the Chihuahua thought.

Maybe this encounter with the boy in front of him would change his entire life.

Chapter 29

Special Laws of Vikir (2)

◆

Dortmeyer Street, the main street of the metropolitan underdog.

A notice on a large banner hung in the center of the crowded street.

It was unusual for the ruling government to post a notice here, but the content of the announcement itself was nothing new.

<Article 00, Section 0 of the Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville. Law on the Prohibition of Illegal Trafficking in Persons… Penalty: Death>

<Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville, Article 00, Section 0. Law prohibiting illegal gambling… Penalty: wrist amputation>

<Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville, Article 00, paragraph 0. Law on the Prohibition of Illegal Private Banking… Penalty: Eyeball removal>

<Article 00, paragraph 0 of the Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville. Law on the prohibition of illegal brothels… Criminalization: Facial tattooing>.

<Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville, Article 00, Section 0. Law against illegal lobbying… Sentence: deportation from the territory>.

.

.

All laws that were originally there.

They are quite strict because they are the laws of a territory controlled by Ironblood Baskerville.

But few citizens trusted them to be upheld.

“Chet. Laws only favor those with power.”

“It’s all the same to the big guys.”

“Isn’t it a world where the law-abiding are the losers?”

“The law is far away, the fist is closer.”

The citizens of Underdog City, which has an unusually high crime rate, scoff at the Manahan Law.

They’ve seen it all before, how the bureaucrats from Baskerville, the fat cats, and the second and third generations of Sedoga collude to get their way.

The moneyed, the powerful, and the mighty make it work in their favor, interpret it, enforce it, and….

If you’re broke, poor, and powerless, there’s nothing you can do about it.

All they can do is cry, drink, blame themselves for their bad luck, or take out their anger on those less fortunate and weaker than them.

Underdog citizens accustomed to this fate are naturally distrustful of the law.

“Well, at least the previous deputy magistrates were busted for bribery, so maybe it will make a difference.”

“Of course not, the new deputy from Baskerville is 15 years old.”

“What? Fifteen is the same age as my youngest daughter. What’s a girl like that supposed to do….”

“That’s what I’m saying. Pretty soon she’ll be roasting in the lobby of the local lords.”

Public opinion was not very favorable to the new deputy.

Some cite his age, some cite his unwritten laws, some cite his scattered gangs, and some cite the myriad temptations that await the novice bureaucrat.

Just then.

“Hey, guys, come on down to the main square! Big news!”

The already bustling place became even more bustling.

People rush to the square to see what’s going on.

Thousands and thousands of people.

And in the middle of it all, as if a meteorite had fallen, there is an empty spot.

A circular space where no one has set foot.

In the center of it all, a cold-faced boy stands with a stick.

It was Vikir van Baskerville, the newest deputy magistrate, 15 years old.

◆

Vikir held a stick in his hand.

Seventy centimeters long. A small stake weighing about three kilograms.

People crowded around to see the new deputy magistrate, but they never got close.

That’s because of the mountainous energy emanating from the boy’s tiny body.

Behind this untouchable aura, several government officials stood nervously.

They were employees of the Executive Office, including Chihuahua Baskerville.

“Oh, my God, what is he going to do?”

“He’s been standing there since the crack of dawn, do you understand?”

“There’s a lot of people here, wow-”

The citizens and officials alike had no idea what Vikir was trying to do here.

Then.

“Listen.”

Seeing that the audience was more or less gathered, Vikir spoke.

“I am the new deputy magistrate.”

The murmurs around him grew louder.

“He’s that young?”, “He looks even younger in person”, “He’s cute”, “What would a kid like that do?”, and other unserious comments.

Ignoring the stares and voices, Vikir continued.

“I’m sure you’ve all seen the notice on the north side of the square.”

For a moment, the crowd’s eyes shifted to the north.

Sure enough, there it was, a law written on a large banner.

<Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville, Article 00, Section 0. Law against tax evasion… Sentence: kneecap removal>.

<Article 00, paragraph 0 of the Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville. Law against smuggling… Sentence: waterboarding

<Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville, Article 00, paragraph 0. Law against illegal drugs… Sentence: tongue amputation>

<Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville, Article 00, Section 0. Law Against Embezzlement of Munitions… Punishment: Extermination of three legs>

<Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville, Article 00, Section 0. Law against adultery… Sentence: 600 lashes>.

.

.

Well, they’re familiar laws that aren’t followed.

Laws that are only abstract to the weak who have no money, no power, and no strength.

The number of commoners punished by these laws since their inception is unknown, and the number of nobles and noblemen punished is zero, a cold reality.

The people’s gaze shifted away from the banner and back to Vikir.

Vikir continued.

“Those are the laws that have been in place since time immemorial, the very laws that have kept Baskerville’s self-governance alive.”

A small chuckle escaped him.

It was a clear mockery of laws that were not being followed, of a justice system that was not being followed except by the rich, powerful, and mighty.

But Vikir did not seek out and punish the laughter.

“….”

He simply scanned the public with an indifferent gaze.

It was an attitude that lay somewhere between generosity and indifference.

Vikir continued, his voice dry again.

“The laws of Baskerville still stand, and they will be upheld, despite the change in Vice-Regent.”

When Vikir didn’t respond to the audience’s jeers, they got a little bolder.

“Pfft!”, “Of course!”, “Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.”

The Chihuahua office manager, who couldn’t believe what he was seeing, yelled from the back.

“You people, what kind of safety do you think you’re talking about? This is a man from the Baskerville family! Will it take a blade to slice through his throat to get him to come to his senses!”

Chihuahua’s director is a local official who is well-liked by the citizens.

So even the people who were booing him craned their necks in recognition.

“Chet. Mr. Chihuahua is talking over there, let’s stop.”

“Gee, I wonder how the director is more charismatic than the deputy director.”

“I’d rather have Mr. Chihuahua be the deputy.”

“Look at that little guy. He can’t even respond to the boos without Mr. Chihuahua.”

“The law is about to get even more fucked up.”

These are reactions that would have been unthinkable under normal circumstances, but Vikir’s youthfulness, youthful face, and indifference to the reactions around him allowed them to get away with it.

“….”

This time, Vikir didn’t react at all.

Even in this atmosphere of being compared to and devalued by his subordinate Chihuahua, Vikir simply stood there with an expressionless face.

The city officials, including Chihuahua’s secretary general, blushed and didn’t know what to do.

Meanwhile, even the citizens, who were booing at Vikir’s unresponsive behavior, were feeling drained.

“Maybe he’s just a kid, but he can’t handle these insults.”

“How can a kid like him be expected to enforce the law?”

“He’s just going to let the criminals run rampant … for a while.”

Gazes of abandonment and resignation, mockery and anger, pity and contempt, were being directed at one Vikir.

And then.

Vikir raised the stick he was holding high.

And then.

…Poof!

He drove it straight into the ground.

Ten centimeters into the ground.

It’s pretty heavy, but it’s only a small stake.

A child could easily pull it out.

…?

When all the citizens are looking puzzled.

Vikir, who had taken a few steps back, spoke up.

“I am hereby promulgating a new special law under the legislative authority of the Deputy Magistrate.”

Article 1, Section 1 of the Vikir Special Law.

“Whoever pulls this stake will be paid 100 million gold in cash.”

It was as simple as that.

Chapter 31

Special Laws of Vikir (4)

◆

The story of the girl who won ten billion by moving a stick quickly spread throughout Underdog City and all of Baskerville’s territory.

Rumour has it that Underdog City even provided a bodyguard to protect the girl’s winnings.

‘Such is the law. It will be upheld.

The short speech of the newly appointed young deputy magistrate was on the lips of countless people.

Naturally, Vikir’s law, or “Vikir’s Special Law,” became even more famous than Baskerville’s self-governance.

The gossips were saying.

“The new deputy magistrate is different, isn’t he?”

“Vikir says that once he says something, he does it no matter what.”

“They say the crime rate in Underdog City has dropped by half since that day.”

“It used to be said that the law was far away and the fist was near, but now the law is near and the fist is far away.”

Break the law and you’re punished; follow the law and you’re rewarded.

This simple principle impressed the citizens.

A society that stands by its principles.

The distrust of the law, which was not being followed, was washed away after that day.

The day after the special law was promulgated, illegal activities were noticeably reduced and the crime rate was halved.

The darkness that had been so deeply rooted in the underdog city had been cleared by this one performance.

◆

Underdog City Hall.

The director of Chihuahua Baskerville was smiling and writing on a signboard.

<Imokji Shin (移木之信)>

A banner to be hung in the Governor’s office from this day forward.

Vikir stared at it from Chihuahua’s side, then spoke up.

“Your handwriting is very good, Chihuahua.”

“Sure. I’ve never met anyone with better penmanship than me since I was born, and I’ve gotten so good at imitating other people’s handwriting because the Archons always make me sign for them….”

The Chihuahua didn’t finish his sentence.

Vikir had blurted out something unexpected.

“Can’t I learn to do that too?”

The Chihuahua’s eyes widened at Vikir’s words.

It was the first time a high-snouted member of the Baskerville clan from the main family had ever asked him to do something that wasn’t a command.

Moreover, despite being a sword eater, he was interested in brushes.

“Of course I can teach you, I’d be honoured!”

“Thank you. I’ll ask you whenever I have time.”

The Chihuahua hums and teases the brush after hearing the praise.

Vikir watched him in wonder.

Chihuahua Baskerville.

He was an outsider, a commoner who had spent three years as an indentured servant to the Baskervilles before being given the surname of Baskerville and formally integrated into the family.

Unlike the swordsmen who become Guardian Knights and are trained in Baskerville-style swordsmanship, administrators are paid less and receive no special training.

While swordsmen are motivated to become part of the Baskerville family, as mastery of the Baskerville style of swordsmanship improves their skills by several levels, administrators like Chihuahua have little to attract them other than honour.

‘As I understand it, … he joined Baskerville with the sole intention of serving his homeland.’

Vikir had seen the Chihuahua a few times before his regression.

A man who, for all that he looked like a ganeshin, had the temper of a high priestess, and who spouted off to the rulers and deputy rulers.

And a capable administrator who was relegated to the fringes and never saw the light of day until he was old and dead.

Vikir was thinking about the Chihuahua.

“By the way, you’re doing a great job, sir.”

The Chihuahua finished his whistle and looked at Vikir.

“Who would have thought you could pull off such an unconventional performance, Chihuahua? I’m truly blown away, and I’ve been here for 20 years, just as a clerk, and I’ve never been so thrilled. I’m still shaking in my boots.”

Vikir nodded slightly.

“The laws of Baskerville are actually pretty good. But it’s not enough to put a law out there, it’s important that the people believe in it and follow it.”

“You’re right, and you’re absolutely right. But that’s not what the previous Deputy Magistrates thought.”

“We can’t afford to be angry at the manors for their distrust of the law or their ignorance of it, so I’ve been thinking about how to engage them and make a strong impression on them.”

In fact, this is a performance that Camus of the House of Morgue would perform quite some time later.

As soon as he ascends to the position of Lord of the Manor, Camus of Morgue, who will later be known as the Auspicious Weather, becomes a formidable figure of power and turns his domain into a strong law-and-order region.

The lords of the land would not pick up money that fell to the ground, and there were no quarrels among them, so much so that the crime rate dropped to almost zero.

‘…However, his reign of terror did not endear him to the lords.

However, in the midst of the war against the demons, Camus’s iron fist was able to increase human survival rates by leaps and bounds, and indeed, even after the Generation of Destruction, Morgue’s estate had the largest population of survivors left.

…That was the last thing on his mind right now.

“Now it’s about going forward.”

Vikir said, looking down at the map of Underdog City.

“With 10 billion in prize money, we’re going to have to find a way to fill the hole, right?”

With that, Vikir picked up a pen and began drawing red X’s all over the map.

As if he knew exactly where everything was, Vikir drew an X in every nook and cranny.

X X X X X X X X X…

In no time at all, the number of X’s on the map rose to over a hundred.

“These are the places where illegal organisations are hiding or will hide in the future. We’re going to crack down on them one by one and return the black money to the treasury.”

“Uh, how do you know these places are where criminals operate?”

“I smell it.”

Vikir presses his nose to his lips and smirks.

Baskerville’s hounds have a keen sense of smell.

With the dazed Chihuahua behind him, Vikir continues to recite his plan.

“In military law, the highest form of procurement is from enemy territory. If we rob everything here, we’ll raise a lot of tax revenue. We can use it to bolster the welfare system for the poor.”

“Yeah. That’s despite the crime rate being cut in half. The performance has reduced the overt crimes, but the ones that remain have become more stealthy and sophisticated.”

But it doesn’t matter.

Vikir knew the location of all of these illegal outfits, and the key players at the heart of them.

“It’s an area we patrolled and cracked down on tirelessly before we went back.”

I still have vivid memories of being a hound dog during the ‘War on Crime’, frantically biting rats in the back alleys.

I also knew the tricks of the trade because some of my close colleagues had been bribed.

I know how criminals think and behave, where they hide, what they do, how they operate, and how far they go.

I also knew all the channels through which underground money would flow for at least the next 25 years.

Whirring, whirring, whirring.

Beelzebub, lurking in the artery in my wrist, senses life and begins to twitch slightly.

It’s hungry for blood.

Just then.

“Deputy!”

The door opens and a clerk enters, looking puzzled.

“There’s a request for an interview at ….”

Both Vicky and Chihuahua turn their heads at the words.

Chihuahua asks first.

“Who’s requesting an interview on official time? You’ve been here less than two days.”

“Well, that is. The Youth Self-Governance Committee of the local government office would like to meet with you once….”

Then the Chihuahua’s face stiffened.

It looked like it had finally arrived.

Vikir broke the ice.

“So, you’re saying you want to see the farting bastards in the community?”

“…That’s right, the youth wing of the Xiangcheng is made up of the second and third generations of the local retainers, especially the influential Sedoga.”

He’s asking to see Vikir among the youth of other smaller families within the Baskervilles’ domain, indigenous families that have long held sway in the area.

Most of them have direct or indirect ties to the Baskervilles, often by blood, sometimes by delay, sometimes by marriage.

The Chihuahua spoke with an air of disdain in his voice that he could barely conceal, even with a tightly clenched fist.

“It’s the Youth Autonomy Committee of the Mali Township Office, but it’s really just a messy social club. Apparently they have something to say about the ‘Vikir Special Law’.”

“…Hmm.”

Hearing that, Vikir leaned back on the couch, chin in hand.

“When you make a law to root out absurdity, it’s the most corrupt places that make the most noise.”

The first backlash against Vikir’s special law. Was it coming from the Autonomous Council?

Turning to his Chihuahua, who was watching him anxiously, Vikir spoke briefly.

“The dung beetles smelled it first.”

Hadn’t he been laying out the shit since his first day on the job, knowing that would happen?

Now it’s time to get rid of the city-eating pests.

Chapter 33

The Social Club (2)

◆

The seven masters gathered in the VVIP room were all smart and ruthless.

The House of Montblanc, the House of Pierre, the House of Louis Vuitton, the House of Channel, the House of Ferragamo, the House of Hermes, the House of Prada.

The seven indigenous families of the province in which they work have lived unnoticed by anyone except the Baskervilles.

Even those from the Baskervilles have been persuaded by their wealth and the public sentiment behind them, and have become friends.

Life had never gone their way before, so they assumed it would be the same this time.

So, it’s true that I was a little naughty this time.

…But.

This time, things were different.

Hoo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo

A shower of glass and champagne bubbles rained down on the VVIP room.

The glass and boiling champagne reflect the brilliant light of the chandeliers.

The seven masters of the Seven Families, whose entire bodies were drenched in the sharp, hot showers, wore dazed expressions.

‘Did you just blow up the Champagne Tower with a mana resonance?

‘Just by touching the table?

‘And not from the bottom up, but from the top down?

All of them had a basic understanding of martial arts in their own right, so they could see the absurdity of what Vikir was doing.

To be able to channel mana into an object, cause it to vibrate with resonance, and then explode it at exactly the right spot was not something that could be achieved with normal mana proficiency.

Moreover, the glasses shattered from above, not below.

It would take a master of the technique to shatter the glass on top of the table while the glass on the bottom is still intact.

And the fact that the direction of action is vertical, not horizontal, adds to the difficulty.

This means that you have to be able to manipulate mana stalks that are much thinner and finer than microfibres, like limbs.

Ultra-difficult mana manipulation. The realm of the truly badass.

There is only one thought on everyone’s minds.

“Gradient!”

Monsters who can slice through boulders the size of their fists with their swords and knock down birds in flight with their momentum alone.

I wonder if these masters, who are barely above the rank of Expert, are not some vague, untouchable powerhouse.

“….”

Vikir’s face remains expressionless.

However, the black aura coursing through his shoulders is that of a grim reaper.

If death had a tangible form, wouldn’t it look like this?

The masters, soaked in a shower of champagne, began to shiver.

‘He’s crazy, he’s a 15-year-old kid!

“Dude, you’re an Expert Intermediate, do something!”

“Shut up! You won’t last a second!”

In the midst of all the urgent exchanges of glances, one of the masters muttered in a dazed voice.

“…That’s right, Vikir, I thought I’d heard of you!”

At that, all eyes snapped to one side.

He spoke in a stuttering tone.

“Vikir van Baskerville. The supernova of House Baskerville! Dived for seven minutes before he was born, strangled two vipers in his cradle, hunted Cerberus at the age of eight, dueled and defeated House Morgue’s Madness Castle….”

The other masters’ faces change as if they’ve just heard some crazy urban legend.

But… But what if they were really true?

The gazes of the masters now turn to Vikir again.

The symbol of the Gradient, the liquid aura.

Unless the urban legends are true, there’s no way to explain the deathly aura that radiates from Vikir’s entire body.

My God, what other 15-year-old kid in the world is already a Gradient at that age!

Even in Baskerville, the home of geniuses, this has never happened before.

Perhaps the same could be said for the Coliseum, the Imperial Academy, or even the entire Yellow City.

In the end, the masters could only smile awkwardly and say something.

“We tried to pay for the ….”

I wonder if they realise that the grim smile they’ve always seen etched on other people’s faces is now etched on their own?

Meanwhile. Vikir, hearing this, replied nonchalantly.

“Of course you will pay for the liquor you have consumed.”

Hearing this, the seven masters closed their mouths in disbelief.

“Oh, by the way. We haven’t eaten yet.”

He had inadvertently given away his plan to embarrass them.

Still, since I hadn’t met Meg yet, I thought I could make a good excuse and get away with it.

…If only it weren’t for Vikir.

He’s only 15 years old, but his soul is already worn out.

Vikir saw right through what the seven masters were trying to do.

“What, you’re going to play with me and then blame me for the cost of your drinks?”

The seven masters jumped and shook their heads at Vikir’s question, which seemed to pierce their veins like a ghost.

“That, that would be impossible!”

“Who would do such an unscrupulous thing!”

“How dare anyone from the Baskerville family ask us to….”

The seven masters felt.

The other party wasn’t just strong in combat power. Their minds were also unstoppable.

In the end, they lowered their tails.

They had been arrogant enough to think that Baskerville was their dog, but now that they stood in front of Vikir, they could no longer afford to be so ruthless.

Apparently, the Baskervilles’ hounds are not easily baked or boiled.

But a certain amount of pride, built up over the years as the second generation of the local holding family, has allowed them to save some dignity for last.

“Actually, we wanted to test you, Deputy Magistrate.”

The Masters composed themselves and spoke in a polite manner.

Vikir remained expressionless.

Taking the silence to mean ‘let’s hear it’, the Masters relaxed and continued in a polite tone.

“Honestly, Underdog City is quite corrupt, isn’t it?”

“If you’re going to purify a city like this, you shouldn’t be able to resist such a temptation.”

“You are indeed worthy to lead us, I will follow.”

“Oh, let me take this great spirit as a lesson for the rest of my life!”

“I will express it to you today, in such a way that you will not be disappointed later.”

They bowed once more to Vikir, and spoke in earnest voices.

Some of them even winked at Vikir in an attempt to appear casual.

And then.

“….”

One corner of Vikir’s mouth slowly lifted.

A smile.

This small change completely changed the mood of the room.

Just a moment ago, it had been a creepy, graveyard atmosphere.

And that alone had been enough to terrify the Seven Masters.

But now?

An almost maddening sense of gravity.

A suffocating pressure began to weigh down on the seven masters, as if they were being buried alive in an earthen tomb.

Unable to breathe properly, they began to shiver, the smiles on their faces completely lost.

Vikir walked slowly to the front of the seven masters, who were now cowering like frogs in a snake’s stomach.

“A master can test his dog as much as he likes.”

“….”

“But not the other way round. A dog can never test his master, under any circumstances.”

It was a moment that reminded her of Hugo’s teaching from long ago.

Vikir paced slowly in front of the frozen masters.

“You have all this money and power, so you’re not afraid, are you?” he asked.

Unsurprisingly, there was no reply.

Vikir continued.

“It’s just that I’ve never seen anything really scary.”

So how dare you pretend to be expected, to be gentle, to be relaxed.

And the price of that “pretence” was heavy.

Vikir pulled a flimsy stick from his arm.

It was the very same stake that had won the girl a prize of ten billion not long ago.

…Billion!

A dull noise.

The stake bent for a moment, then flew out at a tremendous speed, smashing the face of the master in front of her into a bloody mess.

The blow came from nowhere, with no end in sight.

Teeth gnashing, spittle, blood, and tears snorting.

In the time it took him to blink three times, Vikir struck him seven times across the face, head, neck, and shoulders, and then did the same to the others.

The next thing you know, they’re all sprawled flat on the floor of the VVIP room.

Puck! Thud! Thud! Thud! Thud! Thud! Thud!

Vikir didn’t stop beating them for a long time after that.

“Do you know why you were beaten?”

“Ew! I don’t know! I don’t know! Why are you hitting me all of a sudden?”

“If you don’t know, you must be beaten.”

Vikir swung the stake in a nonchalant tone.

Looking at his expressionless face, the masters thought he might actually die at this rate.

“Oh, I know, ugh, I think I know why you’re hitting me!”

The dogs begged desperately through their busted lips, torn tongues, and broken teeth.

They pleaded with their torn lips, torn tongues, broken teeth, and the red blood that gushed like a fountain from every inch of their heads.

But the owner remained unimpressed.

“Sweeten the deal.”

Vikir’s flogging doesn’t stop at the red light.

Chapter 34

The Social Club (3)

◆

The rumours spread quickly.

A group of seven people who had been living high on the hog, indulging in extravagance and vice, had been arrested all at once.

The citizens of Underdog City always talked about it whenever they got together in groups of three or more.

“Well, they were trying to get in the way of the new Deputy Mayor, and they got caught.”

“Oh, aren’t they the ones who used to treat the common people like bugs, and now they’re in charge?”

“But what do you think will happen to them? The new magistrate’s personality doesn’t seem normal, so they won’t just be released, will they?”

“Aye, they’re still the second generation of a native family, I’m sure he’ll let them go with a moderate amount of humiliation.”

The crowd naturally turned their heads away.

In the northern part of the central square, a banner was still fluttering in the wind.

<Article 00, paragraph 0 of the Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville. Law on the Prohibition of Illegal Trafficking in Persons… Penalty: Death>

<Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville, Article 00, Section 0. Law against illegal gambling… Penalty: wrist amputation>

<Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville, Article 00, paragraph 0. Law on the Prohibition of Illegal Private Banking… Penalty: Eyeball removal>

<Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville, Article 00, paragraph 0. Law on the prohibition of illegal brothels… Criminal offence: Facial tattooing

<Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville, Article 00, Section 0. Law against illegal lobbying… Sentence: extraterritorial deportation>.

.

.

As it was originally labelled.

There were no exceptions to the law.

There was no special provision for the rich and powerful to be forgiven.

The crimes of the seven masters could not have been clearer.

They were guilty of illegal sex work, illegal lobbying, illegal human trafficking, consuming and distributing drugs, and making ill-gotten gains in the process.

Tax evasion, assault, and sexual assault were obvious options.

So the sentence is clear.

Death.

No excuses, no mitigating circumstances.

People chattered.

“You’re going to execute the sons of those seven indigenous families?”

“Fool, don’t you know the character of the new deputy? He burned ten billion on a single stake!”

“If you kill those seven bastards, the repercussions will be devastating.”

“Why don’t we just give them a few good whacks and humiliate them?”

“Yes. I don’t think they’ll get the death penalty, though.”

They all spoke in unison.

This is a power game between the new politicians and the indigenous tycoons, and if the latter would just bow out and keep their heads down, everything would be smooth sailing.

And just as people thought, Mont Blanc, Pierre, Louis Vuitton, Channel, Ferragamo, Hermès, and Prada offered their sincere apologies to the new deputy.

The local retainers bowed and entered.

The citizens did the same and clicked their tongues when they saw the carriages representing each family, laden with lavish tributes, making their way to City Hall in the dead of night.

The seven rascals who had been detained would now be released unharmed and would be given a good shouting match by their landlord father.

That was the end of it.

The local keepers will either avenge this humiliation in some way, or they will bow down and look the other way, and for a time the seven rascals will do their time and keep quiet.

The new, young deputy magistrate has scored a nice victory over the native wealthy.

The citizens will be moderately pleased, moderately outraged, and moderately forgetful of this obvious outcome.

They will.

….

…No, I knew it would happen.

Until this morning, when seven heads were hung in the centre of the main square.

Seven heads, salted and disembowelled.

Bereft of their bodies, their heads were contorted as if they had been in terrible agony on the brink of death.

The notices beneath their heads detail the additional punishments they received before they died, before they were executed.

<Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville, Article 00, Section 0. Law on the prohibition of illegal brothels… sentences: Facial tattooing>.

*Executed in accordance with the above law, tattooing the word “colour” on the entire face.

<Article 00, paragraph 0 of the Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville. Law against Illegal Gambling… Sentence: Wrist amputation>

*Enforced in accordance with the above law, both wrists were cut off.

*This sentence is retroactive to the number of times he violated the law, so after his wrists were cut, he continued to cut them for a certain length of time.

This prisoner was sentenced to 72 wrist cuts.

<Article 00, paragraph 0 of the Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville. Law on the prohibition of illegal private finance… sentences: Eyeball removal>.

*Executed without prejudice, taking into account the pleas of the victims of these prisoners.

<Article 00, paragraph 0 of the Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville. Law against Illegal Trafficking in Persons… Sentence: Death>

*Executed according to law.

<Constitution of the Autonomous Region of Baskerville, Article 00, paragraph 0. Law against illegal lobbying… Sentence: Exile from the territory>

*Banishment outside the city walls, except for the head, as they are already exiles.

.

.

The citizens could only gape.

The law itself was always there, so there is no need to think of it as excessive or harsh.

The problem is that the prisoners who were subjected to the law were not ordinary prisoners.

It’s not just a power game.

This is a war of attrition that will last until one of them is gone.

There was no one who didn’t expect a bloodbath.

◆

Not long before the sentence was carried out.

Vikir stood before the grate in the dungeon.

Inside the dungeon, he could see the seven Masters, bloodied and groaning, imprisoned.

“…Now, you shanki, wu abujihate, it’s all over.”

“Get out of here, Ba, how can I!”

“For the love of God, let them go!”

And before him stood Baskerville, the Chihuahua, restless.

“Oh, my lord, my lord. What did you do to beat them like this?”

He sounded more than a little pleased with himself.

Vikir, who had been standing beside him, expressionless, suddenly turned his head.

“Do you think what I did to these men was excessive?”

“What? Oh, yes, of course I do! A fashionista deserves a good beating, and if you turn people into meat patties like this, how are you going to pay for it later…”

Vikir smiled wryly.

“Don’t worry about it. I haven’t even started yet.”

“…?”

Chihuahua asks, confused.

Vikir didn’t answer, but thought about it.

Township offices were originally meant to check and supervise local maladministration, edify local society, and coordinate relations with the city hall.

But over time, they had become more and more like a red herring, and now they had surpassed even the power of the malevolent Baskervilles.

“Gamani no dew!”

“Two, leave it!”

“Huaangfei’s bastardised family name!”

The way they growled, it was even more so.

But Vikir, soaking up their hatred, seemed unperturbed.

“I will execute them all at the end of the day.”

…!

At those words, the masters in the cage fell silent.

Vikir spoke once more.

“While I’m at it, I’ll exterminate them all, from the babes in the club to the demons in the streets.”

The fearsome words were unmistakably true.

Everything would be done according to his word, 100% of the time.

A war on crime had been declared.

The masters looked dumbfounded for a moment, but now they grabbed the grate and began to shake it.

“Now, come on, good boy!”

“Haberma! Haberma bazusae!”

“Gazing all over the place!”

People who usually look at others like bugs crawl on the floor like bugs.

At this moment, the Chihuahua was feeling complex emotions.

He wondered if he would ever see anything like this in his life.

On the other hand, he feared the retaliation of the local indigenous leaders.

Their retaliation is both sleepy and deadly.

From now on, no spawn would come to any of Vikir’s businesses, and attendance at his events would be very low.

The city would be at a disadvantage in trade with other cities, and tax revenues would dwindle.

But Vikir was nonchalant.

It was as if he had all his bases covered.

“There’s nothing to worry about, sir.”

“…Ha, but.”

“Their families won’t be able to protest.”

“Yes? Why?”

Vikir answered the Chihuahua’s question with uncharacteristic ease.

“They’re involved with criminal groups large and small in Underdog City.”

“What? Zee, how does the Archon know that….”

Vikir remained silent, not wanting to say he’d seen it before the regression.

Then the Chihuahua looked concerned.

“But it’s the proof that counts, isn’t it? And even if we do get proof, what kind of retaliation they’ll do next.”

“Don’t worry, there are plenty of them.”

Vikir laughed.

We’ll find the evidence. If we don’t find it, we make it.

And everything that happened next was beyond Vikir’s concern.

For Vikir was already thinking about moving on.

‘I don’t know who’s going to replace me, but it’s going to be tough.

I don’t expect Hugo to stay on as deputy for long.

The world was about to change, and there was a good chance that he would be sent into actual combat in the near future.

So it didn’t matter much to Vikir’s future if he threw a temper tantrum here and now.

He would have to leave as soon as he was accepted into the Academy.

“So, while you’re here as a deputy, you might as well get some discipline.”

The answer was to prescribe medicines that were highly effective, even if they had some side effects.

This would soon become a reputation that would propel Vikir’s career.

It didn’t matter who came after him. Vikir hated members of his own Baskerville family the most.

…But a thousand miles a day.

To do that, I need to make these seven sixth formers… nay masters in front of me spit out all the evidence of their collaboration with the criminal element, and even their location.

Vikir stepped up to the bars and said.

“I will tell you what you are accused of.”

“….”

“Illegal kidnapping and imprisonment of women, sexual assault, intimidation, forced administration of illegal drugs, human trafficking, and forcing them into the sex trade, as well as bribes, extortion, blackmail, and murder of government officials….”

The masters were outraged.

“That’s the karma of the enemy! We’ll punish you when we have proof!”

“We’ll punish him when we have the evidence? Are you saying there’s a crime but no evidence?”

“That’s right, Gerson…”

The masters look at each other, puzzled.

Then a determined look crosses their faces.

“If I have to die here, I will do so without harming the family name.”

If we blow it here, we can’t expect revenge.

The clan would turn on them, and even if they did, Vikir, given the nature of that psycho, he might go further and use the sit-in system on the clan, tearing them down to the roots.

‘Never, I’ll never tell!’

The seven miscreants shut their mouths, ready to die for their family.

…But.

“Oh, now you’re here.”

Vikir waved towards an entrance in the dungeon corridor.

Apparently, he had been standing in front of the grate all this time, waiting for someone.

“…?”

The Seven Masters followed Vikir’s gaze with curiosity and anxiety.

And there, walking towards them, was a gaunt old man carrying a large basket.

“Your customisation is complete, my lord.”

The old man was a torturer who worked in the basement of City Hall.

And then.

Vikir overturned the basket and spilled its contents onto the shelf.

Clink-clink.

What emerged were hundreds of knives.

Each one grotesque and hideous, bent, twisted, distorted, blunt, and sharp.

The old torturer grinned, showing his yellowed teeth.

“Wow, I’ve been torturing people for the past 30 years, and I’ve never seen anything like this before. How did you come up with all these creepy devices?”

“I didn’t invent them. They were commonplace where I was.”

“Was the place you were before … like hell?”

“Well, it was close. You want to learn a lesson?”

The instruments were gruesome, even for a torturer who had been doing it for thirty years.

Vikir picked them up and walked back to the grate.

“…Gain!”

Instinctively sensing something, the Seven Masters crawled away from the grate.

But just as quickly.

…Thud!

Vikir brazenly pushed open the door to the cage and stepped inside.

Before he regressed, he remembered the faces of his old comrades.

‘I remember, even demonic prisoners spat out military secrets before their torture techniques.

The tortures of the Age of Annihilation made even the demons from hell cry and shit themselves.

Vikir, who knows all about the future torture techniques that have improved by leaps and bounds in the short time he’s been dealing with demons, can’t help but find the sandals with their determined expressions cute.

“You’re making faces like you’re never going to blow.”

Vikir says with a faint smile.

“…Please don’t blow.”

This was genuine.

He wanted to keep the memories and nostalgia alive for as long as possible.

Chapter 35

Slave Auction (1)

◆

Night. The outskirts of Underdog City.

For some reason, luxury carriages have gathered in droves in a vacant lot at the back of the city where no one usually comes.

Black tents cover the huge clearing.

Masked aristocrats and wealthy men stalked into the barracks.

Today is the day of the slave auction. Naturally, it is a slave auction that is not officially reported to Baskerville.

As such, the slaves being sold here are undeclared goods.

There were many people who could not be traded as slaves in the first place.

Barbarians displaced from their homes, nobles from distant lands, or commoners kidnapped out of nowhere.

They were chained, hawked, or drugged to the point where their will to escape or report was completely broken.

Or they were commodities that would be.

“Welcome, welcome, welcome. Welcome to tonight’s ‘freak show’, yes, yes, come, come, come.”

A clown dressed as Pierrot welcomes the audience.

Next, a middle-aged man walks in front of the clown.

The middle-aged man, who has a long goatee and a somewhat scruffy appearance, keeps looking around to see what’s so unsettling.

The clown checked the middle-aged man’s credentials.

“Hmmm hmmm. Mr Montblanc the Chihuahua. Ah, so you’re from the Montblanc family, and your fabulous signature is a Montblanc trademark that no one else can copy. …?”

The clown grabbed a middle-aged man named Chihuahua Montblanc as he tried to let him pass.

The Chihuahua is visibly flustered.

The clown squinted at him and said.

“I see the purpose of your visit on your certificate says you’re not here to buy slaves, but to sell…?”

“Ah. That’s right. I came to sell them.”

“What about for sale?”

“Well, I’ve got him tied up in the back there for a while, and I’ve only got one anyway, and he’s a young lad, so he doesn’t take up much room.”

The clown smirked and ducked his head again.

“I see,” he said, “the Montblancs always buy slaves in bulk, and since you’re here to sell this time, I was wondering if you didn’t like the ones you bought last time and wanted to get rid of them.”

The Chihuahua wiped the sweat from his brow with a handkerchief and shook his head.

“No, sir. I’m always satisfied with the quality of the slaves I buy here.”

“Isn’t that right? That’s right, we only sell carefully selected slaves. We kidnap barbarian women, commoners, and young noblemen from distant provinces who have lost their families and homes and have nowhere else to go, and we train them like rats and birds. They are obedient and never think of running away or rebelling, and we guarantee their quality.”

The clown turned to the Chihuahua and bowed politely once more.

“I would like to extend a hearty welcome to the Freak Show.”

◆

There was a strange tension in the auction room.

Under a haze of hookah and tobacco smoke, masked men and women sat in a circle around centre stage.

Here were all the movers and shakers of the underdog underground economy.

A lady in a butterfly mask salivates at the sight of a naked barbarian male slave on stage, while a gentleman in a bat mask salivates at the sight of a mercenary male slave on stage.

There was no discernible public for the things that came up on stage at the auction house.

There were objects – old urns, famous works of art, sharp swords – and there were rare animals and horses, and there were people branded as slaves.

But for the wealthy people who gathered here, the distinction was a good one.

They’re used to seeing objects, animals, and people as the same thing.

The masked dignitaries, their mouths covered by fans, were chatting amongst themselves.

“I hear it’s all the rage in the Imperial Capital these days to capture and display grotesque-looking slaves?”

“I don’t pay much attention to fashions like that, I just think a slave should be pretty and handsome, that’s all.”

“I don’t know, slaves are supposed to be good at work or good at fighting, aren’t they?”

“Hahaha, I’m drawn to the tragic past that slaves have, which is why I prefer them to come from fallen nobility or kidnapped nobility.”

“Well, whatever. I hope there are plenty of slaves available today.”

Most of the attention was on the slaves.

The emcee, dressed as a clown, stepped onto the stage and shouted at the top of his lungs.

“Yes! This sword and shield, surely a relic of an ancient civilisation, has gone for 30 million gold! Any more? All hail the snake-masked man over there who will take home this lucky piece of armour! Now, on to the next item for sale! Everyone, look at this beautiful jewelled crown! It must have been worn by a king of a defunct kingdom somewhere in the history books….”

Then.

The eyes of the crowd, which had been focused on the slaves, suddenly snapped to attention.

It wasn’t a human being, but it was enough to focus all the attention in the room for a moment.

A black buffalo covered in lean muscle.

It has huge horns, a massive body, and three glaring eyes.

<Infernal Buffalo ‘Murcielago’

Danger Rating: A

Size: 3 metres

Found in: Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, Ridge 2

-A type of cattle that inhabits the Oil Realm in the depths of Hell.

It is said to have nineteen hearts and will not stop charging until they are all stopped.

It was a gigantic beast that inhabited the Enemy and Black Mountains.

But the reason why no one runs away when this monster appears on stage is simple.

This Murcielago was dead.

The emcee shouted.

“Now, this sale is a stolen kill from the knights of the Baskervilles, a precious, Danger Rank A beast, with its hide, meat, bones, entrails, and everything else to spare!”

There were nineteen wounds on the Hell Buffalo’s body.

Apparently, it had only died after its heart was destroyed.

The price of this carcass immediately began to skyrocket.

“One hundred million gold!”

“120 million!”

“140 million!”

“190 million!”

“200 million!”

“250 million!”

The entire auction house erupts in excitement, even though the human slaves are not.

Having sold the carcass of a hell buffalo for a good price, the emcee took the opportunity to lead the auction in earnest.

“Now it’s time for the auction for humans and their ilk!”

With that, humans of all kinds began to walk onto the stage.

A barbarian man with a dead look in his eyes as if he had given up on everything, a kidnapped noblewoman crying and begging to be sent home, a terrified commoner boy who still had no idea where he was, and a fallen noblewoman screaming that she would rather be killed.

“One hundred million!”

“Two hundred million!”

“Two hundred and fifty thousand!”

“Take it and seven thousand more!”

“I got that bitch, no one can touch her!”

“You’re being ridiculous. Get more money.”

The more they cry and scream and despair, the more the madness of the humans surrounding the stage intensifies.

Just then.

The emcee, buoyed by the brisk sales, suddenly looks puzzled.

“…? Huh? Huh? You put this one up for sale, too? Huh? G, really? Oh, okay, I’ll see if I can sell it.”

He stutters, as if he’s having trouble communicating with the men behind the scenes.

He composes himself and continues.

“Now, this next one is a little different, a little more appealing, and still has plenty of room for improvement!”

In other words, even the slave traders aren’t quite in control yet.

After the slave was painstakingly wrapped, the emcee dragged it to the centre of the stage.

Unlike before, this time the slave was locked in a sturdy metal cage.

“Kaaaah!”

A series of guttural screams erupted.

Inside the cage, a barbarian girl with a stern face was rampaging madly.

She must have been about 17 years old.

She had black hair mixed with silver, triangular pointed ears, and a face that was a dark colour, but it looked like it had been smeared with ash and was normally a light brown.

He wore a choker with thorns around his neck, and the animal skins he wore as clothing were little more than rags.

Peeking through the rags, its body was toned and lean, but its face was unrecognisable through the ash, and it was snarling and snapping so fiercely that no one bothered to raise a bid.

“!??? ?? ????. ???? ????. ??? ????? ????”

A language I don’t understand at all.

Moreover, the stench of animal feces that had been wafting across the stage since earlier, and the body odour that seemed to have not been washed in decades, caused the noblewomen to turn away with frowns on their faces.

“…Ah, who buys this?”

It’s enough to make even a clown talking to himself.

Still, he had to sell, so he did his best to make a point.

“Come on, come on, slave traders say they’ve picked this one up from the depths of the jungle! Come on, come on, don’t you think a slave this fierce could use some taming? Use him as a night watchman or a gladiator! This is your chance to prove your slave taming skills! I’ll start the bidding at 5 million! Let’s go!”

….

But no one raises their hand.

Usually there’s someone who calls out the lowest bid, for the sake of the moderator’s dignity and the atmosphere of the auction house, but… this time there wasn’t even that.

“Eight, then let’s lower the minimum bid a bit, 3 million, anyone got 3 million?”

….

“Then you don’t have it either! Two million! I’ll take it at two million! I’ll say it again, you don’t have it either!”

….

“Okay, okay, okay, one million! I’ll take one million with my eyes closed! Take him and boil him for human consumption! I’ll sell him for nothing more than meat!”

….

But in the end, no one raised their hand.

The moderator grunted and waved his hand.

“Forget it. This isn’t selling. I told you, only put up guaranteed items. Get them backstage, and use a windbag next time, I want.”

Soon the slavers were on stage, pulling down the cage that held the barbarian girl.

The girl even managed to bite off the finger of the trader holding the cage, cutting it off.

The atmosphere in the auction hall became chaotic.

The organisers had to control it somehow.

So what did they do?

The emcee knew it was time to bring out the big guns.

“Attention, ladies and gentlemen, jumo~ok, keep your eyes peeled, because I have what I consider to be the best lot of the day right now!”

And then. A man stepped onto the stage.

A boy with handcuffs on his wrists and heavy chains dangling from them.

He looked to be about 15 years old.

Despite the weight of the restraints, the boy’s gait is effortless.

There was a faint murmur of admiration from the audience at his confident and calm demeanour.

As he stands at the centre of the stage, the torchlight from above illuminates his face.

The boy’s appearance was revealed in a glow of light.

And the audience’s jaws dropped in unison.

“…Wow.”

The expressions of all the noblewomen and some of the middle-aged men gathered here had become dazed.

Chapter 36

Slave Auction (2)

◆

The appearance of the slave boy on stage silenced the room for a moment.

Cheeks that hadn’t yet shed their milk, but a chiseled jawline nonetheless.

A prominent nose, full, crimson lips, straight dark eyebrows and long lashes.

And those precious black hairs and red eyes.

Vara’s whole body was tanned to a healthy brown color, but there were white underwear marks here and there, suggesting that her skin was originally flawless and white.

The boy’s good looks shone through, even with the basic makeup applied to the slaves on stage.

Vikir. Vikir van Baskerville.

He was on the stage.

The emcee said.

“Now, what do you think, this is the last item up for auction, and with the quality of the goods, we can expect a great bidding war!”

Alas, there is still silence downstage.

Even the barbarian girl in the cage, who had been rampaging on the far side of the stage after winning the auction, had become mesmerized and quiet since Vikir’s appearance.

Then.

Someone raised a bidding sign.

“Six hundred million!”

The lady in the butterfly mask gasps.

“Six hundred million, no, sixty-five million!”

Then the middle-aged man on the other side of the table jumps to his feet, as if he can’t lose.

“Eight hundred million!”

“What the hell! Aren’t you a man!?”

“What’s a man got to do with 800 million!”

“That’s not it! A man would take her and use her for what!!!”

“He’s going to use her as a gladiator, for crying out loud!”

“What the hell, do you think she can even hold a sword properly!”

“Come on, you two. If you want to fight, go home and fight, and I’ll call it a night.”

“I call a billion!”

“One and a half billion!”

“1.3 billion!”

“1.5 billion!”

A bloody price war has begun. Numerical prices now began to jump by the billion.

Just as the moderator was getting ecstatic, calculating the fees.

“Six billion.”

The amount dropped like a bomb.

Out of the corner of everyone’s eye, I see a fat man munching on his food.

“…, The author.”

“Baron Gambino of the Granary, a rare find.”

“Crazy, that’s one big barrel.”

“I’ve heard he’s been raking in the dough lately, absorbing underground funds.”

The people around you turn their heads with bitter expressions.

Some of the noblewomen, gritting their teeth, tried to scrape together enough money to make a stand, but it was a long shot against Baron Gambino, who was now making a name for himself as the newest rebel in the underworld.

Then.

“…Baron. Wouldn’t that be too much to spend?”

The secretary at Baron Gambino’s side spoke up.

Dressed in a greenish-blond short skirt and one-eyed glasses, she looked quite cold and domineering.

Baron Gambino frowned slightly at the secretary’s point, then coughed.

“Well, a slave that off-white can fetch a much higher price in the Imperial Capital. It’s worth it to buy them and sell them later.”

“Even though he’s an off-white boy, six billion seems a bit excessive. Besides, isn’t it the story of the baron who bought him and then left him to fend for himself that makes reselling him questionable?”

“Hmmm. Hmmm!”

Baron Gambino glanced up, seemingly conscious of the stares around him, and then burst out.

“Shut up, you wench, I gave you something you had no right to have, and now you have the audacity to stand on your master’s head!”

“….”

“I like her, I bought her with my own money…!”

Baron Gambino shouted, and the secretary sighed and shook her head.

Then.

Baron Gambino, who had paid a hefty sum for the item, smirked and brought Vikir to him.

He raised his thick hand and began to cupping Vikir’s ass.

“….”

Vikir stared in disbelief, alternating between Baron Gambino and the hand cupping his ass.

Baron Gambino chuckled in satisfaction at the look on Vikir’s face, a look that said he’d never seen anything like this before.

“Why, it’s new to you. Get used to it, for it will happen often from now on.”

“….”

“Hehehe- don’t worry. To be fair, I’ll let you touch my ass too, later tonight….”

Baron Gambino said, scanning Vikir’s body with a lecherous expression.

The moment.

Vikir raised his hands.

Not realizing he was asking for his handcuffs to be removed, Baron Gambino smirked and reached for the keys.

…Snap, snap, snap!

The handcuffs in front of you are ripped off in the blink of an eye.

Steel cuffs tearing like paper. And the chains.

With the force of his grip, Vikir shatters the restraints on his wrists.

Then, at a loss for words, he held out his palms to the dazed Baron Gambino.

“On your ass.”

There was no time to protest, no time to say anything.

Vikir rolled over the Gambino baron’s fat body with such ease that he soon had his hands on his fleshy ass.

Tsk, tsk, tsk!

There was a terrifying sound, and Baron Gambino began to squeal like a pig.

“Off!”

A gurgling fountain of blood drenched the surroundings.

A chorus of screams erupts from the bystanders as they see a man being torn alive.

Soon, the mercenaries who had been acting as guards begin to rush over.

But.

Thud, thud, thud!

The necks and torsos of the lunging guards separated at once and rolled separately across the floor.

Before he knew it, Vikir had drawn a long, sharp blade that protruded from his wrist.

Whirring, whirring, whirring.

Beelzebub the Magic Sword began to weep as it drew blood.

“Strike, strike! Kill him!”

The nobles called for their personal escorts.

Swords drawn, mercenaries and knights charged, their auras rising.

…Tsutsutsutsuts

Vikir unleashed his aura as well.

The swordsmanship that followed was Baskerville’s Fifth Form.

Five of the lurking ambushers flew out at once, biting into the nape of their foes’ necks.

Thud, thud, thud, thud, thud.

A shower of blood.

Headless torsos crumble to their knees.

Behind them, the knifemen, who had barely escaped death, could only stare in horror.

An aura as red and sticky as blood. Gradient!

The ultimate weapon representing a nation’s national power, a killing machine for the sole purpose of killing.

For every step Vikir took, he made sure to cut the throat of another.

Every step he takes, he kills.

Vikir had only traveled a short distance, only a few dozen paces, but already a shower of blood was falling around him.

There was only one thought on everyone’s minds.

“We don’t stand a chance against the Graduates!”

As soon as the swordsmen saw Vikir’s aura dripping like liquid, they gave up the fight and began to withdraw.

But.

“You fools, there’s no business in Daguri, even if you’re a grader!”

“If you run away now, you’re all going to slavery!”

“Yay, so you’re not going to make any money!”

“Think of your families!”

Here and there, the shouts of nobles and signers turned a few swordsmen on their heels.

By now, the chaos in the auction house had subsided somewhat.

Heavily armed mercenaries, now numbering in the hundreds, surrounded Vikir.

“What the hell is that kid?”

“How is he a grader at his age?”

“Are you human! What are you!”

Everyone is confused, but the enemy is clear.

Countless swords, spears, arrows, and magic surrounded Vikir in layers.

No matter how strong the Gradient was, there was no way it could survive this onslaught.

Even.

“You bastard, drop your sword and surrender this instant, or none of your men will live!”

The clown on the stage was threatening Vikir with a hostage.

The clown was holding a knife and about to stab him in the neck.

The Chihuahua, with its long goatee, was shaking and looking at Vikir.

“….”

Vikir paused and stood.

As he does, the mercenaries around him draw their swords and slowly close in on him.

Just then.

“Your Excellency, I’m fine, please take care of yourself!”

The Chihuahua exclaimed with a determined look.

Soon, he grabbed the clown’s arm and began pulling him toward him.

The clown was more surprised by the Chihuahua’s behavior than by the fact that he was trying to kill himself by stabbing himself in the neck with someone else’s knife.

“You’re crazy, what are you doing!”

“Let go! There is no compromise with injustice in my dictionary! Besides, I’d rather die than get in the way of my superiors!”

“What kind of a line is that for a face like yours! Get off me!”

The clown and the Chihuahua began to tussle, killing each other.

Vikir smiled wryly at the sight.

And then.

…Bam!

With a drop of aura that pierced the clown’s brow, Vikir picked up the falling Chihuahua and dropped all the way down to the stage.

All around him, the air is alive with life.

Countless mercenaries and knights of the local Sedoga armed with swords, spears, arrows, and magic glared at Vikir and the Chihuahua.

“Zee, my lord. No matter how good a fighter you are, this number of people is a bit… overwhelming, especially with all the baggage I’m carrying.”

Chihuahua’s concern was justified.

But Vikir remained nonchalant.

“Don’t worry. When we leave the Baskervilles’ mansion.”

He tore a small slit in the flesh of his thigh and pulled out what he had hidden within.

It was a small whistle shaped like a red tooth.

“I have a hidden card from the Lord, ….”

And then.

Vikir brought the blood-red whistle to his mouth and blew.

Beep-.

A tearing sound echoed high in the air.

Those gathered around were tense, unsure of what Vikir was doing, their eyes fixed on the center of the encirclement.

But.

The real action began on the ceiling of the barracks, where no one was looking.

…Tsk tsk!

Shadows were tearing through the curtain that had been stretched out like the night sky and entering through the cracks.

Countless black blood winds fell from the sky.

And then.

Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding!

Wherever they fell, there was always a shower of blood, and people’s heads were torn off.

“Aaahhh! What are these!”

“There must be over a hundred of them!”

“And they’re powered by graders!”

All one hundred of them are Graduators. Killing machines, their blades coated in a blood-red aura.

They annihilated everyone in front of them in an instant, then went behind Vikir and lined up politely.

Only then did those who were spared by their position in the rear realize the nature of Vikir’s group of one hundred Graders.

“Seriously, they can’t be…”

“No? No. Please, please!”

“Ah, yes, they’re the only ones using that symbol!”

It was the red, tooth-like badge on his chest patch.

A ‘knightage Pit Bull’ of the Baskerville family.

It was the rise of the most ferocious knighthood in not only House Baskerville, but the entire Empire.

To these black-cloaked, silent fighting dogs, Vikir gave a brief order.

Chapter 37

Slave Auction (3)

◆

“The way to take down an underground economy is really quite simple, you just have to get to the heart of the matter between the dots.”

Vikir repeated the words he’d spoken to the Chihuahua.

The vast underground economy of an underdog city, and the big players who control it.

Vikir already knew the place, thanks to his pre-regression knowledge.

But it would be impossible for a single man to take down such a large operation.

So Vikir had planned for this.

“I was wondering if I could borrow ….”

A conversation with Hugo before leaving Baskerville.

I’m pretty sure that’s when Vikir said

“I was wondering if I could borrow the Templars.”

Hugo thought long and hard about it, and then granted permission.

He gave her the right to use one knight for half a day, a piece of House Baskerville’s military power.

“I trust you will do nothing foolish. My son.”

The implications of giving up military power, however limited, were significant.

He recognized Vikir as his son and would treat him accordingly.

Thus, the Pitbull Knights, one of the pillars of Baskerville’s military might, came under Vikir’s control.

For the next six hours, all one hundred of the Graduators, the iron-blooded knights who are known for leaving no survivors behind, will be Vikir’s subjects.

And now, Vikir was using them to sweep away the corruption of Underdog City in one fell swoop.

“Hugo was particularly sensitive to the military. It’s a good thing we got the pit bull back in one piece.”

Given Hugo’s tendency to be extremely wary of local officials having private soldiers, it was expected that he would not give up his knighthood easily.

But Hugo’s trust in Vikir was surprisingly strong, and it made things easier.

Vikir glanced at the group of Pit Bull Knights lined up behind him.

A Zagoro fighter must never show his teeth.

A third-rate fighter believes in his own strength and looks down on his enemies.

A second-class fighting dog reacts too quickly to the enemy’s actions.

A first-class fighting dog has patience and composure, but not the life in his eyes.

And finally, the pinnacle of the fighting dog is as calm as an inanimate object, not reacting at all, no matter how furious or threatening the enemy is.

Woody Virtue

It’s as if they were carved out of a tree.

In that sense, the Pit Bull Knights are a very disciplined group of fighters.

They now stood behind Vikir like chunks of wood, waiting for orders.

Vikir started the engine.

“Bite them all to death.”

A hundred pit bulls bared their teeth.

Vikir shouted at the running dogs.

“Don’t kill the ones that stay down. But if they move, kill them without mercy.”

It was a warning.

Vikir’s words were loud enough for his enemies to hear.

Those who lost the will to fight quickly dropped their weapons, dropped to the ground, and raised their hands and feet upward.

The majority, however, could not.

“Aaaaah!”

“Aaaah help me!”

As she screamed and writhed, her head was mercilessly sliced off.

I could see her fat head rolling around under her fur coat, which was stained red.

The fleeing middle-aged man is disemboweled on the spot.

Men, women, and children alike were dying as they fled or screamed.

…That didn’t mean that those who stayed down were unharmed.

“Ugh, let’s just get down. We’ll jump out when it’s a little quieter.”

Several people lay down on their stomachs on the floor and put their hands and feet up.

It was a sign that they were waiting for handcuffs.

But.

“We don’t carry handcuffs.”

A Pitbull Templar smirked as he stepped in front of them.

Just as they were about to ask what they were going to use to bind their hands and feet.

…Thud! …Thud!

The Pitbull Templar’s sword sliced through their limbs.

Wrists and ankles snapped off.

“Kaaaaaah!”

“Aaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!!!”

They crawled across the floor, showing signs of escape, and then quickly dropped like bugs.

The Pitbull Knights, of course, are completely unperturbed and launch themselves at the other moving prey.

Meanwhile.

Beside Vikir, a dark-haired, middle-aged man stands with a thick cigar in his mouth.

He is an imposing man with an inverted triangle of muscle, a square jaw, sunken cheeks, sunglasses shading his eyes, and scars all over his face.

Count Les Baskervilles, a Boston Terrier, asks Vikir.

“Nephew, are you satisfied?”

“Yes uncle.”

“Hmph, boy. If there’s anything else I can do for you, just say the word.”

He was quite fond of his nephew, Vikir, for no particular reason, just because he liked the way the rice leaves fluttered.

The Boston Terrier figured it couldn’t hurt to have a nephew who was also the favorite of his master, Hugo.

Vikir didn’t feel bad for the Boston Terrier, who was not interested in power, honor, or political battles, but purely in blood and fight.

Just then, the Chihuahua beside him spoke up in a shaky voice.

“Your Excellency. But would you mind if I cut off their wrists and ankles like that, even though they’re nobles?”

“What the hell, they’re about to be executed anyway, and the handcuffs aren’t worth the trouble, just make sure they can’t get away.”

Hearing Vikir’s answer, the Boston Terrier Count laughed with even more satisfaction.

“Hmph, nephew, you must join our Pit Bull Knights someday. This uncle will raise you properly.”

Vikir could only reply with a faint smile.

A minute or so later, the Pit Bull Knights stormed in and the situation was over.

It was literally over.

All the big bads in Underdog City were either dead or captured.

Of course, there were some who were casually absent, but that could easily be traced back to their captors’ ledgers and contact records.

“This… is the greatest thing since sliced bread! It’s so perfect!”

The Chihuahua shivered with excitement as he watched the criminals being led away in the distance.

The war on crime was suddenly declared, and it was over surprisingly quickly.

Now we’ll have to clean up the mess, but that will be a piece of cake.

Even the indigenous families who lost their sons will not be able to say anything about it.

The future of Underdog City was clear, transparent, and bright.

“Congratulations, no one will dare to speak against Vikir now, will they…?”

The Chihuahua jumped for joy.

But Vikir, the one who should have heard it, was long gone.

◆

“I think it was around ….”

Vikir had already returned to the back of the auction house.

The slaughter was still going on in front of the stage across the way.

By this time, Vikir had slipped through the back unnoticed and made it to the warehouse where the auction items were being stored.

The warehouse was piled high with gold and silver treasures.

All paid for in cash by nobles visiting the city.

“…The tax revenue must be good.”

All of this would be added to the city’s treasury, and the Baskervilles’ coffers would be even stronger.

I didn’t like the idea of Hugo being happy, but it didn’t matter now, so I let it go.

Vikir searched the warehouse for a while.

Piles of notes and ledgers.

He decided to keep all of them, as they would be valuable evidence in his future raids.

But there was something else he was really after.

Vikir grabbed a white cloth draped over a corner of the warehouse and pulled it open.

And there it was.

“…?”

What Vikir saw was not what he was looking for, but something completely different.

A cage, and a barbarian girl imprisoned in it.

The same girl who had been rampaging ferociously just moments before, cowering in the corner of the cage.

“…Grunt, grunt.”

A barbarian girl making painful noises.

Upon closer inspection, her entire body shows signs of abuse in addition to malnutrition. It looks like she was whipped outside the cage.

“She must have been corporally punished after biting the traders’ fingers earlier.”

Vikir clicked his tongue for a moment.

Then he reached into his belt and pulled out a potion reserved for the Templars.

He opened the door to the cell and sprinkled the potion over the girl’s body.

Qi Yi Profit…

With a loud crackling sound, the wounds healed and new flesh sprouted.

The groaning girl opened her eyes to see Vikir inside the cage, and angrily hid in a corner.

Vikir stared at the barbarian girl.

A mixture of black and silver hair. Pointed ears. Charcoal-black makeup smeared across her face.

The familiar teeth and claw marks on his forearms and thighs.

“Cerberus?”

A memory comes flooding back.

During his practical exam at the age of eight, Vikir had crossed the safety boundary and entered the waters of the Black Mountain with an enemy and encountered Cerberus, a Danger Class A+ demon.

He remembered that Cerberus’ flanks were covered with arrowhead-shaped scars.

“Hmm. Could it be that the barbarian tribe that hunted Cerberus back then was…?”

It was a reasonable guess.

Meanwhile, the barbarian girl, now that her wounds had healed somewhat, was crouched in the corner of the cage, glaring at Vikir.

Vikir spoke briefly.

It means ‘go.

The barbarian girl’s eyes widened at the words.

Vikir shrugged his shoulders once.

‘I can speak basic barbarian.

He had fought the enemy and the barbarians of the Black Mountains countless times before his return.

The barbarian girl’s eyes widen in horror at Vikir’s command to flee.

Only when Vikir leaves the vial with the remaining potion on the ground and walks out of the cage does the barbarian girl cower and follow him out of the cage.

“….”

She glared at Vikir for a few seconds before ripping open the tent and fleeing.

She took the vial of potion that Vikir had set on the ground.

The barbarian girl said something at the last minute, but she spoke too fast for Vikir to understand.

“Now, let’s find what you really want.”

Vikir turned and went back to his work.

Gold and silver treasures, notes and ledgers, checkbooks, antiques, art….

But there was something else Vikir wanted.

“Here it is.”

With that, Vikir pulled aside the red cloth draped over the innermost corner of the auction room.

There lay a large, horned beast of burden.

<Murcielago, the Infernal Buffalo>.

Danger Rating: A

Size: 3 meters

Found in: Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, Ridge 2

-A type of cattle that inhabits the Oil Realm in the depths of Hell.

It is said to have nineteen hearts and will not stop charging until they all stop.

Bing-bing-bing.

Beelzebub on the wrist was whining that he was hungry.

In the distance, the sound of the Pitbull Knights’ swords and the screams of their enemies were getting closer and closer.

I had better finish my meal and get going.

Chapter 39

Sponsored (2)

◆

One ambitious moonless night.

Vikir visited the dungeons beneath the city hall.

The nearly empty cell was filled with the stench of something decaying.

Prisons are inherently creepy, but it’s even creepier to see them so dark and empty.

The guards had all left work early. Unusually, all of them without a single call.

The prisoners have all been executed, pardoned, or transferred, and the area is now completely empty.

Vikir made his way to one of the deepest cells.

The darkest and most fetid.

Solitary.

The most secluded of the dungeons, with the only securely locked door.

And in this dungeon was the only prisoner left.

He was a secretary to Baron Gambino, a major player in the underground economy.

A woman with greenish-blond hair cut short, dressed in a prisoner’s uniform and wearing heavy handcuffs, she squatted in the corner of the cell.

Vikir pulled up a chair and sat down in front of the bars.

Druk-.

The sound of the iron chair legs scraping against the stone floor echoed loudly in the empty prison.

“Your name is… Sen Rose Cindywendy. Is that right?”

Vikir asked, but she didn’t answer.

Instead, she stared down at the floor with vacant eyes.

“Why did you keep me alive?”

Cindywendy’s question was hollow.

The freak show. And the Pit Bull Knights.

That night, when everything that moved was dying, Cindywendy gritted her teeth and fled.

She could never die like this.

Even if she didn’t die, her wrists and ankles would be cut off.

She had a job to do, and she could never die in a place like this and be a wastrel because of it.

Who among the dying was not, or at least Cindywendy thought she was, far more desperate and needy than the others.

But the teeth of the fighting dog before her were cold.

One of the Pit Bull Templars stepped in front of her, and it was a death sentence.

She gritted her teeth as the jagged blade sank into her throat.

But.

…Earth!

The sound the knife made as it plunged into his throat was a bit unexpected.

That’s because the Pitbull Templar’s blade didn’t manage to pierce her throat.

Vikir. The new deputy magistrate.

He holds up a bundle of chains to block the Pit Bull Templar’s blade.

The Pitbull Templar looked very surprised that Vikir had managed to block his blade, but his next words were brief.

“This woman is an exception. Capture her alive without hurting a single finger.”

This is how Xin Diwendi has been imprisoned in the dungeon ever since.

Vikir stared at her in silence for a while.

Finally, he asked.

“If you answer my questions truthfully, I will release you from here.”

…!

That made Xin Diwendi’s ears perk up.

But soon, Xin Diwendi shook her head and muttered to herself.

“I’ve already lost the will to escape from the time I was imprisoned here, and I have no reason to do so now.”

Like it or not, Vikir’s questions had already begun.

“Are you the reason Baron Gambino, who was nothing more than an insignificant sodomite, has been able to increase his power so dramatically in recent years?”

“….”

“I’ve researched you, and you have a knack for making money, and if that talent had blossomed in a place other than the underworld, you would have made a fine merchant or financier.”

Xin Diwendi laughed bloodily.

It was a mocking laugh that seemed to say, “What good is all that now?”

Vikir looked into her eyes and held them still.

Then he spoke in a pleasant voice.

“I assure you.”

“…?”

“Answer my question and I’ll let you out of here, but-”

Vikir trailed off and tilted his head toward the bars, locking eyes with Cindywendy.

Searing red light pierced her green retinas.

“If you do not answer, you will regret this day.”

There was a strange, unknown power in the voice that made the listener feel another kind of intimidation besides fear.

Xin Diwendi opened her mouth to speak, not even knowing what she was feeling.

“If it’s something I can answer, I’ll answer it.”

“Good.”

Vikir asked, bluntly.

“How does it look to you?”

“What do you mean?”

“Do you think I’m doing law enforcement wrong?”

Xin Diwendi replied in a nonchalant tone.

“Who cares about the opinion of a lowly criminal bitch like me?”

“I’m asking an insignificant criminal bitch like you.”

“Then I’m going to go out on a limb and say it: I think you’re doing it wrong.”

At that, Vikir nodded.

“Why?”

“Virtue is the key virtue of a ruler in all theories of monarchy. A strong rule of law may work to some extent in the beginning, but in the long run, well…”

“Virtue, what is it?”

“It’s not getting in a cart when you’re tired, not putting a cover on a cart when you’re hot, and not having armed soldiers in procession. It is his virtue that when a ruler dies, all the citizens shed tears, even the children refrain from singing, and even the triggers do not hum.”

“Is it a great blemish that I am not virtuous?”

“If it is a great blemish, it is a great blemish, for you will not live long because of it. You may have established your majesty by beating up on cheap scoundrels with the Thrash Furun Law, but in the long run, you will kill and injure many commoners, which will build up resentment and anger.”

“Do you think I should fear the resentment and anger of the common people?”

“The commoners won’t like it, but neither will the Baskervilles, and although it’s an underdog city, the citizens will be more afraid of you, the deputy, than they are of the Baskervilles.”

“Hmm. That’s true.”

“The same will be true when your superior arrives, or when your successor does, and the reason you changed the law is to assert your authority and hasten your accomplishments, which will have many native factions gnashing their teeth. There are plenty of underworlders in other cities, too, and I don’t think you’ll have long to live, considering their sentiments.”

“So what do you think I should do?”

“You are as precarious as dew right now. If you wish to live to see another day, you must resign as Deputy Magistrate, return all your powers to House Baskerville, return the balls here to the Gazoo and the Imperial House, and go to a place befitting your age, such as Yazi in Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, or an academy in the center of the empire, and look forward to the future.”

“And?”

“Keep yourself as unnoticed as possible, conceal your strength and cultivate your learning, and suggest to your superiors that you seek out and promote undiscovered talent, honor the elderly, care for orphans, praise the unmerited, and honor the virtuous.”

“And what will I gain by doing so?”

“Your mind will be at ease, for one thing, and by that time the patriarch of House Baskerville will have taken all the blame you deserve; and even if he takes away your immediate credit, you are only fifteen years old anyway. Isn’t that old enough to have a reputation that has spread to the ecliptic, even if it’s only a sham?”

At Xin Di Wendi’s long-winded advice, Vikir smiled a rare smile.

Her advice was very much in line with Vikir’s own plans for the future.

“Good.”

Vikir nodded.

At the same time.

…Clang!

The iron gate swung open.

Vikir ripped the padlock off with the force of his grip, then removed all of Cindywendy’s restraints.

“As promised, you are now free.”

“….”

Xin Di Wendi raised her head and stared at the iron gate in front of her.

Then she turned to look at Vikir.

“Are you really releasing me?”

“I am. I keep my word.”

“You’ll regret it, won’t you?”

A hint of life returned to Xin Diwendi’s eyes.

Seeing it, Vikir smiled wryly.

“I hope so.”

“…?”

Cindywendy tilted her head.

Finally, Vikir spoke up.

“You said something nice to me, so I’ll say something nice to you.”

Cindywendy turns to leave the cell, but stops short.

With her back to him, Vikir spoke.

“There were seven famous native families in Underdog City. The Montblancs, the Pierres, the Louisvilles, the Channels, the Ferragamos, the Hermèses, and the Pradas.”

“….”

“But a few years ago, their number was eight, not seven.”

At that, Vikir didn’t miss the slight shiver that ran down Xin Diwendi’s spine.

“Originally, there was an eighth family called the Messinadna family, the wealthiest of the merchant families.”

“….”

“But they were destroyed overnight, all of their members tragically killed. Do you know why?”

“….”

“They had stolen the Baskervilles’ sword book, and their eight-year-old son had one day claimed to have learned to be a good swordsman.”

“….”

“The patriarch of the Messinadnaro family threw a big party for his son’s birthday and asked him to demonstrate his newfound sword skills.”

“…That.”

Cindywendy held up a hand to interrupt Vikir.

But Vikir was undaunted, and continued.

“With everyone gathered, my son demonstrated his swordsmanship, but everyone there was in for a big surprise, for what he demonstrated was the Baskerville style of swordsmanship, which is only shared in secret among the Baskervilles.”

“…That, stop.”

“The Baskervilles are terribly protective of their family’s swordsmanship. Believing that a top-secret military secret had been revealed, the Baskerville patriarch unleashed the hounds, and from that day forward, House Messinadnaro would disappear from the face of the earth.”

“Stop it, you bastard!”

Cindywendy shouted sharply.

But Vikir didn’t stop.

“But as it turns out, House Messinadnaro was not guilty. It was the children of the other seven houses who lured their son with the promise of a good sword book, and they lured a young boy from Baskerville to take it from them and teach it to the child of House Messinadnaro, and the child demonstrated it in front of a group of adults to prove that it was good. It was by design.”

“But there was one survivor of the Messinadnaro family, all of whom were said to have been wiped out, a little girl of one year old Turl, and the Seven Wretches managed to sneak her out of that massacre.”

“…Ewww. Ewww!”

Xin Di Wendi staggered, then leaned back against the wall.

Her eyes were red and bloodshot.

Vikir finished.

“That girl had to be subjected to all sorts of cruel, low, and shameful tortures just because she was bright and fair, and the details of those tortures… I can’t even begin to tell you.”

“I don’t want to hear any more. Goodbye.”

A bloody tear trickled from one of Xin Diwendi’s eyes.

She took her back away from the wall and staggered toward the outside.

Then.

“I told you, if you don’t listen, you’ll regret this day for the rest of your life.”

Vikir stood in place, unmoving, and continued.

“There’s a sequel to this story.”

“…?”

Xin Di Wendi stopped in her tracks.

Vikir shrugged once.

“And quite a bit of time has passed, and a new deputy magistrate has come to the city.”

“….”

“He brought out all the old enemies within the city and punished them.”

“….”

“And the trigger for the event was the seven rascals who drove House Messinadnaro to ruin.”

Cindywendy turned her head to look at Vikir.

Vikir looked him straight in the eye and spoke.

“The new deputy tortured those seven brats to death.”

“….”

“It was such horrible torture that a torturer who had been working at the castle for thirty years vomited up what he had just eaten.”

“….”

“And as they lay dying, the seven wretches confessed all the sins they had committed, including those against House Messinadnaro. They admitted and apologized for all their sins.”

Then Cindywendy cried out sharply.

“Apologize! How dare they apologize to anyone!”

“To …the sole survivor of House Messinadnaro. To that girl. To the girl who currently goes by the pseudonym ‘Sen Rose Cindywendy’ and whose real name is ‘Messinadnaro Sen Cindywendy’.”

Hearing this, Cindywendy staggered back with a dazed look on her face.

“Ew!”

She vomited out the contents of her stomach.

Her vision spun.

The darkness of the dungeon was pitch black.

The rotten stench that had been hovering in the cell from earlier seemed to be getting stronger and stronger.

Xin Diwendi braced herself against the wall with one hand and held her forehead with the other.

She spat on the floor and asked.

“How can I believe your words?”

“….”

“How am I supposed to believe you when you say you caught them, tortured them, got to the bottom of it, and got an apology!”

Cindywendy screamed.

There was no answer from Vikir.

Only.

…Snarl!

Vikir drew fire from the rod in his hand and lit a torch.

Suddenly, the dungeon cell was brightly lit.

And then.

“…!”

Xin Diwendi’s eyes widened to tears.

Seven headless corpses were kneeling in the corner of the room.

Their fingers were all worn out, and the blood that flowed from them had stained the floor, walls, and even the ceiling.

The entire room was stained red with blood.

Upon closer inspection, the red color of the floor, ceiling, and walls had been covered over and over again with countless letters.

-Please forgive me for my mistake, I deserve to die, I beg you not to touch me as much as my family…

-Meshinadnaro, we are the ones who destroyed the gate, please forgive us for our sins…

-Sincerely apologize to ThindiwendiWe are the ones who have sinned against leather…

-Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong…

-Save me, save me, save me, save me, save me…

-I don’t want to dieI don’t want to die…

-I’m scaredI’m scaredI’m scared…

Corpses that smell rotten.

And apologies scrawled across the floor, all ten fingers worn down from when they were alive.

The blood that made up the apology stained the entire room red.

“….”

Xin Diwendi stood in the center of the red room, looking at Vikir with a puzzled expression.

Then Vikir walked in front of her.

“But the vengeance of House Messinadnaro is far from over.”

“….”

“For there is still one family left.”

Vikir’s meaning was clear.

That meant their greatest enemy, House Baskerville, remained.

Vikir said.

“Blame the Baskervilles. You deserve it.”

“….”

“And apart from that, I speak for all Baskervilles.”

Vikir’s back bent slowly in front of Cindywendy.

“I’m sorry.”

And at the same time.

Dip-dip-dip-dip-dip.

Tears began to fall from Cindywendy’s eyes and land on the stone floor.

“….”

“….”

The two stared at each other for a while, unmoving.

Then Cindywendy spoke.

“Since you are also a Baskerville,… why are you helping me?”

Vikir made no reply.

And the sharp-eyed Cindywendy understood the meaning of his silence.

The dislike and hatred of Baskerville is within and without, but it is the same.

In that way, Vikir and Cindywendy understood each other well.

And then.

Cindywendy walked out of the prison.

She turned to Vikir, who was still inside, and said in a voice that was uncharacteristically calm.

“No matter what you do in life, I’ll make sure you never run out of money.”

Vikir had a new sponsor.

Chapter 40

Morgue’s United Front (1)

◆

The morning dawned.

Last night. Vikir had slept in the pavilion across the street from the city magistrate’s office after his night shift.

Knowing that, the Chihuahua had been there early in the morning.

“Hey, sleepy assistant magistrate. The sun is already up, it’s time for you to go to work…uhhhhhhhh!?”

After knocking on the door, the Chihuahua didn’t get to finish his morning greeting before letting out a grotesque scream.

There was blood everywhere.

Blood, blood, blood, soaking down the white bedspread and staining the marble tiles on the floor in a grid-like pattern.

The walls, the ceiling, the bed, all drenched in blood.

“Ah. Good morning, sir.”

Vikir gets up from the bed with too much nonchalance.

Judging by his sleepy expression, he really was asleep just a moment ago.

And on the bed beneath him lies a corpse, head and torso separated.

A dagger is clutched in the hand of a black-cloaked man, clearly an assassin.

Vikir looked at the assassin’s body on the floor.

“Hmm? I don’t remember him, he must have killed me in my sleep.”

“Zee, is that true?”

“Of course not. It’s a lighthearted joke.”

Vikir tried to make a joke of his own, thinking, “Wouldn’t a 15-year-old be this playful?” but the Chihuahua didn’t seem to realize it was a joke in the first place.

“So, Your Excellency…, what kind of childhood did you have back home?”

“Was it not much fun?”

“No, it wasn’t a matter of fun….”

The Chihuahua seemed in many ways at a loss for words.

Vikir shook his head in disbelief.

“I’ve been getting a lot of these flies lately.”

Two poisoned arrows, four poisoned glasses, six street burying attacks, stabbings, sulfuric acid spraying, sniping, arson, carriage ramming, etc…..

All in the last three days.

This was the first assassin to enter his bedroom, but even he was no match for Vikir.

Every warrior who had lived through the Age of Destruction had mastered the art of sensing the killing around them in their sleep, and Vikir was no different.

“Hmph. I guess I should look on the bright side. It means I’m getting noticed, right?”

“You’ve got some nerve, man.”

“You’re disrespectful to your superiors, sir.”

I retorted nonchalantly and turned to put on my robe.

The Chihuahua stuck out its tongue as Vikir nonchalantly followed her out of the bedroom.

“Looking at you, it’s hard to believe you’re really 15 years old.”

“Where’s the blood in that?”

“Even if it is Baskerville blood… I mean, weren’t the rest of the Baskervilles like this in the first place, and the previous Archon was….”

The Chihuahua continued to babble, but Vikir was already tuning out his words.

Instead, his mind was on the payoff from his last illegal auction house heist.

<Binge Fly ‘Beelzebub’>/ Awl

-Slot 1: Burn – Cerberus (A+)

-Slot 2: Choke – Infernal Buffalo (A)

-Slot 3: Bleed – Hellhound (B+)

Magic Sword Beelzebub.

This strange blade, which drains and absorbs the abilities of those it kills, was sealed with the power of Murcielago the Infernal Buffalo, a beast you met at the auction house some time ago.

The troll’s C+-ranked danger ability, Super Rapid Regeneration, was gone, replaced by the infernal buffalo’s Tight Throat Breath.

While “Super Fast Regeneration” is an ability to quickly heal an injured body, “Tough Breath” is much more versatile, as it makes the body so tough and hard that it cannot be injured in the first place.

In the first place, the Infernal Buffalo was a high-level beast that couldn’t even be compared to a troll, so it was no wonder its effects were superior.

‘I didn’t know there was a Class A demonic corpse in the auction house, I’m lucky.’

After consuming it, he was able to easily defeat the assassin who came yesterday.

The assassin who had infiltrated the palace last night was a Gradual.

Even though he was only a low ranked Gradual, I remembered that he produced an aura that was as sticky as liquid.

It was an unexpected attack, and the dagger slightly pierced my chest.

But thanks to a synergistic combination of the protection of the River Styx and the hardiness of the Infernal Buffalo, Vikir’s body was left with only a faint scar.

The assassin himself would not have known.

“Mu, whose body is so hard…!?”

Little did he know that this would be his last words.

“I’m going to find out who’s behind these assassins and put them out of business.”

“That makes sense.”

In fact, though he hadn’t told the Chihuahua, Vikir was thinking of resigning from his position as deputy magistrate after this job was done.

Just like Cindywendy had told him not long ago.

Just then.

Something happened to help Vikir’s plans.

The call came from Baskerville itself.

A huge black carriage stood in front of the city hall.

A luxury carriage emblazoned with the Baskervilles’ toothy logo.

Visiting the town hall early in the morning was a man Vicky knew well.

Deacon John Barrymore, who had come to see Vikir personally.

“Master. Long time no see.”

“I see, Deacon. You look better.”

Deacon Barrymore beamed at Vikir’s response.

“Look at that. Didn’t I tell you when you left the main house that you would do well?”

The rumors of the outside world had reached the main house.

They were all about the underdog city’s new deputy magistrate.

“Lucky in many ways. The timing was right.”

But the rumor-monger himself remains uncharacteristically modest.

Deacon Barrymore then revealed the reason for his visit.

“My lord is looking for you. Presumably, he wants an accurate report on this incident.”

“If it was a report, I would have already submitted it in writing.”

“Haha, is that the same as having your son come and tell you in person?”

After speaking, Barrymore stroked his mustache and narrowed his eyes.

“You’re so excited. I’ve never seen you smile like that before.”

◆

Hugo Le Baskerville.

He was still sitting at his patriarch’s desk, his face expressionless.

But Vikir could sense an alien aura emanating from him.

It was.

“…Well done, son.”

It was uncharacteristically warm.

Hugo set today’s morning paper down on his desk.

<Underdog City’s citizens’ favorite person is Vikir, number one>.

<Vikir, the #1 most trusted person by merchants in Underdog City>.

<Vikir is the #1 favorite of the peasants of Underdog City.

<Vikir is the #1 person that children in Underdog City admire the most>.

<Vikir is the #1 favorite of intellectuals in the underdog city>.

<Underdog City’s assassins most want to kill, Vikir>.

.

.

The results of the popularity poll of the citizens were on the front page of the newspaper.

“You’ve done a great job.”

“You did what you had to do.”

“There are a lot of dumbasses out there who can’t do what they’re supposed to do.”

Hugo looked at Vikir, a faint smile tugging at the corners of his mouth.

“Illegal slave trading is a felony punishable by death for both buyer and seller. Your actions have been commended by the Imperial Court.”

“I am honored.”

“This is your chance to dispel the myth that Baskervilles are only good with a sword and bad with their heads. You’ve done a great job.”

Vikir’s special law, his performance in proclaiming it, and his vigorous enforcement of the law set a precedent for all the cities under the Baskervilles’ control, and even the imperial family.

Hugo’s unorthodox appointment was rewarded by Vikir’s unorthodox performance.

One of the Baskervilles’ customs is to be sure of reward and punishment.

If you do well, you get rewarded; if you don’t, you get punished.

Vikir had done an outstanding job and should be rewarded accordingly.

And today, Hugo had summoned Vikir to the main house to discuss the reward.

“Admission to the Academy.”

The Colosseo, the Imperial Academy, the place where every elite in the world dreamed of entering.

Hearing that, Vikir asked.

“Isn’t it customary to enter the academy at the age of 20?”

“If you’re good enough, there’s no age limit. You can be an early adopter or a late adopter, as long as you fulfill the following conditions: no more than 25 years old when you enter and no more than 30 years old when you graduate.”

“…I will live up to your expectations.”

Vikir interjected with a short testimonial.

Hmm?

Hugo, who normally would have ended the conversation at this point, showed a rare willingness to continue.

“I’m sending a few people, including you, to the Academy, but I haven’t gotten around to organizing the entries yet.”

“…?”

“Do you have any close brothers who would like to go with you?”

The question was completely unexpected. Didn’t it sound like something a father would ask his son?

“Uh-oh. You’re a father.”

But then Vikir remembered something he had forgotten himself.

He is Hugo’s son, after all.

He hadn’t been treated like a son for so long that he had forgotten.

Vikir hesitated a moment, then spoke.

“I’m best friends with the triplets, Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.”

What’s the big deal about being best friends, if you want them around, you’re best friends.

“…Is that so?”

Hugo’s eyes widened a little in surprise, but then he nodded in understanding.

“I’ll keep it in mind.”

That was the end of the conversation about the academy.

Vikir had just finished his chaplaincy and was about to leave.

“Oh, by the way. Son, stay a minute.”

“…?”

Vikir stopped in his tracks and turned around, and Hugo rose briefly from his seat.

Then he spoke in a low voice.

“I’ve been looking over the laws of your underdog city.”

“They are … immature.”

“You’ve made quite a few changes to the agricultural laws. You’ve done a very efficient job.”

“That’s very flattering.”

Vikir had once reorganized the laws governing the large farms on the outskirts of Underdog City, in the area where Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain met in the lower reaches and wide open plains.

In addition to the ruby mines, there are many fields of sugar cane, tobacco, cotton, and other crops.

They were mainly worked by savage captives.

Is that why? The savages who occasionally raided across the border often targeted farms on the outskirts of Underdog City.

Hugo said.

“Why don’t you take a quick tour of the estate before you enter the Academy? See if the laws you’ve established are being followed. It would be good experience.”

“As you wish.”

Vikir obeyed, still unwilling to argue.

Then.

Hugo, who had been watching the scene with satisfaction, suddenly asked.

“By the way, are you going alone?”

“…?”

Vikir scratched his head.

So he’s going to go on a territorial tour by himself?

When Vikir looked at Hugo with a puzzled expression, he settled back into his chair and spoke in a relaxed voice.

“This is a joint operation.”

At Hugo’s words, Vikir remained silent. It was an indication that he needed a little more explanation.

Understanding that, Hugo got down to business.

“Do you remember the operation you organized when you were eight years old? Why, the ruby mine.”

“…Of course. I seem to recall that it involved leasing the Ruby Mines area to the Morgue and driving the barbarians towards it, keeping the two factions apart untouched.”

Aka the carnage map.

The idea was that if they wanted to expand their borders, they’d have to deal with the barbarians anyway, so they might as well use the Morgue to get rid of them.

Hugo’s mouth curled into a wry smile.

“The plan worked.”

“And by worked, you mean…?”

“The Morgue made the first offer. Very low-key.”

Hugo hadn’t looked this happy in a long time.

He turned to Vikir.

“They’re talking about a joint war of attrition.”

Chapter 43

The Fiancée (1)

◆

A Morgue supernova.

The only daughter of Raspane Morgue, the patriarch of the house.

Bloodline for bloodline, talent for talent, personality for personality, looks for looks.

No one can doubt that she will be the future head of Morgue’s household.

‘And yet a child of fifteen.’

Vikir lifted his head and looked beyond the barrier of fire and the dead pool of skewers.

Camus Morgue. She stood in an arrogant pose, looking down.

Her three sisters, sprawled out on the floor, tremble at the sight of her.

“Oh, it’s a camel, sisters…”

“Ooohhh, they’re just trying to ward off intruders…”

“They started the fight!”

Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis are a year older than Camus.

But they were crushed by the overwhelming force of Camus’s strength, unable to catch their breath.

It was an unusual sight for the Morgue, a martial arts family where the hierarchy between siblings is strictly based on age and achievement.

And then. Camus smiled seductively.

“Camus, are you talking to me, sisters?”

“Hic! Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!”

“Get out of the way. If you don’t want to be like that.”

The camel stretches out a finger in annoyance.

There, impaled on iron skewers, burned corpses lined the border.

It became clear who had created this murderous landscape.

“Gah!”

The three sisters fled, shaken by the words of their one-year-old brother.

An eerie silence falls over the battlefield as they disappear.

“….”

“….”

“….”

Even the Baskervilles’ triplets, who had just bared their teeth, cowered before the camel.

Then the camo reined in his horse and rode toward the Baskervilles.

She stopped exactly in front of Vikir, locked eyes with him, and opened her mouth.

“Welcome, partner.”

She was referring, of course, to the joint operation against the demons and barbarians that was about to unfold.

◆

After seven years, Morgue’s straight face had changed quite a bit.

The freckles on his face are gone, and his wisdom teeth are gone.

Her cheeks were still plump from lack of milk, but she was already showing signs of what she would grow into and how beautiful she would be.

Vikir recalled her appearance from a distance a few times before her regression.

“She must have been about thirty, and she was pretty.”

‘Dazzling’ could not have been a more apt description of her beauty, a beauty that even Vikir, who had never cared much for a woman’s appearance, admired.

With all the love letters and marriage proposals coming in from Camus, Morgue would have enough firewood for the winter.

And the Camoos themselves enjoyed the situation.

She had all the ladies by the skirts and was involved in scandals here and there.

It was a strategic move, of course.

While she despised the men who clung to her beauty, she played with their minds, fomenting rivalries and conflicts between the houses, and absorbing all the byproducts into the Morgue’s service.

In a highly political move, she refused to give her heart or body to any man until the end, which made all men crave her love all the more.

She ruled over countless captive men.

She greatly multiplied Morgue and revolutionized the war against the demons.

…But.

This was before the regression.

In this life, the Camouflage is somehow less scandalous.

She is surprisingly quiet, considering that by the time she turned 15, she was already managing fisheries for the imperial family, as well as the other powerful men of the other six families.

Rumor has it that she is not seeing a single man, despite her age.

“I don’t understand.”

Vikir reined in his horse with a bit of puzzlement.

Beside him, Camus reined in his horse, following closely behind.

“So this is not how things are in Baskerville, …. The damage done by the barbarian tribes is… so we’ve sorted them out, and in Morgue, we’ve decided to forge an alliance with Baskerville against them….”

He rambled on and on.

Vikir didn’t say much, other than a few dry chuckles.

Camus turned to Vikir and asked.

“Apparently, the Baskervilles don’t know much about the enemy and the barbarians of the Black Mountains, do they?”

“Of course not. They fight them all the time, and they should know better than you.”

“Then why did you send only your own men, all of whom are young and raggedy hounds?”

Camouflage had finally realized the quality of Baskerville’s envoys.

Vikir was about to reply that they were Moors, but then he shut his mouth.

It had already been agreed with Morgue that Baskerville’s true ‘home’ lurked in the mountains on the other side.

“What do you ask when you know?”

The camo chuckled.

“I was just wondering if you knew about it.”

“Of course I know, it’s a family affair, and I’m in charge of the mission here.”

“It could have been a scarecrow used as a discard pawn within the House, but I get it now.”

Camus urged his horse forward, toward Vikir.

He looked back at Vikir and smiled.

“That you are quite trusted within the clan.”

The camo continued with his questions.

“Do you know which of the barbarian tribes is the most troublesome?”

Of course I don’t. It was one of Vikir’s primary duties to search out and destroy the enemy and the Black Mountains before returning home.

“From Morgue’s perspective, it would be the Ballak, a warrior tribe, and the Rokoko, a shaman tribe.”

The Ballak are the most common warrior tribe in the Borderlands, and while their numbers are small, each member of the tribe is a powerful warrior, making them a headache for Baskerville.

“Their archery is far more powerful than that of the Empire, and its principles are not well understood.”

“Hmm. That’s right, they’re a mysterious people.”

Camus nodded, then looked back at Vikir, his eyes shining.

“You’re very knowledgeable about the ecology of savage tribes. Eight points.”

“Huh.”

“On a scale of one hundred, you’re flunking.”

Camus stuck out his tongue, and Vikir frowned slightly.

“I answered well, so why is your score like that?”

“Because you answered well.”

“…?”

When Vikir still looked puzzled, the camel grinned, a wry smile curving the corners of his mouth.

“What’s a man to do with being smart?”

“…?”

“I don’t like smart men, Zagoro males are supposed to be dumb.”

Apparently, the mindset that had gripped and shaken so many men before the regression wasn’t going anywhere.

Vikir spurred his horse faster, as if he didn’t deserve an answer.

But the camouflage followed him, giving him a long list of ratings.

“Horsemanship, six. Maybe it’s because you’re shorter than me, but you’re riding a horse that’s too big for you.”

“….”

“Fashion 4. Your clothes are too drab.”

“….”

“No answer? 1 point for manners.”

“….”

“Well, your face is a 99. You’ve grown up nicely. But I’m deducting one point for not managing your facial expressions.”

My ears began to burn from listening.

Vikir cut him off.

“Stop giving me stupid grades.”

“Why is it useless?”

“And where is it useful?”

“Of course it’s for our future, isn’t it?”

Our future?

At Vikir’s incredulous look, Camus shrugged and puffed out his chest.

“You’re my future husband, so I’m going to weigh in.”

“….”

“If I’m flirting with you, then you should evaluate me too, right?”

“….”

“No, I’d rather be judged, because I need to know what you think of me.”

Vikir asked in disbelief.

“Why do you think I’m your husband?”

“Why? You passed your uncle’s test the other day.”

As Vikir thought about what he was saying, he remembered a time when he had competed against Morgue’s deputy, Adolf.

At the time, Adolf the Mad had a jar of water on his head, and Vikir had broken his sword at the end of the duel and used the shards to break the jar, passing Adolf’s test.

‘…But that was already seven years ago.’

But now he was saying it as if it had happened yesterday.

Camus shuddered and said

“How could my uncle judge my husbandliness by such a crude test! He made that promise in front of everyone, and now I’m a married woman, but what can I do? A promise is a solemn law! I have to obey it, even if I don’t want to. I’ll obey it, I’ll obey it, I’ll obey it…!”

No one said anything, but he was burning hot.

Vikir watched and thought.

“What an accomplished fire mage.”

If he had mastered fire magic to the extreme, would he be able to spontaneously combust like that?

Vikir was mildly curious.

Anyway, that’s that and this is this.

It would do no good to go against the wishes of the woman who was to become the head of Morgue’s household, so Vikir was considerate of Camus.

“Forget what happened that day. I’ll pretend it never happened.”

For a moment, the camel stiffened.

Vikir watched and thought.

“A paralyzing spell? That’s amazing for a moment. But why did he cast it on himself?”

Sometimes wizards could do things you couldn’t understand.

I didn’t really care, but diplomacy dictates that I should at least ask what’s going on.

Vikir had just opened his mouth to say.

“Hey, how do you make something that wasn’t there, make something that was!”

Camus suddenly screeched.

For the first time since his regression, Vikir panicked.

He had just opened his mouth to say something.

“I know because I’m a genius and I never forget what I’ve seen!”

With the camo’s shout, something flew into Vikir’s face.

A shredded piece of cloth. It was a blood-red robe, the size of an eight-year-old’s.

Boldly emblazoned with the Baskervilles’ sigil, it was the cloak Vikir had once used to cover the naked camo.

Seven years old, the cloak still smelled faintly of that day’s sweat.

Holding it in his hand, Vikir scowled at the camel as it moved away.

“…You’re giving it away without washing it.”

Chapter 46

The Husband Hunt (1)

◆

“So this is what we’re supposed to do together?”

Vikir looked down, frowning.

In front of him, the camel cupped his chin in his hands and grinned broadly.

In front of him now was a steaming pile of bread, potatoes, boiled meat, and vegetables.

“You need to eat to stay strong. Here, eat.”

Vikir pressed a hand to his forehead as the camouflage man practically shoved food at him.

They had been in the fort for over ten days now.

In that time, the camo had gotten over the grief of his brother’s death.

But the way he’d gotten over it was causing Vikir quite a headache, … because he’d been coming to the door of his quarters every day, demanding to eat with him.

Six times a day!

“…What kind of meals do you eat six times a day?”

“It’s healthy to eat small and often.”

“I tend to binge eat one meal a day. Maybe I should skip the next meal.”

“Uh-huh. Don’t you know that starvation leads to loss of combat power? It’s against military law.”

“Then you’re not really eating.”

At Vikir’s point, the camo frowned and averted his gaze.

He shoves a bit of salad into his mouth and grunts.

“I get full just watching you eat.”

“….”

Vikir chewed her meat and frowned.

He couldn’t figure out why a 15-year-old girl from another family he hadn’t seen in seven years was being so hard on him.

“Is she trying to arrange a marriage?”

Before his regression, Camus had discussed strategic marriage with a number of prospects, but none of them had actually gotten married.

It would be troubling if he had chosen himself as a candidate for an arranged marriage.

“I’m leaving Baskerville.”

If you leave, I will destroy you.

What has been your reward for doing all the dirty work in the house?

You must repay me for all the foul and disgusting sensations of that moment when you stood on the gallows waiting for Guillotine.

So it’s better not to get involved with Morgue’s women.

The last thing I need is a scandal or a love triangle later on.

This was true not only of Camus, but of any woman in the world.

Unaware of Vikir’s thoughts, the camel still looks innocent and asks.

“Is there poop in the meat?”

“…?”

“You look like you chewed shit.”

Hearing the camel’s words, Vikir blinked a few times with a nonchalant expression before picking up his fork and eating again.

All the while, she never looked up.

Meanwhile.

Vikir’s cold demeanor was a breath of fresh air for Camus.

Usually, when she asks to join her for a meal, everyone is happy to oblige, men and women, young and old.

Especially men outside the clan, whose faces were already lit up with anticipation before they even sat down to eat.

It was only natural.

Camus was young, brilliant, beautiful, and a future ruler.

But Vikir’s 15 years of common sense and experience had been thoroughly discredited.

“I think we should eat separately from now on.”

“What? Why?”

“It’s uncomfortable.”

Vikir said, slamming his fork down.

At that, Camus nodded as if he could agree.

He was right, the cafeteria where Vikir ate was almost exclusively filled with women.

Women receiving their meals, women serving them. Hardly a man in sight.

Camus chuckled.

“Alas, what can I say. Morgue is a matriarchal society, so most of the fighters are women, and the men do most of the cooking in the kitchen back there.”

It’s not like the Baskervilles, an extreme macho society.

Just as males have a slight advantage when it comes to swordsmanship, females have a slight advantage when it comes to magic, so naturally Morgue’s army is made up mostly of women.

Instead, the men are in charge of supply in the rear, a job that is actually just as important as combat.

“My uncle, who is in charge of supply, is currently ill with chest pains, so we don’t have many supplies. Eat up, though.”

Camus ignored Vikir’s offer to eat separately.

Instead, he scooped some boiled potatoes onto Vikir’s plate and slyly changed the subject.

“You don’t have this in your house, do you?”

The potatoes were the object of Camus’s shrug.

It was a super potato that had been modified by Morgue’s plant-based magic, making it far more nutritious and faster to absorb than a normal potato.

The downside was that they were so nutritious that they lacked flavor.

Camus chewed on the fluffy potato and said.

“The only flaw in the nutritional improvement is the lack of taste, but it’s still better than the haggis you eat back home, right?”

Vikir looked away from the potato and picked up his fork.

Apparently, it’s hard to shoo away a camel that’s been looming over you for a while.

This was Morgue’s territory, and she was in charge.

Vikir decided to go along with the camel’s change of subject for now.

“It’s not bad.”

“…?”

Camus repeated.

Vikir picked up Morgue’s potatoes with a serious look on her face.

“They’re not bad. It’s just that you guys cook them badly.”

“Eh? I’m sorry, but the cook in this fortress used to be a chef in the Imperial City, and I have a picky palate, so he’s specially brought in. If it’s cooked by him and it doesn’t taste good, it’s not there.”

Vikir shook his head at that.

“Well, with the … supply disruption, we’ll have to eat this for a while anyway.”

Vikir picked up the potatoes, stood up, and headed to the kitchen.

Using a knife, Vikir cut the potatoes into small pieces and lightly rolled them in salt and vinegar.

Then, she added the dried leaves of the mentrake and the juice of the sabik tree to the pot with the potatoes and started steaming.

The chef in the kitchen saw Vikir and came over in surprise.

“Hey, what are you doing….”

But the chef is interrupted by a camel that has just entered the kitchen.

“….”

She’s watching Vikir’s handiwork closely.

Next, Vikir holds a lightly steamed potato in front of the chef.

“This will remove the earthy flavor and bring out the sugar, and the texture will be as crisp as a regular potato.”

The chefs in the kitchen let out a collective gasp.

“Wow, there’s a way to prepare these potatoes like this?”

“It’s amazing, it’s a new breed, how?”

“It’s true, it doesn’t have an earthy flavor, and the texture is just like a regular potato.”

The chefs immediately put Vikir’s simple recipe into practice.

The Morgue warriors were also delighted with the change in flavor of the potatoes in their rations.

So did Staffordshire and the Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro triplets who ate among the Morgue.

“Master, how did you know how to eat those potatoes? Apparently the Morgue didn’t either.”

Staffordshire asked, his eyes wide.

Vikir merely looks away, unable to answer.

For now, this Morgue’s potatoes are new to the market.

In a few decades, it will be a battlefield staple.

In the Age of Doom, when all supplies were scarce, warriors in the war against demons developed ways to make their limited food supplies as palatable as possible during their countless days in the wilderness.

Mercenaries who had been through the wringer had learned to squeeze every last drop of flavor out of the simplest of ingredients, such as those who figured out how to take the astringency and earthy smell out of the potato.

Vikir, too, had been in many battles and was naturally familiar with many survivalist dishes.

Many of them were learned while being poisoned or maimed, and some of them were truly eye-opening delicacies.

Meanwhile.

“…!”

The camel’s eyes widened as he tasted the newly prepared potatoes.

“Hey. Do you want to come over and cook?”

“….”

“Yeah, yeah, yeah. I’ll just take you in.”

Vikir sighed lightly.

The camo still had a twinkle in her eye, though.

“Speaking of which, when do you get into the academy? I’ll match you. I’m probably getting an early entry by a year or two. It would be so much fun if we could be first years together….”

Just then.

“…!”

The playful camel’s eyes immediately changed color.

She stops talking and closes her mouth.

And then.

“….”

Vikir’s mouth fell open as well.

The air outside the window changed in an instant.

They both felt it at the same time. A sense of foreboding that the others hadn’t yet felt.

And then.

Tinkle, tinkle, tinkle.

A loud bell began to ring outside the window.

It was the signal for a barbarian attack.

Chapter 52

Slaves of the Savage Tribe (1)

◆

Chirp-.

A small bird chirped.

Vikir opened his eyes to the sunlight streaming in.

The morning light stabbed painfully through her body.

As Vikir tried to sit up, he grimaced at the pain, as if his entire body had been shattered.

With superhuman strength, he managed to keep his upper body upright, but getting fully to his feet was painful.

“Where am I?”

Vikir thought back to last night, which could have been any number of days ago.

He remembered hurling every ounce of his strength at the darkness under the water.

Mana squeezed hard, aura burned fiercely.

I’d thrown my mid-level Gradient power and my magic sword, Beelzebub, at it, and the result was devastating.

‘Defeated’.

Madam Eight-Legs, a gigantic demonic creature shrouded in darkness, was a creature beyond Vikir’s expectations.

At the crucial moment, she would have been killed if she hadn’t flinched from the sudden blast of light.

And for a creature that could generate such firepower, Vikir’s recoil damage was not insignificant.

Muscles and veins throughout his body were ruptured.

The strain on the bones that had to support them was even worse.

The bones of the fingers and forearms that gripped the sword were shattered by comminuted fractures, and the sharp points of spiral-bent ribs pierced his intestines.

The leg bones that had been thrown out had suffered comminuted fractures, transverse fractures, and variously shattered segmental fractures.

As a result, there was no bone, muscle, blood, skin, or anything else.

“At least he’s alive.”

Vikir breathed a sigh of relief.

He had the protection of the River Styx and the power of Beelzebub’s ‘stiff-necked breath’ to thank for his survival.

The consequences of misjudging Madam Eight-Legs’s fighting prowess were painful, but he was glad to be off Hugo’s radar for now.

His death will be reported to Baskerville soon.

There were plenty of eyewitnesses to his death, including Adolf the Mad, a camel, a Staffordshire, and triplets, so I needn’t worry about proving it.

Furthermore, he did not die for not knowing his fractions, but rather for saving the next head of Morgue from demons and barbarians.

‘…The Baskervilles will benefit greatly from future diplomacy with Morgue.

Moreover, the Baskervilles are a knightly family, and this tale will contribute greatly to their image both internally and externally.

Such a feat would likely be rewarded by the imperial court.

Even in death, he would not be treated as a pathetic bastard for bringing honor and profit to the clan.

If you return to your family in the future and reveal that you’re alive, you’ll be treated even better.

“I must recover quickly and regain my former strength.”

Vikir used the power of Murcielago to heal the wounds on his body.

Bones and wounds that were healing at a ridiculous rate, though not immediately.

Then.

Vikir suddenly noticed the ropes around his neck.

A noose hung like a collar around Vikir’s neck.

This was the other thing that had saved Vikir’s life, besides the protection of the River Styx and the power of Murcielago.

If it hadn’t been for the noose, which flew up from behind and yanked at his throat just before the creature’s attack crushed his entire body, Vikir would have died.

It was a very well-timed snare that nearly broke his neck and killed him, but he’s glad to be alive.

Vikir clutched at the noose around his neck.

The end of the noose’s rope ran through the tent and out the door.

Vikir lifted his head and looked back inside the tent.

A cone-shaped tent made of animal skins. A few wooden supports were the only poles, and the floor was littered with dried leaves.

Rustle.

A glass vial of some sort was lying in a circle beside him, and upon closer inspection, he realized it was a potion bottle with the sigil of the Baskervilles.

The smell of dry earth, fallen leaves, animal fur, and stewing potions mingled in the tent.

Vikir crawled like a dog out of the tent.

Her whole body burned with each step, but she needed to get a sense of her surroundings.

Soon, the landscape outside the tent came into view.

Large and small tents made of leather, drums beating everywhere, flames leaping from high piles of wood.

A large number of barbarians moved among them.

Black or silver hair, brown skin, and well toned muscles in both men and women.

Tops made of deer or jaguar skins, bottoms of cloth dyed with acorn juice.

Tattooed and scarred, they dismembered the carcass of a demon and skinned its flesh, while children played with birds.

The atmosphere was cheerful and lively, but raw, unrefined and unprocessed.

Vikir knew instinctively that this was the home of the Ballak, a barbarian tribe.

In the heart of enemy territory, longtime enemies of the Baskervilles.

He should be on his guard, but he was too weak to do so now.

Vikir wondered what to do next.

Ballak’s warriors walked past him, paying him no mind as he stood there alone.

The women and children stiffened a little and seemed wary, but that was it.

Just then.

“Quick, quick, quick, walk!”

A nervous shout came from somewhere.

Vikir turned his head to see several barbarian warriors dragging rope-bound prisoners.

The prisoners, standing in a line and staggering, were of various races.

Most were black-haired, brown-skinned men of other tribes.

Every single one of them had been tortured and abused in some way.

Vikir recognized a few familiar faces among them.

Warriors whose names he did not recognize, but who were surely members of House Baskerville and House Morgue.

Some he’d met in the fortress, others he’d traveled with to this jungle.

Their entire bodies hung like fish from ropes, their eyes locked for the briefest of moments with Vikir, who wore only a single dog collar around his neck.

“….”

“….”

And then they walked past each other.

Vikir stood silent, watching them.

Then the Ballak warriors stabbed their captives with the tips of their spears.

“Climb up quickly. Unless you want to be mauled to death by wolves.”

They led their captives to a tall tree.

It was an impossibly tall pole, covered in thorns that jutted out like blades.

Ballak’s barbarians forced their captives to climb this bladed tree with their bare bodies.

The captives climb this tower of blades until they are covered in blood.

If anyone refused to climb, the barbarians would set fire to the base of the tree.

The tree was oiled on the trunk, so the flames continued to climb up the tree, faster than most prisoners could climb a tree.

Eventually, the prisoners would either bleed to death from being stabbed and cut by the blade-like trunks, burned by the flames from below, or plummet to their deaths on the ground below.

Thump, thump, thump!

Below the tree, the wolves were howling, pushing their captives up the tree.

Some had been impaled by spears or bitten by wolves for refusing to climb the tree of blades.

The horrific “Tree of Thorns Punishment” was devised by an old Ballak shaman.

Vikir could only watch this hellish execution.

Then.

“Hoo-hoo, be thankful you don’t look like that.”

Someone says to Vikir.

Ahun. It was the barbarian warrior who had shot the camel with the tranquilizer needle the other day.

He was giving Vikir a murderous glare, as if he wanted to kill him right now.

“If you weren’t the captain’s pet, I would have boiled you right there.”

“….”

“Don’t just stand there, go find your master!”

Ahun kicked Vikir hard on the butt with his foot.

“….”

Vikir fell to the ground and stared at Ahun.

Ahun flinched slightly at the stare.

“What kind of eyes….”

There was not an ounce of agitation in those serene eyes.

Not the horrific deaths of his captives, not the pain of his battered body.

Ahun felt a shiver run down his spine as he realized that none of it had stirred Vikir’s soul.

Slowly, Vikir rose from his seat and began to follow the rope around his neck.

Ahun could only follow behind, unable to keep up with Vikir.

◆

‘…The guy from earlier. You said his name was Ahun, didn’t you?’

He probably holds a grudge because he hurt his back falling off the wolf’s back the other day.

Vikir hadn’t forgotten the face of the man who had just kicked his ass.

But he couldn’t do anything about it in his current state, so he’d just have to put up with it for now.

Even now, the protection of the Styx River and the regenerative powers of Murcielago are slowly restoring Vikir’s body to its former glory.

In the meantime, Vikir has decided to visit the owner of the noose that saved his life.

After walking for a while, tugging at the rope around his neck, Vikir finds himself in a remote area far from the village.

A small spring fed a pool with a waterfall cascading down through the rocks.

A few crayfish could be seen crawling in the clear water.

A rope led to it.

“…?”

Vikir stopped walking for a moment.

He’s not sure what to do when he sees that the rope he’s been following leads to the center of the pool and goes under the water.

Just then.

Boom!

There’s a splash and a figure pokes its head out of the water.

Water droplets splashing around, hair a mix of silver and black, pointed triangular ears.

A girl with brown skin and big eyes walked out of the water, naked.

The end of the noose’s rope was tied tightly around her wrists.

“….”

Vikir looked straight into the barbarian girl’s face.

Dark, half-moon eyebrows, foxlike slant, eyes as clear as the puddle he was in now, red lips on an intelligent nose.

The charcoal-black color of his face was gone, but the look in his eyes was unmistakable.

She was the barbarian girl I’d met at an illegal slave auction during the cleanup of Underdog City.

They were diametrically opposed then. Vikir held her eyes steady.

“….”

“….”

A brief silence followed.

It was the barbarian girl who broke it first.

She tugged at the leash around Vikir’s neck and grinned.

“Get down.”

Chapter 53

Slave of the Barbarian Tribe (2)

◆

Aiyen, a Ballak warrior and the daughter of a chieftain.

She spoke to Vikir in front of her.

“Get down.”

Was she trying to make the hierarchy clear?

But it didn’t sound like that was her intention.

Because.

Pfft.

Vikir felt a blast of air coming toward him.

At the same time.

…Pot!

Aiyen pulled on the leash around Vikir’s neck.

As Vikir ducked, a thin arrow flew past his back, hitting the ground with a thud.

Aiyen shouted.

“You boys, can’t you go practice somewhere else!”

Suddenly, a rustling sound came from beyond the bushes, and a group of young children came running.

Each one had a bow and arrow in his hand.

“….”

Vikir lifted his head again and looked at Aiyen in front of him.

The girl shaking off the water in front of her.

The girl he had rescued from the slave auction before.

Aiyen said to Vikir.

“ We meet on the sphere, right?”

He spoke in Ballak, judging his skills in the language to be better than Aiyen’s in Imperial.

“…I see you again.”

Aiyen’s eyes widened at the sound of the Ballak language coming out of Vikir’s mouth.

“Do you speak Ballak?”

“A little.”

She walked to stand in front of Vikir, her eyes wide with wonder.

She had only a few short pieces of deerskin around her, but she didn’t seem to have any shame.

Aiyen stepped up to stand in front of Vikir.

“We were grateful then. We will repay your favor twice and your vengeance tenfold.”

“….”

“You saved me once, so I will save you twice.”

“….”

“I never thought you’d try to fight ‘her’, I ran away and came back just in case.”

Certainly, Vikir would have been killed by Madam Eight-Legs, the Dark One, if the rope Aiyen had thrown hadn’t been caught around his neck in time to pull him back.

…So what is the other time?

When Vikir looked at him as if demanding an explanation, the corners of Aiyen’s eyes drew a fox-like arc.

“Did you not see it on the way here?”

She pointed beyond the bushes to the acrid column of smoke rising from the village.

Vikir thought of the prisoners he’d met along the way.

Perhaps she would share a similar fate.

Perhaps it was the Aiyen in front of him who had prevented it.

If so, that raised a more fundamental question.

“Why did you save me?”

Was it simply to repay a favor? If so, there would be no reason for him to throw the noose around his neck in the first place.

And Aiyen was not the only one who wanted to put a noose around Vikir’s neck.

Every female warrior in Ballak that day had her sights set on Vikir’s neck.

As Aiyen sliced into the pizza, Vikir asked her bluntly.

“Is this some kind of husband hunt or something?”

“Oh, you must have heard about it somewhere.”

It’s not just the Ballak, most savages in the jungle kidnap their spouses from outside the tribe.

The idea is to avoid incest and bring in fresh blood.

The Ballak, of course, are a warrior tribe, so the physical strength of the abductee is a big factor.

Aiyen circled around Vikir once.

Like an appraiser evaluating a piece of merchandise.

In the meantime, Vikir had been thinking a lot.

What if they told the Baskervilles that they were alive, and they negotiated a hostage?

That would put a damper on their plans.

Their plan to stay off Hugo’s radar and build up their strength would be ruined.

In order to stop it, you have to escape this place or annihilate all of them…… That was impossible with Vikir’s current physical condition

But Vikir had worried for nothing.

They didn’t seem to have any intention of interfering with him.

Aiyen glanced at Vikir and said.

“Don’t be mistaken. I am not like the other women. I don’t need a husband.”

“….”

“You have been captured to be used as a slave.”

She wondered, but didn’t say it out loud, if it had been necessary to throw the noose so desperately.

When Vikir remained still, Aiyen waved the dog collar in his hand.

“You won’t be able to pass for a man with that body anyway, so you might as well get used to life as a slave.”

By nature, Ballak women see nothing but breeding in the men they capture from the outside world.

If the man fails to fulfill his role as a male, they usually kill him, but fortunately (?) Aiyen doesn’t seem to have the sense to do so.

Aiyen tossed his clothes to Vikir at the water’s edge.

Vikir catches it, and the collar pulls taut.

Aiyen led the way back to the village.

“You will live in front of my house and serve me.”

Vikir’s entire body screamed with each step, but he kept his mouth shut nonetheless.

The good news is that his body is recovering quickly, thanks to the power of Murcielago.

To Vikir, Aiyen gave his first order, briefly.

“Let’s get our formalities straightened out.”

Walking ahead, Aiyen paused at the entrance to the clan and looked back at Vikir.

He looked down and narrowed his eyes.

“Call me master.”

◆

Vikir descended again into the village of the Ballak.

They lived freely in the dense jungle.

The concept of personal property seemed remote.

If you didn’t have a place to sleep, you slept in a neighbor’s tent, and no one minded.

If they were hungry, they ate from people who had plenty of food, and they were happy to share.

There seemed to be a shared consciousness that everything comes and goes, so let’s share while we have it.

They gathered at a friend’s house with a large tent, played cheerfully, and fell asleep.

Firewood, meat, and alcohol were shared generously, and there was no yamcha.

Even if they had been kidnapped from the outside, once they were recognized as members of the tribe, they could go anywhere and come anywhere.

Overall, a lively and welcoming atmosphere.

But the skeletons of captives hanging from the thorn trees at the tribe’s boundary conveyed a different message.

This is Ballak’s clan, a land that is unforgiving to outsiders but endlessly friendly and free to residents.

…But within the clan, there is a “dignified zone” where even insiders are not allowed to roam.

Vikir’s destination was one of those few places.

A large tent in the center of the village.

It looked like it could hold up to two dozen people, but even the children playing in front of it were not allowed to approach.

Passing warriors always bowed their heads in reverence toward the entrance of this tent.

Those grilling meat were careful to keep the smoke from wafting in this direction, and those preparing the entrails of their prey were careful to keep the scent of blood from drifting away.

“’… Is this the chieftain’s house?”

Vikir guessed from the size of the tent.

Aiyen grabbed the leash around Vikir’s neck and strode inside.

“Mother.”

Vikir could see the figure Aiyen sought.

Inside the tent, there was a chair with a large eagle carved into it, and a woman sitting cross-legged, reclining at an angle.

A grim expression, scars ovipositing all over her body.

She wears a cloak and bottoms made of eagle feathers, and a long, large bow rests on a sceptre behind her back.

She wore a cloak of eagle feathers, with a long, large bow on her back.

Akwilla, the current matriarch of the Ballak.

Vikir knelt silently before her, drawn by Aiyen’s touch.

Vikir had already realized that the chieftainess’ real name was Night Fox, as she exuded a heavy presence before him.

The woman who had scarred the bridge of Heavenly Sword Saint Hugo’s nose.

Even Adolf the Mad had been defeated by her, and had spent some time in the service.

Her presence was the reason why Baskerville and the Morgue were unable to cross the border between the enemy and the Black Mountain.

After all, she had killed 16 Gradient-class swordsmen, 10 fourth-class mages, and 6 fifth-class mages in her short life.

All without a single wound!

She was also the one who had left arrowhead marks on the faces of her enemies and the Black Mountain Demon Cerberus.

“What if it was before the regression?”

If I had been able to unleash the power of my prime, could I have faced this woman?

‘I would have had a 0% chance in a hand-to-hand fight, a 0% chance by assassination, and a… 20% chance by running away.’

That 20%, of course, is the chance of survival.

Vikir’s mind raced as he tried to gauge the woman in front of him.

After all, she was up against a Hugo or an Adolf, a top predator that she was no match for right now.

Meanwhile, Akwilla glared down at Vikir in front of her.

“Daughter, is this the Imperial male you’ve been drooling over?”

“No, when did I ever say that much… but yes, he is.”

“Hmm. He’s younger than you, and I recognize his face.”

Akwilla stared at Vikir with narrowed eyes.

The gaze was like that of a top predator from a vastly elevated position, scanning the lesser prey below.

All Vikir could do was keep his head down and avoid her gaze as much as possible.

Fortunately, Akwilla didn’t see any sign of Hugo on Vikir.

Hugo had strong lines, a square jaw, and a masculine appearance, while Vikir took on more of his mother’s features.

Apart from that though, Akwilla seemed to have a pretty good idea of Vikir’s physical condition.

“I see. What are you doing picking up a wasted man?”

“If you treat him well, he’ll be worth it. He’s the one who jumped on Madam Eight-Legs.”

“Hmph. Yes, but rampaging without knowing your place will only get you in trouble.”

Akwilla said.

“Sure. It doesn’t matter if the body is broken or not, as long as the seeds are intact….”

“Aah! Mother, that’s not it, he’s going to be used as a slave!”

“What? But isn’t that the purpose you’ve been telling me all along….”

“Whoa, that’s what it was originally intended for, a slave, I need one to help me hunt!”

Aiyen quickly waved her hand to stop Akwilla’s words.

Akwilla looked at her daughter with a puzzled expression, then nodded.

“…Well, so be it. It is your freedom to use your slave for whatever purpose you choose.”

As soon as the words were out of her mouth, Aiyen bowed her head and tugged on Vikir’s leash.

Once outside the tent, Aiyen’s expression was much stiffer than before.

The flustered look on his face before his mother was gone.

“From now on, I will give you a mission.”

Aiyen looked down at Vikir, who was only one head shorter than her, and spoke in a high-pitched voice.

“It will be difficult.”

…A pretty tough mission, indeed.

Chapter 54

Slaves of the Barbarian Tribe (3)

◆

Aiyen is the youngest hunting leader of the Ballak.

She leads the young men of Ballak through the jungle without fear.

However, she has met a foe that has surprised her.

His name is Vikir, a slave who was recently captured in a raid on Imperial territory.

“….”

Aiyen stared at Vikir with a blank expression.

Vikir moved swiftly with his uncomfortable body, building a tent for himself, as if he didn’t need anyone’s help.

Chug-chug-chug-chug…

A dozen wooden sticks, each just over two meters long, are lined up in a row, and a mixture of inky black, stone dust, lime powder, and water is applied to the sides.

The structure was a mixture of dry and wet, the walls lined with leaves and covered with animal skins.

The tents were quickly fitted with doors and windows, and the floors were lined with sawdust and fallen leaves.

The few building materials given to the slaves were enough.

In less than half an hour, the tent was ready for Vikir to sleep in alone.

“Order fulfilled.”

Vikir looked back at Aiyen, his voice hard and dry.

The first order Aiyen had given to Vikir was to make him a home of his own.

Aiyen peered into Vikir’s tent in disbelief.

There was a small hole in the ceiling and a flap that could be closed if it rained.

There was even a small fire pit on the floor inside, and a hole for the smoke to escape extended outward across the floor of the tent.

When the fire was turned off for a meal, the smoke would pass under the floor and heat up to the bottom of the tent.

The smoke would escape, the heat from the residual fire would be trapped, and the ventilation and light would be perfect.

Aiyen was dumbfounded.

“…How do you build tents so well?”

She was actually looking forward to hearing Vikir grunt in protest.

Aiyen quickly hid the building materials that Vikir had been trying to give away to make his life more colorful.

Sturdy wooden sticks, oil for baking bricks.

But Vikir didn’t need any of that; he found calcareous soil, scooped it up, and hardened it with water.

He also built a shelter of large leaves to protect against rain and wind.

“…It’s been a while.”

Swordsmen from the Age of Destruction were not just good with swords.

They had to be skilled in all sorts of survival skills to be able to camp and survive in the hot and cold polar regions.

As such, Vikir was also a master of many domestic tasks.

After building the tent, Vikir trimmed the piles of leather near Aiyen’s tent and hung up the torn fabrics.

He also cleared a drainage ditch near the tent, and laid out some firewood for tonight.

Chug-chug-chug-chug…

A slave who thinks and acts on his own before his master asks him to do anything, and takes care of all those pesky chores.

Literally a class A slave.

“The bricks under the chieftain’s tent look unstable.”

“…My mother’s house?”

“Yes. The way it is, the ground beneath the center pole of the tent could shake and leak water during the next rainy season. If you give me the order, I will mix the limestone soil down there with stone dust from the hill across the street, make bricks, oil them, bake them, and reinforce them.”

“…Yes, do that. I was just thinking of that myself.”

Aiyen scratched his head.

Vikir had indeed done so.

Moving on his limp legs, he scooped up white dirt from the hills behind him and flew in stones from the hill opposite, cracking and breaking them to mix into the soil.

Then he added water to make a dough, shaped it into a rectangle, baked it over a fire, and dried the bricks with hyena oil.

The bricks were then used to form the base of the tent, making it even stronger.

Even Akwilla, who was initially annoyed at the extra work, was pleased with the results.

“The ceiling won’t leak anymore. It was annoying that no matter how many leaves or hides I put on the ceiling, it would still leak, but it must have been the foundation.”

Akwilla still didn’t pay much attention to Vikir.

He merely ordered him to make his usual rounds around the chieftain’s barracks, observing, maintaining, and repairing the shabby things.

Aiyen was unhappy that his slave should spend most of his time maintaining the chieftain’s barracks, but he didn’t protest.

He just kept whimpering behind him as Vikir dug drainage ditches around Akwilla’s barracks and set up gutters to keep leaves and dirt from piling up on top.

“Hey, man. Are you okay working alone?”

I’d say, and then do some nervous shuffling.

“So, are we gonna do it alone or in a group?”

Which is usually followed by a few unintelligible words.

“Hmmmm, do you enjoy your job? You’ve been working all day.”

“It’s the rainy season, you’re already digging gutters.”

“You don’t have this at home, do you? Eat it.”

“…The owner is talking to you, why don’t you answer him?”

Vikir had been steadily ignoring him as a distraction from his work, but Aiyen continued to hover around him, disappearing for a moment and then reappearing.

At this point, it was hard to tell who was master and who was slave.

…Puck! …Puck! …Puck! Thud!

With lye and a bat, Vikir finished his laundry.

He’d been a Pathfinder, a herbalist, a healer, a cook, an assassin, a cleaner, a laundress, a cook, and everything in between from the youngest crawler in the field to a seasoned veteran, and his experience was coming in handy here.

‘I know I keep using the Age of Destruction excuse, but… it was just as fierce.’

Vikir took a moment to reminisce about the old days while doing laundry.

“…Khhhh. Hmmm, hmmm.”

Beside him, Aiyen, who had stepped forward to give a demonstration, hid her torn leather skirt behind her back as she watched.

◆

…Meanwhile.

Vikir, whose experience of surviving the Age of Destruction has made him good at keeping to himself.

But even he, who was quite content with a day in the life of a slave, much more so than he would have been in Baskerville or Underdog City, had one opponent who might be a little embarrassed.

“Uh, cool.”

Her name was Aiyen, princess of the barbarian tribe of Ballak.

She was peeing in the drainage channel Vikir had dug earlier.

“I’ve been holding it in for a long time.”

“….”

“Ugh, master, are we supposed to watch you pee like that?”

Aiyen was peeing with his legs open, right next to where Vikir was working.

Vikir was dumbfounded and asked.

“What are you doing?”

“Marking the territory. This is my slave’s house, so it’s also mine.”

“…Doesn’t cover it?”

“It’s not like there’s any shame in open excretion. There is no such thing in my tribe.”

Aiyen lifted her skirt further, as if to show him.

Vikir covered her face with her hands and turned away.

He remembered seeing a research paper on barbarian tribes once.

“The barbarian tribes of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain practice free sexual intercourse among their members. Both men and women have no qualms about exposing their sexual organs to each other, as they must first know if the other person is capable of reproduction and does not carry a sexually transmitted disease before engaging in a relationship.”

‘Did I mention …?

It was a real thing and a culture with its own reasons, so Vikir tried not to be prejudiced.

“But don’t be cheap, at least around the house.”

“Why, didn’t your empire just throw feces out the window a few hundred years ago, and you wore these things called high heels because the streets were covered in filth, and you sprayed yourself with perfume.”

It was true enough.

Vikir didn’t know what else to say, so he kept his mouth shut.

As they chatted, the chores were completed.

Ballak was a very laid-back place when he wasn’t fighting or hunting, and the ever-diligent Vikir couldn’t help but think that life as a slave here was much more comfortable than it would have been in Baskerville or Underdog City, where he had to combine training and work.

Aiyen, however, had a strange look on her face.

“Hey.”

“…?”

“Don’t you want to officially become a member of our tribe as soon as possible?”

What was he talking about?

Vikir frowned, and Aiyen scooted closer to him and sat down.

She was still spreading her legs wide enough that he could see through her skirt, so Vikir kept his gaze fixed upward.

Aiyen said.

“Not bad for a slave, huh?”

“Not bad.”

“You’re getting a good education in speech, I suppose, though I dare not complain from a slave’s point of view.”

“…No, it really isn’t that bad.”

“It can’t be bad, for all the hard, dirty work.”

Aiyen waved her hand in the air, not even wanting to think about cleaning or doing laundry.

“‘Come on. Come with me.”

“…?”

“I will help you. To help you fit in with this tribe.”

There’s no refusal when you’re already enslaved.

Aiyen patted the leash still around Vikir’s neck.

“If you’re good, I’ll take this off too.”

The offer is a bit tempting.

As if I wasn’t already annoyed by this irritating rope at the corner of my neck.

“…What can I do?”

Vikir asks, and Aiyen answers with a twinkle in his eye.

“Hunting.”

“…Hunt?”

“The big one.”

Apparently, you go hunting and catch big prey.

The Hagiya, or Ballak, are a tribe that accumulates food primarily through hunting.

To feed their nearly 300 members evenly, they need to consume a boar weighing over 200 kilograms a day.

That’s if they’re able to supplement it with mushrooms, berries, and edible roots.

In recent years, he says, warriors in his tribe have been eating nothing but mushrooms and berries for days at a time because they haven’t been able to find enough meat.

“In times like these, if we can bring back a large chunk of meat, your freedom is not out of the question.”

Aiyen’s words gave Vikir a strange look.

It was a bit ironic to hear the word “freedom” from a barbarian.

But it wasn’t a bad offer.

“All you have to do is assist me. Apparently you don’t have much trouble getting around or carrying light loads.”

Aiyen said with a gleam in her eye.

It was impossible to tell if her intentions were truly to take down the big game, or if that was all she wanted.

“Alright. Let’s go.”

But Vikir decided to go along with Aiyen’s suggestion for now.

As a slave, he had no other choice.

Vikir nodded, and Aiyen spoke immediately.

“We will leave at dawn today.”

“I see, but why were you laughing so hard earlier?”

“What? When did I laugh?”

Aiyen laughs self-consciously, but when he hears Vikir’s words, he turns serious.

…Something about his attitude was a little suspicious.

Chapter 55

The Hunter and the Hunted (1)

◆

The Ballak are a very warlike people by nature.

It was clear that if you took war and hunting out of their lives, there probably wouldn’t be much left.

As Vikir followed Aiyen to the entrance of the clan, he reviewed what he knew about the Ballak.

‘Their language has only about three hundred words, and most of them are nouns. Verbs are gestural, and there is no distinction between them and us when it comes to possession. Men are ambo, women are akouati, love is aauki, death is utika…’

The people of Ballak viewed the empires as rude, devious, and pretentious.

Conversely, the Imperials viewed the Ballak as barbarians who screamed and punched at the slightest hint of anger.

The people of Baskerville seemed to be somewhere in the middle, Vikir thought, between the civilized people of the Empire and the barbarians of the jungle.

“I wonder if they’re vaguely resembling both sides of the border, never fully belonging to either.”

As Vikir pondered this to himself, the hunters of Ballak gathered in a circle.

Hunters, young and old, gathered in groups of three and four.

Several mounted on the backs of wolves, bows and spears dangling.

Only Aiyen had no companions, just a wolf to ride and his slave, Vikir.

“Gather round, hunters, it’s time for the ceremony.”

A crooked-looking old man came forward with a bowl of black charcoal, which he smeared on the faces of the hunter-warriors.

A series of tattoos peeked out from beneath his black robes, suggesting he might be a shaman.

“Go, all of you, with my blessing, or I will strike you down.”

The old shaman dipped a bowl of tan into the bowl and smeared it over the faces of all the hunters.

The hunters of Ballak feel guilty about killing their prey.

So they smeared their faces with tar before killing, so as not to show their faces to the God of Death.

But the younger hunters, including Aiyen, don’t seem to appreciate the ritual.

“There you go again, that annoying b*tch.”

“Leave him alone. The shaman needs to make his mark.”

“By the way, don’t you think your fortune-telling is a little off?”

“That’s why all they do nowadays are earrings for ears and nose rings for noses.”

All young people, regardless of time and place, dislike and despise old customs and superstitions.

With a look of annoyance, Aiyen stuck out her face and accepted the old shaman’s charcoal-black makeup.

The old shaman rubbed the black paint on Aiyen’s face a few times before moving on, which was quite sloppy compared to what he did for the other warriors, and it was clear that he didn’t like her.

Next, Aiyen slipped the spiked collar around his neck and handed it to Vikir.

“Wear this to keep them from biting your neck.”

Vikir nodded.

One by one, the hunters began to leave the village.

Knives sheathed, spears drawn, bows drawn, wolves herded, the tribe’s hunters departed.

Vikir, the slave, made his own preparations.

“While I’m here, I’ll have to blend in with them.”

He needed to renew his mindset.

Vikir finally felt the urge and pulled down his pants to pee.

He was going to start with something as basic as this and blend into the culture.

…So?

When the people of Ballak saw Vikir peeing, they began to freak out.

The women covered their eyes and watched through their spread fingers, while the men gave him openly competitive glances.

Vikir was puzzled and asked.

“What’s with all the stares? Isn’t everyone doing this?”

Answers came from all over the place.

“…What are you talking about, who pisses in the middle of nowhere like that?”

“Is that how they do it in the Empire? That’s barbaric.”

“We use separate restrooms.”

“Men over there, women over here.”

“You’re so ignorant, you should cover up.”

“How barbaric!”

“What happened?”

….

Vikir turned his head to look at Aiyen.

Aiyen smirked, then quickly averted her gaze.

◆

Aiyen climbed onto the wolf’s back.

“Hold on tight.”

On her back, of course, was Vikir.

Vikir hesitated for a moment, unsure of where to hold on, then squeezed the wolf’s fur.

Then Aiyen reached back and pulled Vikir’s arm around her waist.

“You have to hold on here. Tight. If you don’t, you’ll fall and break your neck.”

Vikir grasped Aiyen’s thighs with his hands. It was certainly wide enough to be comfortable to hold.

But.

…Boom!

The wolf took a single leap, and Vikir was sent tumbling to the ground.

In agony, Vikir almost screamed.

His bones, barely held together by Murcielago’s regenerative powers, twisted again.

Riding a wolf was quite different from riding a horse.

For one thing, there was no saddle and no mount.

Furthermore, wolves had a much narrower waist than horses, and they moved more dynamically.

Aiyen stopped the wolf and lowered himself to the ground.

“Tsk, tsk, you should have wrapped your arms around my waist like that and held on with both hands. It’ll fall off if you hold it that gently.”

She smirked and patted her own waist, as if to say, “How am I supposed to vent without you holding it?”

Vikir was just about to rise from his seat.

…Thud!

A figure stepped in between Vikir and Aiyen.

Ahun. He was riding a wolf, looking down at Vikir.

The atmosphere immediately turns chilly.

Aiyen crossed her arms in a look of displeasure.

Ballak’s hunters compete for every moment.

Ahun is a warrior who has always been fond of Aiyen, and he will challenge her in this hunt.

“This time,” he says, “I’ll bring home the bigger prey. I’m going to be the captain of the next joint hunt, in my grandfather’s honor.”

“Why would you risk your grandfather’s honor on a hunt when all you know how to do is witchcraft? It’s your prerogative to do whatever you want.”

Aiyen didn’t confront Ahun.

He merely jerked his chin toward Vikir across the way, urging him to come quickly.

Vikir had just gotten to his feet and was about to make his way toward Aiyen.

…Puck!

Vikir’s head snapped back.

Ahun, riding on top of the wolf, had kicked him in the face with his foot.

Vikir was still wounded, so he had no choice but to take the blow even though he knew it was coming.

Thank goodness it wasn’t an attack of great force.

The next moment, Aiyen was furious.

“You bastard, what the…!?”

Aiyen stepped forward, but she froze in place.

She glanced back and forth between Vikir, who had fallen to the ground with a strange look in his eyes, and Ahun, who had gained momentum.

Ahun flinched for a moment at Aiyen’s reaction, then breathed a sigh of relief.

Then he looked at the fallen Vikir and sneered.

“You’re using this weakling as a hunting aid. Get a grip, Captain. You’ll only get yourself in trouble.”

“You should look at your own backside before you say that ….”

At Aiyen’s sarcastic remark, Ahun looked down at his waist.

There was nothing there. Where there should have been a quiver full of arrows.

“…!?”

Ahun whipped his head around, furious.

Vikir had somehow gotten up with his quiver and arrows.

He had just swiped it from Ahun before he collapsed.

“‘I owe the Age of Destruction again.”

Before his regression, Vikir hadn’t really had a job he hadn’t done.

The art of pickpocketing comes in handy, too.

“Weapons are like lovers. You use them when they’re taken away.”

Vikir’s grave comment made Aiyen burst out laughing and Ahun blush.

“…You, you insolent slave!”

Ahun drew his bowstring and struck Vikir in the shoulder.

Boom!

With a loud crack, Vikir fell to the ground.

As if that wasn’t enough, Ahun climbed off the wolf’s back.

Boom!

The bowstring swung out once more.

…Boom!

Ahun’s bow had to stop in midair.

Aiyen had drawn an arrow and blocked Ahun’s bowstring.

“That’s enough. Whose slave do you think you’re punishing?”

Aiyen’s words were as cold and hard as frost.

Ah Hun stammered out a retort.

“He’s a slave, how dare he insult a Ballak warrior!”

“You showed your pathetic self first.”

“Nevertheless, he’s a slave, and a slave can never insult a warrior!”

Ahun protested, citing the rules of the tribe.

“….”

Aiyen thought for a moment, then nodded.

“Very well, a slave is a slave, and if he does something wrong, he must be punished.”

“Yes, Captain. That’s what I’m saying.”

“But you have no right to punish him, he’s my slave.”

“…?”

The concept of private property is rare on Ballak, but when it comes to slaves, the lines of ownership are pretty strict.

When Ahun shook his head, Aiyen drove a wedge.

“If there is to be a punishment, it will be mine.”

With that, Aiyen slid off the wolf’s back and stood in front of Vikir.

And then.

…Snap!

Aiyen’s hand slapped Vikir across the cheek.

As Vikir fell to the ground, Aiyen continued to beat him.

His fists curled like snakes, targeting his abdomen, waist, and legs.

Vikir curled into a circle and endured Aiyen’s fists in silence.

After a few minutes of this, Aiyen pulled back, breathing heavily.

Then she glared at Ahun with a cold stare.

“Are we done?”

“….”

Ahun held his breath, as if he was embarrassed by Aiyen’s spanking, and then nodded in disbelief.

Aiyen looked Ahun straight in the eyes.

“I know you have a lot of personal grievances with my slave, falling off the wolf’s back, not being able to catch Saxi….”

“…Yes.”

“After this time, if you do anything to my slave in private, you will be beaten like this. Do you understand?”

Aiyen’s fist dripped with blood.

His eyes were dark and flesh-colored.

Ahun nodded his head a few times in confusion, then turned his bored gaze to Vikir on the floor.

Vikir, who hadn’t screamed up until that point, was simply writhing quietly in place.

With that, Ahun climbed onto the wolf’s back and quickly disappeared.

Only Aiyen and Vikir were left here again.

Sigh…

Aiyen creeped over and squatted down in front of Vikir.

Vikir pushed himself to his feet.

She stroked Vikir’s reddened cheeks with an unfathomable, complicated gaze.

“…Were you hurt?”

His tone had changed slightly, but maybe it was just his mood.

Chapter 59

The Hunter and the Hunted (5)

◆

Alas.

Vikir scrambled to his feet.

His bones screamed at his unhealed joints, but he had no choice.

If he didn’t move now, he would be killed.

Boom!

The tent I had built shredded like tissue paper.

It was the Oxbear’s powerful claws that tore through the night.

Aiyen chuckled in amusement.

“You were lured, weren’t you, you sneaky thing?”

A male oxbear. Even if he was only half the size of the female, he was still a very large carnivore, standing over four meters tall and weighing over a ton.

This seasoned beast already knew it was being tracked.

That’s why it had waited to strike while it was weak.

Aiyen quickly grabbed his bow and arrows and retreated to the outside of the tent.

Bakira, the wolf, crouched low beside her master, snarling.

Aiyen studied the oxbear before him.

“I see you were chosen by the old female for a reason.”

The giant female Oxbear before him had been very picky about her second year, and he was a little puzzled as to why she had chosen this one, who was unusually small among the many males, to be her mate.

If it was simply because she didn’t want to be attacked after mating, there were plenty of other smaller males available.

But now I understood.

She wanted his cunning intelligence to complement her superior physicality.

[Grunt!]

The oxbear lunged at her with two massive horns and both front paws.

Aiyen climbed onto Bakira’s back and quickly nocked an arrow to his bowstring.

Ping-!

Two arrows fly, aiming for the Oxbear’s face.

The oxbear ducked his head and lifted his horns up, so they couldn’t hit him in the face.

The arrows then deflected in midair as if they were alive, striking Oxbear in both shoulders.

Indeed, Ballak’s archery was the best on the continent, and Aiyen’s was the best of all.

Karak- Karak- Karak- Karak

Aiyen strung multiple arrows from a single bow.

Unusually, Ballak’s bow has multiple nocks.

The arrows on each of these nocks can be staggered and fired back-to-back, or they can be fired all at once.

Puff, puff, puff!

Ai Yan fired arrow after arrow, barely pausing to breathe.

The time it took for the first arrow to fly, followed by the second, third, fourth, fifth, and so on, was a blink of an eye.

A truly monstrous rate of fire.

Of course, pulling five arrows at once requires a ridiculous amount of arm strength.

The enormous tension required was covered by Aiyen’s low-level Gradient mana.

[Grrrr!]

The rain of arrows slowed Oxbear’s charge.

Each of Aiyen’s arrows was so powerful that even the oxbear’s thick muscles and furry hide could not defend against them.

What’s more, Aiyen’s arrows didn’t just travel in a straight line.

She shot them upward, sideways, and sometimes even backward.

Arrows that went up would fall in a parabolic arc and hit the top of the head, while those that went sideways would curve back and hit the side.

Arrows that flew backwards even hit trees and rocks, sending grenades flying.

Moreover, the arrows carried a powerful aura.

Oxbear had no idea how troublesome this aura would be.

…Puck! Puck!

Oxbear ducked behind a bush to avoid the flying arrow.

The brambles were quite thick, and he thought they would block the arrows.

But.

“A good arrow will pierce steel if it wants to, but it will not pierce a leaf if it does not want to.”

Aiyen recalled a lesson she had heard from her mother and chief, Akwilla.

Next, she let loose an arrow, which struck the high bush where the oxbear was hiding.

Poof!

Surprisingly, the arrow, traveling at such high speeds, didn’t hit the bramble and bounce back.

Instead, the arrow’s aura left the arrowhead and soaked into the brush.

And then.

Boom!

The oxbear hiding behind the bramble spewed blood from its neck.

[Crunch!]

Penetration.

The intangible energy from the arrowhead went beyond the barren tree and gouged into the oxbear’s body behind it.

Vikir gasped at the sight.

“Indeed, that is the archery of the Ballak!”

A ridiculous archery skill, capable of killing even an enemy behind cover.

But the skilled hunters of Ballak actually do it.

Vikir had moved mana to shatter a table and the glasses on it without destroying it, but he didn’t know if it could be applied to flying arrows.

“If it can be done… it would allow for more precise aura control.”

Vikir lifted his head again and looked at Aiyen.

Seventeen years old and a Gradient junior.

Even in Baskerville, where only geniuses live, I’ve never seen a prodigy this young.

In terms of talent alone, he could probably rival or surpass even Morgue’s camo.

…But.

It was the oxbear that made even Aiyen nervous.

An immature, small male, weak after a prolonged mating.

But even so, the Danger Rank A beast was strong.

Aiyen gritted her teeth as she realized she was almost out of arrows.

Bakira, the wolf who had been his steady companion, was also exhausted.

It’s cold, the terrain is simple, and it’s a moonless night, making visibility difficult.

Now, with all the advantage, Oxbear is ready for the final blow.

The oxbear’s typical attack pattern consists of a horn charge followed by a large swing of its front paws.

But it’s the tooth attack that follows these two moves that really makes the difference.

[He-aaaah!]

The oxbear charged with all its might, opening its wide arms to embrace both Aiyen and Bakira at once.

Its dagger-like jaws were lined with teeth, ready to rip Aiyen’s head off.

“What do we do, we’re running out of arrows, do we retreat, or do we make one last gamble…?”

As Aiyen contemplated his next move.

Something happened that neither Aiyen, Bakira, nor even Oxbear saw coming.

“Move.”

Vikir. He had appeared.

Vikir, an unwelcome intruder into the battle.

He was perched on top of a tall branch.

Then Vikir kicked off the branch and leaped, falling straight down to Oxbear.

“Ow! What are you doing!”

Aiyen was horrified. What Vikir was doing seemed to her to be nothing less than suicide.

But then.

As Vikir leapt from the tree, he clutched a handful of arrows.

And surprisingly, Oxbear didn’t react much to the sight of Vikir falling.

That’s because Vikir’s jump was to the left.

Not long before, the male Oxbear had received a slap on the cheek while moping around in the female’s den after mating, and his left eye was swollen shut.

It was an exquisite dig to fill the blind spot.

And then.

…Poof!

Several arrows in Vikir’s grasp pierced Oxbear’s left eye at once.

Chiiiit-

The sound of fat boiling, the smell of burning meat was unmistakable.

The arrowheads had been loaded with Aiyen’s mana not long ago, and were heated to the limit.

The hot shards of iron tore through the oxbear male’s swollen snowball flesh, popping his tender eyeball and sending the bundle of nerves inside scrambling.

[Aaahhhhhh!]

Oxbear’s scream changed slightly.

Its roar, once a mixture of hatred and contempt, was now tinged with fear.

Vikir snatched the arrows out of her hand and dropped to the ground.

“…Thud!”

The mere act of landing on the ground seems to shatter his entire body.

The oxbear loomed in front of him, its enormous body looming over him.

Aiyen gasped in horror.

“No!”

She quickly fired an arrow, but it only pierced some of the oxbear’s strong back muscles.

Bakira the wolf lunged and bit her hind paws, but Oxbear was unperturbed.

[Argh!]

Blinded by rage and fear, Oxbear opened his mouth in a guttural roar.

No horns, no front paws, just teeth! The Oxbear’s true breath attack flew toward Vikir.

And the expression on Vikir’s face as he faced it could not have been more serene.

“….”

This is not a death wish.

He’s gauging whether his body can handle the technique he’s about to use.

“Come out.”

Vikir ordered in a low voice, and the faithful hound bared its teeth.

…Poof!

A black awl pierced the artery in Vikir’s wrist.

The magic sword, Beelzebub, had been unleashed!

Whirring.

With the sound of a fly’s wings, Beelzebub revealed his appetite for the giant hunk of meat in front of him.

And with that, one of the powerful forces trapped within Beelzebub’s three orbs exploded through the tip of his sword.

<The Gluttonous Fly ‘Beelzebub’>/ Awl

-Slot 1: Burn – Cerberus(A+)

Cerberus. The three-headed dog that symbolizes Hell itself.

Roar!

The oil-based flames, which could not be extinguished by water, combined with the aura of Beelzebub’s blade and exploded.

Fueled by the oils of hell, the flames burned endlessly unless their master’s will was extinguished.

The fiery hound’s teeth sank back into Oxbear’s gaping mouth.

[Cackle!?]

Oxbear stopped charging.

His eyes, blinded by rage and fear, finally opened to the reality of the situation.

…What the hell is that?

I thought it was just some human blood, but it wasn’t.

What you see before you is a gigantic apex predator, the presence of a high-ranking demon that you dare not compare to, the fangs of a monster that belongs in the deepest hells of the Netherworld.

Wherever it has been lying in ambush, the creature that has just bared its teeth is upon you, bringing untold pain and terror.

…Quack!

A short, guttural sound.

The awl that sprouted from Vikir’s wrist shot out and pierced the oxbear’s mouth.

First, it pierced the hanging tongue, then the gums, then the palate, and finally the brain in the skull.

To make matters worse, the tip of the awl emitted a terrifying flame.

The most terrible pain in the world: burning pain.

It was boiling the brains in Oxbear’s skull to a crisp.

[Gah!]

Oxbear let out a near-terminal scream.

Vikir’s attack was short, but intense.

The oxbear was still clinging to life with its characteristic toughness and regenerative powers, but that was all.

No, that wasn’t all.

In the last moments of its life, Oxbear leaned its massive body toward Vikir.

Vikir struggled to move from the pain he felt throughout his body.

Even in death, Oxbear intended to use his massive body to crush Vikir to death.

But.

Pow!

At that moment, Aiyen threw his whole body and grabbed Vikir.

Bakira the wolf scooped up Aiyen and Vikir with her fluffy back and stepped back.

“Are you okay!?”

Aiyen’s eyes widened, scanning Vikir’s entire body.

Vikir nodded with difficulty.

At the same time.

…Thud!

The Oxbear giant’s head slammed into the ground.

The last words of a male who, only moments before, had been frantically mating with a female in the cozy confines of his den, could he have imagined such an end?

In the jungle, where looting, death, and love mixed together.

…The downfall!

Aiyen pulled Vikir into a hug.

She hastily tore off the few strips of cloth that covered them, shouting, “Tell me!”

“Tell me if you’re going to die! We need to get the seeds out of …!”

Vikir couldn’t help but sigh at the success of the hunt.

Chapter 61

The Protagonist of Hunting (2)

◆

The hunt ended with a feast.

That night, the whole event ended with the selection of about a hundred kilograms of the finest parts of Oxbear meat.

The men of Ballak chose the best of the meat and hung it on a tall tree quite a distance from the village.

When Vikir looked confused, Aiyen explained.

“It’s a sacrifice to Madam Eight-Legs.”

Vikir nodded slightly.

He had met Madam Eight-Legs once before, in the darkness of the jungle.

An unspeakable beast. A creature of untold horror that no man could survive.

The barbarians of Ballak seemed to use parts of their dead prey, or the bodies of their prisoners of war, as sacrifices, nailed to high trees.

Surprisingly, no creatures were interested in the meat the Ballak men hung from the tree.

Hyenas, eagles, and even the odd insect were not attracted to the meat.

They didn’t dare touch it because they knew who it belonged to.

“I wonder if the warriors of Baskerville and Morgue were also sacrificed to Madam Eight-Legs once upon a time?”

It seemed likely, given the non-cannibalistic culture of the Ballak.

◆

The next day at dawn.

Vikir awoke early and padded out of his tent.

Along the way, he saw a group of drunken Ballak warriors sleeping in the early morning dew.

Vikir was careful not to step on them, and soon he was walking toward the outskirts of town.

His body was healing faster with each passing day.

And he would need more food if he wanted to recover faster.

The meat, blood, and entrails of the oxbear were not enough, so Vikir traveled to the outskirts of the village to find food for himself.

As a slave, he didn’t expect to be allowed to leave the village, but the guards at the entrance were surprisingly willing to let him go.

“What are you, a slave, wandering around all by yourself because you did well in the hunt?”

The sentry, Ahun, frowned at Vikir’s arrogance, but didn’t restrain him.

“You don’t think you’re scared of the jungle just because you’ve killed a dying bear, Kek, get out and die.”

Ahun waved him off and Vikir walked out into the jungle, pacing.

After a while, Vikir reached the tall tree where he had hung his offering last night.

“…!”

Vikir’s eyes widened slightly.

Sure enough, the hundred kilograms of meat that he had hung on the high tree was gone.

The disappearance of the meat meant that its owner had come and gone, even though the wild animals, flying beasts, and insects that roamed nearby had not dared to approach it.

The area was filled with white, dried slime and charred, dead grass.

“…That’s a nasty demon.”

Vikir turned away from the spot and headed for a stream a short distance away.

A river of muddy water.

There was no boundary between water and ground.

Only overgrown vines and thorny leaves marked the river’s boundaries.

Vikir climbed a high branch and stretched out his line.

He pulled out the longest, toughest strand of Oxbear’s fur and used it as a fishing line.

At the end of it was a hook carved from the oxbear’s scavenged bones.

Vikir bit the tip of his finger lightly to draw blood and sprinkled it into the river.

The reaction was immediate.

Bubbling, bubbling, bubbling…

Judging by the bubbling bubbles on the surface of the tan water, it had worked.

Vikir threaded a frog that had been wandering nearby onto a fishing hook and cast it into the center of the foam.

The bite was immediate.

…Tsk!

A fish with teeth as sharp as saw blades snapped off the line.

<Piranha Natteri>.

Danger rating (single individual) : D

Danger rating (group) : A

Size : 30cm

Found in: Ridge 6, Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain

-Travels in herds of at least a few thousand individuals.

When alone, they are cowardly and shy, but in a group, they will charge at even the largest of enemies.

They are sensitive to the smell of blood and will swarm in deep pools in rivers, and when they catch the scent of their prey, they will swarm away, leaving only the bones behind.

The frog used as bait was torn to shreds, but the oxbear’s fur and bones were intact, as were the line and hook.

A fish with a black body and a red belly.

As soon as Vikir caught it, he threaded it onto a spiky branch.

The next bait was a small piece of flesh from the fish he had just caught.

The Nateri are even more eager now that they are using meat from their own kind as bait.

One, two, three, four… fish kept coming.

Some were over 70 centimeters long, with black or white bodies and red eyes.

“They’re supposed to be hard to catch.”

Vikir muttered as he looked down at the natteri, their gills pierced by long reeds.

They were originally sensitive only to human blood and the flesh of their kind.

Human blood, especially if it has been imbued with some degree of mana, is a favorite.

The hunters of Ballak don’t seem to realize this, so Vikir simply stacks up the food in silence.

Vikir then roasted the nateri over a low fire of fallen leaves and sticks.

He ate some, smoked some, and used them to make fish balls.

By the time he’d caught the freshwater crabs and zaras that crawled along the banks of the river and stocked up on food, the morning sun had risen.

“…?”

As I returned to the village with a sack full of food made of leaves, I saw a strange sight.

In the center of town, in front of Chief Akwilla’s barracks, there was a long line of people.

“What was that?”

Vikir scratched his head.

There were at least thirty people lined up in front of the chieftain’s barracks.

Unusually, all thirty were young women.

“Is this some kind of ceremony?”

To get to the barracks, I have to pass by this line anyway.

Unaware of Vikir’s approach from behind, the young women chatter amongst themselves.

“I’ve been in line since the crack of dawn, thank God I’m in the front of the line.”

“I actually spent the night here!”

“Too bad. I should have gotten up a little earlier.”

Vikir listened, wondering what was going on.

There was something off about their conversation.

“Given your performance at yesterday’s hunting festival, you’re probably going to get off scot-free, right?”

“Then surely you’ll take a woman in the village as a saxi?”

“I’ll talk to the chief and make sure I’m the first to apply.”

“I saw you cutting up the meat yesterday, and it was so hearty.”

“You must be strong enough to hunt down an oxbear.”

“What a handsome thing.”

Vikir shuffled away.

“????”

An instinctive warning goes through me before I can fully comprehend what’s going on.

Vikir is just about to turn away.

“These are real!”

I hear a shrill cry.

Thirty or so women back away, furious.

Where their gazes were directed, Aiyen stood, his eyes glowing.

She was carrying three freshly killed roe deer.

She threw them to the ground and announced to the women of the village.

“‘What nonsense,’ she said to the women, ‘I fed you yesterday to the point of decoction, and now you’re trying to steal from me at the last minute!’”

Then one of the women mustered up the courage to speak up.

“Then use it first (?) and then hand it over!”

“Shut up, you’re talking to a kid who’s not even a slave anymore!”

“Monopolies are vile!”

“If you’re so unjust, go out there with a noose and get him!”

“I’ve been out many times and there’s never been a kid like that!”

“How far have you been out?”

“The borders of the empire!”

“You could go out to hell and back and find him!”

Aiyen exclaimed, pulling his dagger from his inner thigh.

Then the women in the line slipped backward.

Even the bravest of Ballak’s women are afraid of Aiyen, the hunting leader.

No wonder, since quarrels with her go beyond hair-pulling and nail-clawing.

Watching the women slink away, Aiyen snorted hard.

“Sh*t. At this rate, someone’s going to pick it up while I’m waiting for them to recover. I can’t trust a bitch like Sagal. I need to get her well soon so she can give me an excuse……”

She turned away, muttering something to herself.

Aiyen and Vikir’s gazes met.

Vikir, who had been unintentionally hiding behind the tent, panicked.

He hadn’t done anything wrong, but he had been seen.

But it was Aiyen who was more flustered than Vikir.

“….Look, did you see that?”

“….”

“Hmmm. No.”

“….”

“…Khhhh.”

An awkward silence fell between them.

Finally, Aiyen scratched her neck and strode over.

She’s nearly a foot taller than Vikir.

Aiyen stepped closer and looked down at Vikir.

When she opened her mouth, he could smell the sweet scent of tree berries mingled with her warm breath.

“Last night, Mother called a meeting of the Elders.”

“….”

“Among the many items on the agenda was your story.”

From what she’d told me before, it was traditionally reserved for those who caught and submitted the largest game in the hunting system to be freed from slavery.

But now, it seems, the reward is more than just a piece of cotton cloth.

“Listen, you can ask my mother for something. As an honorable hunter of yesterday’s slaughter.”

Aiyen turned to Vikir.

“She will probably try to match you with a mate.”

An outsider, a bonded slave.

The only way to keep such a useful person in the tribe is to know who they will be paired with.

“…I wonder if that’s why those women were lined up all morning.”

Vikir sighed softly.

Meanwhile, Aiyen narrowed her eyes and asked in a low voice.

“You. Do you have a mate in mind in this tribe?”

…There can’t be.

His body is broken, and he’s adrift in the middle of enemy territory, and he’s been fighting dangerous creatures all this time.

As Vikir shook his head emphatically, Aiyen’s expression became subtle.

It was a mixture of anger and helplessness, of relief and misgivings.

…Tuck!

Aiyen threw his arms around Vikir’s shoulders.

Her momentum was strong, but she gently lowered her hands when they reached Vikir’s shoulders.

Aiyen leaned close to Vikir’s ear and spoke in a low voice.

“Later, when my mother calls for you, I will decide what you will ask of her.”

Her eyes sparkled.

“What shall I ask for…”

She looked as if she was planning some sort of trick.

Chapter 62

The Protagonist of Hunting (3)

◆

Vikir sits in his barracks, stoking the fire in the fire pit.

“…Are you there?”

A thin voice called from outside.

As Vikir walks out of his leaf insignia, he sees a girl with black hair and dark eyes looking up at him with a shy expression.

It was the same girl who had risen at the crack of dawn the previous day and stood in line outside the chieftain’s barracks.

“The chief is looking for you, I’ve come to deliver a message.”

She must have come on an errand.

Vikir immediately started walking toward the chieftain’s barracks.

Then.

“Ah, hey, hey!”

The girl calls out to Vikir.

When Vikir turned his head, the girl was flushed red and stammering.

“Hey, thank you for grilling the meat the other day, it was delicious!”

She must be referring to the roasting of meat in the hunting expeditions.

Vikir gave a quick nod and turned away. The chieftain called me, I have to get going.

◆

Even the warriors of Ballak, who roam freely in all parts of the jungle, are not allowed to act recklessly, especially in the presence of the chieftain Akwilla.

Vikir enters through the curtain and immediately sees a mounted eagle at the far end of the barracks.

Beneath it, in a large chair, sat Chieftain Akwilla.

A stern-looking woman, scars scattered across her face.

She’s not very tall, but her rich eagle-feathered cloak and the sense of power she exudes make you think you’re facing a giant.

In particular, the large scar over one of her eyes made the audience feel intimidated.

Nicknamed the Night Fox, she is the current leader of the Ballak and their strongest warrior.

She has won back-to-back victories over Hugo Le Baskerville, patriarch and swordmaster of House Baskerville, and Adolf Morgue, deputy and sixth-class master of House Morgue.

It is because of her that the Ballak, who total only about three hundred in number, are feared by the empires and are known as the strongest warrior tribe in the jungle.

“Chieftain.”

Vikir dropped to one knee and bowed his head in the manner of his training.

Akwilla, the Night Fox, the greatest archer said to have ever lived since Adonai, the legendary archer who led the Ballak at their height centuries ago.

She lifted her one and only eye and gazed upon Vikir with admiration.

Unlike Imperial speech, which circles around its purpose in greetings and praise, Ballak’s is straightforward and raw.

“I see you caught an oxbear this time. Thanks to you, we have delicious meat.”

Akwilla spoke with a gentle smile that belied her first impression.

His voice was as regal as Hugo’s, but without the edge, and instead warm and gentle.

“No, Chief. I was only doing what I was supposed to do.”

“There is no need to be humble. A job well done is a job well done.”

Akwilla smiled even more warmly at Vikir’s modesty.

Vikir was genuinely surprised that the terrifying night fox was capable of such a smile.

Finally, Akwilla spoke.

“In recognition of your deeds of yesterday, I am relieving you of your status. You are no longer a slave, but a member of our family.”

From this moment on, Vikir was no longer a slave, but officially a member of the Ballak family.

Then.

“…Cough.”

A sound of hollow coughing filled with disgust.

Vikir glanced sideways to see a grizzled old man glaring at him with his mouth clamped shut.

“You must be the old man who used to smear ash on the faces of young hunters.”

Ahmen, the shaman of Ballak.

He was the most powerful man in the village, except for the chief, Akwilla.

He is not well-liked by the young, who dislike old traditions and superstitions, but all the older, more seasoned hunters put their trust in him.

The saying “There are no atheists in the trenches” is true.

People who have been through the storms of life are always looking for something to lean on spiritually, and Ahmen understood exactly that.

“By the way, did I mention… Ahun was the son of that old man?”

Ahun, the young hunter who always wears his heart on his sleeve, looks uncomfortable over there, and I can see Ahmen’s feelings echoed in his face.

Apparently, he doesn’t like Akwilla’s recognition of Vikir.

And there’s no way Akwilla doesn’t know that Vikir has noticed.

“Hey, shaman.”

Akwilla turned his head to look at Ahman.

“…Yes, Chief.”

“You don’t like that I’ve accepted that boy as a member of the tribe?”

Akwilla asked bluntly.

Ahmen may be powerful in the tribe, but a chieftain’s authority is absolute.

He immediately recognizes the hint of vulnerability in Akwilla’s words and bows his head deeply.

“Of course not, it’s just that I’m a little concerned about blood of Imperial origin being transfused within the tribe.”

“That is not for a shaman to worry about. All you have to do is make sure the rains are good when they come, the prayers are good when the warriors go hunting, the fires are good when there’s a war, the memorials are good when there’s a death, and the wards are good when there’s a plague.”

At Akwilla’s cut-and-dried words, Ahmen bowed his head deeply.

Behind him, he could see Aiyen clucking his tongue.

Well, whatever.

Akwilla recognized Vikir’s contributions to the hunting frestival and raised his status to official tribe member.

Akwilla glanced down at Vikir’s limp body.

“You seem to have recovered quite a bit, I can’t believe how quickly.”

“Thanks to your care.”

“It’s done. I didn’t take care of anything. If I have any virtue, it’s in my daughter.”

Akwilla glanced away and looked at Aiyen, who stood against the wall.

“….”

Aiyen glanced away from her mother’s gaze and whispered something else.

Finally, Akwilla spoke up.

“Now that you are officially a member of the Ballak, tell me what you want. You are one of my own, and I have not been able to give birth to and raise you, so I will give you something in return.”

When she had finished, Akwilla spoke softly.

“There are many eligible young women in the village. If you wish, I will find one of them and claim her as your mate. Or a slave, if that’s not what you need. I have quite a few girls from other tribes that I’ve captured as prisoners of war.”

There was a brief murmur from outside the tent.

It was the chatter of the village women who had been lined up outside the chieftain’s barracks since dawn.

But Vikir shook his head.

“I appreciate the offer, but the mate is fine.”

Wives and female slaves alike were being offered to increase birth rates, a ploy to capitalize on the human tendency to settle where children are born.

When Vikir rejected the offer, Akwilla seemed to consider for a moment.

“Hmm. You don’t want a woman, do you? That’s unusual. Most of the men among the outsiders want women.”

In truth, most of Ballak’s people were good-looking and beautiful.

Their bodies were built for hunting and training, and their eyes and hair were unusually healthy and vibrant, unlike those of other tribes.

The warriors of the Ballak are unusually attractive compared to the other tribes of the Barbarian.

Thanks to the occasional transfusions of blood from the outside world, they’ve never developed inbreeding diseases.

Perhaps that’s why invaders from the outside often targeted Ballak maidens.

Of course, almost all of them are reduced to wolf’s food by her arrows. …

Meanwhile, Akwilla wrinkled the corners of her nose a little. She seemed to be thinking.

“So, what do you want me to give you, half of the oxbear hide you caught?”

Oxbear hides are a very valuable treasure.

Vikir almost jumped out of his skin when he heard the offer to cut it in half.

Cutting an animal’s hide in half reduces its value to one-tenth of what it is worth, and as someone who knows value, that’s not something I want to see.

Just then.

“…!”

Vikir felt a gaze shoot to his side.

Aiyen was glaring at him intently.

“You didn’t forget what I told you, did you?”

That look, the look that spoke with her eyes.

Akwilla glanced sideways at her daughter, as if she were not used to seeing her like that.

Aiyen is still furiously sending signals to Vikir, unaware that Akwilla has seen her.

Eventually, Vikir speaks up, as Aiyen had urged him to before.

“Material rewards are fine. However, I was wondering if you would be willing to take a bath in the Fountain of Valor?”

Before answering Akwilla’s call, Aiyen had insisted that Vikir mention this as his desired reward.

For the first time, Akwilla frowned.

“…Hmm.”

If even Akwilla, who was quite friendly with Vikir, could react like this, what about the others?

Most of the old men swallowed their grunts in disgust.

Shaman Ah’Heman, who was in the front row, snapped.

“You fool! Who are you to speak in front of me?”

As if he couldn’t take it anymore, Ah’Heman strode forward and knelt before Akwilla.

“Chieftain! For generations, it has been only the proud warriors of Ballak who have been allowed to bathe in the Fountain of Valor!”

The murmuring around them grew louder.

Ahun, standing at the entrance to the barracks, spoke sarcastically.

“The Fountain of Valor is only for those who have proven their strength. How dare you.”

Aiyen, standing on the other side, spoke up.

“Vikir has already proven his strength. He captured an oxbear and submitted it to this hunting festival!”

“Hmph. I guess I was just throwing rocks at him from behind when he was hunting.”

“And you have a back like that from being hit by a rock?”

Ahun’s body began to shake as Aiyen gestured to the bandages and casts wrapped around his waist.

At Akwilla’s question, Vikir thought for a moment, then nodded.

“….The Fountain of Valor. Do you know what it is?”

It is a small spring that flows deep beneath the waters of Ballak’s holiest site, the Tomb of the Champions, where only the bravest and strongest of Ballak’s greatest warriors are buried.

It was said to be blessed by the great ancestors and to cure all internal wounds and traumas by simply taking a dip.

However, the water level is very low, the water takes a long time to collect, and the effects are halved if too many people enter, so the Ballak only allow access to warriors who have earned special recognition from generation to generation.

“Patriarch, that’s too much to ask for, how can you allow an outsider who’s only just arrived to enter the holy grounds…!”

“Still, he’s quite the prospect, having captured an oxbear, so it might not be a bad idea to motivate him for once.”

“Nonsense! Since when did the Fountain of Valor become a place where anyone can soak in it!”

“Heh, but he doesn’t look like he’s even grown up, so we should be nice to him since he’s part of the family.”

The elders around him are also arguing.

Some looked favorably on the capture of the oxbear at a time of need for the entire tribe, while others did not.

Akwilla was secretly tempted to grant Vikir’s request, but she was certainly a little too weak to use the oxbear hunt as a justification.

Some, including Ah’Heman, were less than enthusiastic about having Vikir as a member of the family in the first place, and were even more adamantly opposed to the Fountain of Valor.

Akwilla wanted to grant her daughter’s petition if she could, but it was a bit of a dilemma with the shaman and his unfriendly forces so strongly opposed.

Just then.

Ding, ding, ding, ding.

A loud bell suddenly rang out from the top of the watchtower that stood on the border of the clan’s enclosure, the village.

At the same time, a watchman shouted.

“The outsiders have arrived!”

Something had happened in the village.

Chapter 64

Unfair Trade (2)

◆

“This trade is void.”

Anyway, it’s invalid.

The merchants flinched for a moment as Vikir spoke in Imperial.

It’s natural to be surprised when a raggedy stranger suddenly speaks to you in a familiar language.

Especially when they had just been exchanging curses and foul language.

“Uh… speak Imperial?”

“Did you hear what we just said?”

“Oh, there might have been a misunderstanding.”

“Let us explain. These, these words are just…”

All of the people who were just having a nasty conversation about the color and sexuality of the Ballak natives look away.

Vikir’s eyes widen as he realizes that if he gets caught talking about the color and sex of the Ballak, he’ll be in for a rough ride.

Vikir’s expression was nonchalant.

“You mean insulting Ballak’s warriors with the color of their skin and sexually harassing a woman?”

“Huh! That, that!”

The merchants are flustered.

Vikir kept his face expressionless.

“Not that it matters now.”

Indeed. The merchants were so surprised that Vikir spoke Imperial that they hadn’t thought about what he’d actually said.

Void. The whole deal is off.

Luckily, the merchants’ goods had all been stacked in one place to be sold, so the natives of Ballak could return them to the merchants as they were.

The merchants, in turn, can return the piles of forest products to their wagons.

Upon hearing Vikir’s words, Aiyen sensed something and stopped all trading.

Even the merchants around him looked bewildered.

“No, what’s going on here?” they asked.

“‘We’re not trading, why do we want to buy and lose money?”

“We don’t come here every day, how can we….”

The merchants protested.

Vikir dismissed them quickly.

“Losses? Well, if the trade doesn’t happen, who will?”

Aiyen gave him a puzzled look.

She sidled up to Vikir and whispered softly.

“Look. There are many people in Ballak who are counting down the days until those merchants arrive.”

She was right.

Among the natives of Ballak, I see a girl crying, an old woman stomping her foot impatiently, middle-aged men and elderly women with wistful looks on their faces.

They coveted the merchants and the goods they shared: glass beads, potatoes, corn, and harmonicas, not knowing when they would come again.

Aiyen was controlling the trade, as Vikir had said, and they all looked at each other in silent regret.

But.

“It’s a good attitude to take care of the villagers, but you need to look out for the other side first.”

Vikir’s advice continues.

“…?”

Aiyen’s head snapped up at Vikir’s words, and then.

“…!”

Aiyen’s expression immediately turned to surprise.

While the Ballak’s expression was one of lingering disappointment, that of the merchants on the other side was deadly.

Extreme nervousness made their hands and legs tremble.

Vikir spoke briefly.

“All of your goods are short-lived.”

Most of their trade was vegetables and grain.

Most of these would spoil or rot on the way back.

The Ballak, on the other hand, traded medicines, hides, spices, and other things that don’t change in value over time.

So if a trade fails, the people of Ballak lose very little.

The merchants, on the other hand, would have to carry back what they brought, and the value of their goods would have decreased dramatically in the meantime.

The merchants shuddered and protested.

“If you do this, we won’t come here anymore!”

“Be that as it may. You’re not the only ones who want to come here.”

There was some truth to Vikir’s words.

For when he was well enough to return to Baskerville, he would use Cindywendy to secretly arrange trade with the natives of Ballak.

The merchants were caught between a rock and a hard place.

As they stood there, bewildered, Vikir spoke briefly.

“I know how much these goods fetch locally. If you bargain in good faith, we can resume trade.”

A glimmer of hope appeared on the merchants’ faces.

“How could a mere child know the local prices?”

“‘Hah! The Empire’s commercial laws are very strict.”

“He’s going to leave a lot of money on the table anyway, so why not leave a little less?”

The merchants chuckle amongst themselves.

They decide there’s still room for a few more bargains.

…But.

“Four gold.”

“What?”

“Four gold.”

“No, that’s too….”

“Four gold.”

Vikir knew exactly how much the merchants’ goods were worth.

He also knew perfectly well what Ballak’s goods would eventually fetch if they were to reach the faraway capital of the Empire.

He would….

“I’m the one who set up the underdog city’s commercial code.”

Vikir had been directly or indirectly involved in countless diplomatic and trade affairs during his time as Deputy Magistrate of the Metropolis.

“Chess pieces made from the teeth of hellhounds usually fetch around two million gold a piece, with different prices for kings, queens, bishops, and knights, and billiard balls carved from the horns of oxen are all the rage in the ecliptic these days. They fetch five million gold a piece at auction. Natural red ivory, undyed, can’t be had for ten times that price. And then there’s this goblin chanterelle mushroom here, which has recently become a popular ingredient in new medicines and is almost priceless…..”

The merchants just stand there, mouths agape, as Vikir rattles off the exact local price, wholesale price, retail price, distribution margin, etc. of each trade item in fluent Imperial tongue.

And then. Vikir finishes his calculations.

“I’ll give you a price that’s just right for you, after taking into account transportation, labor, and taxes.”

The asking price is indeed what the consumer wants.

Vikir picked up a pair of antlers, a gnome, and a sea god from the pile of Ballak trade goods and tossed them into the merchants’ wagon.

“This is as much as you can buy with what you have brought.”

Only a tiny fraction of the pile remained.

The merchants’ faces were red with anger, but they had little to argue about.

Vikir’s valuation had been accurate, and they’d actually made quite a bit of money.

In other words, it was a fair deal, with no one getting the short end of the stick.

But for the swindlers, who were expecting to make a fortune, it was a pie in the sky.

I can’t help but be upset that the natives of Ballak were treated so poorly and only received a fair (?) price.

What?

It didn’t end there.

“Okay, now we need to calculate the damages.”

Vikir took back the deer antlers, gourds, and sea gods that he had just placed on the merchants’ carts.

Then he turned to the merchants and held out his palm.

“Give me the money.”

At that, the merchants’ faces went blank.

…Is this a rip-off? Look on their faces.

But Vikir’s judgment is always based on facts.

“I’m asking for severe punitive damages for selling adulterated food and distributing illegal drugs.”

The merchants look stunned.

“What did we do wrong?”

“Don’t you know?”

Vikir stretched out his finger and pointed at the grains and vegetables.

Among the piles of produce were pockets of seeds.

Vikir reached into the pouch and pulled out the seeds.

Thud, thud, thud, thud.

Dumping all the seeds on the ground, Vikir picked up a few of them.

“You lightly roasted them to prevent them from sprouting, didn’t you?”

Several of the merchants turn their heads in surprise.

Yes, they didn’t want the natives of Ballak to farm and become self-sufficient.

They don’t want them to plant seeds and farm for themselves so that they can continue to bring them produce and exploit them.

When the natives of Ballak realized that these were seeds that wouldn’t sprout, they started coming in droves, looking terrified.

Moreover.

“And you’re distributing cheap drugs that the Empire has labeled illegal. You’re out of your mind.”

Vikir pulled out the glass beads and brooches the merchants were giving away for free and crushed them in his hands.

The glass beads were said to bring good dreams when worn to bed.

Passthis…

Inside was a small amount of white powder.

It leaked out naturally through the tiny holes on the surface of the glass ball.

If you keep it by your side, you will naturally fall asleep and have good dreams.

However, it is actually a low-grade narcotic that causes severe damage to the body if left for a long time.

The glass beads, brooches, necklaces, perfumes, cosmetics, etc. were all made of similar materials.

Vikir’s eyes flashed.

“Did the Morgue or the Baskervilles tolerate this?”

It was possible, he thought.

It would be good for the Empire in the long run if Ballak’s warriors were not only drugged and weakened by cheap drugs, but if they also produced deformed children in the next generation.

But Vikir had no intention of acting to benefit the Empire or the Baskervilles.

It would be far more beneficial for Vikir to join their side in order to stabilize himself here in Ballak’s village and learn archery.

Vikir smashed all the glasswork that leaked drugs and picked out all the boiled and roasted seeds.

The merchants’ faces grew bluer and bluer with time.

Some of the merchants, including Lord Smuggler, were furious.

“Who are you to interfere with this? This is a sacred trade, sanctioned by the God of the Forest himself!”

“This is a sacred trade, sanctioned by the God of the Forest!”

“Even the shaman of Ballak blesses us on behalf of the God of the Forest…!”

The merchants keep bringing up the forest gods, but that’s only for the natives of Ballak, and Vikir’s tan hides his skin color, but he’s still an Imperial, so it doesn’t matter.

“It is not the forest gods who rule here, but the Forest Department of Baskerville.”

The merchants all swallowed hard at Vikir’s nonchalant reply.

It was true, but they hadn’t expected to hear it from a native Ballak.

Vikir poured himself another drink.

“If you continue to whine about your ridiculous superstitions, I will have you brought before the judiciary of Underdog City.”

There is no sound a barbarian can’t make.

The merchants retorted, stunned but steadfast.

“We’ve already been inspected for food safety by Underdog City’s Food and Drug Administration!”

“That was done under the previous deputy, and with the new deputy, we’ll have to get the revised laws and go through a new process accordingly. From what I can see, some of the items you’re selling don’t meet the current laws.”

“Yeah, who the hell do you think you are to tell us what the law is?”

The merchants shouted.

Vikir’s eyes widened at that.

“…Do you think I don’t know the laws?”

“Of course you don’t! How could you possibly know the new laws that have been added? They are very strict and demanding!”

Lord Smuggler, the head of the merchants, shouted back at Vikir in a pouty manner.

“‘What black barbarian knows about the Vikir Special Laws’?”

Hearing that, Vikir gave a single, dry laugh.

But since he couldn’t reveal his identity here, he decided to just assume that his laws were still working just fine.

“Anyway, this is the end of this trade. You may consider yourself fortunate that I have not taken your life, and now leave.”

It was Aiyen, not Vikir, who had the last word.

She was furious to learn that the secret plague that had been circulating within the village was not a disease, or a genetic disorder, or a curse, but a drug brought in from the outside.

Some of the warriors were ready to shoot arrows at a moment’s notice, and the merchants were forced to flee.

Naturally, Vikir became the most talked-about man in town for his role in this trade.

It was a rare example of a slave turned hero.

◆

When Vikir returned to his tent after the merchants had scurried away.

…Boom!

Something flew and landed in front of his tent.

It was a smoked boar hind leg.

Vikir turned his head toward the direction the meat had come from, curious.

There stood an unexpected figure, his face flushed.

“…Hmmm. Hmm.”

It was Ahun.

He tore his gaze away from Vikir and looked at the distant mountains.

“Well, thanks for that. For your help.”

“…?”

Before Vikir could respond, Ahun shouted.

“How long is he going to be out of shape? Get well soon, so I can beat the shit out of him… or wrestle him!”

By the time he finished, Ahun was red up to his ears.

“Eat it all and get well soon!”

With that, he turned and walked away.

He left behind a large piece of the boar he had killed.

“What’s wrong with that one?”

Some mushrooms can cause intense visions and illusions when eaten.

If Ahun had eaten it, he might have experienced….

‘Take him somewhere quiet, no mice or birds will know….’

Vikir was thinking to himself.

“Hey. Slave.”

Someone taps him on the shoulder.

He turns and sees Aiyen standing there with a huge grin on his face.

“I’m not a slave anymore.”

“No. You are a slave for life. My slave.”

Vikir frowns at Aiyen’s insistence.

Regardless, Aiyen continued with what he wanted to say.

“Ahun, that bastard. He’s not the same when it comes to his sister. He’s a nice enough guy for a big brother.”

…Sister?

When Vikir gave him a puzzled look, Aiyen explained further.

“The girl you helped today is his sister. Her name is Aheul.”

After some thought, Vikir remembered a girl named Aheul.

The girl in her early teens who had lined up outside the chieftain’s barracks at dawn to become Vikir’s wife.

The girl who had been sexually harassed by Merchant when she had brought a sunbeetle larva to trade with the merchants today.

Aiyen continued.

“Aheul has always been weak. I was worried that she was getting weaker and weaker due to an unknown illness, but now that I think about it, it’s probably because of the glass beads brought by those merchants.”

He had a point.

If it hadn’t been for Vikir, Aheul would have continued to trade with those merchants, and his body would have gotten worse and worse.

She would have become an idler, given birth to a deformed child, or even died.

So Vikir’s actions in this trade could be said to have saved all of Ballak.

“Damn it. I was a fool to let those merchants go. I let them go because it’s a warrior’s shame to kill cowards who don’t resist, but… in hindsight, I should have just killed them and gotten rid of them.”

Aiyen gritted his teeth.

Just as Vikir was about to part his lips to say something in Moorish.

Hudadak-

A Ballak warrior rushed over.

“A message from the chieftain, all warriors assemble!”

This seems pretty urgent.

When Aiyen asked what was going on, the warrior replied.

“It seems that the merchants we chased away during the day are up to something nefarious! They’re coming for us at night!”

Then.

Aiyen’s expression changed instantly.

Vikir hasn’t seen her smile this brightly since he’s been here.

Chapter 65

Unfair Trade (3)

◆

It was a night when the dark clouds swallowed the moon whole.

Lord Smuggler and the Merchant Alliance gritted their teeth and made their way through the jungle.

“Eek! Damn mosquitoes! I’m sick of this damn jungle.”

They grunted in exhaustion.

They made their way back to base camp, swatting at the mosquitoes with the palms of their hands as they clung to them with their freakishly long stingers.

There, a group of rugged-looking men gathered, waiting for the traders.

The furry man in the front row smirked at Lord Smuggler.

“By the looks of your wounds, it didn’t go well, did it?”

“….”

Lord Smuggler didn’t answer, instead shifting his pack nervously.

The men nearby chuckled.

“See? The Ballak are not to be talked to.”

“What kind of business is it to trade with such beasts?”

“Just kill them and enslave them all. Savages.”

They were a mercenary group of ex-convicts, escaped prisoners, and deserters wanted by the Empire.

Lord Smuggler warned the mercenaries.

“Don’t take the Ballak lightly, they’re not easy to defeat in combat, and you’re new to the region, so you may not realize it….”

“Oh never mind, if you’re so scared, why did you bring us here in the first place, didn’t you bring us here to upset the deal if it went bad?”

“No, well, we’ve got escorts from the demons, and we’d rather… than go to all-out war with the Ballak.”

Lord Smuggler pursed his lips in concern.

But even he, who normally would not have dreamed of an all-out war with the Ballak, could not resist the sight of the vast amount of trade goods left behind in the Ballak’s village.

Even the mercenaries and some of the merchants who were new to the jungle began to raise their voices.

“You can’t just waste money like this! I spent a lot of money in the merchant guild’s auction to participate in this trade!”

“Didn’t we agree to pay for our protection as a percentage of the gross profits of the trade? Do you think I protected you from demons for a pittance like this?”

“What’s wrong with Ballak? We ambush them in the dead of night, set them on fire, take their goods, and that’s it!”

Veteran merchants who have traded with the Ballak a few times know the fears of the Ballak warriors.

But even they were greedy for the goods they had left behind in Ballak’s village.

In the end, the vote was close to majority, with a few silent votes in favor.

Lord Smuggler spoke, his sword half-sheathed at his waist.

“Very well, now that it’s getting dark, let’s go quietly and take inventory, and I don’t think I need to tell you who we’re going to kill first.”

The faces of the mercenaries and merchants around him changed.

They see it too. Who ruined their trade today.

“You mean that sneaky little bastard? Okay, we got it.”

“I’ll be the first to put a knife in that cocky black kid’s ass.”

“But he didn’t look black to me. His palms were black. Usually black people have white palms, don’t they?”

“Maybe he’s from the Empire? That would explain why he spoke Imperial so well.”

All the men, including Lord Smuggler, chimed in at once.

Their spears and swords were sharpened, and they were ready to burn everything to the ground.

And then.

In the darkness, they performed their rituals.

Not much of a ritual, really, just a cigarette.

Chick.

The cigarette was lit.

One of the mercenaries takes the cigarette in his mouth and strikes a match to the end of it.

Next, the mercenary next to him takes the match and lights a cigarette.

Soon, he’s about to blow it out.

The third mercenary reaches out and stops him, annoyed.

“Oh come on, blow out the match, there’s still more to burn.”

“Come on, you’re a newbie, you don’t know what you’re doing.”

The first mercenary and the second mercenary sneered at the third mercenary.

“Don’t you know that there’s a saying in war that a single match shouldn’t be shared by three people?”

“What? Is there such a thing?”

“There is. A match can only be lit by two people.”

The third mercenary snorted.

“I don’t believe in that shit.”

He quickly puts the cigarette in his mouth to the match, fearing it will go out.

The next moment, the match that ignited the three cigarettes goes out.

…Puck!

A dull sound echoed through the darkness.

The third mercenary’s cigarette was gone. And his head, too.

The first mercenary and the second mercenary stood there, covered in a hot liquid that splashed into their faces.

Blood. The blood of their decapitated comrades.

Before they could even realize it.

…Puck! …Puck!

Two more arrows flew by.

The arrows were aimed at the cigarettes and struck the mercenaries squarely in the mouths or throats, separating their heads from their bodies.

“Hic!?”

Lord Smuggler quickly threw the cigarette to the ground.

Then.

…Puck!

The cigarette on the ground was instantly struck by an arrow.

The arrows were powerful enough to blow up the surrounding area upon impact, and they rained down from the darkness of the water like a shower of rain.

“Cigarettes! Drop the cigarettes!”

An arrow lodged in the mouth of the mercenary captain, who was shouting instructions.

The mercenary captain lost most of his head, saving only his uvula and lower jaw, and collapsed to the bottom of the floodwaters.

Anyone else who screamed, even for a moment, at the suddenness of the situation was struck by arrows in the mouth and throat.

The mercenaries, who had numbered over a hundred, were quickly cut in half, then in half again.

In a matter of seconds.

…Meanwhile.

Beyond the rain of arrows, Ballak’s archers grinded their teeth.

“First cigarette, position, second cigarette, distance, third cigarette.”

Huntmaster Aiyen ordered.

…Ping!

Aiyen, who had just sent an arrow flying, turned his head and smiled.

“So there it is. Crazy bastards trying to fight us first.”

The Ballak are basically a fighting people.

There’s no way they’re going to avoid a fight on foot when they’re the ones who start it in the first place.

Aiyen sniped at the mercenaries and merchants in the distance, looking pleased, refreshed, and exhilarated.

They had a knack for picking out the most faint of lights, the faintest of sounds.

They had a knack for picking out the faintest of lights, the brightness of a cigarette, and driving their flesh into it.

The same was as of sound.

Whether the words have left the mouth, are still near the uvula, or have not yet departed the lungs, the arrow will always hit the spot where the sound resides.

For a moment, Aiyen fired her bow with joy, but then Vikir tugged on her arm.

“Enough.”

Aiyen’s eyes widened.

“…What?”

“Don’t kill them all. Spare some of them.”

“Why should I?”

Aiyen frowned. Then he spoke.

“You don’t mean forgiveness or tolerance, do you? Words like that, from a crumbling empire….”

“Not that.”

Vikir held up a hand, cutting Aiyen off.

He stared coldly at the few lights flickering in the darkness.

“ …I’m saying that because with a group that size, there’s a good chance there’s a backup group.”

Vikir had purposely left the survivors behind, planning to map out their escape route.

And the location of any base camps that might be in the rear.

Aiyen paused slightly at Vikir’s demeanor, which was far harder and sharper than her own.

Then, a smile forms at the corners of her mouth.

“…Good, I got in.”

I’ve never been able to figure out what she’s giving passing marks for, Vikir thought.

◆

Vikir’s guess was correct.

An arrow pierced his shoulder, and Lord Smuggler scrambled to his feet and made his way through a narrow canyon between rock and boulder.

Behind him, in a spacious campsite, were the remnants of the waiting mercenaries.

A hundred or so men emerged from the barracks to cover the defeated soldiers.

“We’re confident in a hand-to-hand combat!”

“Arrows will be useless against our shields!”

“Aura users, come out!”

“Mages, assemble! Shields to block the arrows!”

There were many mages among the mercenaries, and soon shields were set up to block the arrows.

But.

…PING!

This time, something rather strange began to fly.

Several arrows fell from above in a parabolic arc, with ropes hanging from their nocks.

And at the end of each of those ropes was a large wooden barrel.

“…Oil?”

The mercenaries muttered in despair.

A few arrows join forces and bring the barrels down, one by one.

Boom! Boom!

As soon as they hit the ground or hit the shields, the barrels shatter, scattering wood splinters and spraying oil everywhere.

Then a hail of flames began to ignite the oil.

Crackle!

In an instant, the inferno had completely surrounded the mercenaries’ base camp.

Even if they managed to escape the fire, their food, water, medicines, and weapons were all burning inside the barracks, and it was now impossible to escape the jungle alive.

Dead.

Those who are unlucky enough to be dead, and those who are even unluckier enough not to be dead already, share the same fate.

Lord Smuggler was shaking with rage.

“Tying a rope to several arrows and sending a barrel of oil flying? Do these bastards have such brains?”

Lord Smuggler had seen Ballak’s archers fight many times, but this was the first time he knew they could fight like this.

If only he had known how clever his enemies were, he wouldn’t have picked a fight in the first place.

Right then.

As Lord Smuggler floundered in the flames, something entered his vision.

Vikir.

He could be seen standing still beyond the searing flames.

Lord Smuggler gritted his teeth.

“You bastard, did you set this up too!”

“……Should I say you have a keen eye?”

Vikir said, looking around.

All around them were bodies, flames, death, and explosions.

It was a mockery that if he had been quicker, he wouldn’t be in this situation in the first place.

Lord Smuggler’s eyes rolled back in his head as he heard the words.

“I’ll kill you, you bastard!”

At that moment.

Vikir picked up something.

It was a bow and arrow.

Ping-!

The arrow, which flew with some force, stuck into Lord Smuggler’s lower abdomen.

“Uh-huh!”

It hit him in an obscure spot. A spot that wouldn’t kill him immediately, but would still be quite painful and deadly.

“…Gosh, I wasn’t exactly aiming for that.”

Vikir cleared his throat apologetically.

He’d learned archery from Aiyen, but he still felt he wasn’t good enough.

Kirik.

Sorry is sorry, and regardless, Vikir draws another shot.

Lord Smuggler stretched out his bloodied hand and waved it in anger.

“Now, wait a minute, you can’t kill me, or you’ll be terribly sorry! I’m serious!”

“Why is that?”

Vikir asked, and Lord Smuggler dug into his bosom and pulled out a bloody piece of paper.

“This, this is a prospecting permit from the city of Underdog! It’s real! It’s not a forgery! It has the stamp of the newly appointed Deputy Magistrate! I have the Baskervilles behind me!”

Lord Smuggler’s words were true, for now.

He was one of the researchers officially licensed to explore.

Vikir paused for a moment, then said.

“Bring it over here.”

Vikir gestured toward Lord Smuggler.

Lord Smuggler winced in pain, but took the bloody license and held it out in front of Vikir.

With his other hand, he reached for the dagger hidden in his waistband.

Just then.

Tsk-tsk.

Vikir wiped the tan from his face.

At that moment, Lord Smuggler’s eyes widened to tears.

“Da, are you…!?”

Recognizing Vikir’s identity, Lord Smuggler was so surprised that he dropped his dagger to the ground.

Staring at the blade on the ground, Vikir smirked dryly.

Then he said.

“I take it back.”

He wiped his fingers across his face and drew an X across the stigma on the permit.

The permit became legally invalid in real time before Smuggler’s eyes.

Having revoked the permit’s authority by tampering with it himself, Vikir finally throws it into the flames and burns it.

At the same time.

…Puck!

An arrow hits Lord Smuggler right in the middle of his forehead.

And then.

…Puck! …puck! …puck! …puck! …puck!

Four more arrows lodge in roughly the same place.

Lord Smuggler’s skull was split several times, almost beyond recognition.

“He was a sour one.”

Aiyen snorted, coming to stand beside Vikir.

Just then.

“Captain, it’s time to get out!”

Ahun called from behind the flames.

Aiyen quickly picked up Vikir and carried her like a princess.

He climbs onto the back of the wolf Bakira, who is waiting behind him, and they are off like the wind.

Behind them, the shouts of the surviving mercenaries and merchants echoed in the air.

“The Ballak are coming! They don’t seem to be outnumbered! We have a chance if we give chase!”

“Hahaha! We’re almost out of flames! The fact that they attacked with fire means they’re not confident in their own strength!”

“We’re alive! We just need to retrieve the rest of the supplies! We’re going to counterattack the Ballak!”

Hearing that, Aiyen smirked in disbelief.

“Idiots. They think we started the fire for them.”

“…You’ll find out soon enough.”

Vikir replied coldly.

And then.

Sssssssss…

The water reacted.

The sound of leaves in a wide area being swept in one direction in unison.

Something huge was coming through the darkness toward them.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

A heavy blackness, even heavier than the darkness, casting its shadow across the water.

Explosions, bright lights, and high-pitched shouting erupted from all corners of the merchants’ and mercenaries’ base camps.

And there is one being here that seems to respond to the untimely commotion they create.

The Madam with Eight Legs.

A legendary piece of tales. The moment an untold horror takes an interest in this side.

“Put out the fire! If you put out the fire, we can turn the tables…!?”

“Counterattack! If we counterattack…!?”

“Huh? Wasn’t there something on the other side, I just saw something big…!?”

“Aaaaahhhh help me…!?”

The screams die down, one by one. Fading away.

Aiyen and Vikir clung to Bakira’s back and ran with all their might.

….

Until they could no longer hear anything behind them.

Chapter 66

Unfair Trade (4)

◆

Vikir became a Ballak hero that day.

He had discovered the plague that was secretly weakening Ballak’s warriors was actually a cheap narcotic that foreign merchants were secretly distributing, giving them a huge advantage in trade that they had been losing.

What’s more, he took his flaming arrows one step further and developed an oil barrel arrow strategy, making him an instant hero.

His hospitality was compounded by the fact that he had already earned favor with the tribe for solving their food shortage by hunting down an oxbear that only the bravest warriors could hunt.

Is that the reason?

“I will allow you to bathe in the Fountain of Valor.”

Chief Akwilla was happy to grant Vikir’s request.

However, she wondered how she could grant her daughter’s request when she was so persistent.

With such a good cause, how could anyone say no?

Even the cranky old men who had initially objected were now looking at Vikir with smiles on their faces.

“….”

Only one of them, the shaman Ah’Heman, stroked his beard in disapproval.

The shaman had a history of misdiagnosing drug-addled warriors as “cursed”.

While Vikir’s work has made the Ballak tribe brighter and more energetic, it has also made things quite difficult for Ah’Heman himself.

His position was much smaller and his voice much weaker than before.

This is why he is unable to speak out against Vikir’s decision to enter the Fountain of Valor.

Aiyen leaned in with a wide grin on his face and put his mouth to Vikir’s ear.

“….”

And then she says nothing.

Vikir frowned and turned his head.

“Do you have something to say?”

“Nothing.”

“Then why are you putting your mouth in someone else’s ear.”

“Just. I wanted to.”

Aiyen still smirked in an unintentional way.

She opened her mouth again.

“Well, while you’re at it, why don’t you say a few words?”

“What.”

“I’m thinking, ahhhhhhh, that guy over there seems to be an imposter.”

“Why?”

“…I just have a hunch.”

Aiyen’s instincts, honed by hunting, were so sharp that he could sometimes predict outcomes without any evidence or foreshadowing.

Vikir agreed with Aiyen.

The only difference was that he was able to use his reason, not just his instincts, to spot something fishy about Ah’Heman.

He had described the drugs the merchants distributed as a plague, a curse that could only be cured by shamanic rituals.

In this way, he established his authority as a shaman and grew his position.

This was despite the fact that his granddaughter, Aheul, was suffering from complications from drugs.

Also, Vikir still remembered what the merchants had said so casually the last time.

“You don’t know what you’re doing! This is a sacred trade!”

“This is a sacred trade, bowed to by the God of the Forest!”

‘Even the Shaman of Ballak blesses us on behalf of the God of the Forest…!

The last one cut off mid-sentence, but the sharp-eyed Vikir had already gotten a sense of what was going on.

Vikir translates the merchants’ words into native language, and Aiyen’s eyebrows shoot up in unison.

“We can’t let this bastard get away with this! I treated him like a freebie, and now he’s stuck with a foreign power…!”

“Calm down. You’re still just mad. You don’t have any hard evidence.”

“Then you’re just going to stand by and watch!”

Aiyen’s heart pounded, and Vikir spoke up after a moment of silence.

Vikir spoke in a low voice, and Aiyen’s eyes narrowed as she listened.

“ …You want me to do that?”

“Yes. If we wait a little longer, it will reveal its own tail.”

“Hmm. That doesn’t sound like a bad plan.”

Aiyen thought for a moment.

But it was not in her nature to think for long.

“I see. I suppose nothing is lost by doing as you say. Let’s just focus on what’s important right now.”

Vikir nodded at Aiyen’s words.

As she said, getting his body back on track was the most important thing right now.

◆

Afterward.

Night came, and a beautiful full moon rose.

The jungle seemed to have forgotten yesterday’s bloodshed in a single day.

As the bright, round moon rose, Depht opened his mouth as if to swallow it.

Sssssss…

A light breeze rustled the leaves.

Then, with a strange shifting of the earth’s crust, the rock cracked and hot water began to bubble up from beneath it.

The Fountain of Valor.

Blessed by Adonai, the archer god of Ballak’s distant past.

It is a holy place that few of Ballak’s warriors are allowed to enter.

Vikir stood alone in front of it.

In the depths of the hot, steaming waters, some sulfurous gas seems to be boiling.

In the shallows, some small animals were the first to arrive and take a dip.

They didn’t move as Vikir approached.

There seemed to be an unwritten rule that animals entering the hot springs here, regardless of their food chain, did not bare their teeth to each other.

Vikir took off all his clothes.

He closed his eyes, pushed aside the rabbits, hares, and hedgehogs that were crowding his body, and sat down.

“…!”

The effect was truly eye-opening.

As I entered the hot spring water, my internal body was quickly stabilizing.

“That old shaman wasn’t fussing for nothing, I guess he wanted to come in.”

His mana became more pure, and the bones and muscles in his body settled into place.

Perhaps Baskerville had a similar effect to the River Styx flowing within it.

The Spring of the Valor is only slightly less effective than the River Styx, but the better part is that there is no age limit on its use.

The only downside is that it’s only available once or twice a year, on full moon nights.

As Vikir soaked in the hot springs, he thought about this and that.

It had been a while since he’d been here.

I wonder how Baskerville is doing without him, how the Underdog City is doing.

…Well, probably very well.

‘Though Mr. Chihuahua is probably throwing a tantrum.’

Vikir smirked and turned away.

At that moment, something completely unexpected came into view.

Something so unexpected that even the mighty Vikir was stunned.

“Surprised?”

Before he knew it, Aiyen was soaking in the hot springs beside Vikir.

She leaned forward toward Vikir, smiling broadly, not wearing a single thread of silk.

Seeing this, Vikir thought to himself.

‘Even I, who have lived through the Age of Destruction, did not sense her approach. I must learn this stealthy move.’

It would serve him well in the future.

While Vikir mulled over his strategy.

“….”

Aiyen sighed, disappointed at Vikir’s lack of response.

“Have you become such a man that the sight of a woman’s nakedness has no effect on you?”

“Don’t you go around naked all the time?”

“Not quite. There’s a difference between naked and barely covered.”

What’s the difference?

Vikir didn’t know what to say in response, so he simply turned his head back in the direction he’d come from.

Then, slipping up beside him and leaning back, Aiyen held up a flask and spoke.

“Give thanks to Adonai. He found this hot spring.”

“Adonai. I recognize him.”

“Yeah? No wonder. He was the only one who could stand toe-to-toe with the ‘Madame’. Now that you are a young Ballak, you should have respect for him. And be proud to be his descendant.”

Vikir was struck by the words in two ways.

The first was that the Ballaks viewed the concept of descendants not in terms of blood, but in terms of spirit.

The second was that the archer Adonai was able to take on Madam Eight-Legs.

“An archer who can fight that monster single-handedly.”

How high a level does one have to be to be able to do that, which is still a long way off for the current Vikir.

Then.

Aiyen turned her head.

The tip of her clever nose was within inches of Vikir’s shoulder.

Aiyen spoke, her face flushed with alcohol.

“Those merchants.”

“Hmm?”

“I knew they were going on a rampage.”

Aiyen’s face turned even redder as he remembered bargaining for diamonds and two ears of corn.

“I had a vague idea, but it’s nice to get a good kick in the ass this time. I’m not used to getting my ass kicked. Even if you hadn’t told me, I’d have flipped it at some point.”

“I know.”

Vikir gave a small laugh.

Then Aiyen frowned.

“Don’t laugh. I knew it. It’s common knowledge that diamonds cost more than corn in the Empire.”

“How much more expensive do you think it will be?”

Vikir asked, and Aiyen rolled her eyes for a moment.

Then, she spoke, sounding slightly unconfident.

“One diamond… is worth at least ten ears of corn, isn’t it?”

“….”

“Or twenty?”

“….”

“…Thirty?”

Vikir laughed.

When he told Aiyen how much a diamond was worth in the empire, and how many ears of corn it was worth, Aiyen was horrified.

“You’re crazy,” she said, “a piece of stone is worth nothing, and corn is edible!”

“Isn’t it pretty when it glitters?”

“More sparkling than the dawn dew.”

“It’s hard, so it lasts forever.”

“If you scratch it, it breaks, if you hit it, it splits, if you set it on fire, it burns. What is eternal?”

As Aiyen spoke, even Vikir was at a loss for words.

What is it that makes the difference between civilization and barbarism?

Vikir pondered for a moment, something he didn’t usually do, on such trivial matters.

Meanwhile.

“….”

While Vikir was lost in thought, Aiyen was thinking about something else entirely.

In fact, she was going to see this through to the end tonight.

It’s a bit of an ego thing to ask someone to pick you as a mate, so I wanted to do something naturally(?) in a natural(?) place and in a natural atmosphere(?)., and just go through the motions.

‘He’s cleaned up, his reputation in the village is good, he’s not bad for a husband, and he’s going to stay there today and heal his body so that he’s good enough for his family, and then the rest will take care of itself.’

Her mother, Akwilla, had given her similar advice.

So Aiyen had taken the plunge and brought her favorite drink to bathe beside Vikir.

But.

“But doesn’t your presence halve the mystical effects of the hot springs? Why did you come in? Surely the chief said only I should come in?”

Vikir is now sitting there arguing about this.

Aiyen blurted out in disbelief.

“ …Does it matter now? A true Ballak doesn’t argue about such trivialities.”

“It doesn’t matter, but I’m just asking, not arguing, but just to be sure. If you don’t want to answer, you don’t have to.”

Vikir replied with a nonchalant expression, and when he turned away again, Aiyen’s brow rose.

“ …Show me what it is to be sure?”

A moment.

…Boom!

There was a splash.

Aiyen jumped to his feet and snapped at Vikir.

Vikir’s expression was still nonchalant, but his pupils were dilated with a hint of surprise.

Seeing that, Aiyen grinned wickedly and climbed on top of Vikir’s body.

“You shall remain still, slave.”

“….”

“This master will take care of….”

At that very moment.

A crackle, a crackle, a crackle!

A myriad of splashes erupted from beyond the spring.

A few shadows begin to creep through the steam.

“Wow- it’s the Master!”

“Brother Vikir!”

A group of children began to rush in from nowhere.

“????”

Aiyen looked up, dazed.

Vikir, pinned beneath her, turned her head as well.

Ballak’s children had been swarming into the hot springs for some reason.

Each and every one of them was sick from the side effects of the drugs the merchants were selling.

Naked, the children scurried toward Aiyen and Vikir.

“Master, let’s play!”

Aiyen cried out.

“Hey, you two, you’re halving the mystical effects of the hot springs! Who told you to come in here!”

“The patriarch-oh!”

When the children replied in a stammering voice, Aiyen slapped her forehead with the palm of her hand.

She was being played by his mother.

Even by her mother.

“You’re talking differently. You said earlier that a true Ballak doesn’t argue about such petty matters…”

Vikir pointed out with a serious face.

Aiyen sighed deeply.

The children were already playing with the rabbits, hedgehogs, and squirrels that had come in earlier.

Vikir is soaking in the hot springs, just trying to recover.

Aiyen, having given up on everything, opened his arms to Vikir.

“Welcome to officially become a member of the Ballak.”

She doesn’t know what else to say.

Chapter 68

Blood Relatives (2)

◆

After hearing the report, Aiyen frowned.

“ …You mean she’s still out there?”

For the past two years, Camus Morgue had been steadily searching all over the surface of the water.

In the name of exterminating barbarians and searching for lands, no one knows what her true purpose is.

Except for one person. Aiyen.

‘Obvious.’

I didn’t have to ask, I could relate to her purpose.

She’s looking for a man who disappeared two years ago.

Vikir.

Aiyen remembered the first time he’d met Vikir.

The little boy who had saved her from dying in a cage. She hadn’t forgotten his face since then.

But when she saw him again, he had another woman in his arms.

The woman in his arms was Camus, and she had not forgotten the boy and had come back to this dreadful watery place.

He was determined to find him alive, or at least to retrieve his corpse.

She searches for Vikir with a strand of hope, an expectation she can’t let go of, and an unfulfilled lament.

Her persistence and determination over the course of two years is something that makes Aiyen’s tongue curl.

“If you came for the rubies, you should go back for the rubies. You’re a pain in the ass.”

Aiyen crossed his arms and was silent for a moment.

He was trying to decide if he should tell Vikir this story or not.

◆

In the jungle. Aiyen retraced Vikir’s steps.

She soon found him ahead of her, stalking his prey.

Aiyen rode up to Vikir on the back of the wolf Bakira.

Vikir was measuring the depth of the muddy marks.

“Mushuhushu, the water snake. It’s a very old and large one. If we catch it, it will feed the entire village for at least three days.”

Vikir knew his prey’s size, weight, direction of travel, location, age, health, and even its current mood.

All of this he had learned from the hunters of Ballak.

“….”

Aiyen stared at Vikir in disbelief.

Vikir had changed a lot in the past two years.

He still had his cute face, but his aura was much more commanding.

Two years ago, he could still pretend to do anything by himself, but now he was more experienced than ever.

As such, the boy was definitely becoming a man.

‘Indeed, the woman of Morgue is unforgettable. What a man he is.

Aiyen nodded.

As the next leader of the hostile faction, but a woman before that, she could sympathize with her sentiments.

Aiyen opened her mouth to speak.

She didn’t know why, but there was a slight tremor at the end of her voice.

“…Look, slave.”

She hadn’t stopped calling Vikir that even after he’d been shaved.

Vikir didn’t particularly care, so he answered without looking back.

“What?”

Aiyen asked, after a slight hesitation.

“What was it like where you came from?”

“…?”

Vikir was silent for a moment at Aiyen’s question.

Where I used to live.

Did he mean Baskerville, or the world before the regression?

Vikir answered by blurring the two places together.

“Hell.”

Aiyen scratched her head at that answer.

Then she asked what she really wanted to ask.

“Do you want to go back to where you came from?”

“….”

At that, Vikir paused and looked back.

At this point, Vikir did a small flinch.

“Why do you ask that, and with such a strange look on your face?”

Aiyen felt a little embarrassed, not knowing what expression she was making.

In fact, even at this moment, she was hesitating.

Should she tell the story or not? Should she tell him that the Morgans were looking for Vikir?

She hesitated, then closed her eyes tightly.

She swallowed hard and said.

“I don’t want to lie or hide anything.”

“…?”

“‘She’ is looking for you.”

I said it, finally.

Aiyen balled her fists into tight knots.

Hiding things, lying, and being watched were usually her least favorite things.

And even more so, she didn’t want to do it to Vikir.

As she spoke the words out loud, Aiyen felt a mixture of relief and frustration.

What if Vikir told her he was going to leave her? Should he do it by the tribe’s laws? Was it even possible?

Thoughts raced through his mind.

Then.

Vikir’s answer came back.

“I’m not going back.”

A short answer. With those words, Aiyen felt the power that had been so tightly woven into his body suddenly loosen.

A warm glow filled every inch of his body as the energy drained away.

“…You, really?”

“Yes.”

Vikir nodded.

Why would he go back?

If he went back, he would have fully regained his former powers.

At the very least, it would have to be when he could hide his powers perfectly from Hugo’s notice.

“…And who is she?”

Vikir frowned for a moment.

Was he referring to Morgue’s Camus?

If so, he should be grateful. She still remembers the grace that saved her life.

‘She’s more loyal than I thought. Or is this some sort of diplomatic gesture?’

Vikir closed his eyes and thought about it.

If the Morgue were looking for her, it meant they were still within Baskerville’s territory.

If the Baskervilles were willing to allow Morgue’s search party to enter the depths, it would mean that he had not yet been forgotten by his current family.

Furthermore, the alliance between Morgue and Baskerville would have been strengthened.

Perhaps that’s why they have an annual event where they find themselves, formally or otherwise.

He could sense that the situation outside was complicated and tense.

Sooner or later, Vikir thought, he would have to sneak out of the depths.

Just then, Aiyen spoke up, her voice sounding much lighter.

“Oh, by the way. I have something else for you.”

She pulled an object from her bosom.

It was the dagger left behind by the mysterious intruders mentioned in the last report.

“Do you know anything about this sigil?”

It was a dagger with a sigil, large snake on it.

Vikir’s eyes narrowed at the sight of it.

“I know of it. It’s a famous mark.”

It was the emblem of a certain family in the Empire.

“Leviathan, the Extremist.”

One of the seven great houses of the Empire, alongside the Ironblades of Baskerville, the Mages of Morgue, the Quovadis of Faith, the Bourgeois of Tycoon, and others.

But why would it be found here in the depths at this time of year?

Vikir’s head began to spin rapidly.

“Do you mind if I keep this?”

“Well, do as you please.”

Aiyen nodded readily.

Vikir took the dagger with the snake on it.

Just then.

[Gurgling… gurgling!]

An unpleasant cry came from somewhere.

Vikir and Aiyen turned to find themselves in a muddy mangrove forest.

A large mass was crawling through the gnarled roots.

A lungfish, a fish that breathed with two lungs.

It crawled through the mud, its smooth, scale-free body oozing sticky mucus.

It was a fish that wasn’t even considered food because of its enormous size, over eight meters long, unpleasant appearance, and cries.

Aiyen frowned in disgust.

“It’s definitely the rainy season, with all those things running around.”

“If there are big ones around, it must mean… that this rainy season is long.”

Vikir nodded in agreement.

The muddy ground bore the unmistakable tracks of giant lungfish.

Aiyen pointed to a rotting, fallen tree.

Dozens of meters up in the air, the tree’s rungs hung with dried aquatic vegetation.

“Last year, during the rainy season, the water was up there.”

“It might be higher this time.”

When it rains, the water rises unimaginably fast.

The lungfish know this and crawl out from under the mud in advance.

The moment.

“…!”

The eagle-eyed Aiyen had spotted something.

He could see something sticking out of the body of the giant lungfish he had just crawled over.

It was a harpoon.

“‘Look at that?”

Aiyen moved immediately.

She shot an arrow through its head, killing it, and then drew a knife and sliced open its stomach.

A half-digested human figure emerged from its stomach.

Aiyen’s expression hardened.

“They’re Rokoko.”

Brave men who live on the blood and milk of bears.

They were rivals to the Ballak and the second most powerful tribe on the depths.

They had a cannibalistic culture, and every tribe in the jungle feared them.

Except for the Ballak.

Vikir spoke bluntly.

“Does the fact that they have entered Ballak’s territory mean… war?”

“Well, I don’t think so.”

Aiyen glanced at the harpoon embedded in the lungfish’s body.

The harpoon hadn’t been driven in from the outside, but had protruded from the inside out.

In other words, the Rokoko hunter wasn’t trying to hunt the lungfish, but the lungfish was trying to hunt the Rokoko hunter.

As it swallowed the hunter, the harpoon the hunter was holding pierced the lungfish’s stomach wall and protruded outside its body.

But one question remains.

Lungfish are big, but they’re also skinny and slow, so they couldn’t have eaten Rokoko’s seasoned hunter.

Moreover, the condition of the skeleton suggested that the hunter was a young man, perhaps just entering his twenties.

Aiyen set her jaw.

“I wonder, why was this guy eaten by a lungfish? Lungfish are basically stupid beasts that pick up dead things and eat them.”

“He must have been weak enough to be eaten by a lungfish.”

“What kind of creature goes out hunting when it’s that weak?”

Aiyen’s questions were valid.

Vikir had a short answer.

“Only if the tribe’s situation is so bad that a man that weak needs to go hunting.”

It could be a stretch.

It could be that the hunter was simply weakened by external factors at the wrong time.

But the skeleton didn’t show any signs of trauma.

Nail scratches on the inside of its esophagus and stomach wall suggest that it had struggled, but with very little force.

“I don’t feel right.”

Aiyen instinctively sensed something was wrong.

Vikir and Aiyen began to search the area.

Given the extent to which the body had been digested, and the speed at which lungfish travel, there should still be traces of it around.

Soon, they began to find traces of the hunter’s life.

When he was alive, he had moved around with an unsteady step.

He had no idea that this was Ballak’s territory, only that he was moving about in a frenzy of activity.

There were signs that he was searching for a small, weak beast, or perhaps a tree fruit.

This was a stark contrast to the normally valiant Rokoko hunters, who usually hunted large beasts.

What could have turned the Rokoko’s belligerent hunters into this?

Vikir and Aiyen continued to retrace their steps.

Eventually, they approached Rokoko’s territory.

“…!?”

They both spotted something.

Several of Rokoko’s hunters were gathered in a simple campsite.

With ancient dark elf blood in their veins, every member of their tribe is known for their beauty.

They are skilled in black magic, witchcraft, curses, and command, and their uncanny beauty gives them a unique and sinister aura.

As a result, they were an unusually vulnerable tribe to slave hunting.

But it wasn’t their appearance or aura that struck Vikir and Aiyen.

…It was the fact that all of the Rokoko hunters were dead.

Chapter 69

Blood Relatives (3)

◆

All of Rokoko’s hunters were dead.

Vikir and Aiyen approached through the foul odor and heat of the corpses.

“Is this …?”

Aiyen’s eyes narrowed.

Rokoko’s hunters were talkative, even in death.

They were screaming with every fiber of their being why they were dead.

There were signs of vomit and diarrhea everywhere, signs that they had tried to warm their chilled bodies with bonfires and fallen leaves, and, crucially, red spots on their skin.

Aiyen swallowed hard.

“So this is what warriors look like when they come out to hunt.”

Only the relatively healthy would have gone hunting.

He had no idea what the condition of those left behind in the village would be.

“Let’s go.”

Vikir led the way.

Vikir and Aiyen walked straight through the channel and into Rokoko’s territory.

Normally, they claim a large radius as their territory and leave markers along the way.

They usually hang skulls or corpses to warn trespassers, but strangely, the markers hadn’t been updated.

They had been left up for a long time and were already covered in moss and mold, making them hard to recognize.

It was uncharacteristic of the Rokoko, who were usually diligent about warning off intruders.

“Something must have happened to the village.”

Aiyen pushed through the Rokoko’s boundaries and headed for the low-lying hills that were their home.

There was no sign of life inside the village.

Nor was there any smoke, despite the fact that it was past mealtime.

At the entrance to the village, Vikir and Aiyen stopped in their tracks.

It wasn’t the lack of guards. There were no people wandering around inside the village at all.

The haphazardly constructed barracks were empty, their floors overgrown with weeds.

Crude household items lay abandoned on the ground everywhere.

“Where did they all move to?”

Aiyen frowned and walked into the barracks, pulling on his insignia.

The moment.

Yue Yue Yue-.

A huge swarm of flies burst out of the barracks.

The stench of filth and rotting meat was overpowering.

Inside the tent lay three small children and a woman.

They all looked as if they had died not long ago.

Vikir walked past the insignia of the other barracks next door.

“The others are similar.”

The natives of Rokoko had been exterminated before they could even get out of their barracks.

Most of the bodies were rotting and unrecognizable, but the skin of the few that were still in relatively good shape after their deaths was invariably marked with red spots.

“What is this, a plague?”

Aiyen said, shaking off the chills that ran down his spine.

Jungle warriors are particularly sensitive to poisonous plagues. No wonder Aiyen was so frightened.

“….”

Vikir’s mouth fell open, speechless.

Now that he thought about it, he had heard of this event before his regression.

“…The Red Death.”

The memory became clearer the more he stuttered.

A dreaded plague called the Red Death had certainly been circulating around this time.

A class one plague that killed nearly every barbarian and similar in the jungle.

It was so widespread that it even reached the borders of the Empire.

Once infected, the victims were crippled, lying helpless and slowly dying.

Their metabolism is extremely slow, and it takes a long time to die.

Red spots would appear all over the body, vomiting and diarrhea would occur, lethargy and pain would overwhelm them, and they would finally collapse and die.

The contagion was so rapid that the savages feared that mere eye contact with a sick person was contagious.

“How did they cure it?”

Vikir searched his memory a bit more. It was so long ago that it seemed to take a moment to recall.

Then.

“No, slave!”

A hand tugged at Vikir’s collar.

He turned to see Aiyen shouting urgently.

“Quickly, we must get out of here!”

“Why?”

“Why? It’s a curse! It’s a curse from the gods!”

For once, she was actually scared.

Vikir grinned and grabbed her wrist.

“Don’t worry. It’s a plague.”

“What!? That’s even worse! We have to get out of here! This place is cursed! You Rokoko bastards, every time you practice your unholy commands, you end up like this…!”

“Calm down, it’s not that easily transmitted.”

Vikir glanced back at Rokoko’s village.

Aiyen jumped in surprise, but she didn’t run off on her own.

She merely shivered, clinging to Vikir’s collar and following closely behind.

“Ugh… ugh. Aren’t we really being cursed?”

“If you’re so scared, go back first.”

“And if you die because you’re cursed?”

“If you die, you die.”

Vikir answered nonchalantly, and Aiyen, who had been trotting along behind him, shouted.

“Who cares!”

“…?”

“Of course it’s me,” Vikir thought, but didn’t bother to say it out loud.

Well, whatever.

After a quick walk around their village, Vikir realized that the Rokoko weren’t wiped out.

They just seemed to have moved on, leaving their dead and sick behind.

“Hmm, well. If there were carriers among the survivors, the outcome would be similar no matter where they fled.”

Vikir sympathized with the survivors, who had been forced to make a desperate choice.

But there was no guarantee that they would be safe from the Red Death.

Still, this was a chance to learn more about the mysterious life of the Rokoko tribe.

Vikir searched the Rokoko’s barracks, grabbing a few books and other items that seemed important and stuffing them into a sack.

They would one day make a great scholarly contribution to the study of the enemy and the barbarian tribes of the Black Mountains.

Just then.

I heard Aiyen’s screams from outside the barracks.

“Kaaaaaah!”

It was an urgent scream, and Vikir quickly ran out of the barracks.

Then Aiyen’s terrified screams became more pronounced.

“The curse! Cursed child!”

A terrible fear of the plague is characteristic of all the natives of depths.

Vikir silently shifts his gaze to look in the direction Aiyen is looking.

He saw the child standing on the outskirts of the village, next to the smallest and most shabby barracks.

“…Imperial?”

Vikir squinted.

The child did not appear to be from the Rokoko.

Could he have just turned five?

She had black hair, red eyes, and skin as white as snow.

She was standing barefoot next to a crumbling, shabby barracks, and she didn’t seem to want to leave.

Behind the barracks rose a crude stone cairn that looked like it hadn’t been built for long.

A few purple flowers, apparently freshly plucked, lay haphazardly in front of it.

“Aaahhhh! It must be a ghost, a cursed child of the forest god! We must flee, Vikir! You go first, I’ll be right behind you! Awww, my legs are weak…!”

Aiyen was shaking and sobbing.

Vikir smiled wryly at the sight of the child he hadn’t seen in the past two years of living together.

But aside from that, she felt like she needed to know who this child was.

“I can recognize the last of the Rokoko tribe.”

Vikir walked forward and sat down in front of the child, bringing them to eye level.

The girl flinched as if frightened, but she didn’t avoid Vikir’s hand on her head.

“Who are you?”

“….?”

Vikir asked, but the girl didn’t answer, just shook her head.

Vikir asked a few more times, but the child didn’t answer.

Instead, it listed a few words in a stuttering tone.

“Rokoko. Slave. Kitchen slave.”

The words were a clumsy mix of Rokoko and imperial.

Vikir couldn’t help but think of context in the string of words.

“So you were a slave in the Rokoko. What’s your name?”

“…Pomeranian.”

Vikir nodded at the girl’s answer.

“Your mother must have given you an imperial name.”

Pomeranian wasn’t a very common name, but it wasn’t a very difficult one either.

Either way, it was clear that the girl was from the Empire.

Without further delay, Vikir moved on to the next topic.

He was just about to ask what had happened to the Rokoko tribe.

The next words out of the girl’s mouth stiffened Vikir’s body.

“…La Baskerville.”

The moment. Vikir’s body froze as if struck by lightning.

The Baskervilles’ last name, the middle name “La,” which is only given to direct female relatives.

Not many people in the family have been given the middle names Les or La.

Vikir’s eyes widened, and the girl tried to hide behind the barracks’ pillars as if frightened.

No sound escaped her throat for a moment.

That’s what happens when a person is too surprised.

Unable to hide his disbelief, Vikir raised his hand and wiped his face a few times.

After drying his face, he regained his composure.

“Child, come here.”

“….”

The girl hid behind a pillar, only peeking her head out.

Vikir wondered what he could do to calm her down.

Just then, Aiyen, who had been in and out of the barracks, threw something at Vikir.

“Hey. There’s this inside. Ew, it’s not cursed, is it?”

Vikir took what Aiyen tossed him.

It was a small pendant made of gold.

The front of the brooch was embossed with the tooth-like symbol of the Baskervilles.

Aiyen remembered the Baskervilles’ emblem from the vial of potion Vikir had given her once.

“Isn’t that your family’s symbol?”

“….”

That lent a little more credence to what the girl had said.

Vikir traced his finger across the Baskerville crest on the pendant.

The pendant was made in a style that was quite old, an accessory that could only have been fashionable thirty years ago.

…Click!

Vikir opened the pendant.

Inside was a small portrait drawn with extreme precision.

“This?”

Vikir squinted at the portrait.

It depicted a nameless young woman, a young man, and a girl who appeared to be in her early teens.

The young woman had beautiful blonde hair and blue eyes, the young man had the dark hair and red eyes characteristic of the Baskervilles, and the girl in between had dark hair and red eyes as well.

Vikir recognized the young man in the portrait at a glance.

“Hugo le Baskerville! No way!”

It was definitely Hugo as a young man.

Chapter 70

Blood Relatives (4)

◆

“Why is this person here….”

Does it come out?

Vikir stared at the portrait for a while in disbelief.

But no matter how you look at it, it’s the same old Hugo.

Black hair, piercing eyes, blade-like bridge of the nose, strong jaw, no mustache yet. How could you not recognize this face?

What is it? Why is Hugo’s portrait here?

As Vikir stares in disbelief, Pomeranian sneaks up on him and tugs on the pendant’s string.

With what little strength he has, the tug seems to be a request for the pendant to be returned.

Vikir hands the pendant back to Pomeranian and asks.

“Who are these people in the painting, and what do they have to do with you?”

The Pomeranian flinched at the stern tone, as if interrogating a criminal.

Vikir spoke a little softer, wanting to be gentle.

“Who are the people in the picture, and what do they have to do with you?”

The words were different, but the tone was the same.

The harshness of the tone made the Pomeranian shiver uneasily.

Then Aiyen stepped forward.

“If you ask me like that, the I will not give you a good answer.”

“…? What did I do?”

“You should ask her with a smile.”

Aiyen’s point made Vikir pause for a moment.

Then a wicked grin spread across his face.

“Who are the people in the painting?”

The Pomeranian looked up, looking less frightened than he had earlier.

“Oh, yes, it’s working. You were right….”

Vikir turned his head toward Aiyen.

A moment.

“…?”

Vikir’s eyes caught Aiyen’s blank expression.

She stood there for a moment, looking into Vikir’s face, before she snapped out of it.

“Slave, did you expect me to laugh so hard?”

“….”

Vikir immediately frowned.

He hadn’t smiled widely since he was born, so it was no wonder he was being teased.

Then. The Pomeranian answered.

“Mama. Grandpa. Grandma.”

Vikir’s mouth dropped open at the words.

His head spun rapidly.

A pendant, a faded portrait, decades old. Hugo Le Baskerville and an unidentified young woman and a little girl. A mother and grandmother and grandfather, the Pomeranian said.

“…What?”

Vikir had a theory.

Hugo in the pendant is young. And the young woman next to him was probably his wife.

And the daughter they had together, the first born.

What if that eldest daughter was kidnapped by the Rokoko tribe, and the child she bore here was a Pomeranian?

‘Come to think of it, I’ve heard that Hugo’s personality wasn’t always as cold as it is now.’

I don’t know much about Hugo Le Baskerville when he was in the ecliptic before he came to the Fringes, as Vikir was not yet born.

But I had once heard a rumor from old Deacon Barrymore that Hugo had once been very friendly and homey.

‘I thought it was nonsense at the time and shrugged it off.

Vikir takes a moment to recall the history of the Baskervilles.

Once based near the ecliptic, the Baskervilles had moved far to the west of the empire, to the fringes of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, not because of a demotion.

Hugo Le Baskerville had gone before the Emperor and requested that the entire House of Baskerville move to the fringes.

The reason for this was the death of his first wife in childbirth, and the barbarians who had taken his first daughter, whom he loved dearly.

This caused Hugo to hate his enemies and the barbarians beyond the Black Mountains with a passion, and he cared for his wife and children little afterward.

After this series of events, he became an extremely cold and calculating killer, living only for the slaughter of demons and barbarians.

The Emperor deemed him competent and entrusted him with the task of expanding the empire’s borders, and Hugo threw himself even more into his work to forget everything.

That’s how Baskerville, Ironblade, was born.

And now. A rejected hound of the Ironborn has found an unexpected ally here.

Pomeranian. Pomeranian la Baskerville.

Penelope, the daughter of Roxana, the woman Hugo had loved more than anything else in his life.

And Penelope’s daughter, Pomeranian.

This means that, if my guess is correct, the girl in front of me is the direct granddaughter of Hugo Le Baskerville.

‘…That makes me an uncle.’

It was a strange feeling.

Even now, nieces and nephews were being born somewhere, but none of them were girls.

This is a Baskerville family where daughters are extremely rare.

Come to think of it, there was not a single daughter in Hugo’s direct bloodline.

Not even in the entire family.

There are plenty of sons.

“Anyway, Hugo, he’s the kind of man who only looks for sons and grandsons because he thinks men are more useful in battle.”

What do you think Hugo, the extreme warlord, the fighting demon, the man who sees his children as nothing more than tools, would do if he saw this tiny, delicate granddaughter?

Vikir shook her head.

No matter how I think about it, I can’t think of anything but negativity.

And with barbarian blood in the mix, he might not be so pleased.

Vikir reached out and placed his hand on top of the Pomeranian’s head.

The Pomeranian flinched slightly, but didn’t shy away as he had earlier.

Vikir spoke in a low voice.

“Apparently, the Rokoko tribe has not been treated well either.”

“….”

“Come with me.”

If the Rokoko tribe had been devastated by the plague and left, Pomeranian could not remain here.

But Pomeranian stood firm, clinging to the pillars of the barracks.

Vikir looked up and saw the reason for the Pomeranian’s reluctance to leave.

It was the crude stone tomb behind him.

As Vikir pondered what to do, Aiyen stepped forward.

She bowed her head once in front of the tomb, then spoke to the Pomeranian.

“When our ancestors leave this world, they go to heaven and become stars. So will your mother.”

“….”

“What lies here in this stone tomb is only a shell, but your mother’s spirit is a star in the sky, looking down on you.”

“….”

“She wishes you to leave this dreadful place as soon as possible.”

Then the Pomeranian raised his head. He seemed to understand not only the Imperial language, but Ballak’s words as well.

The Pomeranian pondered for a moment, then released his grip on the barracks’ pillars.

He takes a step toward Vikir.

Black hair, red eyes.

Vikir and Pomeranian looked exactly alike.

Pomeranian looked at Vikir and said.

“Mommy. The hair. Eyes. The color. It’s the same.”

“Yeah. All Baskerville dogs look alike.”

Vikir picked up the Pomeranian.

It was the first meeting of uncle and nephew.

◆

Afterward, Pomeranian came to Ballak’s village.

“Uncle. Where are you going?”

She clung to Vikir’s leg, unwilling to pull away, which was quite a challenge for a child who was used to being alone.

“Uncle has to go to a meeting, the chieftain has summoned him.”

“Aang. Uncle. I’ll go with you.”

Pomeranian seemed scared to be alone.

Now that she had left her mother’s stone tomb, she realized that she was truly alone.

That’s why she seemed to rely more on Vikir, who had the same hair color and eye color as her mother.

“…I can’t help it.”

Vikir quickly picked up the Pomeranian and carried him on his back.

He looked around for something that could be used as a swaddle, and a thick, coarse pelt caught his eye.

It was an oxbear pelt, given to me by the chieftain himself as a reward for our successful trade.

He wondered what he was going to use the pelt for, but he realized it was for a swaddling bag.

Vikir carried the Pomeranian on his back and went outside.

“I’ll have to ask the Chihuahua to do it for me … later.”

He couldn’t keep this girl in Ballak’s village.

Even if he didn’t send her to Hugo, she would have to be raised somewhere out of his sight, at least within the reach of Imperial civilization.

Vikir made plans to get out of the water and into the city later.

“Maybe I’ll pay a visit to Morgue, too.”

It might be worth spying on the alliance with Baskerville to see how it was going.

While Vikir pondered this, he soon arrived at the barracks of Chieftain Akwilla.

Upon entering, he finds Akwilla, Aiyen, and the other elders, all wearing serious expressions.

Aiyen and Vikir are witnesses to the meeting.

Chief Akwilla asks.

“Yes. You mean there’s a plague going around?”

Aiyen and Vikir nodded.

The report went on to detail how the Rokoko tribe had been wiped out, and the state of their remaining villages.

Other hunters also testified to seeing the bodies of orcs, lizardmen, and other apes lying on the ground with red spots sprouting from them.

Akwilla stroked his chin, a serious expression on his face.

“The rainy season is coming soon, and we’re in trouble.”

If the plague came, the damage would be even worse. We had to find a way to prepare.

Then.

“Chief, it’s not a plague, it’s a curse!”

Shaman Ah’Heman stepped forward.

He argued that the Red Death was not a disease, but a form of witchcraft that could be cured through sacrifice.

There were a few old elders who agreed with him.

They emphasized that this was the time for a great ritual, and it was clear that they intended to take advantage of the occasion to greatly increase the authority and power of the shaman.

The young people, on the other hand, said that the Red Death was a plague, not a curse, and that it was time to abandon the village and move on.

The old and young debated heatedly between superstition and practical solutions.

It didn’t seem like it would be easy to decide who was right.

“Hmmm. What shall we do?”

Chieftain Akwilla was frowning.

Someone silently raised their hand to speak.

The one who first coined the phrase ‘red death’.

“I know how to stop this disease.”

It was Vikir.

Chapter 71

The Red Death (1)

◆

Vikir reminisced about the past, long ago.

His mind flashed back to the strange outsiders that Ballak’s hunting party had seen not long ago, and the dagger with the serpentine symbol.

‘…Come to think of it, that incident happened around this time.

The “event” is the Red Death.

A terrifying plague that leaves victims covered in red spots, vomiting and diarrhea, and then dying.

The Red Death quickly spread throughout the jungle and killed a staggering number of natives.

The Red Death raged on a scale that rivaled the Black Death that once plagued the Empire.

This dreaded plague has spread like wildfire, reaching far into the Empire’s territory.

It was not until the Morgue’s weatherman, Camus, raised a barrier of fire to stop its spread to the borders of the Empire.

In addition, a holy woman, Dolores, sent by House Quovadis of the Holy Order of the Sacraments, has been able to heal the sick with her unique and powerful holy powers.

However, the cure was limited to the Empire, and the natives living in the depths of the Black Mountains suffered a death rate of nearly 40%.

These circumstances worked in the Baskervilles’ favor.

The barbarian tribes played a crucial role in Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain’s ecosystem, and with them largely out of the picture as predators, lower-level demons overpopulated, leading to monster waves and a spike in civilian casualties.

The surge in their numbers has increased the influence of the Baskervilles on the border, which has only served to strengthen Hugo’s political position.

“I can’t let that happen.”

So Vikir was going to stop this plague.

Well, he’d heard a fair amount about the Ballak over the years.

Meanwhile.

Within the Ballak, the old and the young were at odds.

The older generation believes that the plague should be stopped by performing rituals, and the younger generation believes that the village should be abandoned and moved elsewhere.

“….”

Patriarch Akwilla frowned and remained silent.

Deep down, she doesn’t want to leave this village, where her ancestors’ graves lie.

And the shaman Ah’Heman understood her feelings.

“How can we abandon this holy place where our ancestors are buried? This migration is ridiculous! We have been here for nearly two hundred years!”

There are more than a hundred ancestors’ remains in the holy sites around the village.

How they would be managed and cared for if they were to migrate was a key point of contention for Ahmed.

But Aiyen, who represents the younger generation, is not backing down.

“What if the plague comes back and kills all the children? Who will take care of our future then? Who will take care of the future of the tribe when the seeds of the future are gone when we go to collect the remains of our ancestors?”

As it turns out, Ballak children do die.

Typically, Ballak women start having children at age 14 and give birth to a new child every two years on average, which means they will have about ten to fifteen children in their lifetime.

The problem is that more than half of them die within the first month of life. Only about 20% of infants survive beyond three years.

Most of the children die from malnutrition, childhood diseases, war, and hunting accidents.

Add to that the fact that mothers die during childbirth or from the aftermath of childbirth, and the Ballak have a much lower birth rate.

Add the Red Death to the mix, and there are no answers. There is only a dark future ahead.

Unable to bear the sight of her clanmates in the midst of a generational conflict, Akwilla spoke up.

“The question is, what path does the Red Death take?”

What is the Red Death, and why does it cling to humans?

Unless these questions are answered, it’s essentially impossible to do anything about it.

To Patriarch Akwilla’s anguish, answers came from many quarters.

“A curse! It must be a curse!”

“Wrong, it is a plague transmitted through the gaze!”

“It’s the spirits of your prey retaliating!”

“It must be because you ate a strange looking mushroom!”

“The ancestors are angry because we have neglected their mausoleum!”

“There must be a poisonous insect!”

“The gods have abandoned us, the forest gods!”

“The imperials have brought the disease with them!”

The people of Ballak don’t know, but they don’t often say they don’t know.

They make a virtue out of giving crappy answers.

It was out of the goodness of his heart that he didn’t want to disappoint the person who had trusted him with the question in the first place, but… wasn’t helping much in this situation.

“…Hmm.”

Akwilla’s brow furrowed in confusion.

Silently, a hand came up.

Vikir’s. His eyes met Akwilla’s and he spoke.

“If there is a way to stop the Red Death, I know it.”

◆

About ten days passed after that.

Clatter, clatter, clatter.

A demon tied to a rope was struggling.

A goblin, the smallest and weakest of the demons classified as similar.

It was currently hanging upside down with its arms and legs tied to the ropes, being tortured.

[Grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!]

The goblin was being dipped into a large pot of water, pulled out, and repeated.

The goblin had been flailing around for a while, but suddenly it became very calm.

Soon, red spots began to appear on the goblin’s skin.

The goblin drooled and vomited, and stopped baring its teeth.

It slowly shudders in anticipation of its coming death.

Meanwhile. Ballak’s warriors tossed the red-faced goblin into a pile of oiled pyres and set it on fire.

There was no room for pity, as the creature was a foul creature that kidnapped and ate human children.

Soon, the goblin with the Red Death burned to death.

Then Ballak’s warriors turned their attention to the next goblin.

Before them stood Aiyen, clutching the goblin’s ropes.

“Vikir. Is the Red Death really transmitted through water?”

At her question, Vikir, beside her, nodded.

“Yes, it is. Contaminated water is the main culprit. But as long as you boil the water once, there’s no problem.”

“Really? Is that so?”

Aiyen looked at Vikir with a trusting gaze.

Then he took another pot of the same water and dipped another goblin in it for comparison.

Then.

[Cackle!]

The goblin died instantly.

Vikir put his hand to his forehead.

“When the water cools, we’ll put him in.”

“Ugh.”

Aiyen also hit his forehead with his hand.

Soon, the water in the pot was boiling again.

When the bubbling water had cooled completely, Ballak’s warriors dipped the goblins into it.

Ten days passed, the incubation period for the Red Death, but the goblin did not become ill.

Then all the warriors of Ballak, including their chieftain Akwilla, exclaimed in amazement.

“We have found a way to overcome the Red Death!” they exclaimed.

“The answer was in the water.”

“You mean just boiling water and drinking it will stop the plague?”

“Vikir, you are a hero of our tribe!”

The praise poured in, the looks of respect and admiration.

The old are delighted and the young look on in admiration.

By nature, Vikir doesn’t like to be the center of attention.

But it is Ballak custom to be sure when congratulating or praising, and everyone surrounds him, drooling over him.

Vikir responds to their praise and gratitude with a wave of his hand.

“Anyway. You have to be careful with the water. It can’t get in your mouth or eyes. It can also be infectious through the respiratory route, so beware of the water mist at dawn.”

Always boil water before drinking. Avoid wetlands as much as possible.

By following these simple rules, the incidence of red death is greatly reduced.

Avoiding contact with the feces or corpses of the sick is just common sense.

“What don’t you know?”

Vikir didn’t say anything in response to Aiyen’s admiring words.

Akwilla said.

“Let the hunting birds spread Vikir’s teachings to the other tribes. Beware of the water.”

At that, everyone nodded. It was good for as many people as possible to know these things.

Then Akwilla rose from his seat and came to stand before Vikir.

Vikir bowed his head in silence.

The first time he’d met her, he’d felt a sense of gravity, like a huge mountain range weighing him down.

But now he felt nothing of the sort.

Instead, I felt a sense of warmth, a sense of home, and a sense of compassion, like a real mother’s greeting.

Akwilla smiled gently.

“Thanks to you, I can see a way out of this crisis, and I thank you from the bottom of my heart.”

One would never recognize this woman as the Night Fox from her current expression and voice.

In response, Vikir could only bow his head.

Then.

“Well, the rainy season is coming soon, so how can you go away from the water?”

Someone questioned Vikir.

The shaman, Ah’Heman, stared at Vikir with a stony expression on his face.

He had once misdiagnosed a side effect from the drugs the merchants had brought as a curse.

When Vikir insisted that the Red Death was not a curse but a plague, and that it could be prevented, he seemed to decide that his position was under threat.

But he wasn’t entirely wrong.

When the rainy season arrives, the rivers will overflow, and countless rains will pour down.

The air would be filled with moisture, and there would be no way to survive the many aquatic creatures that would crawl up to the surface and carry plague.

The preventative measures of boiling water for drinking and washing certainly had their limits.

Ballak’s warriors stirred.

Ah’Heman smiled a smile of conversion as he watched the number of agitated ones grow.

…But.

“The civil works must be done before the rainy season arrives.”

Vikir, still looking nonchalant, was steadily taking the next step.

Dewatering (flood control).

It was necessary for Vikir’s future plans.

Chapter 72

The Red Death (2)

◆

The rainy season has come to Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Dark clouds covered the sky. This rainy season seemed to be the longest ever.

There was record rainfall, the likes of which even the oldest man in the village had never seen.

The rivers were overflowing like crazy, and places that had been flat just a few days before were now swamps with raging torrents.

Everything in sight was underwater.

…Except for Ballak’s village!

“Pull tighter, tie tighter!”

“Pull up the stanchions!”

“Tighten it up! It’s going to float away!”

The low-lying village of Ballak was now on higher ground.

It hadn’t been moved.

They simply built floating houses out of planks and logs in the tall trees and between the trees.

At least 15 meters above the ground, these wooden houses provided cozy shelter while the world around them was flooded by the river.

Vikir was at the forefront of this massive civil engineering project to raise an entire village up in the trees.

“…Luckily, I won’t be swept away.”

Vikir thought as he looked out at the rising river just a few meters below.

Bridges had been built between the tallest trees with ropes, planks, and logs, and the barracks were securely anchored to keep them from being blown away by the wind.

And down below, out of sight of the water, drainage ditches had been dug between the trunks and branches of the trees.

In some places, rocks and earth had been piled up to create banks that redirected the flow.

This allowed Ballak’s village to remain relatively safe from the flooding of the river.

Some men were putting up a rope bridge made of twisted vines between trees through the rain and wind.

They waved to Vikir as he passed by on the plank bridge.

“Hey, Vikir! Our house is safe thanks to you!”

“Thank you! I’m glad I listened to you!”

But Vikir didn’t respond to their greetings.

Instead, he squinted at the huge shadow that was slowly moving toward them from the water below.

“Dangerous.”

Vikir briefly warned the two men who greeted him.

Hearing Vikir’s warning, the men looked down at the bridge in alarm.

Just three meters below them, in the tawny mud, a giant shadow lurked beneath the surface.

And then.

…Poof!

The surface of the water shattered and something leapt out of the water.

It was a catfish with a giant mouth that was more than five meters in diameter!

As soon as it broke the surface of the water, it gaped at the two Ballak men above.

This has often happened since the fire.

Energized aquatic creatures would leap at their prey in the trees.

But the catfish didn’t get his way.

“Get lost!”

Arrows fell like thunder from the tree trunks.

It was Aiyen, protecting the men as they built the bridge.

…Thump!

Several arrows pierced the catfish’s skull, and it twisted and flopped back into the water.

Vikir scrambled across the rope bridge and up into the windswept trees.

“Catfish!”

He looked down, but the tawny surface of the water had already been washed away by the raging torrent.

Seeing Vikir frown, Aiyen grinned.

“That’s not a catfish.”

“What? Didn’t you just see it stick its head out of the water?”

“…I guess you didn’t see the body.”

I was afraid to let him finish.

Suddenly, the surface of the water on the other side broke and something huge rose up from below.

Sure enough, Vikir understood what Aiyen had said.

The head was flat and the mouth was abnormally large, so I thought it was a catfish.

But that impossibly long body sticking out of the water was no catfish.

It was a giant snake.

<Monsieur Hushu>

Danger rating: A+

Size: 32 meters

Found in: Ridge 8, Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain

-Named ‘The Full-body Intestine Snake’.

A snake whose entire body is made up of intestines.

It boasts a large mouth and appetite that can swallow an elephant in one bite, and legend has it that the giant Monsieur Hushu, which has lived since time began, can swallow an entire country.

They are notoriously silent when crawling on land or swimming underwater.

This giant snake of the Monsieur Hushu species was scaled and hissing as if it were about to swallow all the Ballak on the floating house.

Aiyen bit her lip.

“Chet. You’ve got a dangerous one washed up.”

The giant rattlesnake was no match for a species that was naturally fast and strong.

Moreover, the one in front of them seems to be quite old and experienced.

[Shhhh!]

The creature opened its mouth, which was so large that it could have been a catfish, revealing a dense row of teeth that sprawled across its entire mouth.

Aiyen quickly fired an arrow at it, but its sleek, hard scales, and the rain that blinded him, made it difficult to get a good hit.

Then.

“Snakes should be caught up close.”

A black shadow hovered like a ghost behind Monsieur Hushu.

Vikir. Moving in the darkness, he blazed across the snake’s back, unnoticed by rats and birds alike, and then bared his hidden teeth.

He sliced through the artery in his wrist, revealing the magic sword Beelzebub.

And the slimy aura of a Superior Gradient settled over it.

A Baskervillian carnivore.

Six ‘lurking ambush teeth’ have been released.

Intent on inflicting terrible pain on the opponent, and nothing else!

The blood-red aura emanating from Vakir’s sword spins at high speed.

The hard snake scales shattered in an instant, and the soft flesh underneath exploded and scattered as if it had been blown up.

[Kyaaahhhhhhhhhhhhh!]

The snake screamed.

But Vikir was unfazed, grabbing the snake by the tongue and lunging forward, his awl smashing into one of the snake’s eyeballs.

The fatal wounds to its back neck and eyeball caused the snake to back away, splattering hot blood. It then ducked its head under the water and began to flee frantically.

No, it was more like being swept down the torrent than fleeing.

“….”

Vikir briefly considered giving chase, but decided it was too much to ask in this torrential downpour.

“It was a waste.”

Before he knew it, Aiyen was beside him, wrapping a rope around Vikir’s waist.

Tugging on the rope around each other’s waists, Vikir and Aiyen made their way back up the branch.

Soon, all the villagers were out on the wooden terrace watching the battle.

“Awesome! Vikir, you were the best!”

“That big snake is called Ka’ah, and he’s been king around here for decades!”

“You defeated him, that’s great!”

The villagers cheered for Vikir.

Then Aiyen snapped.

“You people! Didn’t you see me shoot that arrow! If it wasn’t for me, you’d be…!”

“Oooh-”

The kids booed Aiyen.

“Ugh, this is why I hate kids.”

Aiyen grumbles and shakes off the mud and splash that has drenched her body.

He looked back at Vikir, who was dripping wet, and asked.

“You’re not going to get the red death from getting this wet, are you?”

“You never know. Go to the fire and dry yourself.”

Vikir strode away, as if the battle that had just occurred had been a minor incident.

Seeing that people were cheering or not, Aiyen went on his way, and he said the words he had been saying for the past two years, one more time today.

“Pass.”

◆

Vikir walked into the barracks.

Outside, the rain and wind were howling, but inside the barracks was bright and warm.

The leather hides on the walls were still flapping about, but they were secured with heavy rocks and strong ropes, so the wind wouldn’t blow them away.

Vikir’s discovery of a way to prevent the Red Death made him a hero to the Ballak, and indeed to all the jungle tribes.

…But the hero is a troubled man now.

It’s a job he’s never had to do before or since his regression.

“Uncle!”

As soon as Vikir entered the barracks, the Pomeranian rushed over and hugged him.

Until then, he had been squatting in the corner of the barracks, staring blankly at the portraits of his family.

Pomeranian avoided everyone else but Vikir, who followed him intensely.

She followed him around all day, never wanting to be separated, sleeping, eating, and bathing.

“ …I want to eat.”

Vikir wasn’t sure how to respond to the child.

It was all he could say to her.

Afterward, Vikir made a simple fire in the corner of the barracks.

With snails crawling everywhere in the rainy season, food was easier to come by than before.

Vikir simply steamed snail flesh with butter, herbs, and backs made from cow’s milk.

He then fried them in a mixture of sugar made from sugarcane and cream made from bird eggs.

The rest of the snail flesh was mashed with spicy spices that he had bought from merchants in the past, and when served with vegetables, it became a quite edible dish.

“Delicious, Uncle.”

“Isn’t that right, your uncle is a good cook.”

Beside Pomeranian, who was cringing, was Aiyen, who was naturally cringing as well.

Pomeranian looked to Vikir, then to Aiyen.

“Mommy. Dad. Same.”

Pomeranian looked back and forth between Vikir and Aiyen and chuckled, and Aiyen rubbed his index finger under his nose.

“As expected, the kids are really nice.”

“…I thought you said you didn’t like children …?”

“When did I say that.”

Vikir pressed a hand to his forehead. The barracks were already cramped because of the Pomeranians, and now that they’d come to Aiyen, they were even more cramped.

“Don’t be too harsh. But at least you can go outside to pee now.”

“….”

Vikir could only sigh at Aiyen’s attitude as she spread her legs again and swished her leather skirt.

Just then.

Whirring.

The tents at the entrance were drawn back, letting in the rain and wind.

A heavy stone had been placed on top of the gate, making it impossible for it to be blown away naturally.

As if on cue, someone stepped out of the darkness outside the door.

It was Ahun.

“…?”

Vikir and Aiyen frowned at the same time.

Ahun had always been an annoyance, and they were already wondering what he was up to this time.

But.

Ahun’s expression when he entered Vikir’s barracks was unexpected.

His blue complexion, contorted face, and the way he looked like he was about to cry.

Then, in a desperate voice, Ahun cried out.

“Please help me, Vikir, my sister is…!”

Chapter 73

The Red Death (3)

◆

The jungle is stormy and windy.

The tents on the walls fluttered wildly.

Inside the barracks, an open fire burns.

Hot breathing echoes from the beds, which are reddened by the firelight.

Aheul. A girl who had just turned fourteen lay there, moaning.

A pale spot on her skin, a red death, slowly eating away at her body.

Aheul’s brother, Ahun, clung to Vikir with a contemplative look on his face.

“Please, Vikir, please save my sister!”

“….”

Vikir closed his mouth and walked toward Aheul.

Red spots on his skin, uncontrollable bowel movements, soaring body temperature, pain in his joints, swelling in his neck, armpits, and groin.

These are all signs of the red death.

“Why did it happen?”

“I went to the swamp to cut down trees for civil works and stopped….”

Ahun answered for me.

Aheul must have gotten the disease when he went deep into the swamp to cut wood.

“What shall we do, slave?”

Aiyen asked, looking worried.

“There’s nothing we can do about it, though, if he’s already fallen ill.”

Prevention is something anyone can do, but cure is the domain of the experts.

Then.

A flutter.

The door to the barracks opened.

It was none other than the shaman Ah’Heman.

As soon as he entered, he looked at Aheul and Ahun and snapped.

“You’re bad, you two, wandering around without listening to your grandfather!”

Ah’Heman shouted, splattering spittle over Aheul’s groaning face.

“You deserve this because you were instigated by the words of that imperial spy! What comes to me goes around!”

“Grandfather, you speak harshly!”

Ahun shouted back, rising to his feet.

Mate-.

But all that came back was a slap on the ear.

Ahun sank to his knees, his cheeks reddening, unable to get back to his feet.

Ah’Heman looked down at him in disdain as he fell to the ground.

“There is nothing different from my mother-in-law. Worthless bastard.”

“….”

Thick tears began to fall from Ahun’s eyes.

Aiyen sighs with a ‘here we go again’ look.

“There is a cure.”

Vikir spoke up.

He snorted, and Ahun’s eyes widened.

Ah’Heman shoved Vikir in the chest and stormed out of the barracks.

“This is a curse from the gods, and the only way to make amends is to make a sacrifice. Now that things have come to this, I’m sure the chieftain will agree.”

The shaman asserted his authority until the end.

Whizz, whizz, whizz.

The wind and raindrops rush in through the open doorway, soaking everyone.

The only ones left in the barracks were Aiyen, Vikir, Ahun, and the sick Aheul.

Vikir said to Ahun

“First, I want you to collect Aheul’s feces. Make sure you don’t come in contact with it. Also, sterilize the used utensils with boiling water, and burn some wormwood in the fire to drive away any mosquitoes, fleas, or bats that might be around the house.”

“Oh, I see. Is that all I have to do?”

“Not just that.”

Vikir turned his head to look at Aiyen.

Then he said what he had originally planned to demand, a little more quickly.

“Take me out of the depths.”

Aiyen’s expression hardened at the words.

There is no discrimination for those who have come from outside and become part of the Ballak.

They are free to go anywhere in the jungle, and inside the village, they are allowed anywhere except the chief’s barracks and the shaman’s festivals.

But only one thing.

They are strictly forbidden to travel outside of depths.

A Ballak from outside the city can only leave the city limits if two conditions are met.

First.

They must have lived in the town for at least two years.

Second.

They must be in a relationship with a native Ballak and have given birth to three or more children.

Vikir didn’t meet either of these requirements.

But that didn’t stop him from asking to be taken out of the floodwaters.

“If you let me out, I will bring a cure for the plague.”

Hearing Vikir’s words, Aiyen bit her lip.

Would his mother and chieftain, Akwilla, allow this exception? Probably not. Akwilla was quite the principled woman.

‘She would most likely abandon him.

A small sacrifice for the greater good.

But Aiyen didn’t want to do that.

She didn’t want to see Aheul, who had always sung in her sweet voice and helped with the laundry and cleaning, dying of vomit and diarrhea.

…But a more fundamental issue was tearing her apart.

Would Vikir ever return?

Technically, he was a foreigner who had been taken as a slave.

If we set Vikir free and allow him to go outside the depths, will he return?

Up until now, Vikir has been able to roam freely on his own, but only within Ballak’s territory.

If Vikir tried to run away, Ballak’s rangers and wolves would find him and bring him to justice that evening when they saw that the camp was empty.

Vikir wasn’t stupid enough not to know that.

But getting a pass to go outside the wall was a different story.

By the time he realized he was on the run, never to return, he would be out of reach forever.

“….”

Aiyen hesitated.

It wasn’t like her to hesitate.

In that brief moment, she thought deeply about the psychological factors that made her hesitate, and soon found the reason.

Looking into her own mind and discovering something she didn’t even know she had.

She looked up.

Her eyes were already red, the color of fire. The only difference was that unlike fire, they were moist with water.

“ ….Go”

The master’s command fell.

◆

Aiyen did not report to Akwilla, for it was a given that she would not approve.

All responsibility fell to Aiyen.

Vikir ran through the night waters with the Pomeranian on his back.

“We can’t completely stop the plague with a flood control anyway.”

Besides, what about the other tribes that didn’t build the flood control?

A more fundamental solution was needed to prevent the spread of the Red Death, the revival of the empire, and even the Baskerville family.

…Tadak!

Vikir crossed the river in one swift motion, stepping over logs as they floated downstream.

With all the stuff that washed up during the floods, he could run on the river, shortening the distance.

Just then.

Vikir’s feet came to a screeching halt on the riverbank.

Shoot!…

The night was pouring with rain. A shadow streaked across the water.

Vikir turned to find Aiyen standing there, soaked to the skin, breathing heavily.

“Why are you following me?”

Vikir asks, and Aiyen opens his mouth to speak, but stops himself.

“I’m following my slave.”

“Don’t follow me.”

“I don’t want to.”

“I said don’t follow me.”

“I’m the master!”

Aiyen shouted in a bitter voice.

But Vikir only drew the line once more with a cold glare.

“It’s unusual to say it three times, you know that, right?”

“….”

“If you don’t want to follow me, don’t follow me.”

Seeing the look in Vikir’s eyes, Aiyen froze in place, shocked.

“How can you look at me like that?”

She asked in a sobbing voice.

Vikir didn’t answer.

Then Aiyen groped for something.

And then, after sifting through many things, he spoke.

“Where are you going?”

“….”

“If you tell me where you’re going, I’ll go.”

“No.”

“Why are you taking Pomeranian?”

“….”

“ …Can’t you at least leave him with me?”

A sight to behold, not knowing who was master and who was slave.

…No, Aiyen, she knew from the beginning.

It was something she’d felt from the very beginning, from the first time she’d seen his gaunt face on stage, when she’d been locked in the cage of the slave traders.

That she would spend the rest of her life beneath him.

The realization dawned on her as she stood in the pouring rain.

She spoke, shivering, her voice damp with moisture.

“Then answer me this one question.”

“…What?”

Vikir asked, and Aiyen took a long breath before she spoke.

“You’re coming back, right?”

“….”

The voice crawled. A tone that hung with anxiety, impatience, and hunger.

And for once, Vikir answered quickly.

“Of course.”

Only then did Aiyen’s expression soften.

She blew out a white breath of relief.

“‘You keep your word.”

“….”

“I will.”

Vikir nodded.

And then.

The hounds ran through the dawn again.

A darkness that swallowed him whole.

And there is one master here who stands still and watches its fading back.

Chapter 74

The Hound of the Night (1)

◆

In the southwestern part of the Empire, among the neat, polished buildings, lies the city of St. Mecca, the center of the estates of the Quovadis family of religious saints.

The white-stoned boulevards, slow-moving carriages, and casual footsteps of people on foot give the city an air of leisure.

At the entrance to the city, paladins in white armor and robes stand guard.

Then.

Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.

A carriage drawn by three horses pulls up to the checkpoint.

The paladins screening entry into the city stopped the carriage.

“There will be a brief checkpoint.”

The merchants from the wagon then offered the paladins their passes and identification cards.

The paladins took them and scrutinized them.

“You must be Mr. Joseph Josta of the Oil Merchants, 108 Dortmund Street, first floor. What is in your wagon?”

“Oil, as it says on the import permit ….”

The merchant stroked his mustache and looked back.

Sure enough, the wagon’s interior was filled with large tin barrels.

The paladins glanced inside.

“Do you mind if we check inside?”

“Of course.”

The merchant nodded, and the paladins drew their swords and climbed onto the wagon.

The wagon lurched slightly as the three or four heavily armed knights climbed in.

The paladins carefully examined the barrels inside the wagon.

They were heavy, each with a tightly sealed lid.

The paladins rapped the barrels together.

…Boom!

They could feel that they were filled to the brim with oil. All of the barrels were like that.

“Can I not take this one?”

“Of course not. There’s more than oil in these barrels.”

The paladins nodded at the merchant’s words.

“ Pass!”

And with that, the wagon drove through the gates and into the city.

A short time later. The carriage pulled into the outskirts of a deserted street, into a deserted back alley.

The merchant checked his surroundings a few times before lifting the lid of the oil barrel.

…Poof! Poof!

He took a giant crowbar and twisted the lid, and with a loud bang, the barrel popped open.

The iron lid, which had been tightly sealed, bent and opened, revealing the oil inside.

The merchant called out in an anxious voice.

“…, Come out now.”

He did. And then something amazing happened.

Pow!

The surface of the black oil cracked, revealing a figure inside.

It was a man wearing a black hat like a pirate captain, a stork’s beak gas mask like a doctor specializing in infectious diseases, and a thick trench coat.

He stepped out of the barrel, covered in black oil, and stood on the floor of the wagon.

The merchant began to shudder at the grotesque sight.

Then, the stork gas mask man reached into his pocket and handed the merchant something.

It was a set of oiled teeth, the fangs of the prized oxbear.

“Go, thank you.”

The price he’d agreed to accept in exchange for hiding in the wagon and passing through the gates.

The merchant bowed and took the oxbear’s tooth and put it in his pocket.

Then, dripping with oil, the man began to walk away down the back alley.

At his heels, the merchant stammered, “Who are you?”

“ …, But who are you?”

The man flicked his stork’s beak and replied in a short, sharp voice.

“The Hound of the Night.”

With that, he melted into the darkness of the alley and disappeared.

The merchant, left alone, stared at the bubbling oil in the tin and muttered despairingly.

“ …How does a man stay submerged in oil for over two hours?”

◆

The Night Hound went back to the back of the dark alley and removed his mask.

“Pooh!”

Vikir exclaimed. He shook the oil off his body and breathed heavily.

He hadn’t been underwater this long since he’d lasted seven minutes in the Styx River when he was barely a year old.

Today, he’d sneaked into the estate of the Quovadis family, a clan of holy men.

“…The hound of the night.”

It’s a reference to the Ballak chieftain Akwilla’s star sign, “Fox of the Night,” but it doesn’t sound quite right.

But it was much better than being called the Hound of Baskerville before the regression, Vikir thought.

“….”

Vikir took a moment to reminisce.

It had taken them exactly four days to get here.

Two days to get out of the depths, a day to explore the Baskerville family estate, and another day to infiltrate the territory of the Faithful Quovadis.

The depths of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain were wide, but the floods helped us escape.

The rapids that sprang up everywhere, and the corpses and logs that floated above them, made traveling many times faster.

Most of the waterways were covered with dense vines and branches, so even rivers and lakes that had nowhere to go could easily be crossed by climbing over the forest canopy.

Of course, there were hungry creatures along the way, but they were no match for the fully-restored Vikir.

Giant catfish, old lizards, ferocious bears, ravenous packs of wild dogs, and venomous bats… were mere rites of passage for Vikir, who had perfectly adapted to the depth ecosystem over the past two years.

“…No, it was dangerous once.”

‘I don’t know about the others, but the bone-sucking mosquitoes, they were really dangerous.

Undaunted by the fierce rain, they chased Vikir in swarms, and he spent nearly half a day trying to keep them at bay.

The weakened Pomeranian caught a cold and struggled for a while.

The first thing Vikir did when he emerged from the water was to take Pomeranian to the city of Underdog.

Mr. Chihuahua, who was sighing at the full moon in the night sky, fainted three times in quick succession when he saw Vikir burst through the window of his small apartment.

Vikir had come to City Hall because he was one of the few people in Baskerville who could be trusted with a personality that belied his skinny appearance.

“…, Deputy, are you a ghost? No, I mean, how did you get here?”

“‘Why don’t I know the layout of the place I used to go to work every day?”

By now, the Chihuahua had come to his senses, and when Vikir told him what had happened, he let out an exclamation of admiration.

‘You are indeed a great man, Deputy. Only you have a different kind of life. What kind of barbarian tribes do you live with for two years…’

“I’ll be back in full force soon enough, so be ready. And keep everything that happened today a secret.”

‘I see, but who is this child, who looks so much like you, Chief Deputy…? Is this the child of Chief Deputy, who has been having some sort of affair with a barbarian….’

‘By blood, yes, but not in the way you imagine, so spare me the nonsense.’

Vikir trusted the Chihuahua with the Pomeranian.

‘He is an important person, so don’t ask him anything until I return, and then take great care of him and give him a basic education.

The story goes quickly, as the Chihuahua still hasn’t forgotten Vikir, the chief deputy, and his eyes are still red from the occasional glass of wine.

Chihuahua quickly summoned a doctor from the city hall, who examined Pomeranian and brought him medicine and food.

“I will take care of her, with my life, until the deputy returns.”

The Chihuahua said with determination.

After two years, he still looked scrawny, but Vikir knew he was a man of his word.

Considering the Chihuahua’s low wages, Vikir handed over Oxbear’s pelt and horns to Pomeranian in exchange for child support.

“Hee hee! What are you giving me for all this?”

“To be sold at your pleasure.”

“Wow, that’s a lot of pelts and horns for a big guy, and if I can sell them properly, they’ll be worth more than ten years of my salary.”

“Make sure the Pomeranian are well provided for.”

“You’re very protective of your daughter. You’re a good father. I have three daughters of my own, so I know how you feel.”

The Chihuahua gave me a fatherly smile and a knowing nod.

There was a hint of misunderstanding, but Vikir didn’t bother to clarify.

Then.

‘Ah! Deputy, this is…!’

As if on cue, Chihuahua quickly opened a cabinet in the corner of the office and pulled out a stack of old papers.

Vikir’s eyes lit up when he saw it.

It was a file of newspaper clippings from the past two years, detailing Baskerville and Morgue’s interactions, current events, and recent issues.

“I was prepared just in case the deputy consul might come back.’ !”

The Chihuahua scratched the back of his neck in embarrassment.

Vikir was grateful that the Chihuahua hadn’t forgotten him, even in this situation.

So Vikir agreed to help solve some of the problems in the city of Underdog, which is currently experiencing a resurgence of criminal activity due to the absence of a magistrate.

“If it interferes with your work, you can find Cindywendy in Messinadnaro. She owes me.”

Vikir told the Chihuahua in a hushed tone.

The Chihuahua’s eyes widened.

Messinadnaro Cindywendy was a criminal whom Vikir had freed in a plea bargain two years earlier.

“How do I find her?”

“Do you remember the girl I gave 10 billion to when I was deputy chief magistrate?”

“Sure. Her name was Judy, too.”

“I’d probably go looking for her, because it’s hard to make 10 billion, but it’s even harder to keep it. She has nowhere to go and no backup, so she’s easy to get to.”

The Chihuahua nodded silently at Vikir’s words.

Fresh out of prison and penniless, finding an investor would be her first priority.

She had once gone to Gambino, a poor local baron, and become his investment advisor.

“But if I find her, will she continue to help me? She must have something against the local government.”

“Tell her you’ll get her some good business.”

“And by good business, you mean…?”

Vikir was kind enough to answer the Chihuahua’s questions.

“‘I will give you a monopoly on trade with the savage tribes.”

The barbarian tribes of the Sioux River have not traded with the Empire since the conflict with the merchants of Bourgeois Street two years ago.

If Vikir, the current hero of Ballak, were to step forward, that trade could be reopened, and the merchant who did so would likely find great wealth.

Add to that the fact that the underdog city’s crime rate has been on the rise again since Vikir’s death, and her counsel would be invaluable in addressing the many problems and ills of the city.

At that, the Chihuahua nodded.

Indeed, less than a few hours after Vikir’s return, the problems of the past two years were already showing signs of resolution.

The Chihuahua was in awe all over again.

…Whoo!

Vikir launches himself back over the window sill.

The Night Hound sneaks out of the underdog city.

‘Deputy Magistrate! Where are you going?

With the Chihuahua’s mournful cry behind him, Vikir heads for the land to fulfill his promise to Aiyen.

A place where the ‘red death’ of Aheul could be quickly cured.

‘…That can easily be accomplished with a single drop of your family’s holy water.’

The Quovadis, one of the Seven Houses of the Empire, a family of faithful saints.

Chapter 76

The Hound of the Night (3)

◆

The doors to the official residence opened.

As expected, there was no one on the other side of the door.

There was only a stone statue with a saintly voice.

[What business have you come to see me for?]

The voice of the saintly Dolores came from the statue’s mouth.

Apparently, she wasn’t going to meet Vikir in person.

“…, Of course. It’s only natural.”

Vikir’s outfit now looked suspicious.

A large hat, a stork’s beak gas mask, and a black cloak covering his entire body.

No wonder the saint wouldn’t meet him in person.

Vikir approached the statue and spoke.

“I have come to report a plague in the slums.”

As he spoke, Vikir held out a bucket of well water, imbued with the energy of the Red Death.

A good cleric would be able to detect the peculiar aura of this water.

The moment.

[….]

The voice from the statue cut off.

Vikir had a hunch. The saint had stopped sending her voice through the stone.

And then.

…Tsk!

The door behind him slammed shut.

It wasn’t the only one.

…Ding! …ding! …ding! …ding! …ding!

The doors on the front and sides began to shut.

In an instant, the main lobby was isolated and shaped like a gladiatorial arena.

Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha!

Out of nowhere, a line of white-armored paladins appeared on the terrace on the second floor.

“….”

Vikir took a quick look around.

Normally a lobby and parlor, the room was designed to be converted into a battlefield in a pinch.

Indeed, with all five doors and corridors blocked, there was no escape in any direction, and above them was a siege network of ever-present paladins.

The various statues tucked into the corners provide no concealment, and once trapped, there is nothing to do but wait for judgment.

“….”

However, Vikir doesn’t react, just stands there in silence.

As if he had already anticipated this reaction.

Just then.

“Who are you?”

The gravelly voice came from among the statues on the first floor.

Beyond it, a man walks out into the center of the square.

Over two meters tall, with a scarred, shaven head, white armor and cloth wrapped around his entire body.

The man has no eyebrows, a noticeably large nose, and a large mouth.

His eyes were gently curved as if he were smiling, but the aura he gave off was quite harsh.

His arms, thick as logs, cradled a large book, which appeared to be a holy book of some sort.

Vikir squinted behind his gas mask.

‘…Inquisitor Mozgus. Long time no see.’

“Mozgus Quovadis. He was a friend of mine before I went back.”

A man I often trusted with my back in battle against demons.

His bulk is like an iron wall, and the holy power he emits can light up a thousand miles.

A man who would never compromise with injustice and could be more cruel than the demons themselves when it came to justice.

It was refreshing to see an old comrade-in-arms here, who had died so spectacularly during the Demon War, single-handedly facing off against a thousand demons.

“Come to think of it, I learned my torture techniques from him.”

Vikir recalled the memories of torturing the masters of the Seven Families in Underdog City.

But those beautiful (?) memories belong to Vikir alone, and in this life, Mozgus is seeing Vikir for the first time.

He held up a thick Bible that must have weighed dozens of kilograms and turned to Vikir.

“You are dressed suspiciously for someone who has come to report a plague in the slums, and I will not allow you to see the holy woman until you remove that mask and show some manners.”

“I can’t remove my gas mask for a reason. My duties are complete at the point of reporting, so I must return.”

Vikir dropped the bag of red death to the ground and raised his arms in a gesture of non-committal.

Then he slowly backed away.

“Blasphemer!”

Mozgus rushed forward.

He slammed his Bible, a weapon in its own right, down on Vikir’s head and tried to stamp on him.

But Vikir was faster.

Vikir took advantage of the gap in the book’s upward motion, and in a flash, he was back through the hollow between Mozgus’s sides.

Boom!

A deep crack appeared in the floor where Mozgus had struck with the book.

Vikir squinted at the white aura emanating from the corners of the pages of Mozgus’s personality book.

‘A book. You still wield an unusual weapon, and you’re an intermediate to advanced Gradient.’

Half as good as he was before his regression.

However, given that this was the home of the Quovadis and that he had the divine power to heal himself, it was almost a tie.

As he watched Vikir take up his stance, Mozgus let out a low growl.

“I sense an evil energy in the water in that stupid thing. If that is indeed a plague, you must be the one spreading it.”

“If I were the culprit, why would I come to report it?”

“We don’t know. Maybe it’s a trick, or maybe it’s a ruse to draw you out.”

Vikir shrugged, because it made sense.

“I’m just here to report a suspicious group of people spreading plague in the slums.”

“Your outfit is the most suspicious for saying such a thing. We’ll hear your statement later, in jail.”

With that, Mozgus swung the book around.

Parallax.

The book opened, the white pages inside flipping over with a loud crackle.

At the same time, bolts of white aura emanate from the pages, targeting Vikir.

“Have you ever been cut by stiff paper? It hurts.”

Mozgus was performing a strange and unique attack, opening the Bible and slashing with his aura against the sharp edges of the pages.

Quack, quack, quack!

Hundreds of pages of parchment scattered in all directions.

However, with a similarly black ghostly movement, Vikir dodged all of Mozgus’s blows.

It was a trick he had learned from the hunters of Ballak.

At the same time, Vikir drew the magic sword Beelzebub from his wrist.

…Blood!

The tip of the blade erupted with a sticky aura.

“Graduator!”

Mozgus and the other paladins were stunned.

Vikir’s aura, a powerful aura that was no match for Mozgus’s, was now intertwined with Mozgus’s aura, forming a tie.

Furthermore.

Vikir had even activated Oxbear’s skill, “Thousand Muscles,” which was sealed inside Beelzebub.

Vikir’s weight swelled to nearly 600 kilograms in an instant.

Mozgus looked down on Vikir’s small size and tried to push him with his strength, but when he couldn’t get him to budge, he was extremely puzzled.

“It’s like pushing a boulder! What the…!?”

It’s not surprising that Mozgus, no matter how big and strong he is, can’t be as physical as Oxbear.

Vikir wielded Beelzebub as he was.

A Baskervillian carnivore, a lurking ambusher.

It looked nothing like a Baskerville on the outside, but it was a Baskerville on the inside.

Its hidden teeth shredded Mozgus’s aura to pieces.

It wasn’t a known swordsmanship anyway, so revealing a bit wouldn’t give him away.

Vikir drew a long blade from his wrist and formed six teeth.

He slashed at Mozgus’s head, neck, both shoulders, and both backs.

“…Cough!?”

Mozgus tried to cover the Bible and hold it up as a shield, but… was too late.

“If you’re going to use it as a shield, you should have used it sooner.”

Vikir slashed the back of Mozgus’s hand as he grabbed the Bible.

A moment.

…Roar!

The breath of Cerberus, the Hound of Hell, blazed hotly from the tip of Beelzebub.

The unquenchable flames of the oil field scorched the back of Mozgus’s hand.

“Aaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!”

Mozgus rolled on the ground, clutching the back of his burning hand.

The fire of Cerberus cannot be extinguished by water or sand.

Palak-palak-palak!

The torn pages of the holy book were consumed by flames.

Vikir looked at the fallen Mozgus and sheathed his sword for a moment. He had not come here to kill him.

But.

“You blasphemer! What sorcery are you practicing!”

Mozgus’s fighting spirit was immense.

With a burst of divine power, he grabbed the water flowing down the statue’s mouth and turned it into holy water.

Push, push, push!

Suddenly, the fire on the back of Mozgus’s hand was extinguished. The fire on the back of his hand was extinguished.

But even with the hasty extinguishing of the fire, the battle was already won.

Mozgus felt a lump in his throat.

He looked up and saw that Vikir had already stepped on the thick holy book and was standing on top of it.

“Stepping on a holy book is blasphemy!”

“By that measure, your throwing and swinging the holy book is worse.”

“….”

Mozgus was forced to keep his mouth shut.

Vikir spoke, boiling a black aura with the tip of his outstretched awl.

“Do you wish to try more?”

“….”

Mozgus clenched his teeth at the arrogance in his voice.

How many other beings in the world were capable of pushing him like this, even though he had reached the upper ranks of the Graduators?

Mozgus clenched his fists tightly together and summoned his aura with all his might.

Quack, quack, quack!

Mana spinning at high speed quickly enveloped his entire forearm.

“Iyaaab!”

Mozgus charged with all his might. With enough to blast the opponent in front of him with a single punch.

But.

Vikir didn’t react.

…Thud!

He merely kicked the holy book off the ground.

Boom!

Next, Vikir kicked the Bible into the air.

The Bible spun and flew toward Mozgus.

Mozgus had just turned his head to dodge it.

“…!”

He had to doubt his eyes.

Vikir, the man who had been in front of him until the Bible was a thin straight line across his eyes, disappeared from view in that brief moment when the Bible stood vertically and took up a large area.

“Where?”

I screamed. A cold sweat runs down my spine.

Suddenly, I hear a ghostly whisper in my ear.

“…Looking for me?”

In the fraction of a second it took for the book to fly and spin, Vikir was out of Mozgus’s line of sight and holding onto his back.

Mozgus spun around in surprise.

…BANG!

Vikir’s aura slammed into Mozgus’s entire body.

Swung like a hammer, Vikir’s aura shattered Mozgus’s full body armor like grains of sand, and even the chainmail he wore was shattered.

Uh-oh! Thud!

Mozgus smashed through three statues behind him and fell to the ground.

The paladins on the second floor terrace could only gape at the shocking result.

They had never seen Mozgus Quovadis, Inquisitor, Archbishop of Quovadis Family, and leader of the Knights of the Inquisition, lose so easily.

“Am I dreaming?”

“Lord Mozgus has been defeated?”

“No way, how could this happen…!”

But after a moment of confusion, they drew their swords in unison like the elite of the Quovadis and leapt to the first floor.

“Get that blasphemer!”

White auras rose from everywhere.

Vikir adjusted the gas mask that covered his face.

“Quite the way to deal with a stray lamb.”

The paladins who had jumped from the second floor now surrounded the front.

What’s more.

Gurgling.

Behind them, among the shattered remains of the statues, Mozgus heaved himself to his feet.

He had stripped off all of his shattered and distorted armor and was clutching a large shard of stone with both hands.

Blood was dripping from his body, but it didn’t seem to bother him at all.

“Only if you want to see the end.”

Vikir drew his magic sword, Beelzebub, as long as he could.

A sticky liquid aura, a testament to his advanced graduator status, bubbled and boiled at the tip of the blade.

All the paladins, including Mozgus, tensed at the overwhelming momentum Vikir exuded, a black ghostly figure.

They couldn’t close their eyes, couldn’t swallow their saliva.

The slightest slip of the tongue would be enough for that black ghost’s teeth to tear at their throats and hearts.

“Where did this monstrosity come from….?”

Mozgus regretted his rashness and took a stance.

One-on-one, a must-lose.

Many against one, half and half.

The opponent was a creature that could not be completely defeated, even with all of the paladins here, including himself.

Normally, he would have taken a step back and formally declared a crusade….

“There is a saint here.”

The stakes were too high for him to take any chances.

Vikir, Mozgus, and the rest of the paladins stood in a tense confrontation.

“…Stop!”

A voice shattered everyone’s concentration.

A figure poked its head out from the terrace on the third floor.

It was Saint Dolores, and she was here.

Chapter 77

The Saintess (1)

◆

Dolores L. Quovadis.

A saintess who turned 16 this year, she is the most likely candidate to become the next head of the Quovadis family.

An undisputed prodigy of the Imperial Academy Colosseo, she hasn’t missed a single class since she entered her freshman year using the early admission system, and now in her sophomore year, she is the vice president of the student council.

Her appearance reminded Vikir of a time before the regression.

In the distant past, she had been a saintess, traveling to the front lines of battle against demons and healing the sick, demonstrating firsthand what it meant to be a living saintess.

Called an angel of the battlefield, she saved countless lives, a living example of goodness.

Although she is still young, she already has a strong heart and a clear mind.

Vikir, like all humans who have lived through the Age of Destruction, had respect and affection for the young saintess.

Vikir bowed his head, and the paladins nearby flinched.

Dolores paused, too.

Her senses were acute, and she could smell the animal scent of Vikir’s soul, the smell of blood, the smell of oil, and the smell of violence, anger, and hatred.

And, at the center of all those swirling emotions, the smell of a terrible sadness, hidden deep within.

“Are you a lost sheep?”

“…Yes.”

Vikir answered with a locked throat.

Dolores nodded.

“You look more like a… puppy than a sheep.”

“….”

“A scarred little puppy.”

As Dolores finished speaking, the faces of all the paladins gathered on the first floor turned a shade of red.

Mozgus exclaimed as well.

“Paladin, that’s not a puppy! That’s a blood-crazed wolf! You need to step back now….”

“Bring me tea.”

Dolores raised her hand to stop Mozgus from speaking.

Then he said in a very firm tone.

“I need to talk to him.”

◆

Soon, a small parlor was set up with a table, chairs, and two teacups.

Warm, steaming cups of peppermint tea.

At the entrance to the parlor, a large Mozgus stood fidgeting.

In his hand, he held a small teapot with a floral design that looked like a large ring.

A small table was placed in the center of the room, and Vikir and Dolores sat across from each other.

Dolores sounded surprised.

“When I heard that Mr. Mozgus had come out, I was surprised and came to see you, because I thought you were going to get hurt a lot.”

Mozgus has the temperament and philosophy of an inquisitor. So does his body.

So there was no reason for him to take kindly to the suspiciously dressed visitor.

But who knew?

That the man who was the military backbone of the Quovadis would be defeated so spectacularly.

Suddenly, Mozgus spoke up from beside him.

“Saintess. I didn’t lose, if it had been a long game, the odds were definitely in my favor….”

The mere fact that he says this is a sign of defeat.

Dolores thought to herself.

“Mr. Mozgus was one of the few Graduators in the Empire, and if he can be defeated so easily, I can’t imagine why anyone would want to….”

She stared at Vikir’s mask in front of her.

But there was nothing she could read in it.

As Vikir stared down at the teacup in front of him, Dolores spoke again.

“I don’t think you can drink tea with that gas mask on.”

Vikir nodded silently.

He hadn’t said anything since earlier, so Dolores decided to cut to the chase.

“I’ve been under a lot of stress lately.”

Vikir’s head snapped up at her words.

Stressed about what? The studies at the academy? Or a home school class?

But Dolores shook her head.

“I’m taking a break from the academy and my family’s affairs because it’s vacation time. It’s the nobles and merchants you saw just now who are really bothering me.”

They dragged their sick bodies to the saintess and begged her to heal them.

Unwelcome visitors, begging for money or prestige.

“The things they ask me to cure are obvious: erectile dysfunction, sexually transmitted diseases, drug side effects – nothing really serious.”

If he had the divine power to heal them, Dolores said, he’d rather help people who are really struggling and sick.

“Justice, righteousness, charity, equality, and the will of God may be these things… but people are too blinded by what’s in front of them.”

Vikir nodded in agreement.

“This is inevitable, since theology is essentially a process of understanding human beings.”

It was a phrase he’d often heard from her mouth when he’d met Dolores on the front lines of the war before he’d regressed.

Vikir had only briefly recalled a memory from long ago, but Dolores’ eyes widened at the sight before him.

Even Mozgus, who stood in the doorway.

“Old Testament, Azmoth, chapter 6, verse 9. Very philosophical and profound.”

“….”

“I can’t believe you know these old words. You must be well versed in theology. Are you a member of the Church of the Runes?”

Vikir was silent for a moment.

He didn’t know or care about Runes, the state religion of the Empire, so it seemed like a good time to change the subject.

“More than that. There is a plague in the slums of St. Mecca.”

“…Is that reliable information?”

“You’ve seen the water in the streets. It comes straight from the wells of the slums.”

“You didn’t have anything to do with it?”

“Why else would I have come here of my own accord?”

Vikir spoke again.

“I hate to see innocent people harmed. Especially since this is my home.”

“Oh, is this your home? I’m from here, too.”

Dolores’ eyes twinkled at Vikir’s words.

It was the first time she had heard of his homeland, so Vikir simply shook his head.

“I believe in absolutes, too. I hope the plague will be eradicated soon.”

“A rough soul, but… a good one, you are.”

Dolores turned serious.

“You told Mr. Mozgus earlier that you saw some suspicious people, didn’t you?”

“Yes, sir. I saw them pouring liquid in vials all over the wells.”

“If this plague is man-made… who spread it and for what purpose?”

Dolores seemed to be thinking a lot.

Plagues are not a simple matter.

Once a plague starts to spread, the hardest hit are institutions where many people live in community, usually monasteries and schools.

When a plague hits a monastery, the number of priests decreases, and cults, religions, and superstitions begin to flourish, requiring even more priests.

In this way, when uneducated and inexperienced priests go out into the field, more heresies, cults, superstitions, and so on are created.

Thus, in the event of a plague, the Quovadis would be at a significant political disadvantage.

To prevent this from happening, they would have to suppress the Red Death early.

Vikir’s answer was brief.

“Those who wish for the downfall of House Quovadis, and those who profit from it.”

“…That’s particularly difficult.”

Dolores furrowed her brow in thought.

Even her mind, rumored to be the brightest in the academy, could not predict the future.

But Vikir knew what was coming, that’s right, because I’ve experienced all of these things before returning.

With that, Vikir drew a map from his bosom.

The locations of the Seven Houses, circled around the ecliptic of the Empire.

Vikir pointed them out, explaining them to Dolores.

“Those who stand to gain the most are the Leviathan and the Bourgeois.”

The extremely poisonous Leviathan will use this opportunity to collect samples from numerous patients, investigate, study, and improve the plague to use as their own weapon.

Since they are a family that uses poison and medicine as their main weapons, the fact that a strong plague has spread is a very good thing for them.

Furthermore, the fall of their arch-enemy, the Quovadis, would be a blessing in disguise for the Leviathan.

In addition, the oligarchic bourgeois were also likely to see significant reflexive gains.

Gold and silver treasures do not disappear in a plague.

The deaths of the workers would bankrupt the landowners, and their warehouses, gold and silver coins, banknotes, and production facilities would be taken over by the bourgeois.

Once the bourgeois has gobbled up the dead and empty factories, farms, stores, guilds, and other real estate capital, they can use their accumulated wealth to start new businesses.

Fashion businesses for the newly wealthy, health supplements for those who remember the horrors of the plague, and so on… sales will soar like crazy.

‘Merchants from bourgeois families would visit Ballak’s villages and try to buy up antlers and ginseng and things like that, right?’

Vikir thought to himself.

‘The ones spreading the Red Death must have been Leviathans, the extremists.

And they probably have a tycoon Bourgeois as an ally.

It was highly likely that they were trading information with each other.

The religious Quovadis and the natives of the jungle are the scapegoats.

“…Therefore, for these reasons, I believe they may be intimately involved in the plague. Just a hypothesis, of course.”

Vikir had actually seen, heard, and experienced the events before his regression, and he was able to flesh them out a bit.

What?

I don’t feel much of a reaction from the front.

“…?”

Vikir tilted his head slightly, as if looking for something.

Then he sees the faces of Dolores and Mozgus behind the gas masks.

Both were frozen in place, their mouths half open.

Chapter 80

The Saintess (4)

◆

When Vikir first came to the barracks where only seriously ill patients were gathered, the priests’ reaction was as follows.

“This is no place for a layman.”

“You could be infected, get out now!”

“Help? We don’t need it, you’re in the way!”

But when Vikir began walking among the patients and blessing them, the priests’ expressions changed.

“That’s not how you bless.”

Vikir said to the priest who was using holy power on a red spot on a patient’s leg.

In general, a priest’s primary ability is to pray to a God to receive a share of his power and to use it to recreate some of the heavenly phenomena on earth.

In its simplest form, the priest asks the god to share his power, the god accepts and sends the power, and the priest receives the power to heal the patient.

If the patient also believes in the same God, the priest’s request for power from the God becomes a kind of guarantee, and the healing effect is amplified.

In short, more divine power is available to the same believer.

This is especially true if the priest or patient has a deep connection to the gods, such as through prolonged prayer or evangelizing.

This was similar to the correlation between a bank’s credit rating and lending.

But.

Priests could only use divine power within certain limits.

How much piety you’ve had.

How celibate, how sacrificial, how much you prayed, how many times you said God’s name, how much you donated, how much you volunteered, and how long you’ve been devoted to God would limit the amount of holy power you could exert.

A priest with 1 divine power could perform 1 miracle, and a priest with 10 divine power could perform 10 miracles.

This was common sense.

But.

Vikir knew.

How a priest with 1 holy power could perform 10 miracles, and a priest with 10 holy power could perform 100 miracles.

“…There’s a concept known as short selling.”

It was a deceptive method discovered by priests in the Age of Destruction as they struggled to make up for their ever-increasing lack of divine power.

In commerce, short selling means “selling what you don’t have”.

In commerce, short selling means “selling something you don’t have,” which means that you don’t have it, but you sell it up front to get the money and then buy it back later to pay for it.

When the time of destruction came, many priests despaired in the face of the swarming demons and the even greater number of patients.

Their own divine powers were not enough to stop the catastrophe.

So the gods of the Rune religion, watching on, came up with a plan.

They drastically increased the amount of divine power available to priests who had performed well and consistently.

This allowed high-ranking priests to perform far more miracles than usual in times of crisis.

But even so, they still didn’t have enough holy power.

Demons and beasts that came out of the oil world literally devastated the human world.

The gods became even more desperate.

It was then that the priests began to awaken.

They began to unleash divine powers that would normally have been unthinkable.

Even their empty mana vessels were able to exert divine power.

Act first, report later. Let’s make a miracle and see what happens.

Any divine power that you have saved up in advance can be used later with interest to make up for it or recover it, but you should use all of it that you can draw from right away.

The journey of creating and using divine power and then repaying it through faithful activities.

Some call it ‘borrowing holy power’, some call it ‘shorting holy power’, and some self-helpfully call it ‘begging for holy power’.

Even those who weren’t priests and had killed a lot of demons were allowed to use some holy power, as it was a time when killing demons to earn karma (experience) was considered a religious activity.

Vikir had slain countless demons, and the karma had been accumulating nicely, stored in his soul.

This was true even after his regression.

As such, the current Vikir is the only one who can wield divine power without being a priest.

However, there was a slight limitation on the use of holy power without being a member of Rune: it could only be done within a sanctuary.

Where Vikir currently stood was the realm of the Faithful Quovadis, and thus a sanctuary.

Vikir walked over to the moaning man and reached out.

…Pit!

A weak stream of holy power began to heal the patient’s body.

The priests, wide-eyed at the sight of Vikir’s holy power, rushed over to watch.

It was the first time they had ever seen someone who was not a priest of House Quovadis use holy power.

Moreover, Vikir was a master at using holy power efficiently.

“That, too, I have learned from surviving the Age of Destruction.”

Priests treating a patient in a mad rush. Looking over their shoulders, Vikir learned how to use divine power.

It was simple, really.

A simple one, in fact: slit the wound with a scalpel and let the holy power seep straight through to the primary injury.

A great deal of divine power is wasted in performing miracles by laying on skin, holding hands, or casting blessings from afar.

Instead, it was most efficient to channel the divine power concentrated at the source of the pain.

Vikir took his scalpel and made small incisions in the reddened spots, channeling holy power through the flowing blood.

The sanctuary of the Quovadis was filled with grace, and Vikir was able to draw upon a significant amount of holy power.

Of course, since he was not a priest, he could not use it for long.

And the priests who had witnessed Vikir’s miracles and performances were beginning to flock to him one by one.

Survival skills that could be used by anyone in the Age of Destruction were considered unheard of and unrivaled here.

Moreover.

The priests’ surprise was not yet over.

Vikir has been delaying the spread of patients with a combination of all kinds of herbs he has picked from the waters of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

It was something he had learned from the warriors of Ballak during the last two years of living in depth.

A medicine that would not stop the plague, but would delay its spread and suffering as long as possible.

Made from recipes and ingredients unknown to the empire, it reduced the fevers and groans of the patients, at least a little.

Like this. Vikir moved among the patients, taking in their filth and their complaints, and yet calmly and silently tending to them all.

This, of course, was done for a reason.

First, to give confidence to the priests of Quovadis, second, to take the essence of the holy water to his friends in faraway lands, and third, out of compassion for those who had died the red death because of him.

“….”

Everyone watched Vikir’s miracle with their mouths half open.

Then.

“Aaahhh- Mommy! Mommy!”

A child cries, shaking the body of a lying woman.

The woman’s body was still pale in color, though a few red spots had sprung up.

The problem was that her body was dangerously weak even in this state.

Vikir placed his hand on the child’s head.

“Don’t worry. I’ll cure your mother right away.”

After saying this, Vikir lifted the disease from the woman’s body.

He also grabbed a bunch of gold coins from his pocket and handed them to the child.

“Sickness is sickness, but you are malnourished. Use this to buy food and firewood to care for your mother.”

The child hangs his head in shame, his face covered in tears and snot.

Then, seeing the child receive the money, many sick people rushed to Vikir.

They, too, stretch out their hands for money.

One of the priests was puzzled and said to Vikir.

“No, no material help, there’s no limit, you’ll have to give them all the money you have!”

Vikir shrugged it off.

“Why shouldn’t there be a limit? There’s definitely a limit to the money in my pocket, and I’ll just have to give it all away.”

With that, Vikir distributed the money to the sick people around him and their families.

Vikir then discarded the empty leather pouch without a trace of regret and returned to his work.

The priests stood dumbfounded, shocked once more.

St. Dolores was one of them.

“….”

She gazed at Vikir’s broad back and remembered what had happened earlier.

The young men who had flirted with her.

They boasted of their noble status and vast wealth, showering the slums with donations and supplies.

But their demeanor was arrogant, and in their hearts they despised and looked down on the poor.

But what about Vikir? He didn’t hesitate to give away all the money in his pocket.

Though the amount was small, it was a great act of sharing and sacrifice.

This is why the Bible says that a beggar who gives a bowl of porridge may be more noble than a rich man who gives a thousand gold coins.

Dolores thought silently.

In a place where filth and pestilence reigned supreme, this man worked harder than anyone else to help the less fortunate.

A man who seems to have lived on the front lines of a fierce battle.

This man with the aura of a pilgrim, a seeker, a prophet.

This man has a sad, lonely soul that doesn’t match his strong body.

A man who calls himself a hound, but inside he is a lost and tired puppy.

This man is crying and bleeding with his soul.

…Where the hell does he come from?

Suddenly, Dolores remembered a line he had muttered in a hushed voice some time ago.

“Theology is essentially a process of understanding human beings, so this is inevitable.”

And then.

…A thud!

A throbbing pulse, a fast-flowing bloodstream.

My heart dropped to the bottom of my chest once, and then came back up again.

A saint, and a still young and immature sixteen-year-old girl.

Dolores’s heart was beating fast.

Toward the faceless man in front of him.

Chapter 82

Lovesickness (1)

◆

Aiyen had a dream.

Her first memory was of being ripped apart by scorching flames and sharp claws.

Cerberus, the three-headed dog of hell.

This dangerous beast emerged from the depths of an oil pit and breathed hot air and snapped its teeth at the uninvited who trespassed on its territory.

As Madam Eight-Legs, the goddess of depths, expanded her territory, the warriors of Ballak were forced to follow her.

They were inevitably forced into a hunting ground dispute with Cerberus, and eventually succeeded in driving the original owner of the realm far away.

In the process, Aiyen was mortally wounded and dropped from the pack.

She thought she was going to die, but… still had a long life ahead of her.

Imperial slavers exploring the jungle found her dying, gave her minimal medical attention, and sold her into slavery.

Thrown into a cold cage by human beings without blood or tears. Aiyen feared death, or worse, doom.

Now it is self-evident that he will never come out of this cage, but will wither and die in agony.

His freedom to roam the vast depths is gone, and his honor as a proud warrior will be tarnished.

What will become of you?

Will you live a miserable life as a castle puppet for the greedy empire of Fatty? Or will he become a gladiatorial slave, doomed to fight demons until the day he dies, and end up as a mere piece of meat on the tables of gluttonous gourmets who lust after human flesh?

Aiyen’s body and mind were weakened by his festering wounds, his rising temperature, and the fact that she hadn’t had a sip of water in days.

As the proud jungle warrior fell to the ground, wings broken, dying a slow death.

A miracle happened.

A boy appeared with a white light.

He casually lifted the shroud of darkness over Aiyen’s fate and cast a beam of brilliant light.

Her eyes were immediately drawn to his beautiful appearance, his combat prowess, and most of all, his brave and regal demeanor, which she had never seen before in her life.

Had there ever been a warrior of her age capable of such strength?

Not even among the strong and brave warriors of the Ballak was there a man of such excellence, among an empire that thought only of them as cunning and dirty.

Through his fading consciousness, Aiyen watched as the slave traders who had mistreated him, treating him like an animal, cattle, were dragged away, all dead or with their limbs torn off.

That bloody night.

The boy took her out of the cage and sent her back to the home she’d always dreamed of.

And since then, Aiyen has never forgotten the boy’s face.

Aiyen has consistently crossed the borders of the Empire with the sole intention of finding Vikir.

To invade the Empire was to risk her life.

She crossed the border, sometimes in groups, sometimes alone, to find the boy.

Living in a small community in the jungle, she had no idea there were so many Imperials.

But the boy was extraordinary, and she knew that if she kept searching through the crowds, she would find him one day.

One by one, Ballak’s other companions achieved their goals.

A man in Ballak kidnapped a woman from the Empire to become his wife, and a woman from Ballak kidnapped a man from the Empire to become her husband.

One by one, her companions succeeded, but Aiyen continued her hunt.

She was waiting. For the one that would one day miraculously arrive. It was inevitable.

While all the other girls her age had captured and paired up with suitable men, Aiyen stood firmly alone.

She didn’t even look at other men.

Until one day.

Aiyen met a boy.

A boy, the same boy from the night before.

But in his arms was a different woman.

A woman. Aiyen felt a black fire boiling in his chest, a fire that burned only in the oil world.

But Aiyen was a cool headed woman, and she quickly tamed the flames within her.

She decided to dismiss the boy’s past favoritism toward women.

It’s not about the past that can’t be changed, it’s about the future they can build together.

The problem was, the boy didn’t fit into her plans at all.

The boy had grown stronger since their last meeting.

He fought brilliantly against several of Ballak’s warriors, proving himself extraordinary yet again.

The more he saw of the boy, the more he wanted him. To own him. To have him as her own.

And that desire grew stronger as she watched the boy charge at Madam Eight-Legs, unfazed.

In Ballak, brave warriors are treated as such. The boy deserved it.

So Aiyen turned to flee.

He wanted to save the boy, even if it meant being caught by the terrifying Madame.

…How could he even think of facing that monstrous creature?

His legs were shaking and he was breaking out in a cold sweat, but nevertheless, Aiyen pushed through his fear.

In a moment of crisis, she threw the lasso and succeeded in freeing the boy from the Madame’s eight legs.

Aiyen then brought the boy back to the tribe, his body ruined by his fight with the Madame.

There was some backlash.

The cranky old bastards didn’t like outsiders from the Empire.

Rumors that the boy might have ties to the Baskervilles, Ballak’s nemesis and arch-enemy, led many to suggest that he be executed.

It was Aiyen who steadfastly refused.

She argued that the boy had saved her life and that keeping him alive would benefit the tribe.

And her foresight was spot-on.

The more the boy recovered, the better for the tribe.

He went on hunts, brought back big prey, scolded traders who had always treated the natives poorly, and even provided cures for the plague.

Other than that, the days of living together in the village began to pass like a lightning bolt.

The days of pissing on each other, eating decoctions of bear genitals, hunting together, and bathing in the hot springs all blur together in a dreamy, Milky Way.

For some time now, Aiyen had really, truly wanted the boy.

It was a feeling that had long since transcended the simple concept of possessiveness.

…Just then.

“Sweetheart, get up.”

Someone shook Aiyen awake.

She lifted her heavy eyelids and looked straight ahead through blurred vision.

She could see the straw woven ceiling.

Aiyen was now lying in bed, sweating profusely.

He was flushed, his temperature was rising, he was losing his appetite, he was sweating profusely, and he was dehydrated.

With difficulty, Aiyen turned his head to look at the figure beside him.

The Ballak chieftain, Akwilla, stared down at him with concern.

Akwilla wiped Aiyen’s face with a damp cloth and spoke.

“You kept looking for Vikir in your sleep.”

“…It’s so painful, Mother, could this be the Red Death?”

Aiyen said, gasping for breath.

Then Akwilla squinted her eyes and examined her daughter’s entire body.

Aiyen lay without a single thread of clothing on her body.

Her temperature was rising, and she was sweating profusely. Her whole body is flushed red.

But there are no obvious spots.

Akwilla pondered.

“His symptoms are a little different from the other children with the Red Death…maybe it’s …, maybe it’s not.”

As she pondered, Aiyen frowned and clutched at her chest with her hand.

“The pain is getting worse, my chest hurts, my body is hot, and I feel like my heart is drying up.”

“Hang in there, girl. Vikir will be here soon. He’s the man you sent for.”

“…I’m fine without him, he’s not coming back.”

But despite her words, Aiyen’s anguish is palpable.

She turns to Akwilla, almost pleading.

“Mother, I’ve never been so sick before, to the point where I blame you for giving birth to me. I shouldn’t be like this, but the words ‘why did you give birth to me’ keep coming out of my mouth.”

As Aiyen sobbed, Akwilla held her close.

Not with the majesty of a chieftain, but with the compassion of a mother.

“My dear.”

Akwilla spoke softly to Aiyen.

“A long time ago. Me and your father planted a tiny little seed in the dirt.”

It was the first time Akwilla had ever told her father’s story, and Aiyen listened attentively through her fading consciousness.

Akwilla continued.

“Your father planted a seed in the soil and your mother watered it every day. Soon, the seed sprouted, and after a few months, it became a healthy, beautiful flower.”

Akwilla said, cupping her daughter Aiyen’s face in her hands.

Aiyen looked up at Akwilla with tearful eyes.

A warm, tender emotion rose between the mother and daughter that was hard to describe.

Finally, Akwilla finished.

“And so we picked the flower, crushed it, squeezed the juice out of it, soaked it in tobacco, smoked it, and, in a dazed and euphoric state, had unprotected sex. That day you were born.”

“….”

“Oh, and your father was executed by your grandfather the very next day for playing mean tricks with drugs.”

Aiyen looked a little defeated after learning the secret of his birth.

“ …My body aches even more, Mother.”

“Wait a little longer. If Vikir comes with a way to cure the plague….”

“Forget it, don’t torture my hopes, he’s not coming back! What slave in the world would come back when his leash is off…!?”

That moment. Akwilla and Aiyen’s conversation was cut off.

A commotion erupted from outside the door.

“Wow, they’re here!”

“ Vikir! Vikir is back!”

“A cure! He’s brought a cure!”

Akwilla, who had good ears, heard the shouts of joy from her tribe.

She turned her head, her face brightening.

“See, daughter, I did not tell you….”

But Akwilla couldn’t finish her sentence.

A bang!

In an instant, she was up and out of her seat, smashing through the wall.

As if she hadn’t been sick before, she climbed down the tree and ran at full speed.

Akwilla stares after her, mouth agape in disbelief.

“…Wasn’t that a red death?”

Chapter 83

Lovesickness (2)

◆

The Hound of the Night has returned.

By the time Vikir returned to Ballak’s village, the Red Death had spread across the lands.

Ballak built a house on the water and built a dam to trap the water, so the damage was small, but the conditions of other neighboring tribes were truly miserable.

Ahun was the first to come out when he heard that Vikir had returned.

He ran up to him, his face full of tears, and as soon as he saw Vikir, he threw himself into his arms.

“You’re back!”

Ahun had been visibly shaken for days.

He had barely eaten or slept since his only sister, Aheul, had fallen ill with the Red Death, and all he had done was care for her.

Ahun took Vikir’s hand through thick tears.

“Thank you for coming back. You are a loyal boy. It’s okay if you didn’t get the cure, just the fact that you came back like this….”

They seemed to misunderstand because Vikir had come empty-handed.

But Vikir had definitely brought it with him.

A miracle that would cure all his friends in the dephts.

“Follow me.”

“…?”

Vikir tugged a dazed Ahun along, heading straight for his barracks.

Ahun’s barracks, right near the entrance to the village, where Aheul lay moaning.

She was the first to be struck by the red death, so she was in the worst condition.

Her face is now halved, but she’s clean, free of dirt and foul odors, thanks to Ahun’s good care.

Without a second thought, Vikir took out the vial of Saint’s Tears.

…Pow!

The Saint’s Tears from his pocket hadn’t even opened the vial yet, yet it still exerted a strong divine power.

Surprisingly, the light emanating from the saint’s tears was enough to drive the red death out of Aheul’s body.

The red spots were disappearing.

The disease that had been tormenting him for so long had vanished with such ease.

“…! …! …! …!”

Ahun’s eyes widened to tears at the miraculous scene.

The fact that he was frozen in place, unable to even scream, gave him away.

Ahun stroked Aheul’s face with a trembling hand.

His face was contorted and sweating, but Aheul was asleep, looking more relaxed than he had in a long time.

All he could do was moan and sweat in a colorful rasp.

“…Vikir!”

Aheul called out breathlessly, and then a few more times in quick succession.

“ Vikir! Vikir! Vikir! Vikir!”

The tone was careful but reverent, like a devout priest saying the name of God in prayer, with infinite trust, affection, and joy.

And it was the same with Ahun’s closest associates.

Friends who had to witness the pain and sorrow of a friend they were close enough to trust with their lives.

They, too, could not help but chant his name vigorously in the face of his miraculous ability to blast away all their anxiety, bitterness, helplessness, and frustration with a single blow.

“Vikir! Vikir! Vikir! Vikir! Vikir!”

The sturdy Ballak warriors stamped their feet and cheered so loudly that the floating house nearly collapsed.

But Vikir remained calm in the midst of all the excitement.

He had just cured one patient. There was still a long way to go.

Vikir turned to Ahun and the other Ballak warriors.

“How many patients do you have?”

“About thirty, including Aheul.”

Vikir nodded at that.

It was still a relatively small number, one that could be suppressed early.

But they shouldn’t let their guard down.

Vikir was planning to not only destroy the entire plan of the poisonous master Leviathan, but also absorb all the ripple effects of it.

“What about the other tribes?”

Vikir asked, and Ahun replied with a dark look.

“It’s hopeless. Some of them have been all but wiped out, other tribes that didn’t build floating houses. But those who took your advice and built floating houses have suffered less.”

“How many patients are there, exactly?”

“I don’t know, but there are a lot of them, like the herds of buffalo in those hilly fields.”

Somewhere in the tens of thousands.

Vikir made a decision.

“Round up all the patients from the other tribes.”

“Huh? Other tribes? But there are so many cures?”

“Don’t worry, there are plenty. Let’s take this opportunity to show the other tribes some respect.”

Hearing Vikir’s words, Ahun and the other young warriors’ faces lit up.

Why should they care about the other tribes?

It is not unusual for tribes to be related by friendship or blood, even if they are strangers in a distant land.

They often had disputes over marriage and hunting, but they had a history of coming together in times of crisis.

Upon hearing Vikir’s words, Ballak’s warriors flew out of the village to spread the good news.

Meanwhile.

“….”

Vikir’s eyes shone as he looked into the tears of the saint.

“We can use this opportunity to put a lot of pressure on the Baskervilles.”

Vikir planned to take advantage of this opportunity to unite the enemy and the barbarian forces of the Black Mountains.

Baskerville is an Ironblade whose primary mission is to explore and destroy the Enemy and the Black Mountains.

Baskerville’s greatest enemies are not the other six Houses of the Empire.

It’s their enemies, the natives of the Black Mountains.

The warrior clan Ballak, the shaman clan Rokoko, and many other native factions are Baskerville’s most feared foes.

They pierced the sword-like blades of the forest with their bare skin and stomped barefoot on the forest floor, which seemed to be dotted with nails and tacks.

Thousands of paces away, arrows hit willow leaves, and axes and swords cut great beasts in half.

Such is the daily life of the natives of Red&Black Mountain.

If Vikir could get them on his side by paying them off, he could take on the entire Baskerville family single-handedly.

Moreover, if the natives were able to stem the plague early and grow stronger, they would naturally be able to put pressure on the Baskervilles and the Empire.

“For that to happen, we need to remain on friendly terms with them.”

Vikir is now a hero of Ballak.

But now he’s about to become the hero of the entire Jungle tribe.

The misdeeds of Leviathan, the Extremist, were working in Vikir’s favor.

“We’re running out of time. We must hurry before the death toll rises.”

Using the light from the saint’s tears, Vikir cured all of Ballak’s patients.

Now all that remained was to purify the water source.

The tears of the saint were to be sprinkled on the teats of the jungle, on the rivers that flowed from the highest places and spread to all the lowlands.

Vikir moved quickly.

He’d been living here for two years and already knew where the water sources were.

And with him came the entire tribe.

Even some of Ballak’s more unusual enemies bowed their heads as they entered, including the shamanic Rokoko, notorious for their cannibalism, and the berserker Renaissance, whose entire tribe could take on an entire company of the Empire with a single axe.

When the chieftain Akwilla led them all to the source of the water.

“All of you may drink of this water.”

Vikir sprinkled the tears of a saint into the river.

Suddenly, a bright light emanated from the entire vast river.

It was a beautiful sight, as if the Milky Way in the night sky had descended to earth and was flowing.

Mesmerized by this mysterious light, the natives spontaneously scooped up water from the river with their hands.

And a miracle happened.

The “red death” began to die.

“Oh-oh-oh-oh!”

The entire jungle erupted in a shout that seemed to carry away.

Akwilla, the Ballak chieftain, cried out in excitement.

“Vikir, I must appoint you shaman of our tribe!”

The Night Fox praises the Night Hound.

All the other tribes gathered here shout out to Vikir, each in their own language and gestures.

They all have different ways of expressing themselves, but they all want to express the same thing.

The expressions of love, respect, and gratitude were heartwarming.

The plague patients, whether they were family members, friends, or patients themselves, dropped to one knee in front of Vikir and paid him the utmost respect.

This means that everyone in the jungle is grateful to Vikir.

Even the crooked old men who had been viewed unfavorably within the Ballak bowed deeply to Vikir.

It was heartfelt gratitude for saving their sons, daughters, sons-in-law, daughters-in-law, grandsons, and granddaughters.

Meanwhile.

“…?”

Vikir was looking for someone in addition to treating countless patients.

A face he’d heard had the Red Death, but couldn’t figure out why he couldn’t see.

Vikir looked around for a long time, but the face he was looking for was nowhere to be found among the cloud of patients.

Just then.

Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.

The sound of footsteps.

Vikir knew from the sound alone that the person he was looking for had arrived.

He turned his head.

Puck.

Something rushes at me at breakneck speed, slamming into me.

Aiyen. She rushes forward and wraps her arms around Vikir’s body.

Thud!

Muscles clench, bones scream.

I had to raise the mana because I thought I might break my back the moment I got out of the way.

Next, Vikir grabs Aiyen’s cheek as she buries her face in his chest.

“I thought you had the Red Death?”

But Aiyen’s face, staring up at Vikir, was intact.

There was no redness in her body, no sweat. Her complexion was normal.

The only thing that bothered him was the youthful blush across her face.

Just to be on the safe side, Vikir splashed some holy water on her face, but the flush didn’t subside.

She looks down at herself with a puzzled expression.

“What is …?”

She scratched her head in confusion.

He looked up into Vikir’s face again and said.

“You’re feeling better, aren’t you?”

Chapter 89

The Ghosts of the Ancestors (1)

◆

“If you don’t know what you’re going to get, don’t bother making anything.”

That’s what Hugo Le Baskerville used to say whenever he had to forge the Seven Teeth.

He has always faced many challengers, and he has always managed to put them under his knife.

Among those who have challenged Hugo in the meantime, there are many who have performed unexpected and unpredictable actions such as surprise attacks, assassinations, ambushes, betrayals, and curses, but in the end, all of them were useless.

Overwhelming strength.

In front of that, all variables and surprises are bound to degenerate into mere tricks.

And Vikir was putting that lesson to use this time.

[Grrrrr…]

The only difference was that the overwhelming power was not his own, but someone else’s.

<Oxbear>.

Danger Rating: A

Size: 5 meters

Found in: Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, 7th Ridge

-A giant bear with two massive horns.

A carnivorous bear, the strongest terrestrial predator, and a perfect killing machine, it is considered the strongest and pinnacle of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain 7th Ridge ecosystem.

They have few natural enemies other than their own kind.

A bear with two massive horns.

Standing at around five meters tall and weighing a ton, it is one of the most dangerous beasts in the world.

This oxbear was even familiar with Vikir.

“…A scruffy, blind female.”

This oxbear was more than twice as tall as the others, and weighed more than twice as much.

If I had to rate this one, I’d give it an A+ or better.

This was the old female’s territory, where the Iliad was taking place.

Vikir knew the location from a previous joint hunt with Aiyen, and had deliberately made a big fuss to attract the female oxbear.

Ah’Heman, who had never been out hunting, hadn’t realized it, and that’s why he’d suffered this fate.

“Ugh….”

Ah’Heman desperately wiped the frothy saliva from the corner of his mouth with both hands.

Oxbear strained his ears to hear what was going on around him.

‘It seems that his already bad eyes got worse.’

This, too, was something Vikir already knew.

Shhh.

Vikir fell backwards silently.

<Binge Fly ‘Beelzebub’>/ Awl

-Slot 1: Burn – Cerberus (A+)

Slot -2: Silent Hill – Mushuhushu(A+)

-Slot 3: Sacrum – Oxbear(A)

Thanks to the skill I gained from capturing the giant snake Mushuhushu a while ago, my steps are silent.

Ah’Heman, on the other hand, can’t help but groan in pain as Cerberus’ fire still burns in the wound Vikir left behind.

“Hmph! Hmph!”

Add to that the fact that his back, which had been struck by Oxbear’s forepaw just moments before, was now feeling the impact.

The slowly recognizable pain, and the constant barrage of pain, eventually forced Ah’Heman’s bloodied lips to twist open.

“Aaaaaaah!”

And Oxbear responded to the sound immediately.

Thwack!

Oxbear slammed its front paws together, sending the lower half of Ah’Heman flying.

He spun like a top and crashed into a tree, his legs and back bent in a strange way.

[Crunch!]

Oxbear once again unleashed his fury on the intruder.

[Screech- Screech-]

Her ears perk up at the sound of a cry from behind her.

He spun around to see two wide-eyed Oxbear cubs.

Their sturdy builds were uncharacteristic of cubs, and their glowing eyes hinted at intelligence.

The female oxbear snorted at the intruders before turning back to her cubs.

At this point, she must have decided that she had demonstrated her motherly majesty and resolve.

And then.

Vikir reappeared outside the bush.

Ah’Heman was lying on the ground, motionless.

But he was clearly still breathing, as his shaky breathing could be felt.

Rustle-pass-sac

The leaves rustled around him.

The warriors of Ballak, who have been watching the Iliad, are gathering.

All the warriors surrounded Vikir and Ah’Heman.

The winners and losers were all too clear. Vikir was unscathed, and Ah’Heman, though alive, was literally hanging on for his life.

“It’s over. We have a winner.”

“At this point, doesn’t it matter if Ah’Heman is innocent or not?”

“Regardless of who’s the innocent one, Ah’Heman was just too ugly.”

“I think it turned out very well.”

The warriors each had their say.

From the Red Plague to the present day Iliad, they’d all had their own disappointments with Ah’Heman, big and small.

And as he listened to what they had to say about him, he sank to the ground like a worm, shivering.

“Why! Why!”

Ah’Heman was screaming.

What was the difference between him and this Vikir in front of him?

Why is his path so different from his own, even though they were both brought as slaves from a foreign land?

He thought of all the years of misery he had endured.

And all that Vikir had.

Youth. The daughter of a chieftain who followed him. The trust of all her peers around it. The support and love of his tribe years ago. Her extraordinary abilities and radiant appearance.

And yet, that glint in those eyes, as if he didn’t care about any of it.

“…! …! …!”

Ah’Heman gritted his teeth. He grinded his gums, even though all his teeth were missing.

He tore his eyes away from Vikir and looked at himself.

Old. An old shaman who treated himself like a sex puppet. Despised and ignored by all his friends. Used and abandoned by the Empire. Unrecognized abilities and a body that was now crippled.

The inferiority complex, defeat, hatred, anger, resentment, and compensatory feelings of an old man who has lost everything to a young man who has everything.

And.

“….”

Ahun quickly turns away from the gaze that met his.

The last straw. His grandson’s exterior ignited Ah’Heman’s emotions, causing them to explode.

Meanwhile.

“….”

Ahun’s head was turned away, his fists balled tightly.

Then a hand clapped him on the shoulder.

Vikir. He looked at Ahun with calm eyes.

“How about taking care of it with your own hands?” he said.

“…I don’t want to.”

Ahun shook his head. He almost lost his sister during the Red Death.

He could never forgive his grandfather for that.

There was also bitterness and anger at the way he had treated her and his sister all these years.

But Vikir shook his head.

“It wouldn’t be a bad thing to protect him at the last minute. It’s not just for the sake of justice, but also to prevent any unforeseen situation…….”

“Enough! That coward deserves to die, he’s not worthy of pity!”

Ahun slapped Vikir’s hand away and turned away once more.

Just then.

Ku-oh-oh-oh!

Something happened.

All over the grounds, strange currents of mana began to form.

Crackle, crackle, crackle!

The sound of bones interlocking, and the corpses of the orangutans that had been struck by Oxbear’s front paws earlier began to rise again.

They shed their heavy garments of rotting flesh and picked up their skeletal bodies.

Ballak’s warriors cringed at the sight of the dead.

The orangutan corpses soon moved like strung marionettes, walking over to help Ah’Heman to his feet.

Then. He raised his bloodshot eyes to look at Vikir, to Ahun beside him, and to all of Ballak’s warriors beyond.

“…I don’t need you. All of you.”

Ah’Heman gave up. He wasn’t talking about the Iliad.

He meant giving up everything he had as a warrior of Ballak.

And.

As soon as one Ballak was gone, one Rokoko was born.

As soon as he abandoned his warrior’s pride, Ah’Heman began to practice a part of command that had been taboo, even practiced within the Rokoko itself.

A forbidden incantation to call the dead back to the land of the living.

When the Ballak warriors heard him recite the incantation, they gave him a look of disdain.

“What is this, another one of your stupid resurrection spells?”

“How ugly. Even though you claim to be a shaman,….”

“But what can we do, we don’t even have monkeys to resurrect anymore!”

There are no more dead bodies in this neighborhood.

At most, a few orangutans here were the only dead that Ah’Heman could raise.

But.

“…!”

Vikir snapped.

He realized that Ah’Heman’s spell was not directed here, but a little further away.

Vikir turned his head to follow the direction of the black mana stream.

There he saw a familiar place.

A valley and waterfall rising high above the low rolling hills, and a spring of dragon’s water flowing beneath it.

It was the Tomb of the Brave, where all of Ballak’s ancestors were said to be buried.

Chapter 90

The Ghosts of the Ancestors (2)

◆

Goo Wook… Goo Kook…

The orangutan corpses began to move.

Although they had only been dead for a short time, their skin was already turning to mush and decaying, revealing hollow bones here and there.

In fact, all living things come from nature and return to nature, meaning that their bodies belong to nature.

Coming from nature and returning to nature is a great providence, a kind of contract to be recognized as a member of the ecosystem.

However.

There are some beings who, after the end of their lives and the time period in which they were given a body, do not return it to nature.

The undead.

They don’t return to nature, even though they came from it by nature.

They are like tenants in a house that is already on a contract.

The ghosts are forcibly occupying a body that, according to providence and the contract of life, should have been returned to nature.

Therefore, nature takes action to reclaim the body.

As the law of nature dictates, all things return to the earth.

In order to reclaim the body from the wraith, nature speeds up the decay of the flesh, so that the undead are always left with nothing but rotting flesh, stinking guts, and hollow bones.

This is why most undead are rotting or skeletal.

…But.

Occasionally, wraiths who possessed noble powers in life were able to resist the laws of nature with even greater strength.

They defy the laws of nature with bodies and strength that are not nearly as damaged as they were when they were alive.

Woodchuck! Woodchuck! Woodchuck! Woodchuck!

Such were the undead that were now crawling out of the valiant’s grave.

“…This is unbelievable!”

Aiyen’s mouth dropped open.

Crawling out of the stone and dirt tombs in the valley, they were skeletons, skinny and dry.

They wore shrouds made of black panther pelts, and their eyes glowed with the black emptiness of skeletons.

They were once, long ago, great warriors and leaders of the Ballak.

Carrying bows, spears, swords, axes… and their buried loved ones, the undead have risen to the surface and are swarming this way in unison.

<Death Knight>

Danger Rating : A ~ S

Size : ?

Found in : ?

-Named ‘Death Knight’.

A corrupted and transformed being who once touched the heights of the living, the dark mana they draw from their souls and bodies is held as collateral until every muscle and vein in their bodies bursts.

Most lose their sanity and spew empty hatred and blind rage.

However, sometimes there are death knights with intelligence, but it is said that there are only seven cases in human history where such objects have appeared.

Usually, Death Knights are fierce and aggressive, and to compensate for this, they are often equipped with thick, heavy armor.

But the resurrected ancestors of Ballak were approaching with the speed of the wind, wearing nothing but a fluttering robe on the dark currents.

Answering the maddening hatred that Ah’Heman was spewing.

Then, Chief Akwilla spoke.

“All, prepare for battle!”

As soon as the words left, Aiyen drew his bow and fired.

Aiming for Ah’Heman, who struggled on the ground.

But one of the Death Knights, running at breakneck speed, fired an arrow before he could.

Puff, puff, puff!

Arrows of tremendous power flew out and began to escort Ah’Heman.

“Heh-heh heh! Die all! All gone!”

Hiding behind the Death Knights, Ah’Heman was rapidly aging.

He had stretched his life force beyond its limits, manipulating the Death Knights.

Soon, the skeletal, faceless Deathknights stood in the way of Ballak’s warriors with swords and spears.

The warriors of Ballak face the past and the present at once.

The warriors of the Old Era and the warriors of the New Era face off against each other.

“The time has come to teach the heroes of the past a lesson. How scary the kids are these days!”

Aiyen fired the first arrow.

Ping-!

Her arrow was filled with a powerful silver aura.

However, to her surprise, the Death Knight in front of her grabbed the arrow with his hand.

…Crisp!

The arrow was blocked, but there was no way he could have gotten away with holding it with his bare hands.

The Death Knight shook his head as he watched the hand that held the arrow turn to dust and crumble.

Perhaps when he was alive, he would have had no trouble catching it.

But now, weakened as he was by decay, he would not have been able to adapt to his deteriorated body.

Then.

Boom!

The Death Knight behind him swung his sword.

A sharp blow flew out, slicing through everything in its path.

The speed was faster than expected, causing Aiyen to panic.

…Boom!

There was someone who deflected the Death Knight’s blow. It was Vikir.

And now.

Vikir scattered his hands towards the two charging Death Knights.

A moment. A white powder flew from Vikir’s hands and landed in the faces of the Death Knights.

Chiiiit!

Smoke billowed out, accompanied by the sound of burning leather.

The Death Knights grimaced in pain and stepped back.

“Be careful. Each one is a named demon.”

Aiyen giggled at Vikir’s advice.

She bent at the waist and stuck her ass out as far as it would go, patting Vikir’s thigh.

“After all, you are the only man I can trust with my back.”

“….”

“Oh, of course, I’m asking you to cover my rear in battle. I hope you don’t misunderstand.”

Aiyen is amused by Vikir’s reaction, even in such a desperate moment.

But in all fairness, now was not the time for playful teasing.

The Death Knights were flying, their attacks growing stronger and sharper.

Aiyen’s expression hardened.

“Vikir, how did you do that?”

He was asking how Vikir had chased away two Death Knights just a moment ago.

Vikir answered easily.

“Salt. The undead are weak to salt.”

He was right. There’s no better way to cleanse the unholy than with salt.

Vikir picked up a handful of salt, which lay like white sand on the banks of a cascading river outside the battlefield of the Iliad, and sprinkled it on the Death Knight.

Soon, the white salt burned black and made a loud crackling sound.

Deathknight jumped back as the salt touched his body, and that was just in time to counterattack.

…Puff!

Vikir grabbed the Death Knight’s back as he flinched from the salt, and promptly punctured his temple with Beelzebub.

Then the Ballak warriors, who had been struggling to hold the Death Knights at bay, found a way through.

“Salt! Salt!”

“Everyone, imitate Vikir!”

“It’s true! It’s working!”

Still, the Ballak warriors were reluctant to wound their ancestors.

They sprinkled the river’s salts with minimal contact, hoping to avoid hand-to-hand combat while still honoring their ancestors.

Moreover, as Ah’Heman’s Turning Point reached its climax, the Death Knights began to be picked off one by one.

Chief Akwilla sneered.

“Your ancestors were not meant to be manipulated by the Necrons.”

His mockery was directed at the dying Ah’Heman.

The moment.

“Kuhhhhh…… Yes, quality rather than quantity.”

Ah’Heman laughed grimly.

He smeared his face with his own blood, drawing intricate lines of incantation. He began to draw upon his life force, drawing upon it beyond life itself.

Even his soul would struggle in agony for eons after death.

But nevertheless, Ah’Heman was forced to use this forbidden spell.

…Thud, thud, thud, thud, thud, thud!

One by one, the Death Knights around him began to fall apart.

But despite this, Ah’Heman kept his eyes closed and kept muttering something.

“…I found it! I found it! I found it! He lay in the depths of the abyss, alone and without a grave! Oh, yes, He really was there!”

Dark mana swirled wildly around him.

The other warriors of Ballak could barely keep their balance in the midst of it all.

“…It is time to end it all.”

The night fox, the chieftain, Akwilla, stood tall and glared at Ah’Heman.

Then her arrow struck him in the forehead.

Pow!

A single silver arrow shot through the dark storm.

It seemed self-evident that in a matter of seconds, it would blow a gaping hole in his skull.

But.

Kwagik-.

To his horror, Akwilla’s arrow stopped midway.

Akwilla’s arrow, the unstoppable force in the current depht, had been caught by someone else’s hand.

“…!?”

All of Ballak’s warriors looked up in astonishment.

It was a lanky man who caught the arrow with his bare hands.

A man dressed in a raggedy shroud.

His face was skeletal and leathery, his lips missing, leaving his gums and teeth exposed.

The shroud fluttered in the breeze, woven in a style from a long, long time ago.

Thick strong bones, tall stature, and the power to catch Akwilla’s arrows with her bare hands.

No one had ever guessed the identity of this long-ago ancestor.

Only one. Except for Akwilla.

“…!”

Akwilla turned her trembling gaze to the undead orb before her.

She had heard the legends of all the great chieftains and heroes of Ballak since she was a child.

She’d always thought she could do that.

Blessed potential, endless possibilities, a once-in-a-century talent.

Akwilla was actually considered one of the most capable chieftains of all time, so he had no qualms about comparing himself to the legendary warriors of old.

…Except for one person.

A hero who had single-handedly declared war on the Empire, who had won declarations of surrender, who had subjugated all the tribes of the Depht, who had led Ballak to his greatest heights, and in the face of all these immense accomplishments, even the arrogant Akwilla could only sincerely admire.

The eternal myth of the Ballak, a spiritual being.

Adonai, the greatest archer since history began to be written.

Chapter 94

Madam Eight-Legs (1)

◆

When Ballak’s warriors, including Vikir, returned, they found their village in terrible ruins.

The tall trees on which the houses were built were broken and bent.

Naturally, the house itself was also broken, lying low to the ground in a pool of water.

Broken boards, wood chips, and other debris floated in the water.

All of the floating houses that had been built for the rainy season had been destroyed.

The warehouses where weapons, prisoners, and other tools were stored were also destroyed. All that was inside was left outside, useless.

Only the food warehouses, where the dry goods were stored, lay shattered and empty.

“…What is this?”

Chieftain Akwilla looked around in disbelief.

There was no way the village could have been destroyed like this without casualties.

There were bodies floating around everywhere.

Almost all of the warriors had gone to watch the Iliad, so those left in town were mostly children, the elderly, the sick and women who couldn’t fight.

There was a minimal guard force left, but they, too, were mostly dead and lying around.

“….”

Vikir came to his senses faster than anyone else, and soon began to realize what had happened.

The first thing that caught Vikir’s attention was the air.

A foul, polluted aura hovered over the entire forest beyond Ballak’s village.

Vikir followed the ominous scent with his hound’s keen sense of smell.

Now there were signs of something more sinister.

The muddy water was nearly up to his ankles, making it difficult to see, but when he dipped his hand under the water, he could feel the ugly scars on the ground.

Deep scars in the ground. As if a giant log had once drummed and scraped across them.

There were not one or two of these deep furrows under the water, but a very complex and irregular pattern.

‘…At least 80 centimeters wide. Maybe 3 meters long.

What kind of creature could leave tracks this big in a flood?

Vikir could name three or four suspects in his head.

And he keeps finding clues that narrow it down even further.

Goo…

The mucus that hangs over his head.

When Vikir tilted his head, it dripped down past his body and onto the surface.

When he looked up, he saw the sticky, slime hanging like a thread from the half-collapsed, tilted floating house.

Black fur and blackened flesh clung to it with a disgusting odor.

The wood around it was blackened and splintered where it had touched.

It seemed to exude a powerful poison.

Then.

Boom, boom, boom, boom.

A louse approached, breaking through the waters up to my ankles.

Ahhhh. She appeared, gasping for air.

She had managed to hide in a jar of spices during the commotion, and as soon as she saw Vikir, she burst into tears and ran to embrace him.

Vikir patted her back wordlessly, and Aheul sobbed into his neck.

“Madam was here.”

At those words, all the warriors behind Vikir stood and froze.

Madam Eight-Legs! Terror of the water. The nightmare of enemies and Black Mountain.

Why would she attack a Ballak village?

To these questions, Aheul stretched out a finger and answered.

“As soon as Madame reached the village, she destroyed it from there, and then, as if she was taking out her anger on us…”

She pointed to a tall building that was unusually badly broken. It was a house carved out of stone, perched high on a rocky outcropping.

Ah’Heman’s temple.

The moment she pointed to it, the warriors realized.

“You will regret this! You will regret leaving me like this…! …! …!”

Ah’Heman’s last words before he died, and the reason he chose to stare at the distant village in his final moments.

Vikir climbed up onto the rocky outcropping and searched through the rubble of a shattered stone building.

It was the temple where Ah’Heman usually performed his rituals, and unlike the exterior, which was unusually badly damaged, the interior was relatively intact.

Vikir pushed aside the rubble and peered inside.

There was a strange assortment of herbs he didn’t recognize, burned to a crisp over time.

The scorched remains of the herbs emitted a strange odor, and tiny insects the size of pinky fingernails swarmed around them, apparently intoxicated by the scent.

Aiyen gritted his teeth.

“ It must be the grass that attracts bugs.”

“….”

Vikir nodded.

Ah’Heman had arranged for Madam Eight-Legs to come here if he was away for an extended period of time.

Normally, the fire is controlled so that the smell of the burning herbs doesn’t spread beyond a certain area, but when there’s no one to tend to it, the fire continues to burn the herbs and the strange odor spreads endlessly.

Eventually, the smell is noticed by a madam who lives deep within the jungle.

Ahun pounded his fist on the stone wall.

“Damn it! You’ve arranged for everyone to die when you’re gone! You’re insane!”

It’s a testament to Ah’Heman’s need for recognition within the Ballak tribe.

But his need for recognition was perverse and eventually led to terrible destruction.

Ahun gained a deeper understanding of his grandfather, but also a stronger hatred for him.

But it was too late.

Ballak’s village was devastated and almost impossible to rebuild.

The good news was that most of the population had gone out to watch the Iliad, and of those who remained in town, most had gone out to gather berries and roots.

This was due to Aiyen’s instructions.

To prepare a feast for Vikir if he won the Iliad.

Akwilla clenched her fists so tightly that they bled.

“The good news is that there were no casualties. We’ll just have to rebuild the village and gather food. These are just floating houses that were hastily built for the rainy season anyway.”

Ballak’s warriors worked diligently to collect the remains of the dead and rescue survivors still in hiding.

Madame consoled herself with the fact that the damage had been so light as to be nothing short of a miracle, considering she had visited the village herself.

Meanwhile.

“….”

Ahun had his head down, deep in frustration.

Vikir tapped him on the shoulder.

Ahun looked back at Vikir and sobbed.

“Vikir. I should have listened to you.”

He spoke with anger and understanding.

“If only I had listened to you, when you asked me to finish off Ah’Heman, if only I had really listened to you…”

“…It’s not your fault.”

Vikir turned his head and spoke to all the warriors nearby.

“The real fault lies with the Empire, or more precisely, the Baskervilles.”

At that, all the warriors turned their heads.

They all knew that Vikir was originally from the Baskervilles, let alone that the Baskervilles were to blame.

But Vikir had no qualms about speaking.

“The Baskervilles are to blame for the reason that Madame has expanded her living quarters here, and for the reason that she raided Ballak’s village in a frenzy of hunger.”

The Baskervilles had been so aggressive in slaying demons that Madame’s prey had become scarce, and she had expanded her hunting grounds.

The natives of Ballak were forced to move to the lowlands of the mountains to escape her hunger.

Vikir pinpointed the hatred of the natives of Ballak for the Empire.

And the warriors of Ballak took a strong liking to Vikir’s clear-eyed condemnation of the misdeeds of their former home.

But there was one thing Vikir didn’t say.

“It’s also because of a policy I set when I was in Baskerville.”

At the age of 8, Vikir presented a united front with Morgue and a grand subjugation plan against the enemy and the Black Mountain.

Of course, this was just Hugo’s pre-regression knowledge of the plan that was already in place, but it still gives Vikir some responsibility.

So Vikir took this opportunity to repay the Ballak warriors for their many favors.

He had fully restored his health, gained strength away from Hugo’s watchful eye, gained access to the skills of various magical creatures, learned the archery of the Bowmaster, learned and experienced firsthand the mysterious culture of unknown barbarians, mastered the art of tracking and stalking, and learned various survival skills in the jungle.

What’s more, all the barbarian tribes of the Jungle have come to support Vikir, giving him great political influence.

For all this, Vikir looked around for a way to repay them.

Akwilla, the Night Fox. The chieftain of the Ballak, she was battered and bruised from the fierce war against Adonai.

Aiyen had stepped forward to help Vikir, but a poisoned arrow in his leg had left him with an unnatural gait.

Vikir said.

“The warriors of Ballak have never treated Madame poorly.”

Everyone turned to look at Vikir’s face.

Vikir continued.

“We even honored her just a week ago, and made offerings to her.”

Indeed. The Ballak have always taken the best parts of their prey and offered them to the Madame’s domain.

The same was true for prisoners of war.

“But she raided our lands and killed innocent children, old men, and wolves.”

Ballak’s warriors listened with bated breath.

Finally, Vikir finished, his eyes glowing with dark blood.

“I must now confront her and judge her.”

Chapter 95

Madam Eight-Legs (2)

◆

“Madame has made a mistake, and I will confront her.”

Vikir’s last words stunned all of Ballak’s warriors.

Not that they hadn’t thought about it.

Innocent children, elders, patients, companions, and wolves had been killed, and they had lost buildings, food, and everything else they needed to survive.

But even so, the warriors were skeptical of Vikir’s words.

“Impossible. No brave warrior has ever been able to do that.”

“‘Vikir. Even if you are the hero of the whole region, that’s a myth.”

“Madam Eight-Legs is the deity of these jungle. She is the evil one of the evil spirits.”

“The damage will eventually be repaired. The only way is to forget.”

For the first time, Ballak’s warriors, who trusted Vikir with anything he said, shook their heads at his words.

For such brave men to say such a thing gives one an idea of the extent of their fear of the Madame.

Then.

…Tee!

Someone put a hand on Vikir’s shoulder.

It was Chief Akwilla, the Fox of the Night, staring at Vikir with a pale complexion.

She had lost much of her usual overwhelming majesty.

The one who had gone one-on-one with the Ancient One, the legendary Adonai, and sent him back to the dust.

But Akwilla, too, had suffered many wounds in the process.

Countless arrow marks scratched his body, and even the poisonous venom of Madam Eight-Legs was too much for even a Master-level warrior to heal.

“Vikir. Young hero of all the jungle and the sun just rising, do not be swayed by the heat of the moment. Where Madame is involved, extreme caution must be applied.”

Aiyen, beside him, agreed.

“The Madam Eight-Legs is a terror to all tribes, not just the Ballak. She is a force of unstoppable causality and the essence of darkness. Her presence is like a natural disaster, and even if we harbor feelings of vengeance….”

But Aiyen didn’t finish her sentence.

[Chuckles…]

She saw a figure crawling through the rubble of the collapsed building.

Bakira. The wolf who had been born on the same day and time as Aiyen, and had been with him all his life.

The one who had run to the village to tell them of Vikir’s victory before the Iliad between Vikir and Ah’Heman.

For a moment, Aiyen couldn’t help but think of his last words to Bakira.

“Go to the village and tell them to prepare to welcome the winner of the Iliad.”

Little did he know the consequences of that simple errand would be so terrible.

[Snicker… snicker…]

Bakira crawled over, dragging his hind legs, and wiped his wet nose at Aiyen’s feet.

One of her right hind legs was in terrible shape.

Not only were all the bones broken, but a dark poison had seeped into the marrow.

The reason for this was obvious. What else could it be but the result of resisting Madam Eight-Legs?

The poison was still surging at this moment, and the situation was so serious that the leg had to be cut off.

Aiyen looked at Bakira in disbelief.

Vikir spoke briefly.

“Will you still say that revenge is futile?”

“….”

Aiyen did not answer this time.

Akwilla glanced between her daughter’s face and Bakira’s moaning legs and sighed deeply.

“We’ll talk later. For now, let’s take care of Bakira. Come on, take care of the others.”

Despite her own mortal wounds, Akwilla tends to the others first.

The chieftain’s words sent everyone scrambling again.

They had to rescue survivors, tend to the sick, and make sure they had food and shelter for the night.

◆

The night was unusually dark and rainy.

There was no moon, so the pitch-black depths were illuminated only by the occasional lightning strike.

A shadow passed like a ghost through the rain that fell like spears.

It was Vikir.

Once again, Vikir had left Ballak without telling anyone.

The hound was now on his way to see Madame.

‘…She’s someone I should have faced at least once.’

Madam Eight-Legs was one of Vikir’s true purposes for coming to Depht in the first place.

An ultra-dangerous beast whose danger is still unknown to the Empire.

If we can hunt it down before it does, the benefits are endless.

Humming.

Vikir thought to himself as he listened to the pulsing of Beelzebub in the arteries of his wrist.

‘In the future, when the Age of Destruction arrives, creatures like Madame will be relatively common, but for now… she is quite unique.’

Besides, the Madame was the one who had forced Ballak’s warriors to abandon their homes and move from place to place.

Ballak’s warriors were in a difficult position, having to avoid the Madame’s constantly expanding radius to satisfy her hunger, and having to avoid the Baskervilles, who were cutting through the jungle to expand their empire’s territory.

“I can set them free.”

Madam Eight-Legs and the Baskervilles. Vikir had the means to bring these two oppressors of Ballak under his control.

It would be a favor to Ballak for all he had done for her, and a favor for their future.

Vikir also wanted to test himself.

How much stronger he had become during his two years in the Depht.

‘This battle with Adonai has made me stronger. Soon I will be able to climb another step….’

As he thought this, Vikir made his way through the rain.

But the hound was soon forced to stop.

A familiar scent wafted through the curtain of rain.

Not a day has gone by that he hasn’t recognized it for the past two years.

Aiyen. She stood before Vikir, drenched from head to toe.

“I’ve been waiting for you.”

“….”

“How long have you been standing there?”

“….”

Aiyen didn’t answer Vikir’s questions.

Finally, she opens her mouth.

“Wolves can’t be tamed.”

“…?”

“No matter how much you tie them up, they break the leash and run.”

Aiyen lifted her head and looked straight into Vikir’s eyes.

“Wolves can’t be tamed, after all. You can only make them come to you when they want to, without a leash.”

She smirked at Vikir.

“You are not a hound. Vikir. You call yourself that, but… no hound ever behaves like you.”

“….”

Vikir looked down at Aiyen’s legs.

Her right leg was wrapped in a tight bundle of leaves and leather.

Once, when they had fought the Adonai, Aiyen had wounded her leg while saving Vikir from a poisoned arrow.

He still limped from the aftermath.

Vikir broke the silence.

“ …You can’t help me with your body. Go back to the village.”

The air is so thick with water that the words come out dry.

But Aiyen kept her mouth shut, as if she’d expected that much.

Then she held out something to Vikir.

It was dried jerky and fruit and nuts wrapped in leaves.

Vikir smirked.

“It looks like a sacrificial meal.”

“Don’t joke about that.”

Aiyen opened his eyes fiercely and glared at Vikir.

Then he added a word.

“I promise.”

The scene was eerie.

The Hound thought it was a little familiar.

Aiyen spoke again.

“Promise me you’ll be back.”

“….”

When Vikir didn’t answer, Aiyen spoke again, in a tone that sounded like he was holding his breath underwater.

“No.”

She hesitated for a moment, then spoke again.

“I don’t. You don’t have to promise to come back.”

A voice that crawls. A voice that hangs with anxiety, nervousness, and bitterness.

Aiyen looks into Vikir’s eyes with a voice that sounds like she’s about to vomit blood.

“You don’t have to come back, just stay alive….”

Vikir is silent for a moment.

Then, a little too late, he speaks.

“…Of course.”

Then the breath he’d been holding came out of Aiyen’s mouth, all white.

A darkness that swallowed him whole.

The master stood still, watching the hound, or rather the wolf, walk away.

The wolf runs through the dawn again.

Unlike last time, there was one thing she couldn’t say to Vikir.

“You don’t have to come back, just stay alive….”

Women have a way of making difficult demands.

For the first time in all his life, since he was born twice, he had lied.

He didn’t know if he could keep this promise or not.

Chapter 96

Madam Eight-Legs (3)

◆

Quack, quack, quack…

A vague earthquake cloud covers the spot where the thunder left off.

It may have been daytime, but with the thick dark clouds covering the sky, the pouring rain, and the frantic lightning, it felt like night.

Vikir pushed his way through the sharp leaves of the Sword Forest.

He had been following Madame’s trail since last night.

It was common knowledge that if it rained during a hunt, the chase would be abandoned. It’s common sense to abandon a hunt when it rains.

But even in the midst of this heavy rain, the tracks of Madame’s movements remain unmistakable.

Half-melted chunks of meat lay everywhere.

They appeared to be part of what Madame had eaten and vomited up, but I didn’t bother to examine them to see what kind of meat they were.

Everywhere, Madame’s mucus and feces blow into the water, creating a foul odor.

Thick hairs that felt like black needles were scattered throughout the area, and the grass and trees around it were blackened and dried up.

There’s no reason we can’t follow the trail.

The hound advances, following the path of death indicated by the dead trees.

Vikir recalled the Madame’s identity once more.

When they first met, she had buried herself completely in the blackness of the water.

So it’s impossible to know the exact shape of her body.

Even the warriors of Ballak, who had suffered under her tyranny for so long, had no idea what she looked like or even what kind of creature she was.

Only their chieftain, Akwilla, was able to give them a glimpse of her identity, based on faint oral accounts.

“…Certainly, it’s hard to tell what species we’re dealing with based on the tracks.”

Traces of crashing into and crushing logs or rocks like land war monsters, flying across rivers or high valleys like birds of prey, traces of digging tunnels like underground monsters…… The biological characteristics of all monsters are all mixed.

What’s even more impressive is that it climbed up a rock wall with a slope of more than 90 degrees.

A cliff so high that even birds can’t climb it. Madame scrambled up it.

Vikir looked up toward the top of the cliff, hidden by clouds.

It looks like he’ll have to climb this high to meet Madame.

“…But first, I need to get ready.”

Vikir stared up at the cliff for a moment, then turned on his heel.

A quick glance around the cliffs reveals that they’re shaped like isolated mountains.

It stuck out like a sore thumb in the flatlands.

Most likely, the Madame was nesting in the higher ground.

Vikir made a quick assessment of her location and turned away.

If he fought now, he would lose, and he would barely survive, let alone win.

Now that he knew where his opponent was, time was on his side.

Vikir slowly moved away from the cliffside.

Trying to gauge how high this sheer cliff could possibly be.

◆

Vikir arrived at a swampy area quite a distance from Madame’s nest.

The first thing Vikir did upon reaching the edge of the swamp was to scatter the bundle of straw he had been carrying in all directions.

He had been sweating profusely as he made his way through the jungle, and his scent had soaked into the straw.

The wind blew the straw, carrying his scent, everywhere.

Now, due to the nature of convection that circles the swamp, Vikir’s scented straws will scatter, enveloping the entire swamp.

They will be carried by the wind deeper into the swamp.

Not only would it be impossible to pinpoint Vikir’s location, but there would be room for her to feel surrounded.

…Who would feel that way?

“The master of this swamp.”

Vikir raised his head and stared into the center of the swamp.

Suddenly, a log floating on the surface sank deep.

And something huge began to crawl out of the swamp through the thick water.

<Bog Salamander>

Danger Rating: A+

Size: 9 meters

Found in: Ridge 8, Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain

-Named ‘Infinite Regeneration Dragon’.

A giant amphibian-like beast that lives deep in the swamps.

It has strong territorial instincts and a gluttonous appetite, devouring everything that enters its swamp.

They are feared by humans because of their unkillable ability to regenerate from any wounds.

It has ruled this swamp for a very long time.

An old, giant salamander emerged.

Its entire body is covered in smooth skin and sticky slime.

In its mouth were the arms and legs of several natives of unknown tribe.

Vikir recognized him at a glance.

“That was Mushuhushu’s rival, I suppose?”

There was a great snake named Mushuhushu who had recently fallen prey to Beelzebub.

That snake’s rival was this giant right in front of him.

The old salamander stretched out his body, growing larger and more powerful as he aged.

[Hiss-]

The old salamander’s head swiveled to look for the intruder in its territory, but it couldn’t pinpoint a direction.

That was because Vikir had sent the straw he had been gathering into the wind, and at the same time smeared mud all over himself to cover his scent.

[Grrrr… shhhhhhhhhhhhh!]

The bog salamander clucked its tongue and continued to crawl across the swamp.

Vikir briefly considered fighting it, but quickly dismissed the idea.

His capture of Mushuhushu the other day was luck in many ways.

He had lost his territory to the floods and had been swept away, so he had lost a lot of stamina, and to replenish it, he had eaten at an uncharacteristic pace, leaving him sluggish.

The hunt had been a relatively easy one, as we’d ambushed him while he was tired, full, and sleepy, and Aiyen had helped.

But not now.

The old salamander was moderately hungry and very uncomfortable.

Besides, isn’t it a monster so strong that it’s on par with Mushuhushu?

If I were to fight him, I couldn’t guarantee 100% success.

Even if I could win moderately, there was no point in wasting my stamina in a place like this, considering the fight with Madame that would follow.

‘Except… there’s something I can do with him.’

Vikir waited until the salamander was completely out of the swamp.

And there was something else he was aiming for.

The straw he’d sent into the wind earlier wasn’t just to hide his location.

It was also to lure in “some dangerous creature” that might be lurking just beyond the wind’s reach.

“…It’s almost time to come out.”

Vikir thought as he carefully followed the salamander out of the swamp and into the woods.

Then.

The response came.

As Vikir’s scent drifted across the jungle on the wind, the creatures began to respond.

Minotaurs, ogres, trolls, and other large creatures responded.

But none of them dared to enter the old salamander’s territory. They could only salivate at the outer borders of the realm.

…But.

Wee wee wee!

Just one.

There was one creature that had no fear of the old marsh salamander and barged into his territory.

Weeeeeeng!

An ominous sound of flapping wings.

It was an extremely eerie sound that made even the most powerful salamanders cringe.

Then, as the old salamander left the swamp and entered the forest in search of Vikir, something huge appeared in front of him.

It was like a dark cloud, very tall, very wide, and very vast.

It moved about, elongated like a snake, and soared upward.

Vikir was familiar with this strange, shapeless creature.

<Bone-Sucking Mosquito>

Danger Rating (Individual) : D

Danger Rating (Swarm) : S

Size: 3 mm

Found in: Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, Ridge 9

-Nicknamed the ‘bone-sucking mosquito’.

Not much is known about it except that it sucks bone, not blood.

It was not a single giant, but a swarm of many smaller ones.

Wee wee wee wee wee!

Mosquitoes flew in swarms, clinging to everything around them.

Even the salamander, which had traveled quite a distance from the swamp.

Vikir looked at the mosquitoes and thought.

“They are terrible things.”

These mosquitoes were worse than the ones people usually recognize.

Normal mosquitoes stick their long, straw-like proboscis into flesh and drink blood.

But it wasn’t human blood that these mosquitoes craved.

It was bones.

They poke their long, pointed snouts into the bodies of their prey and suck out the bones, much longer than the average mosquito, and their victims lose all the bones in their bodies.

What’s even more horrifying is that… these mosquitoes only suck on bones, leaving behind skin, flesh, blood, and intestines.

The old salamander then proceeds to show us in real time what happens to those who get caught by these dreaded mosquitoes.

[Shhhhhh!?]

The old salamander freaked out.

He squirted mucus all over his body to ward off the mosquitoes’ attacks, and he tried to turn and run back into the swamp.

But the mosquitoes were much quicker to react.

Attracted by Vikir’s scent, these mosquitoes cling to the salamander’s body, causing it to die and harden its mucus, while the late arrivals use the corpses of their companions as footholds to sting.

Soon, the mosquitoes begin to suck out the salamander’s bones.

Swish, swish, swish.

The fluid from the mosquito’s saliva is exactly what dissolves the salamander’s bones and turns them back into liquid.

The salamander tries as hard as it can to get back into the swamp, but the fire spreads it a few meters from the water’s edge.

It had lost all its bones to support its weight.

The mosquitoes continued to swarm the swamp long after they’d eaten all the salamander’s bones.

Whirr! Whirr! Whirr!

That is, until Vikir started a fire and used the smoke to scare away all the mosquitoes.

The mosquitoes disappeared as quickly as they had appeared.

Vikir finally emerged from the swamp.

He burned some wet leaves, just in case, creating a thick cloud of smoke.

“…Smoke.”

Vikir looked around and nodded.

The bone-sucking mosquitoes were terrifying.

Each mosquito was small and weak, but the danger level of the whole swarm was far beyond common sense.

Vikir turned his head to look at the swamp.

The salamander had fallen to the ground just two meters from the swamp.

Surprisingly, it was still alive.

The bones in his body were gone, and he was shivering, but he was still breathing, thanks to his tough skin and life force.

Of course, it was obvious that its miserable existence would be short-lived, as it was nothing more than a watery shell.

“….”

Vikir reached out and touched the salamander’s body once.

Flesh and blood oozing from the tough hide, intestines floating around.

Now he was nothing more than a bag of blood.

“Good. Well made. That should be enough.”

Vikir tugged on the still-breathing salamander’s tail.

As the mana of a Advance Graduator passed through his body, he was able to pull the body of this huge monster.

What’s more, the old salamander’s body was lighter because its bones were gone.

[Swoosh! Swoosh-]

The salamander made a bizarre noise every time it was dragged, but it could do nothing about it.

The lungs and other organs in its body were now all mixed up, so it couldn’t even make a sound.

Only thick tears dripped from his eyes.

“Consider this your karma for eating so many humans.”

Vikir’s eyes are cold as he drags the salamander, a giant bag of blood and intestines.

It had been a short preparation, a rather long one.

Now that everything was in place, there was only one thing left to do.

To meet the Madame, and to kill her.

Then I will leave the jungle, and Ballak, with all the debts of my heart.

A return to Baskerville, Ironblade.

It will not be a long one.

Chapter 97

Madam Eight-Legs (4)

◆

It was late at night.

Rumbling… boom!

The rain had stopped, but there was more thunder.

Vikir lifted his head and looked up at the giant rock formation rising before him.

Composed of quartz and sandstone, the massive cliff stood alone as a soaring peak in contrast to the flat terrain around it.

Many caves have been carved into the steep cliffs, and their pupils stare blankly into the darkness, like the eyes of a blind Guani.

Occasionally, in the darkness of a cave, quartz or amethyst gemstones would glint in the reflection of a lightning bolt, and the cliffs would seem to stand guard in every direction, like a thousand-eyed watchman.

Vikir gritted his teeth.

From Baskerville Street to the watery depths of Ballak.

Vikir’s body had been trained to the limit by now, and every twitching muscle in his body was taut.

Vikir began to climb the steep cliff barehanded.

The muscles in his back and arms pulled and released, pulled and released, pulled and released….

Vikir scrambled up the rock wall, one foot at a time.

…Walgrok!

Sometimes the stalactites he was holding on to would snap, or the stone beak he was stepping on would snap off the wall.

Without a single scream, Vikir calmly braced herself with the strength of his other arm or foot, making room for a quick grab or step.

When he felt he had nothing to grab or step on, he drew his magic sword, Beelzebub, and slammed it into the wall, climbing upward.

Thanks to Mushu Hushu’s abilities, no sound was made during the entire process.

…I wonder how long he climbed like that.

When I thought I was halfway up the cliff, I saw a cave.

It was narrow enough for one person to fit in, but it was quite winding inside, so it felt cozy.

It looked like a place to take a break from the climb if anyone happened to come across it.

But Vikir did not enter the cave.

“…A trap.”

This is where the Madame’s nest is located.

I didn’t think there would be a comfortable place beneath the worst of monsters.

There was a slight chance that this was a natural trap to test the will of the challenger.

A weaker man, exhausted from the journey up here, would have been easily tempted, but the seasoned Vikir still had some stamina left.

Vikir didn’t rush into the cave, but kept a close eye on it.

…Or otherwise.

A corpse, a skeleton, rolled around in the cave.

Had there been a warrior who had come this far before?

It seemed that he had entered this cave, never made it out, and died, leaving only his remains behind.

Vikir glanced up without entering the cave.

Now he understood why there were so many skeletons in the cave.

Sticky…

In time, a thin liquid began to trickle down the cliff.

It was a mixture of fluids and excrement that Madame often threw out, and it was usually hard or thick, but when it rained, it thickened and loosened.

The mucus that has accumulated in the stomach is loosened by the rain.

They flowed down, covering the whole area, threatening to block the entrance to the cave.

From the outside, it looked like whipped cream dripping down a giant cake, but the disgust and stench was indescribable.

“…If we walked into that cave, we’d be in trouble.”

Fortunately, Vikir hadn’t gone into the cave, nor had he fallen asleep in it, so he quickly kicked open the entrance and moved to the side.

Luckily, there was a stone beak jutting out like a roof right next to him, and he ducked under it to avoid a shower of slime.

The slime, a mixture of the Madame’s bodily fluids and feces, causes skin to swell and bump upon contact.

Vikir’s skin was imbued with the protection of the Styx River, so he should be able to withstand it, but even so, he didn’t want to come in contact with that slime.

…Gulp!

Soon, the slime had completely covered the mouth of the cliffside cave, and it flowed down the gentle slope of the cavern, filling it with a murky, foul odor.

Dahlgrak.

The skeleton lying within touched the slime and began to float.

The warrior, who must have come to see the Madame long ago, had probably fallen asleep in the cave when he entered for a short rest and drowned, never to return.

It wasn’t the only cave that held a skeleton.

Temptations to rest were everywhere, and it took superhuman endurance to climb the grueling and difficult outcroppings to avoid them.

Nails peel, fingerprints fade.

Every time Vikir felt the urge to take a break, even for a moment, he gritted his teeth harder.

As the hound of the Baskervilles, evil was all that remained of his time in the Age of Destruction.

Vikir climbed the cliffs, dodging dripping slime along the way, and passed dozens more caves containing skeletons.

…How much time had passed?

Vikir could see the top of the peak through the thick mist of water and inky clouds.

He had made it this far without falling off and dying, without being covered in slime, and he had accomplished his goal.

Every muscle and bone in his body screamed, but it was still a remarkable accomplishment.

Now, Vikir looked around the peak.

The black, mushy soil was covered with flimsy, sticky threads that whipped in the wind.

A foul odor emanated from the entire peak. A stench so foul that not even rain and storms could wash it away.

“…It’s as if a large amount of meat has been gathered together and is rotting.”

Vikir took a step toward the center of the peak, and then.

Bam! Swoosh.

The ground at the top of the peak sank in, sucking Vikir’s foot up to his shin.

It was like stepping on the surface of a swamp.

Upon closer inspection, the ground was covered in rotting flesh. That’s why it felt so unpleasantly squishy and hot.

An unpleasant sensation wrapped around my entire leg.

If I hadn’t wrapped my legs in leather, I would have been itching.

“If I stay still, I’ll be up to my waist.”

Vikir scrambled to his feet.

I didn’t know the floor, so I had to choose only the hard footrests that protruded upward because of the floor that was slowly sinking.

Vikir quickly realized the identity of the flimsy footholds sticking out of the slime and rotting dirt.

They were bones.

A floor made of countless bones.

They tangled with sticky, congealed slime to form a massive mass.

The stench emanated from the less decayed chunks of meat that lay beneath them.

These carcasses, apparently leftovers from Madame’s meals, are covered in slime, decaying and fermenting, emitting a foul poison, odor, and heat.

Vikir had to work hard to keep himself from drowning in this swamp of slime and rotting meat.

Then.

“…!”

Vikir stopped in his tracks for a moment.

An ominous aura emanated from the cave ahead.

But that wasn’t what stopped Vikir in his tracks.

The skeletons. Bodies that hadn’t yet decayed, scattered in various fragments.

Brown skin, silver hair, faces contorted in pain and fear.

They were clearly Ballak’s men and wolves.

Abui was a good hunter. Adul, the strong swimmer. Akelon, who was an expert at sewing. Asagl, who was a very fast runner. Asak, who laughed and cried a lot. Aguil, who was always arguing with Ahun when they first moved to the village. Agun, who was unusually gluttonous. Atlatl, who was really good at javelin….

The friends he’d lived with for the past two years, all of whom he recognized, of course.

“ …If you’re going to throw up like this, you might as well eat it.”

Vikir pressed his lips together and gathered the remains of his friends.

Then he observed a moment of silence.

A warrior’s ritual before a final battle. It was a series of steps that transformed the emotions of the past two years into resolve.

“….”

And then Vikir’s head snapped up, his eyes glowing red.

At the end of the long line of flesh and bones, a great darkness lurked.

A gaping hole in the center of the peak. An underground tunnel of bone and flesh.

It was obvious from its size and poisonousness that it was Madame’s nest.

A poisonous exhalation, unmistakable as the Madame’s vomit from the bottom of the deep chamber, billows out of the cavern.

Vikir listened to the breath and stench coming from under the ground.

“….”

No matter how many times he checked, the result was the same.

The grotesquely protruding belly fat, the sound of that chubby lump of flesh flinching was clear.

Madame has been in her tunnels for some time, breathing evenly, as if she has no intention of crawling out.

No wonder she’d raided a Ballak village and eaten to her fill.

Karak-

Vikir silently picked up the bow on his back.

Then, carrying the Baskerville family’s unique dark red aura, he fired an arrow.

Declaration of war.

A red trail flew through the curtain of slime and rotten fibers.

It carried the challenger’s intentions to the depths within.

And then.

…………….

The breath and venom that had been spewing from the burrow stopped.

Then.

[Zzzzzzzzzz!]

A fierce rage erupts.

Madame’s malice spewed forth like an avalanche from an active volcano.

Soon, a sinister presence emerges from the rotting meat lair.

A haunting depht nightmare.

Horrors of unstoppable causality.

A resident of the dark side.

It was the moment when ‘Madam Eight-Legs’ revealed its hideous appearance under the torrential rain and lightning.

Chapter 99

Madam Eight-Legs (6)

◆

<Binge Fly ‘Beelzebub’>/ Awl

-Slot 1: Burn – Cerberus(A+)

Slot -2: Silent Hill – Mushu Hushu(A+)

-Slot 3: Super Regeneration – Bog Salamander(A+)

The third orb of the magic sword Beelzebub spat out red light.

The spirit of a bog salamander raged within the orb.

The destructive energy soon turned into wraith energy, coursing through the veins of Vikir’s body.

The skill ‘Super Regeneration’ has been cast.

Tsutsutsutsuts…

His body was regenerating at an incredible rate, with black steam billowing from every muscle fiber.

New legs sprouted from severed limbs, intestines regenerated, bones fused together, and gaping wounds healed themselves.

Salamanders are some of the most regenerative creatures in the water, able to regenerate their arms down to the tips of their fingers even if they’ve been cut off at the shoulders.

Of course, regeneration on such a large scale is very draining, but it’s far better than spending your life crippled.

Of course, only in battle.

Within seconds of being reduced to a ragged mass on the ground, Vikir had perfectly reconstituted his body.

[Zaak?]

Madame raised her forelegs and scratched the top of her head in confusion.

Vikir cautiously backed away.

‘…If I’d gone in for a follow-up blow, I’d have been killed instantly.’

He had trusted his instincts and retreated when the first attack had been successful.

If I had ignored the warnings of my instincts and moved forward just a little bit, just a little bit deeper for the next attack, I would have been crushed to death, and even the most regenerative of salamanders wouldn’t be able to do much about that.

At least I’d still have a body to regenerate.

Meanwhile.

[Hmm?]

Madame was fidgeting, as if something had disturbed her earlier.

It was the burning smell that wafted past her nostrils.

The smell of fire, which spiders hate so much, was coming from nowhere.

Then Madame realized where the smell was coming from.

It was coming from her own ass.

…Crunch! …Crunch!

The mucous sac on her ass where Vikir’s blow had struck earlier.

The mucus sac, which normally sheds webs, was now wounded and burning.

What was burning in that wound was definitely the dark flames of the oil system!

“How does hellfire taste?”

Vikir asked as he flew to the left.

Earlier, when he had slashed at the spider’s body, Vikir had activated one more skill in addition to releasing his aura.

It was the Burn skill he’d gotten from capturing Cerberus.

Enemies slashed or impaled by the blade of the magic sword Beelzebub would suffer fatal burns.

The infernal flames of Cerberus’ wraith’s remains would continue to scorch opponents.

[Jaaaaah!]

Madame angrily rubbed her rump against the ground.

But even so, the flames were not extinguished, and they burned more intensely.

The mucus leaking from Madame’s mucous sacs continues to draw in the flames, just as the flames are drawn in by the holes in the oil barrel.

Once touched, it burns forever. That’s the curse of Cerberus the Hellhound.

In the end, Madame admitted it. What a nuisance these infernal flames that Cerberus has brought with him are.

Chhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!

Madame held her breath and expanded the hole in her ass, spilling the vast amount of mucus that had been contained inside onto the floor.

Huge amounts of white liquid gurgled out.

Vikir stretched back to avoid them.

Suddenly, the flames that had been burning Madame’s mucus sacs were all out of her ass.

She had expelled a great deal of mucus at once.

[Gag! Gag!]

Madame turned around, her legs shaking in frustration.

Then she turned to me.

“…?”

She did something that would have made Vikir shake his head.

She stuck her leg into the burrow, swirled it around, and pulled out a small, round sphere.

It was an egg.

Vikir suddenly understood why Madame was so hungry all the time.

Madame was pregnant, and she was carrying many eggs inside her.

However, with the current intruder draining her stamina to the max, there is only so much food she can eat.

[Ajak-ahjak-kwadeudeuk-]

Madame gobbled up her eggs, concentrated nourishment, without hesitation.

“What a heartless mother.”

Without another word, Vikir raised his bow.

Boom!

An arrow flew out and headed for Madame.

The arrow cut through the air sharply and lodged in her third eye from the left.

Crack!

The eyeball exploded like a raw egg.

Along with the aura that spun at high speed on the surface of the arrowhead, the flames of the oil system were transferred.

[Gaaaahhhh!]

Madame stretched out her legs in fury, but what awaited her at the end of the trajectory was a sword strike wielded by Vikir.

Denggeng-.

Again, there was a crack as if the night sky was being split in two.

This time, Madame’s right front leg was severed and she sprawled across the floor.

…Thud!

Vikir stepped back, dodging the poisonous blood that sprayed in all directions.

[Giggle-]

Despite losing her front legs, Madame was not at all agitated.

She simply retrieved another egg from her burrow, ate it, and regenerated two new legs from the severed limb.

Poof! Poof!

Madame now had ten legs.

She could no longer attack with her severed legs, as they would always grow back into two.

Vikir remained silent, watching Madame’s every move.

Finally.

Vikir nodded.

“I see. Cut one, make two, right?”

And with that, Beelzebub bared his six gnarled teeth, poking out of Vikir’s arteries.

“Let’s see how far it goes, then.”

A black aura exploded madly from Vikir’s entire body.

Baskerville Sixth Form.

The blood aura at the tip of the magic sword burned as brightly as the sun as it descended toward Madame’s legs once more.

The pointed tip, like the teeth of a carnivorous animal, cut six trajectories in quick succession.

Dengeng- deng- deng-.

The two newly grown legs were sliced off again, and Madame regenerated them as if it were hopeless.

Poof! Woody, woody, woody!

Four legs sprouted from where two legs had been severed.

Vikir let out another long stream of aura.

The sensation of all the blood in his body being transformed into aura, a dazzling realm of martial power!

Feeling as if every vein in his body was on fire, Vikir shot forward.

The aura blade flashed out again.

The high-speed rotating aura of the Graduator sliced through Madame’s rigid exoskeleton.

Two new legs sprouted from the severed limbs.

Vikir continued to burn the mana in his body to produce the aura, and each time he did, Madame grew more and more leggy.

[Jaaaaaah!]

Madame used her many legs to oviposit all over Vikir’s body.

…Puff-puff-puff-puck!

Despite the mind-numbing pain, Vikir’s eyes remained focused.

He stood and endured the terrible agony like a seasoned hound from the Age of Destruction.

The regenerative powers of the bog salamander once again heal Vikir’s body.

But it could not do anything about the terrible poison that had infiltrated his body.

The terrible poison dissolves into his blood, churning through his entire body.

The Graduator’s aura scorches his veins, but it’s clear he won’t last long.

Vikir lifted his blurred vision and glared at the Madame before him.

The mockery on the Madame’s face was only getting worse.

[Kiririk- Jah!]

Madame raised her two forelegs in unison, as if to crush the staggering Vikir in one fell swoop.

It was quite a leisurely movement.

…But?

Stagger.

For a moment, Madame stumbled too.

Not enough strength? No. Madame still had plenty of energy left.

But why is her balance off?

Suddenly, Madame realized.

There were too many new legs sprouting from her forelegs.

She had just released all the mucus in her gut from the annoying burning of Cerberus’ flames, so she was now lighter.

Add to that the weight of his many overgrown legs, and he’s off-balance for a moment.

Vikir did not miss the brief moment when Madame flinched at the unexpected shift in her center of gravity.

“…!”

Vikir launched himself with a sharp cry.

The poison made his mind foggy.

He knew by instinct that this was his last chance.

Madame panicked and flailed to steady herself, but her two front legs were already too heavy and she couldn’t help but fall to one side.

Furthermore, her three left eyeballs were so blinded by the distance that she couldn’t see the trajectory of Vikir’s leap.

Madame stretched out her middle leg to stop him, but her aim was off.

Vikir then stabbed Beelzebub into the spider’s abdomen, which was now empty and missing its middle leg.

Ta-da!

As it turned out, Vikir’s aura could not penetrate Madame’s abdomen.

That’s because beneath her lower abdominal sack was a solid breastplate, a shield that was strong enough to block even the aura of a Graduator.

Vikir’s sword caught in a groove in Madame’s breastplate.

In this aspect, Madame was lucky and Vikir was unlucky.

…However.

Vikir hadn’t aimed to plunge his sword into Madame’s chest in the first place.

“Yaaaaaah!”

With all his might, Vikir pushed at Beelzebub.

The needle of the awl against the hard breastplate pushed it back.

That’s right. I can’t pierce, but I can push.

Madame was off-center under the weight of her heavy forelegs and the empty weight of her mucus sac.

Vikir’s superhuman strength eventually knocked Madame sideways.

And next to her was the ground, which was weakened by squishy flesh and decaying bone.

In this aspect, Madame was unlucky and Vikir was lucky.

[Jaaaaah!?]

Madame panicked and flailed her foot, but it was cut off by an additional aura blade from Vikir.

Vikir’s skillful cut was precise, targeting only the weak joint at the end of the leg.

It was an almost instinctive slash, impossible with his blurred vision.

Soon enough, new legs stretched out, but it was too late.

Thud, thud, thud!

Madame slammed into the soft ground and rolled toward the base of the cliff.

For the first time in her life, Madame shudders at the unfamiliar sensation.

The color in her last remaining eyeball is clearly fear.

She tried to squeeze webs from the mucous sacs on her tail and cling to the rock face, but it was impossible now.

Cerberus’ infernal fire had drained it all out earlier.

…Thud! …Thud! …Thud!

Madame bounced and rolled a few times off the top of the craggy peak before plunging straight down the cliff.

And it was the same for Vikir.

“…!”

Madame did not go alone as she fell to the cliff.

At the last moment, she stretched her overgrown legs as far as they would go and pulled her resentful foe who had pushed her down with her.

Soon, Vikir and Madame were falling straight from the top of the craggy peak toward the ground below.

And then, in one last desperate effort, Vikir pulled out his secret weapon.

…Puck!

Vikir struck Madame in the chest, sending her flying off to the side.

Beside him, he can see the struggling Madame falling toward the ground at a rapid pace.

Vikir’s recoil puts him farther away from Madame, but he’s still falling at a high pace.

“….”

Unlike Madame, however, who was screaming in terror, Vikir simply closed his eyes tightly and held his breath.

It wasn’t fear of the shock of hitting the ground.

…It was preparation. Preparation to land.

And then.

I could see the ground. It was rapidly approaching.

But what greeted Madame and Vikir on the ground was clearly different.

Madame was simply falling toward the ground, but where Vikir was falling, there was a large object waiting for him.

It’s a water balloon, inflated to bursting.

A cushion of something squishy stuffed inside tough leather.

It was the gassy, bloated carcass of a bog salamander.

Chapter 104

The Returned Hero (1)

◆

The Red Salt Castle.

Surrounded by earthen walls and tall watchtowers, it is a massive man-made fortress built by the wizards of Morgue.

Mines were being developed above, with veins of crimson ruby running through them.

The dark night. Vikir climbed over a massive earthen wall and entered the inner court.

He could see men in guard uniforms passing beneath the protruding steel and rocky ridges.

With a soundless movement characteristic of the Mushuhushu, Vikir melted into the shadows and scaled the wall, sliding down the iron frame.

Soon, the interior of the Red Salt Castle unfolded.

The streets were drenched with rain. Dappled light leaked through the dark alleyways.

Vikir headed down the alley in search of an inn to stay out of the rain tonight.

Then.

“…?”

Vikir spotted something towering above the buildings on the other side of the alley.

It was a statue, large and majestic enough to be seen clearly in the darkness and rain.

It was a massive sculpture of a figure standing tall, looking out over the depht to the west, perhaps made entirely of gold.

The golden glow from the lower part of the figure made the surroundings seem illuminated.

However, the upper part of its face was dark and hard to see.

“…What’s the point of putting something like that up there?”

Vikir paused for a moment.

The statue hadn’t been there since he left the fortress two years ago.

Even if this was Morgue’s land, it was still essentially owned by the Baskervilles, so there would have to be a bilateral agreement for such a symbolic sculpture to be built.

Moreover, it’s a statue of great magnificence, with its entire body glittering with gold, so who could it be?

Vikir approached the statue cautiously.

Just as he was about to find out who had built such a golden statue to honor.

“Hey, get the hell out of here!”

One of the guards waved at Vikir.

Apparently, there were some rats trying to nibble at the golden statue’s gold.

“This statue is a monument erected by the Morgue, in honor of the heroes who defended the Red Salt Castle! Do not approach it, only view it from a distance!”

At the overly vigilant guard’s words, Vikir backed away.

He couldn’t afford to argue with the guard. He’d be pretty tired if they found out who he was.

“Even if I’ve been forgotten by everyone for two years… still, there’s no point in causing trouble.”

Not curious enough about the statue’s identity to take a closer look, Vikir quickly turned into the alley.

He was going to find an inn and get some rest.

◆

Eventually, Vikir entered the tavern.

The floor was drenched with rainwater and smeared with a messy mixture of dirt and charred footprints.

The heat was sweltering, contrasting with the cold breeze from the street, and the moisture blinded Vikir’s eyes.

The smells of roasting meat, boiling fish, clinking beer glasses, and loud shouts and laughter filled the air.

Vikir takes a seat.

Then a glass of hot rum and three skewers of salted turkey brine are plopped down in front of him.

As the waitress turns away in an unfriendly manner, Vikir raises his hand.

“I didn’t order this….”

“Hey, this is a basic drink.”

Vikir’s words were answered by a man with a brushy beard who walked up and sat down next to him.

Vikir lifted his hood, and looked sideways.

The bushy-bearded man squinted at him.

“I saw you in the alley earlier, didn’t I?”

It was the security guard who had just yelled at Vikir.

“Wahahaha! I’m sorry I yelled at you earlier, but I’m doing what I do, and I’m on a mission. I can’t help but be sensitive when I’m on guard.”

He patted Vikir on the shoulder and laughed.

The sight of Vikir’s physique, probably in his late teens, made him relax his guard.

Vikir merely shook his head.

“…I understand.”

The security guard raised his hand as if he liked what he saw and called for an attendant.

Then he looked out the window at the golden statue in the distance.

“Whatever, you understand. It’s our job to guard the statue honoring ‘him’, not the other way around.”

“Him?”

Vikir repeated, and the guard sounded excited.

“Yes. The hero who saved the Red Salt Castle two years ago. It was because of him that we survived the great barbarian invasion, and even the wizards of Morgue and the swordsmen of Baskerville.”

“…?”

Vikir scratched his head.

The story was new to him, too.

“Was there such a hero?”

Wasn’t it two years ago, before he disappeared? Was there a massive barbarian invasion then, and was there someone powerful enough to protect Baskerville and Morgue?

Everything is questionable.

Vikir was digging through his memories, trying to recall the names of heroes he might have forgotten.

“Hey! I’m going to buy a drink for my little friend here, so hurry up and get your order! Shit! Did you boil and eat a tortoise leg?”

The guard grabbed the unfriendly waiter by the back of the head and ordered some salt and pepper pork for himself and a bottle of rum.

The guard looked back at Vikir and asked.

“What do you want to drink, kid, I’m buying you something because I feel bad about yelling at you earlier.”

“Then I’ll have a rum too….”

“Wahahaha, by the sound of your voice, you sound like a child, no rum, just a glass of milk, warm it up!”

The guard shooed the waiter away into the kitchen.

The men at the other table, dressed in the same uniform as the guard, chuckled.

“Hey, you talking about ‘him’ again!”

“Well, I’m busy spreading the legend of ‘Him’ whenever I see a stranger, right?”

“Well, I can understand that. He’s the reason we’re still alive.”

“That’s right, we can’t praise ‘Him’ enough, can you?”

The guards chattered away.

When Vikir remained hooded and silent, the guard next to him spoke up.

“Whoa, whoa, whoa. You’re a foreigner, but you should know. ‘His’ fame and accomplishments resonate far beyond the underdog city below, across Baskerville’s territory, and even into the Empire!”

“….”

“Alas, are you speechless with amazement? How can a hero’s tale of heroism, from such a remote little place as this, shake the entire Empire?”

“….”

“Yes, I know, but it’s true, and my cousin, who recently traveled to the Yellow City, can testify to that. How well ‘he’ is regarded in the Empire’s society circles now.”

The guard took a long gulp of rum, then spoke with a gaping face.

“It’s been two years, and I can still remember that day, the thrill, the chills, the goosebumps!”

“ …Hmm. Apparently there was a great hero two years ago.”

Vikir shook his head, and the room erupted in laughter.

The guards at the back table raised their glasses of beer, vodka, and whiskey high in the air.

“Wahahaha! You don’t know ‘Him’! Are you a spy! Well, when you hear of ‘Him’, even a lowly moron like you would say you’ve heard of Him somewhere.”

“Yes, indeed! ‘He’ was so great that day, gallantly chasing after the savages that no one else dared to pursue!”

“He led an army of Morgue and Baskervilles into the dark depths, can you believe it? Into the black depths with those enemies, and at night, too! It was suicide! Ha ha, but ‘He’ did it! Even the mighty Adolf was only a bridesmaid that day!”

“Hey! Those are nothing! I’d be lying if I didn’t mention that He slaughtered over a thousand fearsome barbarians in one fell swoop and rescued Morgue’s frail Barren Jade Leaf! It was all thanks to ‘Him’ that Morgue’s young lady, who was poisoned to death, was able to recover!”

“Uh-huh! If you didn’t see it, shut up! Do you know of His valor as He single-handedly charged a giant, unidentified monster that appeared out of nowhere? I saw His final act with my own two eyes as He threw Himself into the fray to ensure the safe retreat of the Morgue and Baskerville allies!”

…?

Vikir sensed that something was strange going on.

The hero who had slaughtered so many barbarians in one fell swoop.

The chivalry that had saved Morgue’s frail, Barren Jade Leaf only daughter.

A Holy Sacrifice, who fought bravely against a giant monster, buying the Alliance time to flee.

“That great hero who was here with us only two years ago, whose name is…!”

The guard leapt to his feet and lifted his lantern to shine out the window.

There, just beyond the darkness, the face of a golden statue was visible, illuminated by the moonlight peeking out of the clouds.

At the sight of the majestic hero, all the guards exclaimed.

“‘Vi!”

“ Ki!”

At the same time, countless guards turned their gazes toward Vikir.

If they didn’t recognize him by now, they would throw stones at him.

Eventually, Vikir answered.

“…R?”

Then all the guards chimed in.

“Look, you know who it is, Vikir van Baskerville!”

The golden statue that towered over the central plaza of Red Salt Castle was in Vikir’s image.

Chapter 105

The Returned Hero (2)

◆

“Come on, let us celebrate! You too, join us!”

“We always show our appreciation for Lord Vikir’s statue like this at night.”

“He is the reason we survived the attack that day ,we survived because he stopped that giant beast!”

“What’s happening my friend. You’re a peculiar young fella, you are heartless! Put more energy into it! Clap harder! Come on, mate!”

Was said as the guards of the Red Salt Castle looked at Vikir’s statue and clapped twelve times at mid-night on the hour.

The passersby can tell the time by the sound of the guards’ clapping.

Vikir observed the faces of the guards who forced him to clap, one by one.

Around two years ago, in the Depth’s of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain. The faces of those who ran away from Madam Eight-Legs.

Some of them looked like the soldiers he’d seen then.

The hairy man who served Vikir the glass of milk chuckled.

“Anyway, if you don’t know Vikir’s name in this region then you’re a spy. Of course, it’s a bit of an exaggeration to say that the rumor has reached the other side of the world. Still, the rumors are true. If it’s not, why would the House of Morgue have offered such a large amount of gold to honor his achievements?”

It is said that every year, politicians and nobles from neighbouring cities come to pay their respects and perform ceremonies in front of the giant golden statue.

Vikir sighed, pressing his hood deeper into his face.

Sure, he’d achieved a lot in the depths two years ago, but most of his accomplishments… had been grossly exaggerated.

Not only did I kill thousands of natives in one fell swoop, but I also rescued the allied armies of Morgue and Baskerville, and even rescued Morgue’s fragile (?) Barren Jade Leaf.

To be clear, it was Adolf Morgue who did the most damage that night.

Vikir had merely lessened the amount of time for them catch up to the barbarians at night.

‘…, Though I did play the role of a martyr against Madame at the end.’

Vikir sipped his milk and reminisced.

‘Anyway. It was clear that all that was accomplished by Adolf Morgue ,and the combined forces of Morgue and Baskerville armies that night were ,warped and twisted into the credit of one man, Vikir.

Just as Vikir was trying to figure out how to make sense of this situation.

Creak.

Suddenly, the door to the inn burst open.

The sound of the fish boiling, the smell of the skewers cooking in the salt, the heat of the pork lard sizzling, all of it vanished in an instant.

The night breeze swept away the hot, thick and dirty air of the tavern.

The night breeze came in the from behind of three women in long robes.

With their thick eyebrows, catlike eyes, and beautiful features, the three women could be triplets.

Upon seeing them, the guards rose to their feet in unison and saluted.

“Loyalty, we greet the commanders of the fortress!”

Their change in posture drew Vikir’s attention.

Vikir looked at the three women as they entered the tavern.

“…!”

He had seen them before, if he recalled correctly

They were the Three Flowers of Morgue, or the Three Misfortunes.

Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis.

Specializing in grass, earth, and water magic, they walked up to the table with their distinctive red hair and sat down.

The men’s eyes were momentarily dazed by their beauty, but they could not make a mistake.

Neither could Vikir, especially because the triplets’ personalities were truly terrifying.

“What were they talking about that was so funny?”

“The obvious. It’s midnight, they’re probably clapping again.”

“Were they talking about Mr. Vikir?”

The guards answered the triplets’ question with a roar.

“Yes, we were!”

Then the eldest, Highsis, laughed as she grabbed the cold mug of beer in front of her.

“Ho-ho-ho-it’s no wonder, for his accomplishments are great, and I still get a thrill thinking about how I felt when I saw him that day.”

The rookie guards’ eyes sparkle at Highsis’s words.

“Did you ever meet Him in person, Commander?”

“Of course.”

Highsis and the other two sisters narrowed their eyes and laughed.

“When I first saw him, I thought he was just a pretty boy, but I got to know him during our time together in the fortress. I saw him for who he really was: someone incredibly kind and charismatic.”

Vikir, standing right next to her, could hardly believe his ears.

He remembered his first encounter with them as less than pleasant.

But for some reason, the sisters Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis seemed to remember their time with Vikir as something truly beautiful.

“He was wonderful. I honestly spent the whole time he was living in the fortress ogling him.”

“Though we only bumped into each other a few times in the mess hall.”

“We did see each other at the cotton field boundary, however, though we didn’t get a chance to have a long talk before the three Baskervilles interrupted us. If I’d known this was going to happen, I would have talked to him at a bit more.”

She took the guards aside and began to chatter.

The woman who had been so unfriendly to them earlier noticed and politely served them drinks and snacks.

Vikir sat alone at a distant table, listening carefully to the triplets’ story.

He hoped to hear at least a little of what had been going on in Morgue and Baskerville.

The triplets were quite talkative, and Vikir was able to get plenty of information out of them.

The changes since Vikir’s disappearance two years ago and the eventual declaration if his death were astonishing.

The most shocking was the number of times Hugo Le Baskerville had visited Morgue in a furious rage.

And that the Morgue rewarded the Baskervilles diplomatically with an enormous amount of money.

Despite this, Hugo Le Baskerville did not relent in his anger.

And finally, that only a few weeks ago, Camus Morgue had personally led a search party through the depths of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

Vikir had accepted all of this with a grimace.

Well, if Hugo was upset about his disappearance, it was because he’d lost a useful hound.

And if he’s still angry, it’s because he thinks the reward given by the Morgue’s is too small.

The only thing that seems surprising is that Camus still hasn’t forgotten Vikir after two years.

Until just a few weeks ago, she had been steadfastly leading a search party through the depths, and then she suddenly disappeared.

…Rumor has it, she’s gone into hiding deep within her family and gone into retirement?

Whatever.

The triplets told Vikir’s story, subtly bragging to the guards about their experiences and connections.

“By the way, that golden statue over there doesn’t even capture half of Vikir’s true appearance. It’s a shame, because if he were still alive, he’d be a good match for me by now.”

“Who’s paired with whom? That’s ridiculous, if he were alive, I’d definitely be the one to pick him up.”

“Don’t fight, sisters. We’ll all get along, What man would turn down the three of us?”

But then the triplets’ sisters all silence at once.

“What’s the use of fighting, he’s already gone.”

A somber mood settled over the tavern for a moment.

By this time, Vikir had gotten up and climbed the stairs to the second floor.

He couldn’t wait to get to his room and lay down.

He was tired of listening to his own story, which was becoming unfamiliar.

Then.

Unfortunately, out of the corner of her eye, Highsis caught sight of Vikir’s hood.

“You there! Your outfit is suspicious. Get over here!”

She wasn’t in the mood for a little teasing, so she immediately used the fortress commander’s powers to stop and search.

Vikir paused in while moving up the stairs.

If he took off his hood here, the atmosphere would be overwhelming.

He considered pretending he hadn’t heard and continuing up the stairs, but that would only fuel Highsis’s foul temper.

“Hey! Stop! Can’t you hear me?”

The guard next to me spoke.

“Miss. I bought this kid a glass of milk earlier… and he isn’t suspicious.”

“Shut up, at this time of night, the natives outside are strangely quiet, we should be more vigilant!”

Highsis leapt to her feet.

He stretched out her hand towards Vikir.

A powerful stream of mana swirled around Vikir.

“Bind!”

The wooden railings of the staircase creaked, and long vines grew around Vikir, trying to wrap around him.

But.

Whirik-

Vikir flew out of the way easily, avoiding the grasp of vines.

Highsis’s eyes widen at the sight, as do those of Middlesis and Lowsis, and those who were standing behind them, looking impressed .

The men of the guard beside him were so surprised that they spat out their drinks.

They hadn’t expected him to be able to evade the magic of Morgue’s three sisters so easily, especially since it came from Highsis, the strongest of the three.

“…Shit.”

Vikir sensed that things were getting troublesome.

He thought about hiding in the night, but Morgue’s trio were no match for him.

The three sisters, Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis, quickly rose to their feet and drew upon their magic.

The guards, who had been laughing and talking a moment ago, also drew their swords, bows, staves, and magic, and surrounded Vikir with a sharp edge.

“Who are you, remove your hood and reveal your identity!”

Highsis shouted sharply.

Vikir sighed softly.

He might be able to escape, but it would turn the entire fortress upside down.

He didn’t trust himself to escape without spilling blood.

And it wasn’t as if he needed to wear a hood to disguise himself in the first place.

‘I’m on my way to inform Baskerville that I’m back anyway….’

Whether Baskerville or Morgue found out first was merely a matter of sequence.

Eventually, Vikir obediently stopped and raised his hands.

Then, under the watchful eyes of all, he slowly pulled back his hood.

….

The moment Vikir’s hood came off, revealing his face.

“…Uh-oh.”

“…Ahhhhhhhhh.”

“…Ahhhhhhhhhhhh.”

The triplets exclaim in unison.

It’s not a reaction to seeing a familiar face, it’s purely a reaction to Vikir’s appearance.

And then.

One by one, they begin to realize that Vikir’s face bears a striking resemblance to something.

Several guards slowly turn their heads to stare at the face of the golden statue outside the window.

“…?”

Then they turn again and stare at the face of Vikir, standing on the railing of the stairs.

“…!”

And they go stiff.

The shock spreads to every man in the guard. It spreads to every man in the tavern, and even to Morgue’s three sisters, Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis.

Soon, all who recognized Vikir’s face stood with their mouths agape and their index fingers trembling.

“Vi, vi, vi, vi, vi, vi….”

Vikir Van Baskerville. The missing hound of the Iron-Blooded.

The hero of the Red Salt has returned.

Chapter 106

The Returned Hero (3)

◆

The next morning.

Vikir pushed himself out of his shabby bed in the tavern.

He had declined the offer from Highsis last night to come and stay in the fortress’s guest quarters.

He’d already paid for the room yesterday.

As he descended the creaky wooden stairs and stepped onto the first floor, where the guards from last night stood guard in front of the tavern and saluted in booming voices.

“‘Salute!”

“…I am not from the Morgue family, you do not need to salute.”

“Sir Vikir, you are the hero of Red Salt Castle, and we have not forgotten how you saved our lives in the depth two years ago, so we salute you from the bottom of our hearts…!”

That’s where Vikir decided to give up.

He would have to get used to the salutes and words of honour that will follow him from now on.

He couldn’t afford to feel awkward all the time.

Just then, one of the waitresses from last night rushed over and handed Vikir a bag.

“Hey, there’s…, if you don’t mind, I thought I’d give you a snake for your travels ….”

It was a skewer of the best cuts of beef, some herbal antiseptics, and dark coloured beer in a cold glass bottle.

When the guards saw it, they sighed deeply.

“What in the world has happened to that woman?” they said.

“How can Nancy, the cold wind of the tavern, the epitome of rudeness, be so kind…”

“I guess she’s suddenly awakened her spirit of hospitality .”

“ What a cruel world. Looks are all that matter.”

But Nancy wasn’t the only one who had changed.

Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.

As soon as the sun rose in the morning, three steeds approached Vikir’s tavern.

The three horses were followed by numerous other carriages and servants.

Riding on the horses at the forefront were the three flowers of Morgue.

Highsis Morgue, Middlesis Morgue, and Lowsis Morgue.

For some reason, they looked different than they did yesterday.

For starters, they no had fairer skin, red lips, darker eyebrows, and more defined features.

They looked natural, as if they weren’t wearing makeup, but they were actually wearing heavy makeup that took an extreme amount of time, money, and effort to put on.

On top of that, they were wearing formal outfits, that they would never normally wear.

Afterward, Morgue’s three sisters who greeted Vikir dismounted from their horses.

Even the notoriously ill-tempered Highsis said “thank you” in a gentle voice to the servant who helped her to her feet.

Vikir said to the triplets.

“Is it okay to travel unarmed in wartime?”

It was an innocent question.

But they answered with a glint in their eyes.

“I am armed.”

“I am also fully armed. It’s called ‘combat readiness’.”

“Ho-ho-ho, although my sisters’ makeup is more like camouflage than armour.”

The youngest of the three sisters’ expressions stiffened at her sisters’s comment.

“What? Camouflage, that’s referring to the face you hid with your brush~”

“I only hid my face, what about you sister? You covered the outline of your chin altogether. You also made your nose really stand up with shading, but what? That’s almost like a civil engineering.”

“Okay, move your bangs out of the way kid, so I can play soccer on your forehead.”

As the three Morgue suddenly began to argue with each other, the air around them began to swirl with magical power.

Despite their smiling faces, the air around them was growing chilly.

However, their fight was quickly interrupted by a single word from Vikir.

“Have you contacted the Baskervilles?”

Highsis was the first to raise her hand and answer.

“Yes, I sent an owl just yesterday to tell them that Mr. Vikir has returned.”

Slowly, his title changed from “sir” to “mr”.

It was Highsis’s way of trying to be more respectful.

Vikir, of course, wasn’t phased at all.

“All right, then. I’ll go by myself from here.”

They were still in front of the tavern. He just meant he’s going to make the trip alone.

The three sisters were openly disappointed.

“Are you sure you don’t want us to accompany you …?”

“It’s a long way to the fortress border.”

“The roads are complicated, and you could get lost.”

“I’m sure you’re busy, but it’s okay.”

“We are not busy! We are not busy at all!”

“We’re so bored we’re sleeping all the time these days! The barbarians are quiet, we’re not busy at all.”

“Why don’t you just come with us, we’ll show you the sights and give you some advice…”

“No, thank you. I’d appreciate it if I could just borrow a horse.”

Vikir clapped his hands and thought to himself.

“When I return home, I’ll have to report that Morgue’s men are playing around.”

Such disloyalty is unforgivable, sleeping around while borrowing someone else’s land.

Then. Highsis came up behind him, pulling a pale white horse.

Only it’s ears were dyed pink.

“This one is my favourite, his name is Poppy, and I’ve had him since he was a baby. When you’re riding him, you’re also riding me… No, no, please think of it as riding with me, eh, eh.”

“Sis, didn’t you buy that horse in a hurry at the market last night.”

“Yeah, yeah, yeah, I picked the best one I could find, and I pushed the stallholders hard, but it was a real deal~”

Highsis grits her teeth and menaced at her siblings.

Whatever.

Vikir climbed onto the horse.

Until then, the three sisters had been arguing over who would lead Vikir to the edge of the Red Salt Castle’s boundaries.

Then.

“…, I have a question for you.”

Vikir turned his head.

Meeting his gaze, the three sisters stopped moving for a moment and stared up into his face with blank expressions.

It was as if they were mesmerised.

But Vikir’s next words brought them back to reality.

“Where is Camus?”

Camus. Camus Morgue.

Hearing the name brought the three sisters back to reality as if a bucket of cold water had been poured over them.

“That, that, that’s right. That’s right, there was Camus, ugh.”

“…We’re gonna have to look all over the place, aren’t we?”

“That’s why I told you not to do that, sisters!”

The three sisters gasped, realising what they had just done.

Then Highsis answered Vikir’s question.

“If it’s Camus, she’s entering closed-door training.”

“…Closed?”

Vikir repeated, and Highsis shook his head, filling in the blanks of what could have happened.

She had heard that after Vikir’s disappearance, Camus had organised a search party and spent years searching the Depths of Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain.

But after failing to recover Vikir’s body, let alone save him, Camus abruptly stopped searching and entered into a closed-door training session.

And what he heard from Morgue’s three sisters was startling.

“She’s separated from Uncle Adolf.”

Highsis said, sounding surprised herself.

I heard that Camus has changed a little since the time he stopped searching for Vikir.

She had lost much of her brash personality and spoke less.

Then, out of the blue, She announced her withdrawal from the “Light Side”.

Since Camus always followed Adolf like a parent, who was her uncle and the leader of a light faction, the Morgue family was shocked even from within.

However, Adolf did not express any official comments about this incident.

He just silently watched Camus, who had defected, joined the “Dark Side”, which stands at the opposite end of a “Light Side”.

“…The Dark Side.”

Vikir frowned slightly.

There are two factions in Morgue.

The Light Side, which uses magic to achieve results both internally and externally.

And the Dark Faction, which is less publicly visible, but deeply researches and develops magic within the family.

Members of the Light faction travel in and around the clan, slaying monsters and constructing buildings.

Members of the Dark Side, on the other hand, generally don’t travel outside of the family.

Instead, they study a particular field or genre of magic in depth, and through countless trials and errors, discover and recreate new magic.

It’s the difference between a practitioner and a researcher.

‘The current leader of the Light Faction is Adolf Morgue , and the leader of the Dark Faction is Snake Morgue.’

Snake Morgue. He is an archmage who leads the House of Morgue and holds the title of Marquis of the Empire.

The same rank as the patriarch, Raspane Morgue, and a distant relative of hers, he was not known to the public.

The only thing that comes to mind is his reputation as being incredibly pompous and stubborn.

…Of course, Vikir, who had lived through the Age of Destruction, was familiar with the man known as Snake Morgue.

“This is unexpected.”

Vikir frowned.

Before the regression, Camus and Snake had never gotten along.

But somehow, in this life, Camus had suddenly joined hands with Snake.

Since Morgue’s party is composed of one delegate, 20 senators, and 400 representatives, Camus would most likely have been a senator.

Maybe she wasn’t even a senator at all.

Vikir hesitated a moment, then spoke up.

“Can you deliver a message to Camus?”

Highsis nodded as if it were obvious.

“Sure. It’s a favour from a friend.”

“Okay. Then I’ll ask you to keep it short.”

Vikir nodded, and all three sisters took out pens and paper, ready to dictate.

But what actually came out of Vikir’s mouth was very simple and short.

-When you get a chance, let’s meet face to face.

…?

Is that it?

Weren’t they supposed to be reunited after two long years?

The three sisters, Highsis, Middlesis, and Lowsis, stood in place in a daze.

Turning to them, Vikir added, as if it had just occurred to him.

“Oh, and. Be sure to leave the dark Side.”

Chapter 107

The Returned Hero (4)

◆

Vikir rode his horse to the city of Underdog.

A city where he had once served as a deputy magistrate.

Vikir rode his horse through the streets and alleyways of Underdog City.

The city’s security had been greatly improved.

For the time being, there were noticeably fewer homeless people and drunkards wandering the city, and the streets were cleaner.

One thing I noticed was that there were very few children around.

Children are usually running around and playing in the streets and alleyways, but strangely, there were no children in the alleyways.

There were a few kids wandering around, probably running errands, but they were always accompanied by a guardian.

Otherwise, they’d rush back into their houses ,as if there was something scary outside.

“…?”

Vikir tilted his head, but urged his horse toward the city hall.

The main entrance to the city hall was now in sight, he felt bit nostalgic.

He hadn’t been there since he had temporarily left the depths to find a cure for the Red Death.

<移木之信>/<The Faith of the Tree>

There was a plaque with those words clearly written on them by Chihuahua.

It was made in the past when Vikir burned 10 billion on a bet.

As he entered the city hall building, he was greeted by a bustling staff.

Without a sound, Vikir dismounted and made his way through the crowd to the inside.

This was to meet up with Chihuahua, Baskerville.

He spotted a woman busily working in front of the Deputy Commissioner’s office.

Judging by the unfamiliarity of her face, she was a new employe.

Tap.

Vikir knocked once on her desk.

But the woman was so busy, she didn’t answer except for a brief frown.

Tap.

Vikir knocked on her desk a second time without effect.

Tap.

But the woman didn’t respond this time.

“Take a waitlist and wait.”

She said in a very businesslike tone.

“….”

Vikir thought for a moment and nodded.

Currently, Vikir was listed as dead, so he was not officially a deputy.

So, in principle, it was right to draw a number and wait.

Especially since he had no intention of making a scene.

<Waitlist number 3021>.

Vikir took the ticket and sat down to wait.

“….”

None of the employees walking by paid him any mind, their faces were buried in their papers.

After he had waited for hours.

Finally, Vikir’s turn came.

The 3020th customer in front of him had just finished his business and went away.

Vikir had just gotten up and was approaching the woman.

…Bang!

A desk near him shook as if it was going to shatter.

A male employee jumped to his feet and shouted in an excited voice.

“News from Red Salt Castle! Lord Vikir is alive and well!”

“What! Really!?”

“It’s true! It’s true! It’s a message from the Commander of Morgue family himself! He’s leaving the Red Salt Castle and is on his way here!”

Then there was an uproar.

The atmosphere in the city hall quickly turned into a simmering pandemonium.

“Lord Vikir is alive!”

“It’s the return of a hero! Contact the main house of Baskerville now!”

“Lord Vikir is on his way here! Roll out the red carpet now!”

“We only have a white carpet! What should we do?”

“Make it red with your own blood, and welcome him with all you got!”

The city hall staff began to scramble, abandoning all their important work.

That included the woman Siting in front of Vikir.

“For God’s sake, we need to get ready to welcome Sir. Vikir right now!”

She threw down the 3021st waitlist and stormed out.

Or better said she would have don so if Vikir hadn’t gotten in her way.

“Wait. You have to take care of my complaint first.”

“If it’s urgent, just send it in, and I’ll do it first thing tomorrow morning!”

“It’ll be too late then.”

The woman shot Vikir a look of incredulity.

“I’m sorry, but I can’t help you right now! We have a guest, a very important one at that! I don’t know what your business is, but under these circumstances, you’ll have to wait until later…!”

“I need to see the director.”

The woman paused as the name of the Chihuahua Baskerville came out of Vikir’s mouth.

If he was going to go straight to the office, he was a pretty important figure, and she couldn’t ignore him.

So she grunted and gathered up the papers.

“Oh, no, I don’t want to do this now that Mr. Vikir is on his way to …. Why didn’t you tell me you had a meeting, so I could get it canceled sooner?”

The woman glanced back at her coworkers, who were busy preparing to welcome Vikir, and gave the “genuine complainant” a look.

Then she slid a piece of paper in front of Vikir.

“Write down your name and the purpose of your visit here, please, as fast as possible!”

Vikir did as he was told.

-Name: Vikir Van Baskerville

-Purpose of visit: Reunion

The woman snatched the papers out of Vikir’s hand.

She had dealt with so many complaints that she was used to dealing with nobles.

She didn’t even bother to read the papers before knocking on the door of the Directors office.

“Mr. Chihuahua, you have a visitor!”

Chihuahua’s voice came from the other side of the door.

“What? I don’t have any meetings today.”

“Yes, but you have a visitor!”

“I said I don’t have a meeting, and I’m canceling any one I have. Mr. Vikir is on his way, so just send him home, and they’ll understand.”

The woman turned away as she still hadn’t read the paperwork.

She sighed and waved the papers in her hand at Vikir, who stood still.

“Mr. Director said that there’ll be no meeting today, and he’s busy with an emergency, so next time, please make an appointment before you come in. What was your name, the paperwork says… yes Mr. Vikir. In the future, please be sure to contact me in advance and send me a message at ….”

And a moment. The woman’s body went rigid.

She looked dazed for a moment, then she adjusted her glasses and looked back at the paperwork.

Soon, the letters in the name field of complainant 3021 are clearly visible on her glasses.

-Name: Vikir Van Baskerville

-Purpose of Visit: Reunion

As the woman stood there with her papers, one by one, busy employees walk by and look at the contents of her papers.

“Hey, I’m busy, what are you doing here not rolling out the red carpet… eh!?”

“Hey, don’t get in my way, can you get out of my way, please… huck!?”

“What’s with all the prying…?”

The people gathered around the female employee one by one and froze in place.

The number of people was getting bigger and bigger.

Soon, the entire city hall staff had gathered around Vikir, and they were all frozen in place.

The office was silent as if it had never been so busy.

After a long moment of silence.

“Customer number 3021 will enter….”

The female employee’s voice echoed softly as she crawled away.

◆

Chihuahua Baskerville looked at Vikir as he burst into his office.

“Oh. At least you came through the door this time, last time you came through the window.”

He had gotten quite used to Vikir’s unusual behaviour.

Vikir flopped down on the sofa as soon as he entered.

Suddenly a child came running At to him.

“Daddy! Daddy!”

It was Pomeranian. It was Pomeranian La Baskerville.

Vikir grabbed Her by the waist and lifted her up.

“Not daddy, uncle.”

“Uncle! Uncle-!”

Pomeranian laughed as if she was amused by Vikir’s behaviour.

She clung to Vikir’s side, her hands digging into his waist.

“Uncle! Hehe. I’m a rat! Catch the rat-”

Pomeranian had learned to speak a little.

The Chihuahua’s training must have worked, Vikir thought.

Pomeranian held out a rat to Vikir, but it didn’t look like the kind of rat you’d keep as a pet.

It was so skinny and scrawny that it was nothing but bone and skin.

Vikir nodded approvingly.

“It’s a cute little rat, but be careful not to catch the plague.”

“Hehe. Awww, Uncle!”

Vikir patted the Pomeranian on the head, then turned his attention to the Chihuahua.

Chihuahua filled Vikir in on the details of what had transpired while he was gone.

In return, Vikir recounted the events that had occurred to him in the depths.

As Chihuahua listened in awe and amazement.

“So, did you finally defeat the mysterious creature that was found in the depths?”

“Not completely. However, it fled to a cold and barren place with fatal injuries, so it has probably frozen to death or starved to death.”

“Kya, our Deputy Magistrate, once you owe some one a debt, you pay it back to the end!”

This time it was Vikir’s turn to ask a question.

“Have you solved any of the underdog’s problems?”

“Oh, it’s all been resolved thanks to your suggestion from last time, Cindywendy’s very good at her job.”

Suddenly, the Chihuahua’s normally cheerful expression darkened for a moment.

Vikir didn’t miss the change and asked.

“Is something wrong?”

“…In fact. There’s a case that even Cindywendy can’t seem to figure out.”

Then Chihuahua stood up and pulled out a sheet of paper from the bookshelf.

<Unsolved Serial Infant Abduction Case>.

It was a cold case in the city of Underdog.

“Recently, children from the slums have been disappearing one after another. It’s a serial phenomenon… I don’t think it’s a kidnapping for money. The trail is not quite clear.”

“Is it the work of the same person?”

“If my guess is correct it is a solo operation, though I have no proof.”

“‘Don’t Cindywendy’s a capable human being, I’m sure we’ll get a lead soon.”

“I hope so.”

The Chihuahua shook its head as if it he in trouble.

Then.

“Dad! Uncle, this is Baba-”

The Pomeranian grabbed Vikir’s arm again and sagged.

Vikir couldn’t help but turn his head as the Pomeranian clung to his arm with his entire body.

The momentary separation seemed to have made her even more sullen.

“So, Pomeranian, what do you want?”

“Rats! Rats!”

Pomeranian held out another rat to Vikir.

Vikir nodded appropriately and tried to live up to Pomeranian’s expectations.

At that moment.

“…?”

Vikir took another look at the rat in Pomeranian’s hand.

Something was off about it.

Vikir squinted his eyes and examined the rat.

The rat reeked of death.

Upon closer inspection, the rat was long dead, nothing left but bones and skin.

And Pomeranian was playing with it.

“…!”

Vikir’s mouth opened halfway.

The rat was now dancing on Pomeranian’s palm.

This was clearly a corpse resuscitation technique, a death magic spell that could be performed using negative mana.

“Pomeranian.”

“Ung Uncle!”

“This rat, did you revive it?”

Pomeranian nodded with a cheerful expression.

“Ung!”

“Since when did you know you could do this?”

“Ung… one night, two nights, three baam….”

The Pomeranian wiggled her fingers eagerly, and then stretched out five fingers.

Vikir nodded.

“Five nights ago?”

“Mmm.”

“Who taught you how to play with rats like this?”

“The tribe!”

Vikir was silent for a moment at Pomeranian’s words.

Pomeranian had been found in the village of the Rokoko tribe.

Vikir had assumed that she had learned the secrets of the Rokoko tribe, who, are known for their black magic and command skills, over their shoulder, but he was not certain.

“At this age, you’ve already sensed mana, even the most elusive negative mana?”

Even the children of the Baskervilles and Morgue, who are said to be geniuses, don’t feel mana until they were eight years old.

But Pomeranian felt mana at the age of five and was playing with it freely.

“…Hmm.”

Vikir thought for a moment.

A magical prodigy had appeared in the Iron-Blooded Sword family, and she was the illegitimate granddaughter of the patriarch.

“I wonder how Hugo would react if he found out?”

Vikir tried to imagine Hugo’s reaction to seeing the Pomeranian.

‘If it was the Hugo he knew, probably.

‘…Granddaughter. And you don’t even know what kind of bastard’s blood she’s mixed with? You worthless thing!’

It was likely to be something like that.

Hugo judges all his children by efficiency.

A woman can’t wield a sword as well as a man, so she’s already going to be judged negatively.

And magic, black magic!

That’s not exactly Hugo’s favourite type of witchcraft.

‘…Plus, I don’t know what he’ll think of her being his granddaughter.’

Vikir closed his eyes and considered.

There were few daughters in the Baskervilles. No, almost none.

You have to look far and wide to find one, and even then, Hugo doesn’t even know their names.

In fact, there were no daughters in Hugo’s direct lineage at all.

“…Pomeranian must be the only one.”

Vikir muttered, looking down at the Pomeranian clinging to his leg.

Pomeranian La Baskerville.

She was the only child of the eldest daughter of the current head of House Baskerville, Hugo Le Baskerville.

In other words, the most direct of the direct line.

The first daughter of his first wife’s first daughter. How would Hugo react? Is it a good idea to introduce Hugo to the Pomeranians in the first place?

Vikir shook his head, remembering Hugo’s cold look.

“I can’t imagine what that cold-blooded man would say to Pomeranian.”

I’m sure he’ll say something nasty, like they’re useless, a waste, a mongrel, or something else.

Or maybe he’ll just give her a cold, unfeeling stare, like he’s looking at an invisible object.

‘If that is the case, then it might be best not to confront them….’

Just as Vikir was contemplating what to do with the still very young Pomeranian.

…A bang!

Something crashed through the window.

Chihuahua opened the window in surprise and sees an owl with a letter tied to its leg.

The Chihuahua quickly took the letter and read it.

Then he looked back at Vikir in horror and exclaimed.

“Mr. Vikir, we’re in trouble!”

“What?”

“It’s from the main house! God, my lord! Gee, directly! As soon as he heard the news of Vikir’s survival, he, he is on his way… !”

At the same time. There was a noise that cut off the Chihuahua’s words.

A bang-bang-bang!

A knock on the front door of the city hall. And the panting of horses that had traveled a long way at a fast pace.

Finally, the Chihuahua finished speaking.

“He’s here!”

Chapter 109

The Great Banquet (1)

◆

Hugo Le Baskerville.

The iron-blooded swordsman who rules Baskerville.

One of the seven pillars that support the Rock of the Great Empire.

In recognition of his great contributions to the unification of the continent’s powers into a single empire, he was awarded the Star of Swords, and was knighted as a Marquis, at the age of fifty.

About a decade had passed since then.

Hugo was a man with literally iron blood and a furnace heart.

He drove the rampaging barbarians far beyond the borders of the country and wiped out over a hundred species of demonic creatures.

His exploits, and the power that made them possible, gave him a tight grip on the center of power.

Countless Baskerville hounds had been sacrificed along the way, but Hugo didn’t care.

Hugo was a man who, once set on a path, never looked back.

…But.

That iron-blooded man was wavering now.

Hugo stared at the small girl before him with a blank expression he hadn’t seen in decades, not even from Butler Barrymore, with whom he had spent his entire life.

Pomeranian.

Suddenly bursting out of the next room, she ran straight to Vikir and hugged him.

“Uncle! Thunderclap! Musher!”

But Vikir could do little more than hold the Pomeranian still.

Vikir couldn’t do much more than hold the Pomeranian still, because the reaction of Hugo, whose eyes were now wide open in front of him, was too unexpected.

He glanced to the side, hoping to see something, and found Butler Barrymore staring at Hugo with an even more astonished expression.

Hugo’s reaction is understandable, as there is no way in the world that Hugo would have such a look on his face.

Shock and horror. An awkward silence fills the office.

Then, like a man possessed by a ghost, Hugo took a step forward.

“Are you, are you… that face… can’t be…?”

Hugo’s hands and voice trembled. It was only now that Vikir realized it could be a tremor.

His unsteady gaze darted to the side of the Pomeranian’s face, to the blood-red eyes half-hidden by black hair.

Meanwhile. Pomeranian, who had been squirming in Vikir’s arms, looked up and gasped.

“ Wooooaaah! Uncle!”

Pomeranian cried out loudly and stumbled backwards.

It’s a natural reaction for a girl to have when she sees a middle-aged man with a mustache approaching her with a shaky hand outstretched.

“Moustache! Nose hair! Offensive! Shirer!”

The Pomeranian squealed, hiding in Vikir’s arms.

And to Hugo’s surprise, he froze in place in shock.

“My nose… mustache? My mustache?”

With trembling hands, Hugo groped under his nose.

Just then, Vikir stepped forward.

“Mr. Hugo, please calm down.”

The cold, emotionless tone of his voice sobered Hugo.

As Hugo straightened up, Vikir asked.

“This is a child I picked up on my way here. I brought him here to run a personal errand, but I don’t know if you’re bothered by…?”

“Eh, eh. Picked him up on the road, huh?”

Hugo glares at Pomeranian even as he answers Vikir.

But Pomeranian was already in Vikir’s arms, so he couldn’t see her face again.

When Hugo dared to lift his head once more to look into the Pomeranian’s face, Butler Barrymore came to Vikir’s aid.

“My lord. There are as many children in the world as there are grains of sand. There’s nothing particularly strange about the Master picking up a child to run an errand for.”

At that, Hugo stopped shivering.

“…I’m mistaken, then. The butler is right.”

And then. Hugo reverted back to his stern expression.

But why was he fiddling with his mustache?

“Does the mustache bother you?”

“No. …What are you talking about, butler?”

“Oh, no, no, I don’t know!”

Barrymore blurts out, earning a favorable glare from Hugo.

Hugo sighs as he sits back down on the couch.

“I see. I was mistaken for a moment. I apologize for being so distracted, son.”

Hugo apologized. This surprised Vikir once more.

Next, Vikir summoned the Chihuahua director to send the Pomeranian to the bedroom.

“Mr. Director. Please give him a quiet room today, since the thunder scared him so much.”

“Yes, sir, and I’ll have hot cocoa.”

With familiarity, Chihuahua takes the Pomeranian.

It looked as if it had been with the Pomeranian for a long time, and Hugo could see once again that his agitation was an illusion.

Chihuahua was a quick-witted person.

Sensing Vikir’s embarrassment, he gave Hugo and Barrymore a quick nod, then casually turned and covered the Pomeranian’s face.

Then, with a fluid motion, he picked up Pomeranian and carried her out of the office.

Hugo had been rubbing his face with his hands.

Vikir looked at Hugo, who was still very much shaken, and wondered.

Master. A swordsman who has touched the realm of the Supreme is not merely physically strong.

Their souls are extremely disciplined and tempered. A Swordmaster can only be reached by having a strong soul as well as a strong body.

But for Hugo, a man with such a strong soul, to be so disheveled…….

“There must be something to it.”

Vikir decided to think more deeply about the Pomeranian.

Then.

“…Son.”

Hugo opened his mouth to look at Vikir.

“Yes, Father.”

Vikir replied with a short bow.

Then came the line Vikir had been expecting.

“Come to the great banquet tomorrow.”

The Great Banquet. A small, exclusive dinner for the Baskervilles’ direct descendants, the very elite.

It is the lifelong dream of every lowly Baskerville to attend, even once.

At one point, Vikir was one of them.

A typical seventeen year old Baskerville, especially one with a Van middle name, would have jumped for joy and wagged his tail at Hugo’s offer.

But Vikir merely nodded meekly.

“I will see you tomorrow evening, father.”

Hugo nodded back, completely unmoved, and didn’t say anything else.

Only Butler Barrymore dabbed at his slightly reddened eyes with his handkerchief.

“You’ve been a good boy all these years.”

Still, it was plain to see what the old butler was thinking.

◆

That night.

Vikir retired to his bedroom in the city hall.

After a hot shower, he lay down on the fluffy bed and felt out of place.

After sleeping on dried straw and fallen leaves for the past two years, such a comfortable place to sleep felt foreign.

Eventually, Vikir left the bed and got down on the floor.

Before getting down, he tucked a pillow under the covers to disguise his bulge.

An occupational disease (?) from years of assassination experience.

“….”

After lying down without a blanket on the hardwood floor, I finally got used to it.

“Come to think of it, I always chose a hard stone floor like this to sleep on when I went hunting.”

The two years he spent with the wolves, the warriors of Ballak, were an experience he’ll never forget. For a while, it seemed to stick with him.

Vikir lay on his arms and thought about what was to come.

“Come to think of it, Hugo’s reaction today was quite unexpected.”

His reaction earlier had convinced him to some extent that he should report the matter of the Pomeranian and the pendant.

‘I’ll think about it tomorrow after the great banquet.

“Then I’ll pull out my hand at the most effective time.”

Maybe it would be a good opportunity to give Hugo a last-minute, decisive blow.

Either way, it would have to be in a way that wouldn’t harm the Pomeranian.

Vikir closed his eyes, planning his move.

“…!”

Suddenly, one of Vikir’s eyes popped open.

Whirring.

A gust of wind, so slight that a normal person wouldn’t have felt it.

The cold night air brushed against his skin.

The window opened soundlessly, and a shadow crawled through the crack.

The shadow approached the bed silently, and in its hand it drew a dagger with a sharp edge.

It smelled faintly of mana.

Then, The Shadow stood before the bed. It was where Vikir would normally lie.

But no.

The Shadow did not swing the blade directly at the bed. It simply lifted the end of the blanket and slipped quietly under it.

Of course, Vikir was on the floor, not under the covers, so he was able to watch the shadow’s movements from start to finish.

“You’ve been back less than a day. You’re a fast learner.”

Vikir smirked and pushed himself up.

And.

The physicality of the Graduator Superior is on full display.

Bam!

Vikir drew his Beelzebub and knocked the shadow’s dagger away in one swift motion.

…Puck!

The Shadow’s dagger spun around and flew away, embedding itself in the wall.

At the same time, Vikir’s grip flew out like a snake’s gills and grabbed The Shadow by the throat.

In an instant, The Shadow’s arm snapped and he fell backwards onto the bed, Vikir stamping fiercely on top of him.

Vikir climbed on top of him and whispered low in his ear.

“Next time, you might want to make a formal request for an interview. I’ll kill you if you make a mistake.”

“…I’ll have to.”

The Shadow’s breathing was steady and measured.

Then, the black cloak that covered his face slipped off.

It was the old face he hadn’t seen in a long time.

Chapter 111

The Great Banquet (3)

◆

A blazing sunset at the tip of the spire.

The night of the Great Banquet has come to Baskerville.

Vikir entered the depths of the inner castle, where only those who had enemies in the main house, especially those in important positions, were allowed to go.

The first floor of the inner castle was the great hall.

The interior of the great stone room, carved out of black stone, was neither luxurious nor glamorous, but it was certainly large and magnificent.

The gothic interior had an eerie, cold atmosphere. It’s hard to imagine this as a place for a family dinner.

The demeanor of the servants bringing the food was also strange.

The servants, both male and female, were pale and expressionless.

They moved like puppets, carrying food and arranging utensils, and when they weren’t working, they stood upright against the wall, waiting for their master’s orders.

Meanwhile.

At a large, circular table, several people sat down to eat.

Long, grim shadows cast against the hard, angular walls and ceiling.

At the end of it sits Hugo, the iron-blooded patriarch of Baskerville.

Hugo Le Baskerville. He was still eating his meal with a cold, sharp edge.

Slowly cutting his meat, chewing it, swallowing it.

Not once did he open his mouth as he continued with that horribly monotonous and repetitive task.

Meanwhile, two men sitting far apart on either side of Hugo glared at each other the entire time.

Boston Terrier Le Baskerville. And a Great Dane Le Baskerville.

Leading the Knights of the Pit Bull and the Knights of the Mastiff, respectfully, they had been antagonizing each other since they entered the dinner hall.

“Hmph!”

The Count of Boston Terriers coughed and twirled his fork around, then spoke up, his voice full of complaint.

“Well, isn’t the meat a little undercooked?”

The Boston Terrier’s words caused everyone at the table to stop eating for a moment.

The Boston Terrier picked up his fork and nervously poked at the steak in front of him, then lifted the meat off the end of his fork.

Blood dripped onto the plate.

The servants’ faces turned red as they looked at the bleeding meat.

The chef’s face, in particular, was so white it looked like he was looking at a piece of paper.

Finally, Hugo turned his head.

“Boston Terrier, do you not like the meat?”

The Boston Terrier shook his head in surprise.

“Uh, no, no, brother, it’s not that. I was referring to the meat on the plate across from me.”

With that, all eyes turn to the other side of the table.

“….”

There, a large man sits, silently slicing away at his knife.

He chews and swallows a rare steak dripping with blood without a word.

He was the Count of Great Dane, leader of the Knights of the Mastiff.

“…What’s your complaint?”

The Great Dane asked the Boston Terrier.

The Boston Terrier scowled at the scars on his face.

“Nothing. I think the meat is too raw. I’m telling you to cook it a little longer.”

“…I like it just right.”

“Aha. I see.”

The Boston Terrier smirked at the Great Dane’s blunt reply.

Then he spoke in a voice that simmered deep in his throat.

“You’re always one to eat raw, aren’t you? The meat, too, and the new knights.”

At that, the Great Dane stopped forking.

“…I’m eating something raw?”

“Ew. Did you hear that? You have very bright ears.”

“Say that again. What am I eating raw?”

“…You don’t have very bright ears again. You didn’t hear me, did you?”

The Boston Terrier bared his teeth and laughed in response, and the Great Dane clamped his mouth shut.

Their confrontation made the atmosphere at the dinner even colder.

The Boston Terrier turned to the Great Dane.

“I eat plenty of meat raw, and I don’t care if I get food poisoning or not, but don’t expect a new Knight to eat it raw.”

“I don’t know what you’re talking about. Is this some kind of out-of-character behavior at a dinner party?”

“I’m saying that I know you’ve come here with the sole intention of inducting my lovely niece into the corrupt Knights of the Mastiff.”

The Boston Terrier was now growling quite openly.

But the Great Dane remained calm, even as he wiped the corner of his mouth with his handkerchief.

“A dear nephew, I’ll grant you that, but there’s a problem with that statement: ‘My’ dear nephew. Vikir is your nephew, but he’s also my nephew. And as an uncle, it is my duty to discipline and guide my nephew on the right path.”

“And why is throwing him into a ragtag knights of mastiffs the right path?”

“……Be careful what you say. It is far better to join the Knights of the Mastiff than to join the Knights of the Pit Bull, who are dull and unintelligent.”

“I’ll be careful what I say, and you better be careful what you convert, because it’s about to get bitten.”

“I can only sigh when I see the barking, unable to identify friends and family.”

“What’s with the big head and the hollow heart?”

The Boston Terrier and the Great Dane were having a nervous breakdown.

It’s all about getting Vikir to join their knighthood.

“….”

Vikir, who was eating quietly in the middle, was at a loss.

He’d been in charge of a knightage Pit Bull once before, so he had a general idea of its power.

An order of one hundred Graduators specializing in extermination.

They are known as the most fierce knights not only in Baskerville, but in the entire Empire.

In the past, when Vikir was Deputy Magistrate of Underdog City, the illegal slave auction houses of Underdog’s underground were home to some of the biggest criminals in the Empire.

The Pitbull Knights had slaughtered and beheaded the beasts of this massive criminal organization in just half a day.

He went so far as to set fire to the Club Burning Suspension, which was a hotbed of luxury, pleasure, illegality and crime.

And it all happened under Vikir’s leadership.

That was why the current Count of Boston Terrier was so fond of his nephew, Vikir.

“Nephew, you can only trust this uncle. I will make you the strongest pit bull ever.”

He chomped on a piece of meat dripping with blood and laughed sardonically.

The servants around him shudder in horror, though he puts on an innocent face.

But the Boston Terrier wasn’t the only one courting.

“C’mon, nephew, the Knights of the Fire Mastiff aren’t bad, either. …what. I’m not just saying this because I’m the leader, I’m recommending them because they’re really good.”

The Great Dane, too, had been sending Vikir a wary glance from earlier.

The ‘knightage Mastiff’ he leads is an elite organization that is comparable to the Pit Bull Knights.

While the Pitbull Knights were known as “knights specializing in extermination” to create an atmosphere of fear through unilateral slaughter and butchery, the Mastiff Knights were known as “knights specializing in war” to formally subjugate their opponents.

Like the pit bulls, there are one hundred Graduators.

They are mobilized only in the event of a formal duel or a declaration of war, and they beat their opponents to submission in a fair contest of strength.

They operate a little differently than the Pitbull Knights, who are similar in that once they’re out there, they’re always out for blood, but they’re also willing to assassinate on occasion.

Overall, however, their ratings are similar, and that’s why the Count of Boston Terriers and the Count of Great Dane are now baring their teeth and snarling at each other.

“You sandbags who can’t even show your teeth without a letter, trying to ruin somebody’s nephew’s future, eh, where’s your conscience?”

“You must have exiled your concepts to the distant North Seas, where your only skill is killing your opponents by dirty tricks. Do not pollute my nephew’s chivalry.”

“Dirty and sleazy? See if we can get you a set of shiny armor so you can put on a show.”

“I’ll be the first to admit that you do nothing but good for others, you dirty dog.”

All of this bickering is in an effort to recruit the highly anticipated super-rookie Vikir to their respective knighthoods.

If they can recruit Vikir, whose stock is at an all-time high, they will not only bring all of Vikir’s stories and accomplishments under their umbrella, but also the future of the Knights.

It would be exciting for the Knights to have someone of Vikir’s caliber who had already reached the mid-level of the Graduator at only seventeen years of age.

Moreover, it is the custom of the House of Baskerville to admire, love, and revere strength itself, and the two Counts were no exception.

The same goes for the other five counts, who were unfortunately unable to attend due to distance.

…But.

In truth, Vikir had no intention of joining the knights.

“Because I’ll eat them both.”

I’ll have the other five, the seven great knights of House Baskerville, all under my feet.

The idea of swallowing the entire Baskervilles whole. It’s a plan I’ve had in mind for the past seventeen years, ever since my return.

But for now, the dispute is certainly troubling.

The confrontation between the two counts, a Boston Terrier and a Great Dane, who were constantly barking at each other over Vikir, was becoming increasingly heated.

Caught between a rock and a hard place, Vikir turned away with a puzzled expression on his face.

He turned to Hugo, the patriarch and host of the great banquet, for help.

…But.

“?”

Vikir couldn’t help but express his disbelief.

Hugo had been watching the two half-siblings argue with an amused expression on his face.

Chapter 113

The Great Banquet (5)

◆

The Boston Terrier lifted the goblet of wine that had been bubbling just moments before and downed it in one gulp.

The Great Dane swallowed a large chunk of steaming meat in one gulp, too.

“This must be my nephew’s brew, the flavor is wonderful!”

“Meat cooked with the Graduator’s aura, what a delicacy.”

The two counts began to stare at Vikir in the center with intense eyes.

No matter what, they wanted to bring Vikir back to their knights.

Meanwhile. Vikir thought to himself.

‘Perhaps it’s best that I only reveal my Intermediate Graduator.’

In fact, he had shown glimpses of this power a few times before.

I’d done something similar when I blew up the Champagne Tower in Club Burning Suspension, and I’d unleashed this much power when I first met the Madame of the Depht.

The difference now is that his hidden abilities have reached the highest levels of the Graduator.

With his previous life’s power fully restored, the blessing of the Styx River, the Baskerville-style Superior Sword Technique, and the demon sword Beelzebub, he was confident that in a one-on-one match, he would be a match for the current Seventh Count.

“By the way, are you saying that the Intermediate Graduator skill you briefly demonstrated two years ago hasn’t spread to anyone yet?”

Vikir glanced over to the head of the great feast table.

There, the triplets – Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro – were sitting and eating in silence.

“….”

“….”

“….”

From the looks of it, they hadn’t reported their last encounter in the depths to Hugo.

I don’t know why.

‘Still, it was helpful. I wonder if I should have revealed my advanced Graduator level.’

I’m glad I was able to keep my power to a minimum.

Vikir picked up his fork, knowing that he would have to enforce the High, Mid, and Low Bro’s mouths once again after the great banquet.

Meanwhile.

The Boston Terrier and Great Dane couldn’t stop praising Vikir’s accomplishment.

“To cook meat and brew liquor just by touching the table and creating a mana resonance, that’s no ordinary mana proficiency. Hehe, that’s amazing, and I was an advanced Sword Expert at best at that age.”

“That’s a mana control that would be impossible to achieve unless you’re at least an Intermediate Graduator. This must be an all-time genius in Baskerville, because I was at that level when I was thirty-three.”

The average hound in Baskerville would not have been able to reach this level until they were thirty-five.

He did it at the mere age of 17. He was nearly two decades ahead of the curve.

The Boston Terrier and Great Dane looked at Hugo and exclaimed.

“An intermediate graduator! What I didn’t accomplish until I was thirty-three, and at only seventeen! What a slope!”

“Hahaha, I’m sure you’ll be pleased, brother. This is a triumph for the entire family. A toast to my proud nephew’s accomplishment!”

The two men looked completely mesmerized.

Even Hugo was smiling broadly at the situation.

The corners of his mouth turned up in a way that made it clear he was smiling.

Soon, Hugo and the two counts were talking about Vikir.

More than 90 percent of the conversation centered around a request to send Vikir to join their knights.

When the adults’ attention is momentarily diverted.

A new voice spoke to him.

“Little brother.”

Accurate pronunciation, cold voice.

Vikir turned his head in the direction of the voice.

There he saw long hair hanging like a black curtain, and red eyes shining through it.

“Osiris Le Baskerville.”

Currently the strongest Late Exponent of the Baskerville family. First in line for the family succession. The man in line for the position of Small Householder, acting in the absence of the Householder.

He was currently sitting diagonally across from Vikir, looking this way.

“….”

Vikir met Osiris’s eyes.

A tiny absolute, a being so arrogant and high-minded that he hadn’t dared to look him in the eye before his regression.

But now Vikir had the skill and strength to face such a being with dignity.

Vikir met Osiris’ gaze without flinching.

Finally, Osiris spoke.

“You worked hard.”

Vikir’s pupils dilated slightly at the words.

He was surprised that the man had spoken to him first, but a compliment? It was unthinkable, given his pre-regression image.

But the surprise didn’t stop there.

“Well done. Keep up the good work.”

Osiris continued to give Vikir a series of virtuous words.

His voice is still cold, his expression unchanged, and a normal person would think he was angry.

The younger Vikir, before his regression, had thought so, too.

But as he grew older, he realized that was not the case.

Osiris’s expression and voice were certainly icy cold, but there was a tiny, slight warmth underneath.

A warmth that could not be expressed in face, gesture, or words.

A warmth that was so clumsy, it was clear that even he didn’t know how to express it.

‘…Now that I think about it, you weren’t so scary after all.’

Vikir thought to himself as he bowed to Osiris.

Why did he seem so frightening before the regression? Was it because he was the family patriarch? Was it because of his arrogant, high-minded expression and voice? Was it because of the vast disparity in status and power? Was it simply because he was more than ten years older than him?

But Osiris, as he is now, is much younger than Vikir actually is.

It was then that the clumsiness and awkwardness of Osiris began to come into focus.

The way he’s not very good with a knife, the way he picks and chooses what he doesn’t like to eat, the way his face crumples at the mere smell of a very weak drink, the way he can only straighten out a crumpled napkin if he’s forced to do it over and over again….

‘He was surprisingly human.’

Once you get past the stereotype of the untouchable celestial overlord, you start to see the real him.

Osiris Le Baskerville.

He was not the perfect, bloodless, tearless superhuman as the world had known him, and as Vikir had remembered him before his regression.

Just then.

“Wow. Big brother complimenting little brother, that’s amazing.”

A new voice spoke from Vikir’s side.

Turning his head, Vikir saw a handsome man with unusually white and pale skin winking at him.

A handsome man with black hair and red eyes with deep dark circles.

He was Seth Le Baskerville, Hugo’s second son.

He smiled in a friendly way and spoke softly to Vikir.

“I’ve never seen Osiris praise someone like that, or smile so wide with such joy.”

…Was that a smile?

Vikir glanced away and looked at Osiris.

Osiris was slicing a steak with an expressionless face.

It was still a look that could be mistaken for anger.

“That’s why everyone feared Osiris before the regression.”

But that was a smile, and it’s amazing to hear it again.

“….”

When Vikir was speechless, Seth smirked.

“You have a poker face like your brother Osiris, don’t you? Well, everyone in my family does. Blunt and all. It’s a shame.”

Unlike Osiris, and unlike anyone else in the family, Seth was expressive.

Vikir watched as Seth smiled wistfully.

Seth Le Baskerville, as Vikir remembered him, was a good man.

Despite his lack of talent with the sword and his lack of compassion, he cared for everyone in the house.

A gentle man who would listen to the discomfort of a maid, even if that maid was new to the house.

The only one of his immediate family to lay chrysanthemums on the tombstones of his dead hounds.

I can still see him weeping for his father, who had no blood or tears, and for all his brothers, who were dying for him.

On days when he was ignored by his father or brother as a weakling, he would go to the flower garden by himself and let his tears fall.

And that was true even now, after his regression.

Hugo and Osiris had all but ignored Seth.

It was only natural that Seth, the underdog, should be ignored by the powerful Baskervilles.

So Vikir had pitied and respected Seth in his heart before he was turned.

He had fallen into his line and worked for him, even though he had nothing to gain.

He had pitied Seth for being so soft-hearted, and he had admired him for putting up with it and being so good to hounds like himself.

…But now it was different.

Vikir replayed in his mind the information Cindywendy had given him yesterday.

<Seth Le Baskerville>

Rank: Underdog city magistrate and senator.

Title: Viscount

Rank: Intermediate Graduator

Other: Second son of Hugo Le Baskerville, the patriarch of House Baskerville. Currently second in line of succession.

.

.

Gentle and warm personality. Weaknesses. No talent for swordsmanship. Hated by Hugo. Well-liked by all the lesser members of the family. Has been away from the Underdogs for a long time. Stepped out briefly for a great banquet during his closing exercises…

A rambling list of information that Vikir already knew.

But at the end of it, there was a line that even Vikir had never seen before.

‘Seth Le Baskerville’ is assumed to be non-human.

Chapter 116

Falling in Love (1)

◆

The sun was beginning to rise.

First thing in the morning, Vikir did as Hugo had instructed him at the banquet last night.

“Enter the Academy.”

Hugo’s tone was still blunt.

A sheet of paper was slid in front of Vikir.

It was a home letter announcing that the Academy was recruiting new students for the new semester.

<Academy ‘Colosseo’ is recruiting new students for the 20th class>

Application submission: November 04, 19th year of the imperial calendar ~ November 26th, 19th year of the imperial calendar

Class period: 8 semesters (4 years)

Entrance date: January 1, 20th Imperial Year

Academy Colosseo. A large-scale collective educational institution in Imperial Rock.

It has a staggering number of students, over 7,000, and if you count the post-academy students, the number is over 20,000.

The number of faculty and staff alone reached 4,000.

Considered one of the greatest institutions of higher learning in the history of mankind, the Colosseo attracts students from many families, including the seven families that hold the Empire together.

Every noble young man in the Empire considers it a lifelong honor to be admitted, and indeed, graduates of the Academy have proudly served as elite members of the Imperial family and in the highest ranks of society.

From the first Emperor of Imperial Rock, most of the heads of the Seven Great Families have already graduated from the Academy, as well as billionaires of all kinds, heads of the largest guilds, renowned scholars, and other social leaders who hold top positions in politics, law, business, culture, media, academia, sports, and more.

The alumni network was already unrivaled in the empire and the most influential of all social groups.

“….”

Vikir stared down at the document in front of him.

Students at the Academy are not discriminated against during their four years here, admission and graduation are based solely on merit.

The majority of the Academy’s students enter at the age of 20 and graduate at the age of 24, although there is some deviation.

Academy graduates are given the option of remaining in the Imperium and working for the Empire or returning to their original families.

Hugo had hoped to return home after the Academy, and his eldest son Osiris had followed the same path.

And Vikir, of course, intended to follow suit.

“I’ll be back.”

Vikir didn’t hesitate to accept Hugo’s offer.

He’d been to the academy before, before the regression.

‘…Of course, I wasn’t eligible for admission then.’

He had followed the students as a hound, escorting them to various services.

For the record, the Academy’s first class of students were triplets: Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

Hugo nodded, then turned to Vikir.

“Do you have a brother who would like to come with you?”

The Academy had given the Baskervilles a certain number of seats at the Academy.

It’s a kind of seed assignment, TO was vacated, but considering the brand and name value of the Baskervilles, it’s natural.

Vikir didn’t hesitate to answer.

“I want to go with my brothers to the Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.”

He had said this to Hugo before.

Hugo still rubbed his chin in disbelief, but then he was convinced.

“‘Cause they’re the only brothers in your row that’s worth going with.”

But Vikir didn’t want to take the triplets for that reason alone.

Naturally, his mind wandered back to the end of yesterday’s great banquet.

’ … It was unexpected.’

On his way to his bedroom, Vikir had gotten a visit from the triplets.

Sigh.

With a strange look of determination on their faces, they drew their swords and stood in his way, intent on exterminating him, who was in more ways than one.

To bury them, along with what happened in the depht two years ago.

But.

The triplets had a completely unexpected reaction.

…Shake!

All three knelt on their right knees in front of Vikir, heads bowed.

The tip of the drawn blade was resting on the instep of their right foot, and the tip of the handle was pointed at Vikir.

If the Vikir reached out and pressed, their swords would go straight through their own insteps.

It was an act of surrendering one’s life to the other, or in dog terms, lying down on one’s stomach.

“What are you doing?”

Vikir asked in disbelief.

Why would the knights of the Empire make such a vow to him, a vow that is only made when they meet their destined masters?

The triplets answered.

“We wish to repay you with our lives.”

“I will.”

“I will.”

Their reasoning was, in retrospect, quite surprising.

The triplets had been afraid of Vikir ever since he had beaten them when they were nine years old.

That fear became recognition when Vikir hunted Cerberus, and respect when Vikir killed a troll in a single blow.

And finally. Madame of the Depht.

The moment Vikir unleashed the Graduator’s aura on the massive creature that loomed like death itself.

The triplets’ feelings toward Vikir changed once more.

A sense of reverence. Respect.

The kind of ambivalent feelings that humans have when they encounter a genius they can never surpass.

The triplets were rescued that day, carried on the backs of their guardian knights, and saw their own powerlessness in the face of Vikir’s sun-blazing strength.

And on that day, the day they barely escaped with their lives. The three of them gathered together and vowed in unison.

“From this day forward, we are the Trident of Vikir.”

To repay the debt of their lives that day.

From then on, the triplets never spoke of Vikir.

Not even about the ridiculous status he had displayed two years earlier.

And two years later, when Vikir returned alive, he never said that the achievements he showed had not grown at all compared to two years ago.

They were aware. They knew that Vikir had already been a Intermediate Graduator two years ago, and that in the past two years, he had grown stronger than ever.

But even so, they kept their master’s secret.

‘….’

Vikir stroked his chin silently.

Born to be hounds, the trio needed a master to obey.

Their skill and loyalty had been proven in their last life.

Before his regression, they had threatened and driven him more than anything else.

Vikir stopped reminiscing and looked at Hugo.

“How many other squires can I take with me?”

“As you wish.”

Hugo nodded readily.

Vikir nodded silently.

In the past, Vikir had also lived within the Academy as a squire, assisting with the admission of new students to the Academy.

Squires rotate through the academy on a semesterly basis to assist their families’ entrants.

His duties as an aide consisted of little more than escorting and running errands.

It was a typical knight’s squire role.

Vikir had entered the Academy as a squire of the Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro before his regression.

It was nice to look over his shoulder and listen to the Academy’s lessons, but other than that, it was all dull and tiring.

He had to run errands such as washing clothes, preparing materials for performance evaluations, memorizing timetables and meal plans, sometimes escorting, sometimes settling disputes, sometimes being a dueling opponent, and even delivering love letters.

‘There was a lot of persecution back then.’

When he returned home, he had seen so many harsh scenes that his face was covered in scars and his legs were limp.

Is that why? The fine-bred noble sons and daughters of the academy would scowl and show their disdain whenever they saw Vikir, who came to serve as a quarterly squire.

‘Well, it doesn’t matter. You’re not going to the academy to learn anything anyway.’

Vikir wanted to join the Academy for two reasons.

First, to get off Hugo’s radar and build his power.

Second, to take care of the “black list” he’d compiled before his regression.

It occurred to him that he might have to wear the Night Hound mask he’d kept sealed away for so long.

Then. Hugo spoke up.

“That’s all for now. You may leave now.”

When Hugo had said all he had to say, he called for a celebration.

But.

There was one thing left for Vikir to do: make a deal with Hugo.

Instead of walking away, Vikir raised his head toward Hugo.

“Father. There is something I would like to ask you.”

“…?”

It was unusual for Vikir to ask for something first, so Hugo looked interested.

Then, as if to double-check, Vikir asked Hugo a question.

“I understand that my disappearance two years ago has greatly benefited the Main House in its diplomacy with the Morgue.”

Hugo nodded at Vikir’s straightforward statement.

Vikir continued.

“And my father has told me that he is rewarding me for this.”

“That’s right. I said I’d reward you appropriately, but we’re still discussing that.”

Vikir’s accomplishment was so great that a modest reward would not clearly recognize it.

Hugo was considering it, but Vikir spoke up first.

“I want that reward now.”

“Hmm. Do you want something?”

It was also unusual for Vikir to want something first.

Hugo looked at his son’s face in front of him with a gleam in his eye.

And then. Vikir’s mouth opened.

“What I want is for you to answer my question, Father, honestly.”

“…?”

Hugo’s brow furrowed slightly.

It was a demand that could be offensive to some.

Hugo opened his mouth.

“I don’t understand the question.”

“Then I’ll ask it with your permission.”

Vikir looked Hugo in the eye and asked in a much more direct manner than Hugo had.

“What was your relationship with the late First Lady, the Marquise de Roxana?”

Hugo’s entire body went rigid.

Is this the expression of a dragon that has been stabbed in the back?

Extreme agitation. Hugo is reacting in a way I’ve never seen before.

“…What are you trying to do?”

Hugo’s voice became extremely cold.

A terrifying chill, a cold aura, radiated from his entire body.

But Vikir was unfazed.

He didn’t flinch, despite the fact that all the intimacy and rapport he’d built up to this point was collapsing.

Hugo opened his mouth.

“Get out.”

“….”

“Forget about the Academy, it’s a blank slate.”

Hugo threw up his hands.

It had never happened before in his life that he’d let his emotions get the better of him like this.

But Vikir was still in his face.

“I understand that your admission to the Academy has been canceled.”

“….”

“But the trade gains my family made from my disappearance two years ago cannot be canceled.”

That meant he’d better answer quickly.

Hugo gave Vikir a look of irritation he’d never seen before.

“What the hell do you want an answer to!”

“It’s a question.”

Vikir said, still in an even tone.

“What did you think of the Marquise de Roxana?”

The Pomeranian’s smiling face floated around in Vikir’s mind.

What would Hugo’s reaction be if he learned of the existence of a granddaughter he hadn’t even known existed?

Would he be as displeased as he was now? Most likely, he would.

‘…Because he’s a man without blood or tears.’

The first wife he met through an arranged marriage, the eldest daughter born with her and kidnapped by the natives, and the granddaughter of mixed native blood.

Vikir had already run through 365 different scenarios in her head of how Hugo would react to the discovery of the Pomeranian’s existence.

And in every case, she had made arrangements to benefit herself and the Pomeranians.

…?

Hugo began by saying something that wasn’t in any of Vikir’s 365 plans.

“She was the only woman I ever loved in my entire life.”

Chapter 120

The Hunt for the Second Son (2)

◆

“….Uh, how?”

Seth looked up, his eyes wide.

Vikir van Baskerville. Hugo’s illegitimate son.

He must be some lowly bastard from an insignificant birth.

Just another hound to be used and discarded.

However, it was also true that he was born in the fastest time ever to pass through the Cradle of the Sword and was favored by the River Styx, and from an early age, he hunted high-ranking demonic creatures such as trolls and Cerberus.

Two venomous snakes were placed in the cradle to remove him early on, but they failed.

Not long ago, he miraculously returned from the battlefield after being thought to be dead, revealing a stunning achievement of Intermediate Graduator.

At only seventeen years old, he had achieved the rank of Intermediate Graduator, a feat no one else in Ironblooded Baskerville had ever accomplished.

Even the first son Osiris, rumored to be a genius, was over thirty years old when he reached Intermediate Graduator.

So even as Vikir demonstrated his power in the Banquet Hall, Seth clicked his tongue.

‘Tsk, tsk, he shouldn’t reveal all his secrets like that.’

Power should be shown in moderation and hidden in moderation.

That way, you can make the most of your future with less pressure from those around you.

Wearing your power on your sleeve was the behavior of children who wanted the praise of adults.

In that sense, Vikir was still a child who didn’t need to be watched.

At least, that’s what Seth thought.

…But.

In-person, Vikir’s true character was far more formidable. Almost unbelievable to the naked eye.

Who would have thought that at the age of only a few years, he would have achieved a level of mastery that would allow him to cross into the realm of the supreme.

“‘Advanced Graduator … No, Supreme?”

Seth’s mouth was half open at the sheer unreality of the sight.

Honestly, if it weren’t for his enemies, he might have thought it was a sight to behold.

Meanwhile, against Seth’s dazed expression, Vikir unleashed all of his hidden combat power, without restraint.

“You don’t have eyes to see anyway, so it doesn’t matter.”

“ …I don’t have eyes to see, little brother, because you do.”

“It’s an eye that will soon be gone.”

Vikir’s next move wiped the smile off Seth’s face.

Kwaki-gigi-gigi-gig-.

Baskerville’s seventh form. A small but sharp flash of the seventh tooth, the one that only Patriarch can master.

When combined with the aura of a top-notch Graduator, its killing power is enough to frighten even the highest-ranking demons.

“You’re insane, how could you use a seventh tooth that only a patriarch can master!”

Seth exclaimed in astonishment, but he couldn’t afford to be surprised.

Vikir hadn’t bothered to tell him that he knew how to deploy the eighth, ninth, and even the tenth.

He just kept silently swinging his sword until he mastered the seventh and broke through the wall beyond.

Bang! Bang! Kagagak!

The surrounding stalactites and stalagmites bend like reed stems.

Seth is backed into a corner with no time to catch his breath.

‘He’s an experienced bastard. Even the worn and tattered old knights of Baskerville aren’t like this….’

It was as if he was facing a mountain, a feeling similar to when he had faced one of the Seven Counts in the past.

Seth gritted his teeth and swung his flamberg.

A Baskerville carnivore. Six teeth blocked seven teeth.

But.

The teeth that drew from the tip of Vikir’s blade were shaped differently than Seth’s.

“Stabbing fangs or not, what is this?”

By the time the question was asked, it was too late.

…Puff-puff-puff-puck!

Seth’s body explodes in all directions.

It’s an ambush bite, one that exists solely to inflict pain on its opponent.

It sliced through the flesh and stabbed deep into its very core, unleashing seven deadly and irresistible stabs all over Seth’s body.

“Aaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!”

Seth stumbled back, dragging his tattered body.

He could barely keep his balance after his left arm had been severed.

And Vikir, like a seasoned veteran, took advantage of his enemy’s hesitation.

…Thud!

One step back, two steps forward.

Boom!

One swing, two swings, and a slash.

Pooh-pooh-pooh-pooh!

Baskerville’s hound, Death’s Tooth, ferociously bites Seth’s entire body.

It would be more appropriate to say that it stabbed rather than slashed.

“Eueueueug!?”

Seth was unable to resist, seeing his flesh fall off as he was turned into pieces of meat.

He couldn’t think clearly.

Looking at this relentless sword attack, it was clear that it was not a skill that had been killed once or twice.

‘Nonsense! It’s only a human, and seventeen at that! How many have you killed before?

Seth barely managed to swing his sword back.

But.

…Hook!

Vikir, the Hound of Death, closed the distance.

Suddenly, the scent of Vikir assaulted Seth’s sense of smell.

It’s a smell that no amount of washing can erase, a smell that sticks to the soul, not the body.

It is the smell of a demon, or more specifically, the smell of a demon as it bleeds and groans in pain!

A ray of light shimmered in Seth’s black eyes. It was a light of terror.

‘…Ah, demon hunter!??’

Yes. In front of him. The young adult body of this young.

Unbelievably, his soul exuded the scent of a butcher who had killed countless of his kind.

Do dogs recognize their masters and wag their tails?

Seth felt his entire body stiffen.

How many demons had he killed so far?

With each burst of Vikir’s momentum, Seth’s eyes flashed before him a terrifying landscape, with mountains of demon corpses and rivers of blood flowing through it.

“No, nonsense, nonsense! How could such a young guy go through such an out-of-human demon scene!”

Seth opened his mouth, but it was only to increase the volume of space for Vikir’s attack.

Thwack!

Vikir’s slash flew in.

It sliced through Seth’s gums, knocking out several of his teeth and slicing through his tongue and uvula.

Sapuk.

It sliced into Seth’s left cheek, retrieved the protruding sword tip neatly, and flicked it once.

“….”

Vikir started to ask something but stopped.

I already know his plan, and his purpose.

It was something he could guess, given his knowledge before and after the regression.

‘He’s a higher being from the Demon Realm. He probably wants to destroy the human world.’

Before the regression, ten demon kings opened a gate to the depths of the Demon Realm and caused an era of destruction.

They were called the “Ten Corpses,” referring not only to the ten demons, but also to the ten corpses that were taken over by them.

Some of them were known, some were not, and in the case of the Seth Le Baskerville before us, they were not known.

‘…For even I did not know his identity until the day of my execution.’

Even the heroes who closed the gates and ended the Age of Destruction were never able to find the Ten Commandments and condemn them once and for all.

But.

This time is different.

The Age of Destruction has not yet begun.

The gates to the depths of the Demon Realm have yet to be opened, and the Ten Commandments that would open them have yet to appear.

And Vikir had already found one of them.

“You die here.”

Vikir declared.

If you can kill him here, the future will change.

Killing one of the Ten Commandments would not prevent the Age of Destruction from occurring at all, but it would slow it down immensely.

This would give Vikir much more time to plan.

Time to solidify his plan and prepare for every variable.

‘I will never lose a single game’

With all errors and variables blocked and sealed off in advance, Vikir swung his sword with all the power he had before his regression.

His swordsmanship was even more noble than before his regression, his aura even more powerful, and the blade of his magic sword, Beelzebub, blazed with sun-like red light.

And naturally, Seth who was only an Intermediate Graduator, with the power of an advanced one, was unable to parry Vikir’s sword.

“Gaaaah!”

Seth screamed through his tattered body.

Even if he was weak, that was only by Baskerville’s standards. As Hugo’s second-born son, his talents shouldn’t be inferior.

The problem was, he had his mother’s weak bones and pelt, and couldn’t contain the powerful qualities he inherited from Hugo.

So no matter how hard he tried, he could only become a Graduator Advanced, and that was his limit.

This was a terrible humiliation for a genius outside the standard, someone who had achieved great things, even if it was by blood.

Still, it was nothing new for Seth.

Because before Vikir, it was Osiris.

“Mmph… mmph!”

Blackened blood dripped from Seth’s eyes, nose, and mouth.

A terrible sense of inferiority washed over him.

Seeing this, Vikir hesitated.

‘Was Seth’s soul still there?’

Obviously, Seth’s body had been taken by the demons after he was hanged.

But it seemed clear that somewhere in the depths of his soul, Seth’s memories and personality remained.

‘But that was that, and this is this.’

Even if he paused for a moment, it was a matter of the mind, and the hands and knife were still relentlessly slashing at Seth.

Puck! Puck! Puck! Puck!

Seven teeth flew out, slicing through Seth’s entire body.

Eventually.

“How dare you, you dirty Baskerville, you filthy hound!”

Finally, Seth, or rather, the thing that had been wearing Seth’s skin, showed its true colors.

Tsutsutsutsutsutsutsuts…

Formless magic erupted from the holes in Seth’s body.

It soon wriggled like the mud on a doll and began to take shape into a single, massive form.

And Vikir realized the nature of the demon that had consumed Seth’s body and soul.

<Andromalius the Tenth>.

Danger Rating : S+.

Size: ?

Found in: In the depths of the Gate of Destruction, ‘The Serpent’s Womb’

-Nicknamed ‘Tenth Corpse’.

One of the ten catastrophes that lead to humanity’s natural enemy, incomprehensible, and unkillable.

“They shall swarm like flies.”

– 『The Ten Commandments』 10: Top-

The final boss, “ Ten Corpses (十上尸)”. One of the ten top corpses.

One of the ten keys that unlocked the Age of Destruction.

Chapter 124

The Hunt for the Second Son (6)

◆

A few days have passed.

In every territory under Baskerville’s jurisdiction, in every square, rooms have been set up.

<Information on the process for investigating and compensating for the disappearance of infants within Baskerville’s territory>.

-The purpose of this room is to uncover and compensate for all cases of infant disappearances that occurred between the years B,C 10 and A,C 19 of the Empire.

In accordance with the principles of Article 1, Paragraph 4 of the Vikir Special Law, a compensation plan is being sent to all families and nurseries where missing children occurred during this period, so that the liquidators and related parties can fill out the relevant documents and submit them to the city hall within the time limit and recover the remains of the lost children. …

The Baskerville family has thoroughly investigated a series of incidents, including infanticide and kidnapping, and conducted compensation procedures.

While they did not reveal that a demon of the highest order had descended, they did not mince words about the horrific acts committed by the Baskervilles’ second son.

This was a small consolation to the bereaved family, whose lives had been destroyed by the loss of their child, and who had organized protests and hunger strikes to demand an investigation and find out the truth.

They were also able to receive real-time reports on the punishment process of the perpetrators and see them in person.

The first to be brought to justice was the set’s mother, Noot, who served as a participatory judge and juror.

She was surprisingly not brainwashed by the demon and cried out the whole way to the courtroom to be allowed to see Seth.

Noot was summarily executed on a total of 1,642 charges, including releasing poisonous snakes in the children’s rooms, first-degree poisoning, conspiracy to kidnap the eldest daughter, and aiding and abetting the kidnapping of Seth’s infant.

Seth’s nannies were subsequently lined up and publicly executed, as were Seth’s henchmen who worked under him to systematically kidnap and transport children.

The trial and execution of a high-ranking member of Baskerville’s inner circle on the spot came as a shock to many estatesmen.

It reaffirmed the perception that the laws of Baskerville were so severe and thorough that not even Baskerville could escape them.

Also.

Numerous orphanage directors who sold children were decapitated, and brokers, lobbyists, and government officials who participated in the falsification of documents were torn limb from limb.

Countless others disappeared or were crippled as dew on the sentence.

For those children who had no family, memorials were erected and maintained annually by high-ranking officials.

Many annual rituals were organized for constant remembrance.

All of this was the handiwork of Osiris, the patriarch of the House of Baskerville, and entirely under his care and control.

No, one. There was a being to whom Osiris had ceded some of his authority.

Vikir Van Baskerville.

This hero, who survived a war with barbarians outside the borders, was recognized upon his return as the original discoverer and chief contributor to the project.

He was given a share of the state’s authority and his fame grew to great heights.

Osiris and Vikir’s work was swift and precise.

Within days, all the relevant special laws were in place, and it was no more than a week before they were actually enforced on the ground.

It was an event of such magnitude that an imperial commission was sent to investigate it, but it was unusual that no noise was heard afterward.

◆

“Right, right, come here, Pomeranian.”

Hugo shaved his mustache, a lifelong vice.

It didn’t exactly make him more likable, but it was surprising to see him try so hard to look pretty for his granddaughter.

Pomeranian touched Hugo’s dull chin and smiled brightly.

“Look at her smile. He looks just like Roxana, and just like Penelope.”

Hugo held the Pomeranian’s gaze with a mixture of happiness and sadness.

Meanwhile. Vikir had been summoned to Hugo’s office and was watching the scene.

Osiris was there, too.

“Long time no see, brother.”

Hugo has been overworked lately, and his eyes are a bit hollow.

But as he smiles faintly at Vikir, his face seems much more human than before.

To Vikir, who bowed reverently, Hugo said.

“You must be very busy these days.”

“Yes.”

“By the time I’m done with this matter, it will be too late. Hurry up and join the Academy.”

Vikir shook his head.

“The family is still in turmoil. I’ll have to wait until things are a little more organized before I go….”

Vikir still didn’t believe Hugo.

Purge. A large-scale purge.

Hugo seemed to be using this incident to reorganize the power structure within the family.

Reality is not a fairy tale.

This series of trials and punishments, which seemed to be a process of justice being served, was actually just a show, Vikir thought, an outgrowth of the political battles of the big boys.

It was rare for a Baskerville family to fully admit responsibility and pay compensation in a high-profile case like this infanticide and kidnapping.

But Hugo had done so.

It was an act of cold political judgment, not an appeal to emotions like morality or humanity.

“To officially recognize the family’s responsibility for the incident, and to remove those involved from their positions of authority. To eliminate many of their enemies and consolidate their power.”

Re-weaving the plate. Aka ‘making a new board’.

The number of those who have been ousted from the power structure due to this set incident is numerous.

From the most insignificant to the most prominent.

When these people are purged and demoted at once, several lines are shaken.

For example, the power of the seven counts to keep the family in check was significantly weakened.

It was only natural that the limbs were cut off.

There was also some shuffling within the Knights.

A series of elderly senators and deputies were purged to punish demonic infiltrators, a process spearheaded by the family line, Osiris.

Vikir, with his pre-Regression knowledge, was of course part of the operation, and not just to solidify his position as a representative of Patriarch Hugo’s line.

Data on the contacts Seth had been secretly making.

Vikir smuggled it out and handed it over to Cindywendy to analyze.

To determine the identities and current locations of the other Ten Commandments.

‘I don’t want to do this! I’m already overworked enough as it is, and what, you want me to track the location of demons at the King level? How many heads do you think I have?

Of course, she didn’t want to take on such a dangerous task.

‘So. You don’t want to trade with the natives?’

In the face of a mega-deal of epic proportions with the natives of Depht, she had no choice but to give in.

…Well, let’s just say it was.

There was one thing Vikir didn’t understand right now.

‘Why would they want to send me to the Academy, especially at this point….’

Vikir has no reason to refuse, but the timing is a little too good to be true.

It’s good to have a public figure like Vikir as a face when you’re trying to weed out the noise like Hugo is doing now.

It’s good to have someone like Vikir as the face of the family when there’s no one in the family who doesn’t know that Vikir is Hugo’s line, so that Hugo can take the knife with a good cause.

After all, Vikir was the first to recognize and report Seth’s corruption.

“Sending me to the Academy now would be inefficient from Hugo’s perspective.”

So Vikir didn’t understand why Hugo was trying to send him to the Academy so soon.

Normally, Hugo would take the initiative and tell him to delay his enrollment for a few years….

“Is he up to something?”

But since he couldn’t ask outright, he could only suspect.

Then.

Osiris, who had approached, spoke up.

“My father is concerned that you will be caught in the aftermath of a power struggle and get hurt.”

…Concerned?

Vikir laughed in disbelief.

Hugo wouldn’t do that. Who was the great man to be worried about that heartless scoundrel?

It was strange that Osiris should even be listening to him in the first place.

“Isn’t this supposed to be Butler Barrymore’s job?”

But Butler Barrymore was too busy marveling at Hugo’s mustache.

“My lord. You look much better without a mustache.”

“Indeed, but it makes me look very hollow.”

Hugo smiled weakly as he styled the Pomeranian’s hair into a feather braid, a skill he didn’t know where he’d learned.

‘What an unfamiliar sight.’

Vikir thought to himself.

…Tuck!

Osiris’s hand came up to rest on his shoulder.

It was unexpectedly warm.

Vikir looked up to see Osiris standing next to him, looking down at him.

“Thanks to you, I know. That I have duties as an individual, but also as a brother.”

“….”

“Do not worry about yourself, but go to the Academy.”

Osiris seemed to be trying to change, at least a little, in the way he treated his brothers from now on.

He turned to Vikir with an awkward, clumsy smile.

“I’ll have everything sorted out by the time you return home for your first vacation.”

Chapter 125

Admission to the Academy (1)

◆

Easterners, don’t boast of the pyramids.

Westerners, don’t talk about Babylon.

There is no place for them in front of the emperor’s academy ‘Colosseo’.

All fame is for this.

All shall be in its shadow.

◆

The Colosseo Academy. The most prestigious academy in the world, from east to west, north to south, and across the central continent.

Located in the heart of the Central Continent, in the capital city of the imperial family, the academy occupies the entirety of the most fertile yolk land in the Imperial Capital.

Unlike the ‘Magic Tower’, which specializes in magic, and the ‘Varangian’, which specializes in martial arts, there is a tendency to value both literal and martial arts. It is famous for not being able to enter or graduate if you do not meet the strict standards.

For the start of the new semester, crowds of students flocked to Venetior, the capital of the ROK.

Freshmen.

And their families.

And the groups escorting them.

And the hordes of people trying to sell them stuff.

It’s the one time of year when the largest concentration of people can be found at the Academy.

All the new students from the East, West, South, and North who flocked to the Imperial City had to marvel twice: once at the beauty of the capital, and again at the grandeur of the Academy.

Venetior, the city of water.

The capital of the Rok Empire, Venetior is a gently sloping basin, where rivers from across the continent converge to create a myriad of waterways.

As you drive into the city center, you’ll be greeted with sweeping views of the entire city on the land below.

With a crystal clear freshwater lake gently hugging the ecliptic, 112 islands on top of it, and nearly 400 bridges, the metropolis looks like a paradise.

Slow, warm rivers.

Countless waterways and bridges connecting them.

Beautiful architecture rises high above the crowded streets above the bridges.

Numerous aerial bridges connect skyscraper after skyscraper, and greenery grows all year round on the piers.

The city’s waterways have become important transportation routes, creating a unique and beautiful cityscape, and it is not uncommon to see canoes traveling on the waterways in the alleys, as well as various street vendors on them.

As an imperial capital, it is also home to a number of modern cultural institutions, including theaters, museums, clock towers, churches, opera houses, the Imperial Library, and huge public baths.

But it’s the Academy that’s most famous. Home to some of the continent’s finest materials.

The Colosseo.

This massive, circular cluster of buildings is home to about 20,000 people, including students, professors, and workers of all kinds.

Together, the buildings form a gigantic arena surrounding a single large stage, and a walk around the diameter of the Academy grounds would take the average person over four hours.

The academy is divided into two main parts: the dormitory building, where students live, and the classroom building, where classes are held. The dormitory building is divided by grade and gender, and the classroom building is divided by grade and class.

Since the school is a four-year program, there are four grades.

Students are divided into first, second, third, and fourth grades, and there were rare cases of students taking a leave of absence or returning to school after failing the graduation examination.

There were two main classes.

The “Cold Class”.

And the “Hot Class”.

The Cold Class includes students who specialize in swords, bows, and spears, and they take courses related to their specialty as required courses for their majors, other Cold Classes as electives for their majors, and courses in the Hot Class as required courses for their general education.

On the other hand, the Hot Class contains students whose primary specialty is magic, and they take courses related to their primary elemental magic as required courses, other magics as electives, and courses in the Cold Class as general education requirements.

In other words. It doesn’t matter if they specialize in swords, bows, spears, fire, ice, earth, or plant magic, the end result is that they have four years to develop a general knowledge of all of them.

In addition to these classes, of course, there is a wealth of other general electives in languages, theology, law, astronomy, geography, military studies, etc.

In order to graduate, students must take a certain number of credits of these major requirements, major electives, general education requirements, general education electives, and courses for majors and minors, sometimes voluntarily, sometimes compulsorily, according to their schedule and aptitude.

Class schedules are organized, sometimes voluntarily, sometimes by force.

Naturally, there is a pecking order among students based on their grades, which has a huge impact on their later academic life.

In addition, students are limited in their ability to participate in clubs, volunteer activities, work experience programs, and other internal and external activities such as choosing a major.

Therefore, freshmen are eager to take the academy’s placement test for the first time.

Seniors are also very interested in the results of the freshmen’s placement test.

They want to recruit the best possible juniors for their clubs and social organizations.

…Is that so?

The Academy’s current students have been buzzing since February, when the freshman placement test ended.

They wanted to get a head start on the new students who had already stood out.

“I heard the freshman placement test is over?”

“Who stood out the most?”

“Probably the ones who did well in the practical evaluation, right?”

Except for the professors, the freshmen’s information is off-limits, but… the grades and rankings of the freshmen were already circulating among some powerful students.

Like stock market speculation, the names, grades, and rankings of the new students were traded at a high price depending on their accuracy.

This is because most of those who enter the academy are likely to enter the upper echelons of the Empire in the future, so it’s important to make connections in advance.

“Oho, look at this, all the new students this year have great grades~”

“Huh? Isn’t the first place in the Cold Class tied?”

“Tudor from the Sun Spear Clan and Bianca from the God Bow Secret House are tied for first place.”

“They’re tier one. They are our club’s top priority for recruitment!”

The current students of the Cold Class were already excited by the rumors of an outstanding junior would be joining them.

Tudor, a spearman, and Bianca, an archer, are likely to receive a lot of offers from their seniors, as the school values practical skills much more highly than written ones.

These geniuses have caught the attention of professors and seniors alike.

-Ranking in the Cold Class’s practical evaluation

<1- Tudor Donquixote, Usher Bianca>

<2- Highbro Le Baskerville>

<3- Middlebro Le Baskerville>

<4- Lowbro Le Baskerville>

<5- Sancho Barataria>

<6- …>

.

.

Tudor, eldest son of Donquixote, one of the seven great houses of the empire and known for his spearmanship.

Bianca, the eldest daughter of Usher, one of the seven great houses of the empire and known for her archery skills.

And the Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro triplets from the Ironblades of Baskerville. Sancho Barataria, who was selected as a scholarship student by the Northern Mercenary Guild Alliance, and others are the super-rookies who are currently causing a stir in the Cold Class.

On the other hand, the Hot Class was also in a frenzy.

“Wow, there’s a kid who got a perfect score on the practical exam?”

“He’s second in the written exam, too, so he’s really good at studying!”

“‘Sinclaire’? A genius among geniuses has been admitted.”

“Did you hear the rumor? This is information from the admissions office…… What a beautiful girl…….”

The department was paying all the attention to Sinclaire, a genius who scored a record-breaking 1st in the practical assessment and 2nd in the written assessment.

-Practical Evaluation Ranking of the Hot Class

<1- Sinclaire>.

.

.

She didn’t reveal her family name, but it was safe to assume that she had some sort of fancy background behind her, as she was the top of the mage class, which required an enormous amount of scholarship money in the first place.

In addition, the tycoon Bourgeois, the ultra-violent Leviathan, and the religious Quovadis also admitted many talented students.

Normally, the seven great families would avoid admitting students from similar grades so that their own talents could easily take the top spot, but this time, the great talents of all seven families were admitted at the same time.

It was such a strong entry that this generation of freshmen was dubbed the “Glory Generation”.

This was because there was a massive influx of talented students who could have become class leaders and student council presidents if they had entered at different times.

….

And.

Overshadowed by a strong freshman class the likes of which we haven’t seen in recent decades, and an academic culture that values practical skills far more highly than written work, there was one person who was not being recognized.

-Comprehensive Written (Theory) Evaluation Ranking

<1- Vikir>.

.

.

Study bug.

Sandman.

A commoner without a surname.

Common names.

A hound with no name tag or leash entered the Academy.

Chapter 128

Admission to the Academy (4)

◆

A dark night.

In front of a large, shabby warehouse, several mercenaries were burning cigarettes.

As they chuckled and gossiped, they spoke with a sense of relief.

“It’s so refreshing to not have to listen to the children whine.”

“The warehouses have been full of them the last few days.”

“But where have they all gone, in one day?”

“At dawn, a wagon came and loaded everything up. I didn’t ask where you were going. Live long.”

Not long ago, the warehouse was home to a number of orphans with no connections.

But now the warehouse is empty, and in a few days, a new batch of children will be transported from somewhere.

And then they’ll disappear, no one knows when or where.

“I want to know where they’re coming from and where they’re going.”

“Arthur, wondering about useless things will lead you to your destiny.”

“I heard they go to some kind of nursery in the center of the Imperial City.”

“That’s right, a nursery run by the Religious Quovadis. Don’t worry.”

The mercenaries make small talk, stretching and yawning.

Then.

Suddenly, the mercenaries fall silent.

A hulking man who must have stood at least six feet tall stepped to their side.

Captain Ron Bartison.

A fierce mercenary from the North. ‘The Flesh Grinder’, ‘The Butcher’s Hammer’, and other gory nicknames followed.

“Stop talking and stand guard, if you want to take home a handful of coins for your wasted life.”

“….”

“Trashy stuff.”

Bartison clicked his tongue and continued on his way.

He sneered inwardly at the mercenaries who couldn’t speak a word at his size.

What kind of argument could a lowly mercenary with no mana have against a man of his stature?

…?

The standing mercenaries didn’t just talk.

Thud.

A man slumped to the ground.

He was followed by the other mercenaries, who went limp.

“What the hell?”

Bartison quickly reached to the hammer at his waist.

Now, a long shadow is cast in the glow of the roaring campfire.

“What, what?”

Bartison was startled.

A figure peered down from the roof of the warehouse.

A black cloak, a black hat, and an ominous stork’s beak mask covering its face.

“…Are you Ron Bartison?”

The spooky voice said.

Bartison swallowed dryly.

Tsutsutsuts…

Bartison’s hammer took on an aura.

A liquid aura that could only be used by those who had attained enlightenment, an aura that symbolized the Graduator, wrapped around the hammer.

“What are you doing!”

He swung the hammer with all his might.

…Tried to swing it away.

But all he could manage to swing were his two wrists, which were now missing.

Thud!

The hammer flew upward with such momentum that it landed behind him, scattering the aura it carried.

“…?”

Bartison staggered backward.

No blood gushed out. The cut where his wrist had been severed had been instantly dried by the heat.

“Uh-huh?”

Bartison opened his mouth to scream.

But he couldn’t.

The ominous shadow had crawled down from the roof of the warehouse and was now looking into his face.

“Ron Hubert Bartison. First pact with the demon four years ago, when he molested and killed the 13-year-old girl next door and sacrificed her. Since then, he’s been stealing information from the Northern Guild Union and feeding it to the demon. Finally, he betrayed his platoon, the 1st Platoon, 4th Company, 207th Regiment, 75th Division, 5th Legion of the Humanity Alliance, by handing over the location of the platoon’s sleeping quarters to the enemy while on guard duty. Led a friendly platoon to destruction. Is that right?”

The Shadow’s question was hard and chilling.

Bartison stammered a reply.

“Ughhhh…… At the very beginning, the incident from 4 years ago is correct, but what happens after that!? I didn’t do them!”

“Yeah. They’re just things you haven’t done yet.”

“What, what?”

Bartison gasped, stepping back.

But he couldn’t.

This time, his ankle was severed.

“No!”

Bartison couldn’t even scream anymore.

The Shadow stretched out his right hand, and a black sword was drawn and plunged into his throat.

Bartison struggled, and then he was dead.

“….”

Vikir. The hound of the night.

He stared down at Bartison’s body in front of him.

No, he wondered.

In time, Bartison’s corpse would quickly begin to decay and turn to mush.

Just as Seth Le Baskerville had said.

“The odor is still there.”

Vikir’s brow furrowed slightly.

Those who have made a pact with the demon emit a rotten odor from their very souls.

A stench that grew more and more foul with the degree of corruption.

Veteran swordsmen who have lived through the Age of Destruction recognize the scent like a ghost, but the people of this age will not yet be able to smell it.

So for now, only Vikir knew how to smell it.

Tsutsutsutsuts…

Bartison’s face melted like ice under the sun, and soon he was gone, his skeleton on full display.

It was unusual for the face to decay so quickly compared to other body parts.

“I wonder if this is the ability of the Ten Commandments who made a pact with him? I’ll have to investigate that as well.”

Vikir took an owl from his bosom and wrote a letter detailing the situation.

It was addressed to Cindywendy, who had a number of agents and informants at his disposal.

With the letter in hand, Vikir turned away.

Several bottles of liquor lay in front of the roaring campfire.

Vikir picked up the strongest bottle of rum and poured it over the bloodstains on his cloak.

…

The strong liquor washed away the dirty blood.

Vikir tore the page from the entry in the kill book that listed the name Ron Bartison and threw it into the bonfire.

The page turns black in an instant and curls into a ball, then turns to ash and floats away into the sky.

…Soon.

“Off.”

“It’s your back.”

“What, did I fall asleep?”

The mercenaries standing in front of the warehouse began to wake up one by one.

“Huh?”

But all they saw was a dying bonfire that had lost most of its wood, and a faceless corpse lying in a heap beside it.

◆

Ding- ding- ding- ding- ding- ding- ding- ding- ding- ding- ding- ding-

From the clock tower at the center of the academy, the majestic bell chimed twelve times.

A little after midnight. The night’s tasks were over earlier than he’d expected.

Vikir had visited mansions in upscale neighborhoods, warehouses on the outskirts of the city, gambling dens in the slums, glitzy clubs in the basement, secluded houses by the lake, brothels, and more, and that night alone he had snapped twenty-nine heads.

The only thing they all had in common was that they’d made pacts with the demon, were accused of betrayal and infidelity, and their faces melted immediately upon death.

Unfortunately, Vikir got almost no clues out of this whole process.

This meant that his assassination was going to be a long and arduous one.

‘I didn’t expect a harvest from the first step.’

Today is literally just the first day.

Vikir returned to the academy, the pages of the Killing Journal still thick in his mind.

…Jaw!

He climbed over the Academy’s outer wall, which was as high and solid as a city wall.

From this vantage point, you can see that the Academy’s buildings are indeed large and magnificent.

In the distance, the dormitories are silent in the darkness.

Vikir flies toward the lecture hall.

Bright lights and boisterous laughter emanated from the windows of the buildings in the other direction.

‘…OT, is the freshman welcome party still going on?’

Vikir thought for a moment.

Should he go back to his dorm and sleep, or should he stay up late and attend the freshman welcome dinner?

After a few moments of deliberation, the answer came quickly.

‘Just show up.’

It wasn’t about networking with seniors or classmates.

I just wanted to have an alibi, just in case.

He was also a little worried about Pigi being alone.

Vikir took off his mask, tucked it into his arms, and landed on the roof of the lecture hall.

As he was about to descend the stairs leading down.

…Ping! Boom!

A single firecracker shot high into the air, lighting up the night sky.

In the next moment, Vikir could see two men and woman standing by the railing of the rooftop stairs.

“…!”

Vikir’s eyes narrowed.

The brief glow of the firecrackers as they exploded and faded was enough to tell him who they were.

The beautiful woman, tall and sharp-featured, was unmistakably Usher Bianca, a freshman in class 20.

She was a super rookie who was making a name for herself by ranking first in the Cold Class placement test.

The boy’s face, on the other hand, was not one that Vikir remembered particularly well.

Their vibe was odd.

The boy squeezed his eyes shut and called out to Bianca.

“I… fell in love with you the moment I saw you! Won’t you go out with me! I’ll be nice to you!”

Apparently, he was a second-year student.

But Bianca was adamant.

“Hah….”

With a deep sigh, she swept her bangs and squinted one eye.

“You’re right. Did you call me up to that rooftop just to say that?”

“Uh, yeah. Uh, yeah, right?”

“Well, first of all, let me apologize, I can’t afford to go out with a guy or anything right now, and I only got in today in the first place.”

“Ha, but you have nothing to lose by going out with me! I’m in the student council and I’m also in the leading club…!”

“Yeah. I’m sorry.”

And with that, Bianca turned and kicked her confessor to the curb.

Vikir stood behind the stone pillar of the railing and thought.

‘Good times. Well, it has nothing to do with me.’

Watching the innocent lovemaking of children twenty years younger than him made the tip of his nose tickle.

Vikir soon pulled away, his back to the pillar.

At that very moment.

“…!”

Bianca’s head snapped up.

“Who’s there?”

Bianca asks in a cold voice, and then she takes a step and shoots toward the stone pillar that Vikir is hiding behind.

‘Oh no. You must have good eyesight because you’re from the Sacred Palace.’

Vikir shrugged once.

Bam!

Vikir slammed into the wall and leaped down.

No need to take the stairs.

Vikir leaped from railing to railing, pillar to pillar, and quickly disappeared in the direction of the lecture hall.

Bianca caught up with him a few minutes later, and her eyes widened.

“…What was that? I could definitely feel the presence.”

Bianca looked again at the stone pillars, railings, and stairs that had been kicked in just before.

But something that had been there was gone, like a ghost.

“Did I see it wrong?”

Bianca scratched her head.

The divine archers of Usher, the superhumans, can see and hear things miles away.

They are also masters of the art of archery, and their bodies are so strong and gaunt that it is no exaggeration to say that no one can match their speed, especially in pursuit.

Bianca, the eldest daughter of such a family, chasing someone and losing them?

That couldn’t happen, at least not within this academy.

“I must have been looking in the wrong place, I was too sensitive.”

Bianca turned to look between the stone pillars.

It was time to return to her seat at the new student reception.

…Just then.

“!”

Bianca stopped in her tracks.

A faint smell wafted past her nostrils.

It was the unmistakable scent of strong rum.

Not the kind of smell you’d expect to find on a rooftop exit staircase with nothing but the night breeze and moonlight.

What does that mean?

‘Someone was here.’

Bianca’s expression hardened.

Someone had been here just moments ago.

But that didn’t matter now.

What mattered was that someone was here, and that someone was gone.

And that someone who had been here had evaded Bianca, the prodigy of the Usher family!

‘…No way!’

That person must have been there when Bianca was feeling the hits.

But what about the fact that there’s nothing in front of her now?

It means that the person has fled at a speed that ‘barely’ exceeds her own.

‘Who could it be? A senior or a professor?’

But there’s no reason for a senior or a professor to run away from Bianca’s pursuit.

Moreover, Bianca was confident that she could outrun any senior or professor in terms of speed.

After all, she’d demonstrated that in her practical assessment.

“…But who.”

Did he mean that anyone in the academy could just walk away and leave her behind?

Bianca sniffed, confused, at the scent of rum that was slowly fading on the night breeze.

Then.

“Hey, Bianca, come on, it’s almost time for the freshman talent show!”

I hear my classmates waving and calling from the window below.

“….”

Bianca can’t help but turn on her heel with a nervous look on her face.

With only the scent of cheap rum wafting behind her.

Chapter 130

The Freshman Talent Show (2)

◆

High mountains, deep valleys, deserted mountains. Snowy fronts, we go.

The spot where a young soul died. The wounded old pine forgot his words.

Do you hear, comrade, that angry voice?

Can you see it, comrade, the tearful eyes.

-From the military song 『Going to the Front』-

◆

As the ages of the audience changed, so did the evaluations.

Older professors who had previously laughed at the newcomers’ talent show as a child’s game began to speak seriously.

“…I’ve never heard a military song that touched my heart so deeply. It’s as if you can read my soul.”

“It reminds me of the last front, fifty years ago, just before the empire was united, and so many of us died, Lieutenant Bigfresher, Sergeant Wisehawk, Corporal Upham, and Private Ryan, far from home… I miss you.”

“Old comrades, I’m sorry I’m the only one left standing, I’m sorry, I’m sorry, I hope you don’t hate me for living up to your share….”

The old professors, who were veterans who had spent half their lives on the battlefield, began to tear up.

And the young professors and teaching assistants who had been through a war, big or small, were also wetting their chests with alcohol.

The old soldier read the waves of emotion in the old soldier’s crude song and resonated with them.

It was a fine song, filled with a heavy sadness that the young pups couldn’t understand.

…Do they know?

Just before. That a far-off successor who crossed the axis of time held a ceremony for themselves who were once senior or superior.

Meanwhile.

Tudor and Sancho, who had been forced to share a room, were scratching their heads at the sight of such a Vikir.

“Why is he singing a war song like an old man? Hey, Sancho, I thought you said you were a mercenary. Have you ever heard a war song like that before?”

“It’s a war song that doesn’t exist in the north. It’s so good, I’d like to learn it.”

“Do you have a veteran in your family? He must be the same age as us. Oh, and by the way, was he the top scorer in the written exam this time?”

“Hmmm. That’s pretty ambitious for a nerdy kid. I can’t believe he’s thinking about singing a military song at the talent show.”

It seemed that the young prospective heroes were not yet able to sympathize with the sentiment of military songs.

Then. Tudor and Sancho’s conversation was interrupted.

“Hi. Excuse me, are you a Cold Class, and if so, do you recognize the man who just sang the military song?”

A pretty girl with short cropped white hair.

Sinclaire’s interest was piqued as she walked down the hallway from the Hot Class.

“Uh, no. We’re in different class. I don’t know him. Why?”

Tudor and Sancho shook their heads, and Sinclaire watched Vikir and Pigi disappear into the distance with a twinkle in her eye.

She had actually been watching them earlier.

The way Pigi had twitched nervously at the sound of his name being called, and the clumsy hand on his shoulder.

“…Just.”

At this, Sinclaire nodded with a faint smile.

“He seems like a nice guy, I just wanted to get to know him.”

◆

Vikir finished the talent show and returned to the bar.

Several of the older professors came over and spoke to him before he had even sat down at the bar.

“Is your father a soldier? I’ve never heard of a military song before. Is it from your old country?”

“…What, you wrote the song yourself, no way, such a great song!”

“Our Royal Academy often holds a competition for military songs. You must enter!”

“You. Why don’t you take my songwriting class as a liberal arts elective?”

Vikir was somewhat embarrassed, but he didn’t decline the professors’s offer.

How could he refuse a drink from a gray-haired old professor who had once been his commanding officer, a senior officer who had taken a sword to the heart so many times on his behalf as a rookie officer…, a man who had gone into enemy territory in short order to save his men and died in the line of duty, and whose face was young and vibrant.

The Academy is a gathering place for heroes past, present, and future, so it’s no surprise that he’s met quite a few people from his past life.

Vikir drank all that was offered and returned to his seat.

The moment.

“…!”

Vikir turned to go back to his seat and paused.

Bianca. The Usher family prodigy, the only child, the only daughter, was standing in Vikir’s way.

Vikir silently pushed past her to get to his seat.

The moment.

Bianca turned her head toward Vikir.

“The rooftop.”

“….”

“Smells like rum.”

“….”

Vikir considered stopping and turning around, but didn’t.

Tsk-tsk-tsk-tsk-tsk.

Vikir continued on his way, as if he didn’t realize he was being spoken to.

Bianca smelled the familiar rum on his breath.

It was the same rum she’d smelled after the rooftop chase earlier.

No matter how fast she ran, she could never close the distance between them.

Despite running as hard as she could, Bianca had failed to uncover the identity of the man.

She’d never lost a race before, but she’d never been so overwhelmingly defeated that she couldn’t keep up.

Bianca frowned and called out to Vikir.

“Hey, wait, you were definitely on the roof earlier….”

But Bianca couldn’t finish her sentence.

“Here we go, newbies! Cheers!”

“Drink! Drink! Drink! Drink!”

“The liquor’s going in, chug-chug-chug-chug!”

A few drunken seniors clinked their glasses together with a loud noise, blocking Bianca’s view.

Clink- clink- clink- clink- clink- clink- clink- clink.

Glasses clink in front of her, splashing droplets of alcohol.

Among the many glasses in Bianca’s path was a glass of rum.

“…Hold on, I’ll pass!”

Bianca pushed her way through the crowd, brushing aside the arms of her seniors and classmates.

But.

Once the toasts were over and the glasses were gone, Vikir was nowhere to be found.

“Where did he go…!?”

Bianca looked around, but couldn’t find him in the crowd.

She stopped in her tracks to follow him.

Come to think of it, there’s a lot of rum here now. It smells strong, too.

She couldn’t say for sure if this was the same smell she’d smelled on the roof.

‘Am I mistaken?’

Bianca frowned slightly.

The bitter rum scent that had seemed to emanate from Vikir was now completely gone.

Instead, her sense of smell was numbed by the other crude alcoholic odors wafting around them.

At this point, she wondered, had she really smelled rum on the rooftop earlier? She wondered.

Maybe the whole charade was a sham.

‘…Yeah. It must be the mood.’

Bianca turned her attention away from Vikir.

Where was the strength and speed to outrun him, she wondered?

There was no reason to pay any attention to him just because he sang a military song she couldn’t relate to and didn’t know where it came from.

Meanwhile.

Vikir stood in the opposite direction from where Bianca’s gaze rested.

‘You’ve got good instincts.’

The rum on his breath must have been picked up when he subdued the mercenaries outside the academy.

Luckily, there were plenty of drunken seniors and classmates around to hide the scent.

He looked up and saw Bianca in the distance, looking around, then giving up and walking away.

‘I shouldn’t dismiss them as just kids, I’ll have to be more careful in the future.’

Baskerville of the sword, Morgue of magic, Quovadis of divinity, Donquixote of the spear, Usher of the bow, Leviathan of poison, Bourgeois of money.

Even if they’re just one-day puppies, they’re descended from seven great families.

He would have to be more careful.

Vikir breathed a sigh of relief.

…Just then.

Avoiding Bianca’s gaze, Vikir found one more pair of eyes still lingering on him.

St. Dolores, the Academy’s student council president and head of the newspaper club.

She was glaring at Vikir.

‘What is it? What is it? There’s something familiar about his aura?’

Dolores was scratching her head, trying to figure out what she was thinking.

Vikir quickly pushed back his bangs and adjusted his glasses.

He locked the door to his mind firmly to prevent the saint from reading his soul, then blended into the crowd as harmlessly as possible.

Fortunately, Dolores’ gaze lingered for a few more seconds before fading away.

The old professors, including the department chair, had gotten his attention with compliments.

Vikir moved out of the saint’s line of sight, doing his best to keep the Night Hound’s identity a secret.

‘That’s enough of that. I must return to my dormitory.’

It was getting close to the end of the night.

A few drunken classmates were being carried out of the dormitory building.

Vikir thought he would take advantage of the atmosphere and go home a little early.

…However.

Just as he was about to disappear from everyone’s sight, something caught his attention.

“Hey, did you make a funny face at the talent show earlier?”

“Is it nice to bury your roommate, are you a parasite?”

“Dude, you should sing by yourself. Ah, you have to learn to do it alone!”

“Bitter- senior told you to do it, why don’t you do it sooner?”

“Guys~ Pigi is singing from now on~ Everyone listens up!”

A ragtag group of second graders surrounded Pigi.

Pigi was hiccuping with embarrassment.

“Stop, seniors. I’m not very good at anything, and I’m not very interesting, so I’m not going to… hic!”

His face was red from the alcohol, and he was sulking.

But the second graders were giggling and laughing at him.

“If you can’t do anything good, what’s the point of going to school? Why don’t you try dancing, you were so good at it earlier?”

“All you could do was pump your fists and stomp your feet as if you weren’t good enough, hahaha!”

“If you can’t do it, drink it! Here, finish this and I’ll let you off the hook! One shot if you’re a man!”

“Guys, Pigi says he’s about to show you something, pay attention!”

They giggle as if they’ve caught a toy that they can play with for years to come, a ball that they can do whatever they want with.

Cruelty, harshness, ruthlessness, malice.

There’s a lot of that kind of violence in the eyes of the sophomores as they look at Pigi.

And then.

Standing some distance away, Vikir is watching the second years with similar eyes.

The only difference is.

“….”

Vikir is not smiling.

Chapter 131

The Freshman Talent Show (3)

◆

The sophomores surround Pigi and boo him.

“This time it’s Nagari, look forward to the next one.”

“If the next one is also Nagari~ pull out all your teeth~”

“One beat off! Two beats off! Three beats off! One, two, three, four!”

“Hurry up and do something, brother, the ladies are bored!”

This group of six, three men and three women, continued to harass Pigi.

Naturally, Pigi was too timid to say anything, so he just stood there with tears streaming down his face.

Then the girls giggled.

“What is it, is he crying?”

“Oh, my God, poor thing.”

“You’re so mean! Why are you picking on him!”

The boys giggle and retort.

“When did we bully you?”

“It’s all about getting to know you, we’ll be seeing you for a long time.”

“Dude, why are you crying and XX, are you trying to make us look bad?”

Just then, a girl tapped Pigi on the shoulder.

“Dude. Stop crying. Get a drink.”

At the same time, a large glass began to fill with liquor.

Gulp gulp gulp gulp…

A vile bomb of fermented and distilled liquor.

One drink and it was clear that his head would crack the next day.

The schoolboy looked into Pigi’s face and grinned.

“One shot, and we’ll let you off the hook.”

The six of them surround Pigi and giggle.

They weren’t going to let him go until he finished his drink.

Eventually, Pigi started drinking with a sullen face.

The result came less than two sips later.

“Ew!”

Pigi gagged and spit out the contents.

Since he hadn’t eaten any appetizers, the vomit consisted mostly of alcohol and gastric juices.

Meanwhile, the rest of the team freaked out when they saw Pigi throw up.

“Yuck! That’s so gross! It’s all over your tights!”

“Wahahahaha, you’re puking, you’ve been so colorful since OT!”

“From now on, your nickname will be Puke! Puking Pigi!”

“I’ll call you Puke until I graduate!”

Gazes snapped to attention. The murmuring around them made Pigi cower even more.

Then.

A flutter.

Something covered the top of Pigi’s vomit on the floor.

It was Vikir’s cloak.

A cloak given to new students.

Embroidered with the Academy’s logo, it was so symbolic that newcomers treasured it next to their lives.

Vikir took it off and covered the vomit on the floor.

Then he walked to the front of the group of dazed second years and slapped Pigi on the back.

“Go to your dorms. I’ll clean up here.”

“….”

Pigi looked at Vikir with a shaky gaze, but Vikir merely wiped the floor with his cloak in silence.

Then.

“Hey. You.”

The sophomore grabbed Vikir by the shoulders, his face crumpled.

“Are you crazy, hanging up on a senior when they’re talking to him?”

“What are you doing with that cloak, and how dare you think you know what kind of cloak it is….”

“You bastard, are you this guy’s coworker, you’re in class B of the Cold Class, what’s your name, take off your bangs and show me your face.”

The atmosphere was becoming even more tumultuous.

Several members of the group patted Vikir’s glasses and cheeks, giggling.

“You must be pretty confident, coming out like this.”

“Dude, your friend left you some leftovers, you should finish them.”

“This is Pigi’s glass, and if you finish it, I’ll let you and Pigi go.”

“You’re his friend, you’re going to drink it for him, don’t you think he’ll just leave? Show some loyalty!”

The men dangled large glasses in front of Vikir’s eyes.

A bomb of vodka, rum, pulque, and more.

Pigi had only taken two sips, so at first glance it looked like more than a liter, and it was sloshing around the edge of the glass.

It would be impossible for a human to drink this.

But.

“….”

Vikir picked up the glass without another word.

And then.

Gulp- gulp- gulp- gulp- gulp.

Without a single change in expression, he emptied the glass.

Children in Baskerville always take a small amount of poison with their meals. To build up their tolerance.

They can’t get drunk on a mission, so a tolerance to alcohol is also essential, along with a naturally strong liver.

Vikir has seen his fair share of drinking in his previous life, even amongst the toughest of men.

“….”

Vikir downed a full liter of the bombshell too easily, then slammed the glass down on the table.

Then he walked away as if nothing had happened.

As he walks away, the crew stumbles to their feet and tries to follow.

“Hey. What’s all the fuss over there? Did someone throw up?”

Student Council President Dolores, who was walking back to the Hot Class, called out to them.

“Ah, ah, ah, one of the newcomers threw up.”

“We’ll clean it up!”

“It’s no big deal!”

Dolores can only shake her head in response to the awkward smiles of the first-year students.

“You guys, you can’t be harsh on the new students. Protect the dignity of the Academy’s upperclassmen. Do you understand?”

“Yes, of course!”

“…Good.”

The saintess glanced at the sophomores, then turned and walked back the way she came.

The sophomores looked up, but Pigi and Vikir had already disappeared.

“Man, these assholes just ran off.”

“I’ve never seen an asshole wipe someone else’s vomit with a commemorative cloak in my life.”

“Yeah. Maybe they’re commoner assholes or don’t realize the value of this logo?”

“I’ll find them later, and I’ll beat them both half to death.”

“Oh, how are you going to do that? You do realize that dueling is forbidden without an upperclassman initiate of at least two grades, right?”

“Well, we could just beat them flat at a sporting event or something.”

The sophomores walked away, each muttering a few words.

Each one of them grumbled a few words, thinking about how they would harass the two juniors who had been caught today.

◆

A few hours later.

“Man, you’re drunk. We should go out and get some ice cream.”

The sophomore class had gotten quite a bit drunk.

They left the lecture hall where the drinking was going on and strolled for a while toward the shopping district outside the Academy’s walls.

“It’s a bit far, but the ice cream is always better outside.”

The group of sophomores giggled and walked out the Academy’s back door and into the shopping district.

In the alleyways, small festivals were taking place alongside the academy’s otis.

The sophomores made their way down the street to the various food vendors.

…No. I tried to move it.

Boom!

Until one of them was grabbed by a hand that shot out of a narrow back alley in the dark night.

“Whoa! Eup!?”

The first boy to be grabbed looked up, startled.

A dark shadow loomed eerily in front of him.

A black leather glove wrapped around his face, and an unyielding grip.

Beneath a wide-brimmed black hat, a stork’s-bill mask, with a pestilential aura.

His eyes bore into those of an unseeing monster.

Puck! Woof!

The next moment, he was hit by a flying fist and slammed against the wall.

He didn’t even have time to raise his mana.

The monster’s fists were fast and strong.

One hit had already shattered his nose and teeth, sending him sprawling on the ground.

Puck-puck-puck-puck-puck-puck!

The same fate befell the other five.

Dragged into the mud of the back alley, the six sophomores looked up in disbelief.

Night Hounds.

An existence that looked like a hell beast was staring down at them, looking like it would pounce and bite them all to death at any moment.

Pfft.

The jaws of the first one to be captured snapped back.

Teeth broke through the back of his head, and then through his cheek.

His nose was broken into three pieces and twisted into a zigzag.

His cheekbones were sunken and hanging down, and blood was leaking from every hole in his face.

The bravest of them all opened his mouth.

“Uhh, do yu knw wh I m?!”

It was a classic “do you know who I am?” threat.

Vikir, in Night Hound mode, nodded once.

Then he let out a mana-modulated growl that sounded like a hoarse old dog growling.

“I know, I know.”

The second-year students were stunned twice, once by the eerie sound of the Night Hound’s voice, and again by the fact that he knew who they were and had done this to them.

The Night Hound continued.

“From right to left, Uspear, Realbelt, Yellowlove, Acme, Redmin, and Southmid. They are sophomores in Class B of the Cold Class, scions of House Pal, House Vetri, House Housings, House Seaweed, House Bison, and House Euler, respectively. Their parents are Baron Oppenheimer, Baron Munich, Viscount Osburn, Count Germa, Lord Upham, and Lord Dowsing.”

As the names, houses, locations, and even the names of their parents come out, the faces of the sophomores turn pale.

And then. The Night Hound thrusts a sharpened dagger in front of their eyes.

“Uhhhh….”

The second-year students shook their heads in horror, but they could not escape the firm grip on their jaws and the slow draw of the dagger across their foreheads.

The blade, with its ominous aura, left a festering scar on their foreheads.

X

A mark like a bull’s-eye.

It was both a symbol for a target and a stigma that would not be erased for years to come.

“Make a nuisance of yourself inside the Academy one more time.”

The Night Hound had warned them sharply as they paced, blood dripping from their foreheads.

“Then I will kill not only you, but your father and mother, and your family.”

Chapter 132

Test Your Skills (1)

◆

At six in the morning, the wake-up bell rings in every dormitory at Colosseo Academy.

All students, boys and girls alike, gather on the field in front of their dormitories and begin their morning routine with gymnastics.

After about 30 minutes of gymnastics, everyone goes their separate ways to eat breakfast, take a shower, or catch up on sleep.

At 8:00, all students head to the lecture hall, unless they have something else going on.

Depending on the day, students with no classes or classes that didn’t require attendance could use the gym, library, theater, or other cultural facilities.

Vikir and Pigi planned to finish gymnastics that morning and then go to the lecture hall after eating.

Then.

Pigi was on his way back from gymnastics when he ran into some patients coming out of the infirmary.

They were the same sophomores who had harassed her in OT yesterday.

“…What?”

Pigi froze in place, and the six sophomores froze as well.

And then?

“Hee hee!”

All six of them scurry away from Pigi.

“…?”

Pigi flinched, then turned to look at the seniors who were dodging him, and gave them a puzzled glance.

“Why are you all running away?”

“….”

Vikir looked at Pigi’s bewildered expression and the backs of the scurrying sophomores.

Suddenly, the events of last night came flooding back.

‘Try being a nuisance in the academy one more time. I will not only kill you, but also your father and mother and your family.’

‘….’

‘If one day you suddenly hear that your entire family has been wiped out…, consider it your own doing.’

‘….’

‘If you offend one of them, expect the rest of your kind to suffer.’

Last night, Vikir had nearly beaten the second years to a bloody pulp.

‘…If you’re willing to go to such lengths to bully someone, you must be a real heartthrob.’

But they don’t have the balls to do that.

Someone with that kind of ego wouldn’t take pleasure in picking on people who are weaker than them.

They disappeared, leaving everyone around to stare at them as if they’d harassed many people before.

Vikir smiled bitterly.

In his last life, Pigi had dropped out of school because he couldn’t stand the bullying, and he’d made a hard living as a low-level government employee.

His parents had gone into debt to send him to the Academy.

Then, when the Age of Destruction began and the Great War with the demons began, Pigi volunteered to go to the front lines, where he contributed greatly to the Allied Forces of Humanity by implementing numerous supply strategies and analyzing and gathering intelligence.

Then, just a few months into the war, Pigi was assassinated.

Vikir still remembers the devastated look on his parents’ faces when they saw their son’s cold, dead body.

‘He was an honorable comrade-in-arms.’

Vikir glanced at Pigi, who was yawning next to him.

He hoped that in this life, his comrade-in-arms would not have such a tragic life.

Then.

Vikir and Pigi were just about to enter their joint general education classroom in the center of the lecture hall when someone stopped them.

“Stop. Wait.”

The person who stopped them had a familiar face and voice.

St. Dolores Rune Quovadis. The third-year student council president stood with a stern look on her face.

“The center staircase here is for professors only. Students are not allowed to use it, so from now on, only use the stairs in the left or right hallways.”

“Yes. I understand.”

“And. I’m going to have to give you demerit points for walking in a restricted area, both of you, minus one demerit point. Please state your names, class, and grades.”

The saintess was stern.

Vikir and Pigi both received demerits.

This is recorded on the enchanted scoreboard, which is updated in real time.

Then.

Dolores frowned for a moment as she looked at the demerit list.

“Vikir. What did you do to earn so many demerits already?”

Dolores looked up in surprise to see that Vikir had accumulated quite a few demerits since the first day of school.

He had already gotten demerits for the same thing a few times now for wandering into the restricted areas of the dormitory and lecture halls, as well as other buildings.

‘It’s a necessity to familiarize myself with the Academy’s topography.’

In order to transform into a Night Hound and go on a night hunt, you need to find a lot of openings that lead outside.

But Dolores, unaware of this, just sees Vikir as a lazy, bad student.

“You know that accumulating too many demerits, no matter how many attitude points you have, will hurt your grades. In some cases, you may have to miss lectures and do community service outside the school. It will also affect the image of the class, so try to be more diligent and careful in the future. Do you understand?”

“Understood.”

Vikir replied in a businesslike manner.

He was trying to sound as normal as possible, but it made Dolores and Pigi jump.

“Vii, Vikir… don’t just answer like that!”

“…?”

Pigi punched Vikir in the side of the head.

When Vikir looked at him with a puzzled expression, Pigi sighed lightly and bowed ninety degrees to Dolores.

“I apologize, senior, I’ll be more careful!”

“…What. All right, we’ll see.”

Dolores nodded.

He glanced back at Vikir once more with a frown, and then disappeared down the hall.

“Uh-oh-isn’t this going to get us caught?”

Unlike Pigi, who was running his hands through his bushy hair in agony, Vikir

Then.

The window of the lecture hall opened and someone spoke in a fluent tone towards them.

Es la misión del verdadero caballero. Su deber. ?No! Su deber no. Su privilegio.

-It is the mission and duty of a true knight. No! It is not a duty, but a privilege.

So?ar lo imposible so?ar.

-To dream the impossible dream.

Vencer al invicto rival,

-To defeat the invincible enemy,

Sufrir el dolor insufrible,

-To endure the unbearable pain,

Morir por un noble ideal.

-To die for a noble ideal.

Saber enmendar el error,

-To know how to fix the wrong,

Amar con pureza y bondad.

-To love with purity and good will.

Querer, en un sue?o imposible,

-Falling in love in an impossible dream,

Con fe, una estrella alcanzar.

-To have faith, to reach for a star.

A romantic poem straight out of chivalric literature.

The speaker was a nobleman with beautiful blond hair and blue eyes.

Tudor Donquixote. A top member of the Cold Class.

Strength to strength, intelligence to intelligence, good looks to good looks, toughness to toughness.

The perfect man, with nothing missing.

He leaned against the window and winked at Vikir.

“You’ve been spotted by the student council president since the first day of school, my friends. You’d better be a little more punctual in the future, I hear this student council president is very strict about tardiness.”

Just then, a cold sneer comes from the side.

A female student with long raw hair tied back in a tight bun spoke up after Tudor.

“I don’t care if you get detention or forced community service for being late, don’t ruin the image of the entire Cold Class. Apparently, there’s such a thing as a group attitude score.”

This was Usher Bianca, a top member of the Cold Class.

As Tudor and Bianca each said something to Vikir, the front door of the classroom opened and a girl with disheveled gray hair and a short skirt stepped out.

“A~ What’s wrong with you both~ Friends shouldn’t be arguing with each other on the first day of school! Over there… are you Vikir and Pig, right? Come on in, you two, your seats are in the window row on the right!”

The girl gesturing to Vikir was Sinclaire, the overall top student in the prefect’s class and head of the joint general education class.

She had memorized the name, and she called Vikir by her first name.

Pigi was equally impressed that Sinclaire had memorized his name and called him by it.

Even if she did spell his name slightly wrong.

◆

Class began.

General Studies, a class that all Hot-Class students and all Cold-Class students were required to take.

It’s a theory class where we study the ecology and culture of monsters and barbarians.

Many students are intimidated by the difficulty of the course and either take notes frantically or give up altogether.

Some freshmen were intimidated by the notorious difficulty that their seniors had warned them about and chose to drop out.

And.

Tudor and Bianca, co-leaders of Cold Class, glared at each other.

“You know how I cut it off at the seams when I was talking to my tardy friends earlier? Don’t do that in the future.”

“It’s my business, and I need to be told off when I see something pathetic.”

“I don’t look kindly on tardiness either. But I don’t like to be interrupted. You should know that.”

“I know. Why do I need to know what you like and dislike? You’re an idiot.”

As co-leaders, the tension was already high.

Is that why? Even in theory class, Tudor and Bianca would listen to lectures with their eyes glowing, trying to outsmart each other.

Also. They had one more common enemy besides each other.

Sinclaire, the head of the Hot Class, smirked at Tudor and Bianca, who were glaring at her.

She was so well versed in theory that she was ranked second in the class, not only in practice but also in writing.

So in addition to keeping an eye on each other, Tudor and Bianca were also keeping an eye on Sinclaire.

In other words, it was a battle of the hot and cold, and a battle within the cold.

Then. The professor turned to all the students and asked a sudden, out-of-the-blue question.

“…In this way. We’ve finished our general lecture on the culture of the barbarian tribe, the Ballak. Now it’s time to test how well you’ve memorized and understood what I’ve taught you.”

The stern-looking professor adjusted his tiny glasses on his hawkish nose.

Then, in a dry, dry voice, he asked the question.

“Based on the locations of the places where the hunters of the Ballak have been said to have been found, I want you to guess the location of their home base. It is of great military importance to know where the enemy is based on the places where they have been engaged.”

This was a difficult question to answer without memorizing the culture of the Ballak, their fighting style, and the geography of the locations where they had been spotted and their immediate surroundings.

“….”

There was a moment of silence in the room.

There was no way any of the freshmen could answer this difficult question.

After all, this was a question that even third-year students would struggle to answer.

When no one answered the question, the professor took the roll call.

“Who’s number one in the Cold Class this year, Tudor. Is that you?”

“What? Yes, yes, yes!”

At first, Tudor is quick to answer.

But with the professor’s glare demanding an answer, he had none.

“Well, first of all, the clashes between the Ballak and the Empire took place at the 1st, 8th, and 75th Heights on the Western Front… to….”

“The 1st, 8th, and 75th, is that all?”

“That, that is….”

When Tudor failed to answer, the professor clicked his tongue once.

Then he turned his attention to the attendance book.

“I see you’re the one in charge of this Cold Class, Bianca. Would you like to answer the question?”

“What? It’s, uh, it’s….”

Bianca rolled her eyes.

She was about to add what she knew to be flesh to what Tudor had said earlier.

“The clashes between the Ballak and the Empire took place on the western front, at heights 1, 7, 8, 75, and 207, and um… considering that these are all low basin terrain… perhaps the Ballak’s main base is in the low plains….”

“Wait. Are you sure that there are only 1, 7, 8, 75, and 207 heights, and are you sure that all those forts you just mentioned are all in basin terrain?”

“That’s, that’s, that’s, that’s….”

Bianca stammered, as did Tudor.

The professor clicks his tongue again.

He turned to the attendance book and called out the next name.

“Sinclaire, you’re the head of the Hot Classs this term, aren’t you?”

“Yes, …. Professor.”

Sinclaire nodded, trying to sound calm.

Her expression, however, was lightly set with tension.

The professor looked at the attendance book and nodded, then raised his gaze to Sinclaire and nodded once more.

Her cue to answer.

Sinclaire took a light breath and opened his mouth.

“According to what the military has published to the academic community, the locations of the clashes between the Ballak and the Empire are the 1st, 4th, 5th, 7th, 8th, 30th, 75th, and 207th heights on the Western Front. All of these locations are basin terrain, with the exception of the 8th, which is atop a high mountain peak. Taken together, this suggests that Ballak’s home base is likely to be in a low-lying area, deep in the jungle, along the lines of the map.”

It was a neat explanation. It was also the best theory that fit the academic literature so far.

The stern professor nodded in agreement.

“This year, I’m going to add 10 points to your attitude score, Sinclaire, and 1 point to the overall attitude score of the class.”

The faces of all the hot students brightened at that.

The faces of all the cold students crumpled.

Tudor and Bianca could do nothing but grunt and groan.

Just then.

The professor’s already furrowed brow furrowed once more.

He spoke up, sounding slightly offended.

“…No, I don’t think it’s the Hot Class that’s outstanding, it’s the Cold Class that’s terrible, judging from that pathetic sight.”

The Cold Class students were stunned.

All of the students in both the hot and Cold Classes turned their heads to follow the professor’s gaze.

It was a seat by the window on the right side of the lecture hall. It was in the back, just below where the curtains fluttered in the wind.

A boy with bushy hair that covered his face and thick horn-rimmed glasses dozed with his arms crossed.

It was Vikir.

Chapter 138

Men are Power (1)

◆

“The Venompion is a dangerous B+ rank monster that can be easily caught as long as you pay attention to the first stinger on its tail and the second stinger on its stomach.”

Professor Banshee furrowed her brow at Vikir’s announcement.

“…Second Stinger’, what is that?”

Venompion are large scorpions that live in the desert and carry a single large stinger near their tail.

A sting can kill you before you can take more than a few steps, which is why desert travelers are wary of the area around its tail when they encounter one.

But even Professor Banshee had never heard of a Venompion with two stingers before. …

The Empire’s danger rating for Venompion was A, not B+.

Vikir closed his mouth in disbelief.

‘I see. It must have been at a time when research on Venompion was still in its early stages.’

What was so obvious to adventurers who lived through the Age of Destruction would be unfamiliar to those in the present day.

The same goes for the strategy around Venompion.

At this point, the Empire is still in the midst of a major demonic monster extermination campaign.

It’s no wonder so little is known about them.

It would be years before the Empire would be able to properly study the Venompion, so it was still a new monster to them.

The second stinger, originally hidden beneath the Venompion’s belly armor, was discovered by a researcher by accident.

After examining the hard exoskeleton piece by piece, down to the smallest unit that would no longer disintegrate, the researcher accidentally spilled the solution and melted a section of the Venomphion’s belly armor, thus revealing the existence of the tiny stinger.

Since then, the Venomphion’s playbook has been redefined, and the mysterious behaviors and unexplained attack patterns of the vile scorpion have been explained, leading to its downgrade in danger.

But all of this was information that no one in the modern world would know, so Vikir simply kept quiet.

“…I think I’ve been researching the wrong material by mistake.”

But Professor Banshee wouldn’t let him off the hook.

“How dare you make a mistake in my class? You don’t deserve to be in my class if you make a stupid mistake like that, and I’m deducting 10 points from your overall attitude score.”

Professor Banshee glared at Vikir, and then at the entire Cold Class.

There were sighs and groans from around the room.

Some of the students were glaring at Vikir, not at Professor Banshee.

Vikir sighed, knowing he had no choice.

If he went on like this, the student’s scores would be lowered, and he would make more enemies than he needed to.

Without further ado, Vikir recalled what he knew.

“However, before you deduct any marks, perhaps if you could examine the carapace of the scorpion carcass you have in your possession, things might become a little clearer.”

“Does that mean that your findings are correct?”

“If not, feel free to make my attitude score zero. However, I would ask that you do not deduct any points from the group score.”

Professor Banshee smirked, the corners of his mouth twitching.

“Very well. I’ll give you a chance to examine my specimen for your petty sacrificial act.”

With that, Professor Banshee turned over his prized scorpion carcass.

A hard spot can be seen in the center where the disgusting legs are curled up.

Professor Banshee picked up his scalpel, imbued it with mana, and sliced through the armor.

He cut through the armor to hard spots that normally would have been untouched.

And then. The students in the front row jumped back in surprise.

…Poof!

Suddenly, the poisonous stinger that was hidden near the stomach shot upward.

“Hmph!”

Prof. Banshee stumbled backward and landed on his ass, startled by the poisonous stinger that had just shot up past his nose.

Professor Banshee’s bangs were severed, and her hair fell in tufts.

Vikir looked at it and thought to himself.

‘The Venompion’s deathbed flip is the final act of becoming one with its opponent. The reason the world has never seen that sting is because the witnesses are nearly all dead.’

With that, Professor Banshee picked himself up off the ground, panting, and turned to Vikir.

“Now, how did you know this?”

“I just made a guess.”

“…Guessing about what?”

“Well, the reason there are so few sightings of Venompion is that the eyewitnesses are all dead, and I wondered where this scorpion hid such lethal technology. I also wondered if the sting of its obvious tail would pose that much of a threat to adventurers, so I took note of its largest and most intricately constructed belly armor.”

Hearing this, Professor Banshee looked dumbfounded.

You’re doing this research for such a random reason, and it’s turning out to be so significant?

But it’s hard not to believe it when it comes from the undergraduate student who made the big discovery.

Professor Banshee muttered under his breath.

“I see. This explains why Venompion sometimes exhibits erratic attack patterns, such as leaving their pincers behind and attacking with their middle or end legs. The stingers near the belly are disposable, and it takes a long time for them to regenerate after use, so in the meantime, their attack patterns become simplistic and ignorant.”

Professor Banshee’s mutterings were met with a collective oooh from the students.

…Except for one.

As they all looked back at Vikir in admiration, there was a white-haired girl in the front row with her head down.

“….”

It was Sinclaire, the model student of the Hot Class.

What was she thinking now, having just categorized the Venomphion’s three personalities, when Vikir’s research analyzed the phenomenon so much more accurately and informative than her own?

Regardless of her feelings, however, all the students in both the Cold and Hot Class were gossiping about Vikir’s presentation.

“Wow, this is amazing. How can someone do research like that?”

“I thought it was cool to be athletic, but… It’s cool to study that well.”

“But isn’t he athletic, too? The last time I saw him, he was fighting Tudor and Sancho.”

“Oh, that’s because those games didn’t use any mana. We’ll have to use mana for the official tournament later.”

“What’s the point of studying well? He’s a commoner and doesn’t even have the basics of mana. He’ll probably get screwed during the midterms.”

“But he has a great attitude. Did you hear him say that he’s willing to lower his score but not his team’s score? That’s loyal.”

Public opinion was generally favorable.

Vikir didn’t like the idea of having opinions formed about him, good or bad, in the first place.

Meanwhile.

A few of the freshman girls were sneaking glances at Vikir and whispering in his ear.

“I think I’ve gotten a better idea of my tastes this time around. I seem to like things that are a little nerdy. I guess I’m a nerd.”

“Nerds have to be good-looking too….”

They laugh out loud about what’s so great about Vikir, imagining the face hidden behind his bangs and glasses.

Suddenly, one of them looks up and glances at the girl behind him.

“Hey, Bianca, what about you? Isn’t he okay?”

Bianca. The eldest daughter of the Usher and co-head of the Cold Class looked up.

Bianca replied in a deep tone.

“Being handsome or smart doesn’t mean anything, unless you’re pretty.”

“Eh? Then what does it mean?”

Bianca’s answer to her friends’ questions was simple.

“A man is strength. He has to be strong.”

Bianca’s reasoning was loud and clear.

“I’m not interested in men who are weaker than me. Is it Vikir or Vakar?, What can you do with a child who isn’t even an expert?”

“Eh, but didn’t he do pretty well in the last Naphtali?”

“That was without using mana. The concentration and size of the aura are the true test of strength. He’s probably going to bleed to death during the midterms, weaklings can’t survive in the academy.”

“Aww, you’re being too hard on him. I just want him to be handsome and smart.”

The girls turn away and gossip amongst themselves again.

But Bianca is still staring at Vikir with an unimpressed gaze.

‘What’s so good about that dirty little bastard?’

She clicked her tongue when she noticed how other female students her age looked at men.

Bianca’s gaze then turned to Vikir.

The way he answered Professor Banshee’s questions, step by step, did not inspire any emotion in Bianca.

“You can’t even be an expert, can you, …?”

Bianca closed her eyes and yawned once.

Then she turned her attention away from Vikir completely.

◆

A small, run-down nursery in a fairly remote location, even in a corner of the Imperial City.

“Master! Swordmaster!”

A panicked Terminus spits out.

“Say, save me! Please save me!” “I’m not at fault!”

It’s long past midnight. When everyone else is asleep.

A fat man is crawling across the floor, wiping away tears.

Behind him stood Vikir, the Night Hound, with a long sword and a red aura.

Vikir’s brow furrowed.

‘Swordmaster.’

Strictly speaking, Vikir is still the highest level of Graduator.

It’s just that the aura he emanates from his magic sword, Beelzebub, is so thick and dense that it’s almost solid, nearly liquid.

Perhaps this villain, who is about to be beheaded, saw the aura of Vikir, the highest grade graduator, and mistook him for a master.

Vikir spoke in a dry voice.

“……Doxeller. 52 years old. The mayor of the District and the director of an orphanage. They colluded with the demon and sold children. As the Imperial Capital is overflowing with illegitimate children of nobles, only high-class orphans would have been treated. Yes?”

“High-class orphans, there’s no such thing!”

“Fair, fair-faced, literate, cultured, with blood from a noble family. All of those things are a premium for you. Isn’t that right?”

“No! There’s nothing good or bad about orphans, they’re all blood bags anyway, what… huck!?”

Without realizing it, Mr. Doxeller had unwittingly admitted his crime.

A broker in the guise of a nursery director.

It doesn’t matter if he knew or didn’t know he was dealing with a demon.

Vikir lifted Beelzebub.

Now, with a downward thrust of his arm, his head would fall off his body and roll across the floor.

Just then.

“…!”

Vikir felt a blast of cold night air behind him.

Boo-boo-boo.

It was too cold and heavy to be a natural breeze.

Boom!

Vikir jumped up and something big and heavy flew at him from behind.

It was meant to kill, instead, It smashed into the shoulder of the fat Doxeller and thudded into the stone pillar behind him.

“…?”

Vikir turned his head.

Through the glass panes of his plague mask, he saw something bizarre.

A man in a neatly styled black suit.

A black sack-like thing covered his face with stitch marks, and in his hand, he held a large hammer.

And worst of all.

‘…This smell.’

An overwhelming odor emanated from him, the kind only a demon could emit.

“Is it the Ten Commandments?”

Vikir flicked Beelzebub once.

Hudududug-

The sword’s temporary bend was restored by the force of the blow, and the auras on its tip scattered like water droplets.

Amidst the rain of bullets, the man in the black sack raised his hammer.

…Quack!

He slammed the hammer down on the ground, sending dust and stone fragments flying, and with it, he blocked Vikir’s aura shots.

[Grunt… grunt…]

He let out an unpleasant sound beneath the black sack he wore on his head.

Vikir narrowed his eyes at the black aura on his hammer.

“A graduator. Intermediate, maybe even advanced.”

A strong fellow, but not a Ten Commandments demon.

Probably one of the minions working under the Ten Commandments.

“That’s good, I’ll be able to meet Ten Commandments when I’m done with you.”

Behind the mask, Vikir’s face flushed with excitement.

This was the first clue he’d gotten since coming to the Academy.

…?

[Grunt…]

Vikir’s complexion changed as the black sack man raised the hammer.

The way the monster held the hammer was very familiar to Vikir.

“…That.”

The creature was exuding the smell of the demon.

What he was about to use was clearly the blunt technique of the Faithful Saint, the Quovadis.

Chapter 144

Volunteering for the Golden Week (2)

◆

“Uh, excuse me…”

Sinclaire appeared out of nowhere and addressed Vikir with an awkward respect.

When Vikir stared at her, wondering what was going on, Sinclaire stammered.

“Um, Mr. Vikir, did you sign up for regular volunteer work here as well?”

“No.”

“Uh-huh, then why are you here…?”

“I’m here for demerits.”

“…Ah.”

At Vikir’s short answer, Sinclaire nodded.

“Well, I’m planning to do some regular community service, and even though I have to do it to earn merit points, I feel good and accomplished after helping someone less fortunate, so I’m doing it….”

“I see.”

Vikir nodded once, not really interested in Sinclaire’s personal life, and turned to leave.

Sinclaire, however, followed Vikir closely and kept talking.

“By the way, it’s a coincidence that we’re both volunteering at the same place.”

“It is.”

“Actually, I saw you signing up to volunteer last week, but I didn’t realize we were going to the same place.”

“I see.”

“Vikir can be reached at…”

Sinclaire giggles, not sure what’s so funny, even as Vikir continues to give short answers.

Vikir interrupts Sinclaire.

“Relax, you look about my age.”

“…Ah, actually, I’m 17. I’m a year younger than Mr. Vikir.”

“It doesn’t matter.”

Vikir nodded, and Sinclaire’s expression brightened even more.

“If that… be the case, I’ll make it easy for you!”

“Okay. Let’s make it easy next time.”

Vikir thought he’d ended the conversation gently enough, and left the room.

To wash the mop.

Sinclaire, however, followed him closely this time.

While Vikir went into the men’s bathroom to wash the mop, Sinclaire stood in the doorway of the men’s bathroom and glared at him.

‘Thank goodness she didn’t follow me into the men’s bathroom.’

Sinclaire waited patiently in the doorway until Vikir was finished with the mop, then slipped in beside him.

“Look. I thought you were just trying to keep track of your service credits when you turned in that volunteer form on your day off.”

“I was forced to submit it. I’ve accumulated too many demerits.”

“Well, I see. I knew you were a good student, so I figured there was something to this.”

Sinclaire continued to stare at Vikir as he spoke.

With a light sigh, Vikir said.

“I’m in a hurry, so if you want to ask me something, do it quickly.”

“Ugh! Can I?”

Sinclaire asked excitedly, coming up beside Vikir.

She began to blurt out the questions she had been dying to ask.

“How do you study?”

“How many hours a day do you study?”

“How much time do you devote to practicing and reviewing?”

“Did you get the new Introduction to Magic genealogy that came out this time? Shall I show you?”

“What are you majoring in Cold Class?”

“Swordsmanship, ah, did the professor in charge of swordsmanship at the Cold Class teach you well?”

“You got all the questions right on the last Cold Class essay. I only got one question wrong. How did you solve it? It was beyond the level of an undergraduate student.”

“Oh, by the way, did you see the ‘Ethics in Dissection’ section on the lecture notes for Animal Biology A? What do you think of the controversy over the solution?”

“Ummm, again… ah, I had a lot of questions, but I can’t think of them when the time comes.”

“Then how do you know everything so well? Did you get an early education?”

“You didn’t? Wow- that’s amazing, so where did you go to school before you joined the academy?”

“I don’t know if I should ask you this, and you don’t have to answer if it offends you. I heard that you’re a commoner, but what region are you from?”

“Oh, but do you have bad eyes? Those glasses look really high. Oh, they’re not as high as I thought, then why are you wearing glasses?”

“Is your hairstyle intentional? Oh, you just let it grow. Are you ever going to cut your bangs or slick them back? Oh, no?”

.

.

Most of the questions were about studying.

Vikir answered in a dry tone, but continued to do his chores like sweeping the hallways, doing laundry, and taking out the trash.

Sinclaire followed closely behind him, eager to help out.

When the chores were done, Sinclaire rummaged through the squadron on his back and held out a bottle of milk to Vikir.

“Here, drink this while you work!”

“….”

Vikir took the bottle and looked down at Sinclaire for a moment.

“…?”

Sinclaire looks back up at Vikir, still with the same blank expression.

Vikir realized that if he left her alone, she would follow him around all day and bother him, so he slipped away.

“I’ll have a drink. Bye.”

“Oh, where are you going? Let me help you!”

“To the bathroom.”

Sinclaire’s face instantly turned bright red when she realized what Vikir had said.

“Uh, uh, that’s a little hard to help with, so go ahead and go~”

Sinclaire said, standing against the wall of the restroom hallway.

It looked like he was going to wait for Vikir to come out from doing his business(?).

◆

Vikir finally succeeded in sending Sinclaire elsewhere and being left alone with his barrage of questions.

“ …I see you’re a very studious student.”

Vikir emerged into a deserted hallway with a bucket and mop.

All of his fellow academy volunteers were either eating outside or having dessert with the children.

Vikir had planned to focus on the building’s internal structure during mealtime, when everyone was most distracted.

Then.

“…!”

Vikir was walking down the hallway when he bumped into a kid.

“….”

Age to be in her early teens. Beautiful blonde hair. Fair skin. Slightly sunken eyes that looked somewhat sad.

Around her neck was an old, crude, gold-colored necklace.

The word ‘Nymphet’ could be seen written on the necklace.

Vikir waved the bottle of milk Sinclaire had given to him earlier at the girl who was staring at him.

“Drink.”

“….”

The girl glares at Vikir.

She snaps.

Vikir flicks his wrist once, and the milk spins in the bottle.

The girl gives him a quick glance, then turns and runs off down the hall.

Without a second thought, Vikir put the bottle back in his pocket.

Then.

“Her name is Nymphet.”

A voice said from behind him.

Vikir turned to see Dolores standing there with a knitting basket and a bunch of dolls.

The academy’s student council president, head of the newspaper department, and a saintess of Quovadis Family, she volunteers here every weekend.

Dolores narrowed her eyes at Vikir and asked.

“Are you doing your community service? You have to work hard to make up for your demerits.”

“…I’m working hard.”

“Good.”

Dolores nodded once.

Then he looked at Vikir, his gaze still cold and stern.

“You’d better not do that kid any favors.”

“…?”

Vikir shook his head, and Dolores continued.

“She was born here, and I’ve seen countless volunteers come to the orphanage over the past 13 years.”

“….”

“At first, she was friendly with the students who volunteered, too, playing big sister and big brother.”

“….”

“But the sisters and brothers I became so close with started to visit less and less as time went by. It’s something that can’t be helped. As they go up in grade, they have to study more, graduate, and get a job. It’s the same for me right now.”

“….”

“Out of every 100 volunteers in the first grade, maybe one will continue to volunteer in the third grade, and even then, they stop coming after they graduate or get a job, so it’s hard for the kids at the orphanage to warm up to the volunteers. For the volunteers, the kids here are a part of so many lives, but for the kids here, their sisters and brothers are a big part of their lives.”

She was right, for the most part. The students at the academy come to volunteer here to fulfill their community service requirements.

Dolores turned her gaze to the back of Nymphet’s head as she walked away.

“She’s tired of short-lived relationships, long-lived misses, and eternal separations, so she’s made a promise to herself that she won’t give any to outsiders.”

“…Isn’t that right?”

“Yes. But every time I see her, she becomes more guarded, and at some point, she doesn’t talk to me at all. I feel like she’s put all her expectations on other people, and it breaks my heart. I wish she wasn’t so skeptical of the world.”

Dolores lamented that she had been volunteering here for more than three years and Nymphet still didn’t return her greetings.

Just then.

“…!”

Vikir’s expression immediately changed as he listened to Dolores’ words.

“I hope Nymphet can speak again soon. Aphasia is a disease that is caused by a broken heart, so it requires warm love and attention from people around it…… Whoop!?”

Dolores couldn’t finish her sentence.

Vikir’s hand flew out quickly and clamped over her mouth.

…Jaw!

Vikir clamped his hand over the saintess’s mouth and shoved her into the recess between the walls.

It was a small recess, carved out by an architectural mistake, with cabinets jutting out on either side, and it was shaded, making it hard to see from the hallway.

“What?”

Dolores pushed her hand away from Vikir’s breastbone and tried to remove the hand covering her mouth, but Vikir wouldn’t allow it, instead pushing her even closer to the wall.

“Shhh.”

Vikir’s husky voice echoed in Dolores’ ears.

Dolores felt her mind go blank.

‘????’

This suddenly? No, no, no, what’s going on here?

She hadn’t been this close to a man since she was born, that’s for sure.

As she braced herself for this sudden, rude, … situation(?) she’d never been in before.

“….”

Vikir squinted, scanning the hallway.

The muscles in his face stiffened.

He could feel the stench of foul mucus digging through his nose getting closer and closer.

Thud, thud, thud, thud.

Footsteps pounding on the marble floor.

There was a man walking toward them from the far end of the hallway.

A gentleman in his fifties. A devout religious man. A successful businessman. A loving father.

A man who looks perfectly normal on the outside, but exudes an overwhelming odor from within.

This monster was Vikir’s latest assassination target, Quilt.

Chapter 145

Volunteering for the Golden Week (3)

◆

Quilt was fairly middle-aged.

His appearance, which resembles a famous theater actor who retired and disappeared a few years ago, is clearly visible even from a distance.

Vikir recognized him at a glance.

‘Tenth or ninth time!’

The face is different, but the foul essence inside is the same.

The stench that assaulted his nose was unmistakably demonic, weaker than it had been before his regression, but still intimidating enough.

Moreover, there was one more factor that added to Vikir’s confidence.

It was the four shadows walking in an escorted circle around Quilt.

Shuffle, shuffle, shuffle, shuffle.

Walking directly behind Quilt was a large, burly man in a suit. He wore a black sack over his face.

He wears a golden nameplate with the word “Ephebo” engraved on his chest.

Walking on either side of Quilt are two lanky men, also dressed in suits, with black sacks over their faces.

The words “Pedo” and “Hebe” are emblazoned on their chest pads.

And finally, the shadows walking in front of Quilt.

The shadow in front of him was a woman.

She was lithe and athletic, with a black sack over her face.

The nameplate on her chest read ‘Geronto’.

Three men and a woman.

Vikir’s attention was drawn to the man walking behind Quilt.

‘…Ephebo, that must be him.’

Vikir knew him well.

I’d been with him once before, on an assassination mission.

I’d gotten so close, only to lose it when one of the structures self-destructed.

I bent a steel beam and impaled it all the way through its torso, and it ripped it off and ran away.

‘It was an undead of the Advanced Graduator class. It used the blunt techniques of the Quovadis, so it was tricky to deal with.

Vikir held his breath and waited for Quilt to pass.

Finally, Quilt, leading the four shadows, passed the wall where Vikir was hiding.

Moment.

[….]

Ephebo’s head tilted to one side for a moment.

As if sniffing something.

Vikir stiffened and stuck to the wall.

Hiding in the lonely gap between wall and wall, in the shadows cast by the cabinets.

[….]

Ephebo turned his head a little further, in the direction of Vikir’s hiding place.

Just then.

“Well, well, well.”

Quilt’s voice from the front snapped Ephebo’s head back to its original angle.

Quilt was holding the hand of the fat man who had appeared earlier with a humanized smile on his face.

The fat man smiled back at Quilt.

“You’ve been so busy with this, I can’t even see your face.”

“Oh, well, there are so many noblemen who want to meet with me these days to repent for their sins.”

“Me too, hehehehe. Speaking of which….”

The fat man turned to Quilt and said in a low voice.

“I’d like to buy some ‘indulgences’.”

“Indulgences, how much?”

“I’d like to buy about a billion gold.”

Quilt replied with a smile.

“A billion gold, that’s enough price for any crime. Have you killed anyone lately?”

“Heh, heh, heh – no, that’s not a big deal, I have a little girl I bought a while back, but she’s a barbarian, so she’s a bit rude, and after I pampered her a bit, she couldn’t stand it and ran away.”

“Oh, so the slave was spoiled.”

“That’s right. Maybe it’s because there’s been a crackdown on illegal slaves lately, or maybe it’s because the goods are being sold without warranties. Anyway, so I took my escorts and gave her a little discipline on the way to get her, but she didn’t last long on the run… and then she just snapped and died.”

“Hmm, so you’re buying yourself a billion gold worth of immunity for just killing a slave girl?”

“Alas, no. On my way back from killing the slave girl, I got so frustrated that I stopped and burned down an entire village of farmers people I met on a mountain pass. I think I burned about thirty of the bastards to death.”

“Hahaha, if that’s the case, then 500 million gold should be enough, right?”

“Hehehe, the other 500 million gold is more like a ‘tip’ to a grateful god for forgiving my sins.”

And the two men laughed coolly together.

Quilt nodded and said.

“That’s a good idea,” said Quilt, “in the Rune Religion, we’re tolerant of human error, and as long as you’re human, you’re going to make mistakes and sin and stuff, so you can pay for it with an offering.”

“That’s right, whatever sin you commit, you pay for it in the offering.”

“That’s right, even if you’re forcibly insulting a saint, you can still repent by paying an offering. Your soul goes from hell to heaven the moment your earthly coin clinks into the offering plate, which is also recognized by the former Cardinal of the Old Order of the Runes, His Holiness Humbert L. Quovadis.”

Quilt and the fat nobleman walk to the end of the corridor, giving and taking.

Ephebo, Pedo, Hebe, and Geronto followed Quilt out of sight.

…Meanwhile, Vikir listened to the entire conversation.

His sense of smell was paralyzed by the disgusting smell of the corpse that Quilt had left in the hallway just moments before.

“It’s suffocating.”

Then.

A cold voice came from under Vikir’s chin.

“ …Who doesn’t want to be suffocated?”

Only then did Vikir retreat, thinking it was a mistake.

Dolores stared back at him, her face hard and icy.

Dolores, who had just stepped out of the gap in the wall, looked very displeased and accused Vikir.

“What did you just do?”

Vikir was at a loss for words.

He couldn’t tell the truth about the existence of demons.

…?

Seeing that Vikir remained silent, Dolores seemed to misunderstand.

“Do you think I’m going to thank you for this futile consideration?”

“…?”

What was this again? Vikir looked up, puzzled.

Then Dolores snapped.

“You think I’m going to be uncomfortable with the author, Quilt! But no! I am not afraid to face him! How dare you treat me like a coward!?”

Vikir suddenly realized what Dolores had misunderstood.

She was misinterpreting Vikir’s reason for hugging her and hiding between the walls.

She thought Vikir was trying to keep Dolores away from Quilt, or something like that.

So why was Dolores so uncomfortable about running into Quilt?

The answer can be found in a newspaper article I read not long ago.

[The Night Hound, the villain who terrorized the Imperial City, who is he?]

-March 0, last night at dawn. A mysterious creature appeared and ravaged the 00 nursery school…

[The Faithful House in Danger, is it okay as it is!?]

-Meanwhile, within the Quovadis family, the Old and New Order factions are currently at odds…

Some have criticized the family for being slow to respond to the terrorist crisis due to internal strife…

[Old Order vs New Order, Quovadis squabbling over terrorists!?]

-The battle between the Old Order and the New Order is as old as time, and the two factions have been at odds over whether or not the sale of “immunity charms” and “indulgence charms” by the denomination is justified…

[Is the “Night Hound” a real villain?]

-Whether this is a travesty created by the Old and New Orders, or the manifestation of a truly rare evil, remains to be seen…

There are two factions within the Quovadis of the Faithful.

The Old Order faction, led by Cardinal Humbert, and the New Order faction, led by Cardinal Martin Luther.

The Old Order and New Order factions differed in many ways, but one of the biggest differences was the acceptance or rejection of indulgences.

An indulgence was a certificate that excused a person from a sin, a sort of talisman.

The idea was that you had to pay a ransom equal to the weight of your sin to offset it.

The Old Order Rune Religion sold indulgences and collected vast sums of money to build a powerful organization.

They were mostly older, high-ranking priests.

The New Order, on the other hand, criticized the Old Order system and sought to reform it.

The younger, lower-ranking clerics were the members of the New Order faction.

St. Dolores was a prominent figure of the New Order, known as the ‘awakened young blood.’

She was on a very different path from her father, Cardinal Humbert, the godfather of the Old Order, and the father-daughter relationship was known to be somewhat rocky.

Meanwhile, Quilt, who had just passed through the hallway, was a typical Old Order figure.

His family, the Indulgentia, was also one of the strongest pillars of the Old Order.

It’s easy to imagine, then, that St. Dolores and Quilt, the orphanage’s director, don’t get along very well.

In fact, just a few moments ago, Quilt had said some very ugly things to Dolores.

‘You know, even if you’re forced to insult a saint, you can still repent by paying an offering.’

In hindsight, Quilt might have thought Dolores was hiding between the walls.

No, he must have known.

Is that why?

Dolores is so angry that tears are forming in her eyes.

Her normally gentle and calm voice shook precariously with emotion.

“This kindness is only an inconvenience, and my family’s affairs are my own! How dare you say you know what…!”

What’s more, Dolores didn’t like Vikir in the first place because of all the trouble at school.

To her, Vikir was a lazy, negligent tardy student with a lazy attitude towards life, and a rude brat who didn’t know much about the Night Hounds.

Dolores exploded with all of her stress and frustration at once: the shame of having her family’s inner affairs exposed to an outsider, the self-loathing for wanting to hide in fear at the sight of Quilt, even if only for a moment, the subtle feelings she harbored for the Night Hounds who antagonized her family, and everything else.

“You’re the worst!”

She was holding it together, but she was still young and immature.

With that, Dolores turned her back on Vikir and disappeared down the hall.

“….”

With her gone, Vikir was left alone.

‘What the hell.’

It didn’t matter that the saintess was angry right now.

In fact, thanks to Dolores’ distraction, Quilt and Ephebo walked past Vikir without a second glance.

In many ways, this is lucky.

Vikir immediately began to follow Quilt.

It was daylight, so he was unmasked, but his eyes were already glowing an eerie blood red.

The Night Hound bared his teeth.

Chapter 147

Volunteering for the Golden Week (5)

◆

The days are bright and sunny.

Vikir is pulling weeds that have sprouted in the yard.

But even while doing the dirty work, Vikir’s eyes and ears are always open.

He wants to make sure he doesn’t miss a single detail about Quilt, so he does his best to gather information.

It’s almost impossible for a volunteer to meet Quilt in person, instead relying on information about his work and daily routine from a distance or from those around him.

This was made all the more annoying by the fact that he was often interrupted by Geronto, Pedo, Hebe, and Ephebo, who were always at his side.

“They’re strong guys. Especially that Geronto girl….”

Vikir turned his attention to the smallest of Quilt’s four shadows, a mage woman.

She exuded strong magic, probably at least fifth class.

Her body clearly belonged to a girl who appeared to be about Vikir’s age, but the power she possessed was definitely unnatural.

The black sack she was wearing was also quite ominous, emitting an unpleasant odor.

It seemed to be a relic from a distant and ancient time.

In any case, unless we can somehow deal with those four sack people who are escorting Quilt, the purpose of the mission will not be fulfilled.

‘Alright, let’s just focus on what I can see for now.’

Vikir began to think with only the information he had at hand.

After analyzing the circumstances, Quilt’s job was nothing special.

His primary job was to sell indulgences and plenaries to nobles and merchants visiting the church, and he occasionally mailed investment reports and indulgence sales ledgers to the Quovadis family.

The recipients of the mail were almost always Cardinal Humbert L Quovadis of the Old Order.

Vikir would sneak over the barrier at night and intercept the mail by shooting pigeons and owls flying away from Quilt’s office with arrows.

The letters usually contained the following.

Viscount Beckin: Murdered parents who wanted to donate their inheritance instead of passing it on to their children, faked an accidental death, and stole the inheritance = all sins are forgiven by paying 1.5 billion gold in tribute.

Baron Lageso: Terrified and murdered his twin sisters, who were working as maids, and buried them in the sewers = All sins are forgiven with a 200 million gold tribute.

Lord Finnegieg: Murdered a business partner and stole his investments, while his family suffered and committed mass suicide = 800 million gold.

Count Eisel: Charged with massive tax evasion, nearly 100 billion gold in tax evasion alone = Pardoned by paying 300 million gold in tribute.

CEO Quarkar: Accused of stock price manipulation, driving over 10,000 ant investors to suicide = Pardoned by paying 5 billion gold.

.

.

For example, a rich man evaded taxes, a high-ranking noble intimidated a servant, a merchant murdered a business associate, or a trader bought and sold indulgences for… whatever.

Vikir read each and every one of these letters while pulling weeds in the yard.

He concluded.

“…I don’t need to know about this.”

These were bad guys, sure, but at least they weren’t in league with the demons and betraying humanity.

At least they weren’t being hunted by the Night Hounds.

Vikir was about to throw the letters away when he paused.

Confessions of the criminals the Old Order priests were dealing with, and their secret crimes against humanity.

“Maybe it would be a good gift for someone.”

This “blacklist” would be a politically potent weapon.

Vikir set the letters aside for a moment. He’d tuck them away somewhere.

Then.

…Wiggle!

Something moved in the pocket of Vikir’s arm.

“…?”

Vikir felt a rare moment of panic.

What had just wriggled out of his pocket was enough to make even the usually expressionless Vikir’s eyes widen.

An egg. It was a rather large black egg.

The egg of Madam Eight-Legs, the one he had saved when he was adrift for two years in the depth of the Black Mountain with his former enemy.

I’ve always carried it in my pocket, just in case, but why is it wriggling now?

“…?”

Vikir looked up.

In the direction of the egg’s wiggling, a group of children were running a lead race.

“What?”

For a moment, Vikir’s mind wandered.

Madam Eight-Legs Egg had once grown up in the same nest as the wolf pups in Ballak’s village.

The pups had cuddled, rolled over, licked, and played together.

Is it possible that this egg misses that simple life, and that’s why it wants to join the children at the orphanage when it sees them playing? Is it a coincidence that neither Madam Eight-Legs Egg nor the children at the orphanage have parents?

“No, it can’t be. There’s no spirituality in a mere spider’s egg….”

But if it’s an egg of a high-ranking creature with a danger rating of S, Madam Eight-Legs, it might be something else.

Then.

Bam!

A ball kicked by one of the children made a loud noise.

At the same time, the expressions of all the children turned to horror.

“Ouch!?”

Had the ball gone too far?

No, it wasn’t.

There was a loud pop, but the ball didn’t move an inch from its spot.

The leather had torn and the air inside had burst.

“Alas, this was the last ball….”

The children gathered around the worn-out ball and cried.

The orphanage made a lot of money selling indulgences, but the toys the children played with were always old, shabby ones that had been donated long ago.

The balls the children used to play football with were worn out and had holes in them that had been stitched together several times to form a ball.

Eventually, it burst, and the children could no longer play ball.

“….”

The last child to kick the ball panics, not knowing what to do.

Vikir thought the face of the flustered child was quite familiar.

Nymphet. A girl who doesn’t often open up to volunteers.

Her usual expressionless face was gone, and she was looking at her classmates with a tearful expression.

A look that said she was sorry and didn’t know what to do.

And then. Something amazing happened.

…Pot!

Madam Eight-Legs’s egg pierced Vikir’s chest and shot forward.

Pow! Pow! Pow!

Madame’s egg bounced and rolled lightly across the floor, as if urging a child to play with it.

“Huh? A ball!”

The children are delighted to see Madame’s egg bouncing this way.

The ball deflected and bounced in a few odd directions, but the kids generally didn’t seem to mind, and used Madame’s egg as their lead ball.

“…That’s crazy.”

Vikir’s mouth was half open as he watched Madame’s egg bounce around the playground, chasing the children.

The egg seemed somehow amused as it bounced off the children’s hands and feet or soared into the air.

It didn’t crack on impact, but rather bounced around like a rubber ball.

The perfect material, as if the heavens had sent it down to be used as a ball when playing ball.

…But even so, it was definitely a demonic creature’s egg, and certainly not something for children to play with.

Vikir took a step forward to snatch it away from the children.

At that very moment.

“Hmph!”

A raspy cough came from behind him.

Vikir ignored it and took another step forward.

“Cough! Cough!”

The coughing continued, as if trying to force Vikir’s attention.

“…?”

Vikir’s eyes spun around to see a familiar face.

St. Dolores stood before him, her face slightly flushed.

Vikir quickly snatched up Quilt’s ledgers from his side and tucked them into his arms.

Dolores narrowed her eyes at the sight.

“Studying for a writing exam? Are you studying while doing volunteer work? … Hmm, you’re surprisingly diligent.”

“What is it?”

Vikir asks in a stern tone, and Dolores coughs once more, averting her gaze.

“Uhm, uhm, just, uhm. I was wondering what your volunteer work is like, and from what I’ve heard from some of my friends, you seem pretty dedicated to it. Is it worth it?”

“Yeah.”

“….”

“….”

“…Ah, is that it, answer?”

“Yeah.”

“…I see.”

Dolores couldn’t help but notice that Vikir’s short answers didn’t sit well with her.

She was used to asking one word questions and getting ten or a hundred answers.

Dolores twisted the ends of her hair around her fingers a few times before she forced herself to speak.

“…, Actually. I came to talk to you about what happened yesterday.”

“…?”

Vikir’s brow furrowed slightly.

“Yesterday?”

It was unimportant, so he must have forgotten about it right away.

As Vikir was trying to recall what had happened with Dolores yesterday, Dolores hesitantly continued.

“Well, I guess it’s because we have a bit of a family situation… and I think I overreacted to you yesterday, but I’m sure you were just trying to help me, and I’m really sorry for the way I yelled at you yesterday…..”

Dolores was apparently referring to yesterday when she was pushed down the hallway by Vikir with her mouth covered.

But.

“…!”

Vikir wasn’t paying attention to Dolores at all right now.

Because something much bigger than that was happening right now.

Bam!

Madame’s egg, kicked by the Nymphet, flew high into the air this time.

But he had chosen the wrong trajectory.

…Pow!

He fell into the deep sewers at the edge of the playground.

The kids all screamed.

“Ouch! No! That’s the last ball!”

“We’re not going to make it without it!”

“Pick it up! We have to pick it up or…!”

The problem is that the filth and wastewater flowing in that sewer is being sucked straight into an underground sewage treatment plant, and the ball that fell into it isn’t just any ball.

Purrrrrr…

Even as the kids are panicking, Madame’s egg is making its way to the sewage treatment plant.

The sewer is too deep for them to get into and the flow is too fast.

A dire situation in more ways than one.

So Dolores couldn’t finish her sentence.

“I’m sorry… okay?”

Vikir, the object of her apology, scurried out onto the playground as she spoke.

“It’s deep. Move.”

Vikir gave a quick warning to the kids who had gathered in front of the sewer and were scrambling to get out of the way.

And then.

…A puff of air!

Without a moment’s hesitation, Vikir dove into the filthy, floating sewer.

Chapter 148

Volunteering on the Golden Week (6)

◆

Dolores Rune Quovadis, Saint of the Faithful Quovadis.

She hadn’t always liked Vikir.

Or rather, she was more of a hater.

Ever since she’d first met him at the Academy, she’d had an unflattering image of him.

-‘Vikir. Class B. What did you do to earn so many demerits already?’

-‘….’

-‘You know that accumulating too many demerits, even if they’re attitude points, will hurt your grades. Sometimes you’ll have to miss lectures and do community service. Do you understand?’

-‘I understand.’

-‘… Let’s see.’

A lazy junior with a pile of demerits for being a freshman.

He didn’t even show any embarrassment or guilt when he was called out for his bad behavior, such as being late or entering restricted areas.

Not only was he lazy and shameless, but he was also arrogant.

Even Vikir, as soon as he entered the newsroom, didn’t hesitate to say something sour about the Night Hound.

‘He’s a villain, that’s for sure.’

When Dolores heard Vikir speak ill of the Night Hound, she felt something stir inside her.

Who was he to judge him so presumptuously?

How dare he judge him, a freshman college student with a full stomach and a roof over his head, a lazy, delinquent life in a cradle like this?

Dolores thought of the Night Hound.

Sure, he was now a suspect in the terrorist attack on Quovadis’s branch, but Dolores firmly believed in her heart that he was not a bad person.

The memories of treating the poor with him when the plague known as the Red Death ravaged the slums of St. Mecca were still fresh in her mind.

‘How could I call him a wicked man when I saw the way he never stopped treating his patients, even when he was covered in their own feces?’

The holy spirit of sacrifice that the Night Hound displayed then was certainly not something that could be mimicked by acting.

For indeed, his soul was rough and scarred, but it nevertheless radiated an aura of purity beyond that of any of the priests.

Who the Night Hound was, and where he came from, Dolores did not know.

But she could guess that he had walked through countless thorny paths in his life, and the good that had blossomed out of those wounds was holy and noble, she thought.

To be vilified, oppressed, persecuted, and yet persist in doing good and making sacrifices. A martyr.

That’s how Dolores characterized the Night Hound.

That’s why she didn’t like people who criticized martyrs.

She didn’t like people who spoke ill of martyrs, because she knew how much of a burden they put on the shoulders of those who walked the thorny path, hiding in their safe and comfortable places, with words spoken without thought.

…Is that why?

Dolores could never harbor good feelings for Vikir.

The first time Vikir covered her mouth and pushed her up against the wall, she was dumbfounded.

But later, when she saw Quilt pass by in the hallway, she was furious.

She was a saint of the Quovadis, and Quilt was a lowly cleric, a mere member of her family.

There was no reason for Dolores to be intimidated by status.

‘I mean, even if you’re forced to insult a saint, you can still repent by paying an offering.’

Quilt had even said some insulting things about Dolores.

This made Dolores even more angry at Vikir.

If it weren’t for Vikir, he would have stormed out of the room and punished Quilt.

Dolores then walked away, angry at Vikir.

And exactly a few seconds later.

She regretted her anger.

As with any good person, time passes and the anger subsides and you see your mistakes.

Dolores thought back to the situation earlier.

Vikir had obviously been acting in good faith, covering up for him to avoid an uncomfortable situation.

And to be honest, Dolores felt uncomfortable, even a little scared, to see Quilt.

You might be thinking, why be afraid of an inferior, but Quilt wasn’t just an inferior.

Sometimes in life, there are people who are clearly beneath you, but they don’t feel like beneath you.

For Dolores, that was Quilt.

His smirking, brash, and laid-back demeanor at any given moment made Dolores feel uncomfortable.

She was also well aware that Quilt’s absolute confidence came from money, especially the enormous offerings he made to the higher-ups.

As the patriarch of House Indulgentia, Quilt used the money she earned from selling indulgences to pay bribes in the guise of offerings, and she had built up an impressive network of connections and power.

With his wealth and connections, it’s clear that Quilt is a man not to be trifled with, not even by the saintly Dolores of Quovadis Family.

So when he openly insulted her sexually, she had no recourse other than to get angry.

And this conflict within the Quovadis was already known to the world through newspaper reports.

Under these circumstances, it’s hard to blame Vikir for trying to be considerate.

‘…No, you should be grateful.’

Dolores had to admit to herself.

If she had run into Quilt in the hallway earlier, she might have lost control of her expression and made a mistake.

And he had Vikir to thank for preventing that from happening.

…What’s more.

‘It’s suffocating.’

Vikir frowned, obviously looking at Quilt.

It’s clear from this that Vikir doesn’t like the idea of Quilt selling indulgences either.

Dolores agreed with Vikir on that point, which made her feel slightly better about his image.

‘Still, it’s not like he’s going to shove a girl he doesn’t know up against a wall, and it’s not like we’re having some kind of… thing going on.’

For someone who had never been with a man before, being pushed up against a wall in his arms was definitely a powerful memory.

Honestly, it still makes her heart skip a beat when she thinks about it,

‘You really freaked me out.’

Dolores rubbed her hands together, feeling her face grow slightly hot.

“Maybe… is actually a good guy, except for being lazy.”

In Dolores’ mind, Vikir’s rating rose ever so slightly.

It was quite an unusual and generous assessment for a woman who usually held to a puritanical ethic, a belief that sincerity was good.

A little more time passed.

Dolores sought out Vikir to apologize for what had happened in the hallway.

…?

Even after half a day of walking around the entire building, it wasn’t easy to find Vikir.

When it was time for recess, I asked some first year students who were taking a break.

“Eh? Vikir? He was cleaning the toilets with us a while ago. He went to the cafeteria to help out because they were short-staffed, and he volunteered to go first when the person who lost the game of rock-paper-scissors asked him to go.”

Tudor, who was standing in the restroom, replied cheerfully.

From the restroom, Dolores headed to the dining room.

There, Sancho, who was eating with the kids in the dining room, testified.

“Aah, Vikir? He was just handing out meals to me and the kids a few minutes ago, and then he heard that there was no hot water in the dining room, so he went to check the plumbing. Dude, you can’t even eat your meal because you were handing out meals….”

Dolores went from the restroom to the plumbing room in the dining room.

There, a water-soaked Pigi pointed his finger at the building in front of him.

“Oops, boss, good lunch, you’re looking for Vikir, he must have gone to the laundry room by now, because he just fixed the plumbing so I can wash my clothes!”

Dolores went from the restroom to the dining room to the plumbing room to the laundry room.

There, Sinclaire, who was washing clothes, saluted him cheerfully.

“Senior Dolores, hi! What’s up, Vikir? He was doing laundry with me earlier, but the kids wanted to play, so I dragged him to the playroom! They’re so energetic! What? I’m a girl, so why do I call Vikir hyung? Isn’t that right? He told me not to call him oppa, so I called him hyung and he didn’t mind, ahaha!”

Dolores went from the bathroom to the dining room to the plumbing room to the laundry room to the playroom.

There he found Bianca, who was giving the children rides with a troubled look on her face.

“Who’s that, Vikir, haha… He was just giving me and the kids a horseback ride a few minutes ago and then the kids said they wanted to go out to the playground, so he went to do some maintenance on the playground, but I guess I’ll live with him taking the kids, they’re so fit… They never get tired….”

Dolores had to run from the bathroom to the dining room to the plumbing room to the laundry room to the playroom to the playground.

On the way out to the playground, Dolores thought to herself

‘I mean, how much work does he do in a day?’

From what he had seen so far, Vikir was doing the work of a dozen people.

Cleaning toilets, ministering in the dining hall, fixing plumbing, doing laundry, playing with the kids, and maintaining the playground.

Each one was incredibly demanding and arduous, and how many had he already accomplished in the morning?

The average academy student is barely able to help because they don’t have the hair to do the dirty work.

I mean, when do fine people ever get to do this kind of grunt work?

But Vikir was doing it all on his own, in the shadows, where no one would recognize him, without even a hint of a sulk.

(Of course, Vikir had done all of these odd jobs in the army before he regressed, so he’s pretty good at them, and now he’s on an intelligence hunt, so there’s no way Dolores can tell that he’s deliberately shooting around and gathering information under the guise of work.)

But she thought to herself.

‘I was wrong all along, and I was wrong for a long time. She’s an incredibly sincere person….’

To think that she’d thought of him as lazy and neglectful all this time.

Dolores felt ashamed of her prejudices and wanted to crawl into a rat hole.

She thought she had treated everyone without discrimination and without prejudice, but here she was, looking at her junior, a newcomer to the club, with such prejudice.

Dolores completely reevaluated Vikir and decided that she owed him an apology for all of this.

And then.

Dolores went out to the playground where Vikir was.

Across the field, he could see kids kicking balls and running laps.

And there was Vikir, sitting a few feet away.

Vikir was digging up weeds and boulders and flattening the area so that the children could use the playground.

Mumbling…

All the while, he’s pulling papers out of his pocket and reading them.

‘He seems to be studying.’

Dolores was genuinely impressed.

He works so hard for the children, and yet he doesn’t neglect his studies.

This is the epitome of a true student.

‘…Did he study well?’

Dolores didn’t know Vikir’s grades.

She’d see how Vikir did on his written exams when she went back to school later.

‘Maybe I can tutor him if I have time.’

Dolores was confident that she would be able to help Vikir, as she had never been outside the top three in her class in third-grade writing.

As he thought this over, Dolores walked up behind Vikir and coughed.

“Hmph!”

Dolores tries to apologize, but the words don’t come out right.

Dolores was usually quick to apologize for her mistakes, but for some reason, it was difficult for Vikir.

Perhaps it was the memory of Vikir cursing about the Night Hounds.

‘That’s just an excuse, I was wrong, and I should apologize straight away.’

Dolores coughed in vain once more.

“Hmph! Hmph!”

He coughed in vain, as if trying to get attention.

Only then did Vikir turn his head.

“…?”

As soon as Vikir saw Dolores, he shoved the papers he’d been reading into his arms.

Dolores opened her mouth in an awkward tone.

“Studying for a writing test? You’re studying all the way through a volunteer job? … Hmm, you’re surprisingly diligent.”

“What is it?”

Vikir’s tone was hard. He was obviously upset about yesterday’s incident.

Dolores stuttered slightly.

“Uhhhh, um, I was just, uh, wondering. I was wondering how your volunteer work is going. I asked some of your friends, and it seems like you’re working pretty hard. Is it worth it?”

“Yeah.”

“….”

“….”

“…Ah, is that it, answer?”

“Yeah.”

“…Okay.”

Dolores panicked, not knowing how to continue the conversation.

‘Was conversation supposed to be this hard?’

All of the people she’d met so far had always spoken to her without her having to initiate the conversation, and the answers had always come naturally.

Before she could even ask a question, she’d have a long list of things she wanted to know, and things she didn’t want to know.

But Vikir was different.

He doesn’t say anything unless it’s necessary.

Even if the other person is the third-year student council president and a saint of one of the seven great houses of the Empire.

Eventually, Dolores decided to come clean.

“…, Actually. I’m here to talk to you about what happened yesterday.”

“…?”

Vikir’s brow furrowed slightly.

Apparently, the memory of yesterday was very uncomfortable.

Dolores closed her eyes tightly and decided to be honest.

“Well, it’s just that we have a bit of a family history… and I think I overreacted to you yesterday, but I’m sure you were just trying to help me, and what I did yesterday when I yelled at you was really….”

But.

She couldn’t finish her apology.

…Pot!

Vikir jumped out of her seat and ran off somewhere.

“I’m sorry… huh?”

Dolores looked up.

No, forgiveness can’t be forced, but still, it’s a bit much for someone to apologize so sincerely and then just walk away….

Dolores looked up, embarrassed, ashamed, and disappointed.

What?

“What!”

Dolores’s eyes widened.

The direction Vikir was running was toward the sewers where the children were clustered.

It was too deep and dirty for them to go near.

Some of the children were already peering dangerously into the sewers.

Dolores quickly ran towards the sewer.

As she approached, she saw that Nymphet was crying.

‘Oh, the ball….’

The ball they were playing with had fallen into the sewer.

She knew that because of the lack of supplies, the children were using the same old ball over and over again.

She would often buy a new ball for them every time she visited, but with so many children playing with it, it would quickly become worn out and burst.

How heartbroken would the children be to have their new balls go down the sewer?

…When Dolores is thinking.

“It’s deep. Get out of the way.”

Vikir’s short warning followed.

“?”

Dolores turned her head with a puzzled expression.

…Blast!

Vikir leaped into the sewers. Without a moment’s hesitation.

…Puff, puff, puff, puff!

In the disgusting wastewater, Vikir moved like a swimmer, eventually retrieving the ball that the children had dropped.

Yuck!

As Vikir climbs out of the sewer, he is approached by a group of frightened children.

“Don’t play near the sewer, it’s dangerous. I’ve smoothed out the playground over there, so you can play there and… the ball is dirty, so I’ll wash it and give it back to you.”

Vikir said nonchalantly, dripping with filth.

And.

“….”

Dolores looked at Vikir’s broad back, covered in dirt, and suddenly felt her whole body heat up.

‘What, what, why?’

His cheeks grew so hot that he had to bring a cold palm to them.

It was a truly strange and strange feeling that even I could not guess its identity.

Chapter 151

The Drinking Game (1)

◆

“He, help me. Vikir. Please, just once!”

The budding Tudor, the wannabe superhero, always so proud and confident, is now pleading in a miserable position.

“Ugh. I’m going to die like this. …Yes, kill me. It’ll be impossible to beg for mercy from you, Vikir, anyway.”

Sancho, the next mercenary king aiming for the supremacy of the North, has an indomitable fighting spirit and also accepts death without losing his will to fight.

“Vikir, you betrayed me! How could you do this to me!”

Pigi is just Pigi. But he trusts Vikir more than anyone else, so his frustration is deepest when a knife is plunged into his back at the last moment.

…But. Vikir killed his friends without mercy.

“If you can’t do it, die.”

Vikir’s voice rang out dryly.

Charak-.

The cards moved.

Colorful horses moved across the wide cardboard board.

Vikir’s black pieces devoured Tudor’s blue pieces, Sancho’s red pieces, and Pigi’s yellow pieces.

At the same time, Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi were sent back to the starting line.

…Along with three glasses of punishment.

“Alas, I lost again! Why is this bastard so good at board games?”

“I think I’ve already drank a liter of punishment drink.”

“…I feel like I’m going to puke.”

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi sulked as they watched the distance they’d worked so hard to travel on the board get reset in an instant, and as they watched their drinks pile up in front of them.

Meanwhile, the girls were in a frenzy of laughter and chatter.

“Hey Vikir, you’re really good at board games.”

“Do you have a trick for throwing the cards?”

“You look like you’ve been playing games all day! Ho ho ho~”

Churlish, light makeup, and a faint smell of soap instead of perfume.

These are the usual attire of the normally modest academy girls.

The male students who came to the girls’ room late at night were enjoying the atmosphere of the drinking party with their hearts pounding.

Late at night. The lovers(?) led by Tudor secretly escaped from the men’s dormitory and sneaked into the women’s dormitory.

The girls had broken the latch on one corner of the window in the first-floor restroom, as arranged with the boys, and after sneaking in through the first floor, the boys managed to climb up the drainpipe to the second floor, then up the fire escape to the third floor, and finally to the girls’ floor on the fourth floor, which was forbidden territory.

Of course, they were stopped a few times along the way by the on-duty officer, but the supervision of the wardens was unusually lax today.

Probably because they didn’t want to crack down too hard on young men and women’s secret meetings.

…Well, whatever.

So here we are, boys and girls in a room playing a board game.

The game is called Yut, and the penalties are mostly drinking punishment liquor, but there are also individual penalties written on the board for moving and settling the pieces.

For example, “Hold the hand of your crush for 5 seconds,” “Kiss the forehead of anyone wearing red for 10 seconds,” “Hug the person in front of you for 30 seconds,” etc.

Almost every space had a non-punishable penalty, with the level increasing as you got closer to the goal.

“…Is a thumb game, not a drinking game.”

Someone looking at the board grumbled.

It was Bianca, sitting on the bed in her sweatpants.

Tudor frowned.

“Don’t you think you’re being a little too whiny about no one wanting to fuck you?”

“I think you misspoke when you said no one wants to go out with you, asshole.”

Another war of words between Tudor and Bianca.

Sinclaire, who was standing next to them, interrupted them.

“Aww, come on, guys – it’s fun drinking.”

Sinclaire smiles like a sweet puppy.

As a model student, she always wore an elegant school uniform and had a flawless image, but now that she is wearing a loose tank top and dolphin pants, she looks quite familiar.

The boys began to murmur amongst themselves.

‘…Hmm. Maybe we should have paid less attention to our clothes?’

‘Are you stupid? You think they don’t care about their clothes? Those are their combat uniforms, man.’

Sancho and Tudor exchanged a look.

“Yut.”

Vikir moved his horse again.

Tudor and Sancho’s horses were eaten again.

And then.

“Yut.”

“Mo.”

“Yut.”

“Mo.”

“Yut.”

“Mo.”

“Do.”

Vikir’s black horses serially slaughtered, advancing and retreating strategically.

“Aaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh! Hey, let’s get some other penalties!”

“You’re just drinking yourself to death ….”

Tudor and Sancho regretted bringing Vikir with them and picked up their glasses of punishment liquor.

Then.

“Hey, hey, hey, hey… kids, even the students drink a little.”

It was St. Dolores.

She, too, was sitting on the bed, dressed comfortably in a stretched T-shirt and pajama pants.

In fact, she was deep in thought.

‘They’re volunteering during the Golden Week, so it’s okay for them to deviate once in a while. I’m not a jerk at this point, am I? Well, I should probably have a few drinks, just in case there’s an accident. Hmmm… look a little old-fashioned, too? Do I look like an asshole?’

At Dolores’ troubled look, Tudor smirked and picked up the glass.

“Don’t worry, Ms. President, this isn’t alcohol, it’s soda!”

Suddenly, Dolores is relieved.

Of course, she didn’t realize that some sodas also contain alcohol, although in trace amounts.

Meanwhile, Vikir was still racing alone at the board game.

Why is Vikir, who doesn’t usually like to be in the spotlight, doing so well in the game?

‘…It reminds me of the old days.’

It was the memories.

The game.

Four tiles are thrown, and depending on the situation in which they are flipped or flipped, Do (Pig), Gae (Dog), Geol (Sheep), Yut (Cow), and Mo (Horse) are selected and move forward or to the side.

If you encounter an opponent’s horse along the way, you can eat it and send it back to the starting line.

This board game was very popular among soldiers in the field, in ambush, or on standby during the Age of Destruction.

Not because it was particularly fun, but because there were no other board games to play in the army’s internal affairs department.

‘…I played this game until I got sick of it while fighting in a five-minute standby in the trenches of Hill 7 on the Western Front.’

In the midst of a protracted war and prolonged confrontation with the enemy, the soldiers lived a boring daily life.

It was one of the few things they could do together as a group of men.

Of course, at that time it was an outdated classic game that was not played by anyone except soldiers on the front lines, so there were many old people and outcasts who learned all kinds of unusual techniques…

‘Now it’s a trendy board game that’s been around for a while.’

That’s why there weren’t any skilled players.

Even Pigi, who is the second best board game player right now, its throwing skills are terrible.

‘If I throw … like that, I’m going to lose to my fellow soldiers on the military salary.’

Most soldiers on the front lines in the Age of Destruction would have had enough.

Vikir wasn’t much of a gambler himself, but he’d been dragged by his superiors often enough to learn the tricks.

…Thud!

Yut, and a thud to the back.

Vikir’s black piece moved forward and ate Sinclaire’s white piece, which was five squares ahead.

Then, on the very next turn, it moves backward one space and eats another of Sinclaire’s white pieces.

The two white horses are rolled back to the starting line at the end of the turn.

Sinclaire, down two pieces, cries out.

“Hyung! Are you a professional player? Why are you so good? It’s bad enough that I lost in my studies, but now I’m losing in games….”

He told her not to call him oppa, but she was calling him hyung.

Tudor, who had five horses stolen by Vikir, asked Vikir with an shocked expression.

“No, you’re good with your hands, you’re good with dice, you’re good with cards,… is there any game you can’t play?”

“No.”

Vikir said firmly.

Everyone in the room gasped at his overwhelming confidence.

“Hey, Vikir, Vikir, can’t you give me a ride on your horse?”

“Hey, I want to see your face, hehe, can’t you just take off your bangs?”

“Let’s take off your glasses, okay?”

“Isn’t it stuffy, do you want me to cut your hair, especially those bangs….”

Some of the girls sidled up to Vikir’s side and touched his arm, knee, etc.

Then, another girl showed interest in Vikir.

“…You’re good at board games?”

It was Dolores, the student council president.

“And do you know how to play Go?”

She didn’t know any other games, but she was confident in this one.

Finally, Vikir nodded.

“I can play some.”

“Really? What’s your level of Go(棋力)?”

“ …About level 2.”

Dolores laughed inwardly.

‘Second-grade, that’s good enough to go out and show off.’

For reference, she was a level 5 amateur.

She was the top ace in her freshman year, and in her second year, she was the vice president of the Go Club, a position she held with great enthusiasm, because there was no one in her family who could play Go.

…Although the club was closed after that because no new students came in.

No one would play with her after that, and most of them didn’t know how to play in the first place.

Dolores also had a busy work schedule that made it difficult for her to play a game of Go, so the hobby naturally fell by the wayside.

But here we have a kid who thinks he’s good at all board games. With only a second-grade skill.

“Huh, Ms. President, are you going to play a game with Vikir?”

“Sis, you’re awesome!”

“The jack-of-all-trades vs. the newbie who specializes in board games! How’s that for a match?”

The mood of the room was welcoming to Dolores’ participation.

Dolores jumped out of bed, unable to resist the cheers.

Until now, she’d watched from the sidelines because she didn’t know how to play board games, but this was different.

The only board game she knew how to play, and the only one she was very good at, was Go.

It’s been a long time since we’ve had a game like this.

“Shall we have a little fun, then?”

The saint smiled as she held up the simple checkerboard Tudor had brought with him.

Amateur level 5 hides his strength.

The difference between Dolores’ power and Vikir’s was as great as the difference between heaven and earth.

And she was keeping it a secret right now.

“As for the penalty, how about a cup of punishment liquor per house?”

The other students, who had been crushed by Vikir, cheered at Dolores’s bold provocation.

And.

“…OK.”

Vikir could only nod, as tasteless as ever.

Chapter 155

How to Keep Your Night Shift Employees Safe (2)

◆

-This orphanage provides the following rules of conduct for the safety of employees who work at night.

Please do not disclose the following information to anyone outside the nursery, and the nursery will not provide any compensation for accidents caused by violating these items.

This sign was obviously not there when I arrived during the day.

“…For the safety of our night staff.”

Vikir muttered to himself.

Below the sign,

there were a number of caveats.

(1). If you see a child alone in the hallway during your nightly patrol, ignore them and go back the way you came.

If the child approaches you or tries to put something in your hand, immediately leave the area as quickly as possible.

We strictly prohibit children from walking in the hallways at night and will never leave a child alone without a guardian under any circumstances.

(2). If a group of children approaches the guardhouse and tells you that there is a problem with the water pipe in room 66 on the 6th floor of the main building, reply that you understand and then lock the door to the guardhouse.

Afterward, hum your favorite song. ‘They’ hate the sound of singing.

For your information, there are a total of 65 rooms on the 6th floor of the main building, and room 66 does not exist in this building.

(3). Masturbation is absolutely prohibited in this orphanage, regardless of gender.

Anytime, anywhere, in any manner.

(4). If, while patrolling the halls, you find that no matter how far you walk, you never seem to get to your destination, and you keep seeing the same scenery over and over again, you should immediately exit by the fire escape stairs, crouch down with your forehead against the wall in the corner, close your eyes, and cover your ears.

Daytime security guards check the fire escape stairs first thing when they arrive for work.

Stay in that position until morning when you hear chickens crowing.

* If there is anything else on the list below that negates item #4, you should never pay attention to it.

(5). Occasionally, a body is found that has committed suicide. This is a common occurrence in other orphanages, so you can follow the usual protocols.

However, if you find the body of a child hanging in a very ordinary place, be careful.

Calmly check to see if there’s anything to step on and if there isn’t, and you’re wondering how a child could have gotten up there and hanged himself, immediately leave the area as fast as you can, go into the security office, turn off the lights, and lock the door.

Note the order very carefully, it’s turn off the lights and lock the door, not lock the door and turn off the lights.

Also, in this case, you should never sing. You shouldn’t even make a breathing sound if you can help it.

‘It’ has darkened ears.

(6). If you’re patrolling a hallway and there’s nothing around you, but you hear something like a strange breathing sound in your ear, immediately get low and get on the floor.

Then crouch down and make yourself as small as possible and likewise make no sound.

If the sound subsequently stops, call another employee to locate and clean the stain on the ceiling.

(7). There are always two night patrols at all times, no exceptions, no exceptions, absolutely no exceptions.

(8). If there is someone hanging out in the center of the lake above the nursery, never go near it, and lock all hallway doors.

You should also lock all the windows in the ceiling and at the top of the attic on the top floor.

For reference, the lake is 35 meters deep.

(9). You should never knock on an empty room. Do not pull a locked door handle more than three times.

And under no circumstances should you put your ear to the door and eavesdrop on anything.

(10). If a child you don’t recognize comes up to you and asks for the name or address of the night patrol, etc., you should never answer.

If you are dutifully wearing your name badge, there is no reason to ask for your name, and your address is personal information, and the orphanage bylaws do not allow you to ask for it.

Also, as in paragraph (1), the orphanage does not leave children alone without a guardian.

(11). If you see a group of children in the center of the stairs on the 6th floor of the main building, Room 6, with only their upper bodies over the railing, asking for help, do not take a single step closer.

You should leave the area as quickly as possible without looking back.

Also, try to yell or sing as loudly as possible.

Due to the structure of the building, this location is just an ordinary wall and there is no 7th floor in the main building.

(12). If you need to go to the restroom during a night shift, be sure to take a companion with you.

No matter how often or how inconvenient, you should always have at least two people in the restroom.

But the best thing to do is to avoid going to the restroom at night.

(13). If you are walking down the hallway and hear a moan from within the walls, laugh out loud immediately.

You should laugh until the moans turn into cries.

If the cries then stop, leave the area as quickly as possible, go to the guardhouse, and lock the door.

And do not check the attendance of the children in the nursery for three days, starting with the next morning’s check-in.

(14). Item 4 doesn’t exist in this handbook; any nursery would leave that ominous number blank.

If you see something written in the number 4, always do the opposite of what it says.

Never follow number 4.

*If you see anything else in the list above that negates #14, don’t pay attention to it.

It seems like a strange list of rules.

Vikir nodded, sensing the ominous vibe of the notice.

‘…Shallow tricks.’

The usual tricks of the demons, feeding off of human fear.

If the night guard did indeed see something, it would be dismissed as a simple matter of discipline.

Vikir ignored the notice and stumbled through the darkness of the corridor.

The guardhouse in the center lobby of the corridor was unlit, its door firmly shut, and not a single breath escaping from within.

‘The night watch must have seen something.’

This will make my job easier.

Vikir stepped quietly past the front of the guardhouse and made his way to the back of the third building.

Just then.

“…!”

Vikir stopped in his tracks.

At the end of a long hallway. There was a figure standing there.

A girl in a white pajamas, standing still and staring this way.

It was Nymphet.

“….”

Nymphet stared at Vikir with a strange expression on her face, and then she disappeared down the other side of the corridor.

Vikir quickly scrambled to his feet and headed back to where Nymphet had been.

But when he rounded the corner, the Nymphet was gone, leaving only a torn piece of curtain lying on the floor.

“What was that? Did I see something?”

Vikir furrowed his brow and bent down to pick up the piece of curtain from the floor.

And then. The words on the curtain were imprinted deeply on Vikir’s retina.

‘Help me.’

Suddenly, Vikir’s mind flashed back to item number one on the sign.

‘This is a very unpleasant place.’

Vikir immediately began to chase after Nymphet.

The layout of the building was clear in his mind.

Vikir focuses on the spaces where Nymphet could disappear from view in an instant.

But something doesn’t feel right.

‘…Is this …?

Vikir realizes that from the moment he saw the Nymphet, he’s been seeing the same scene over and over again around every corner in the hallway.

Same walls, same ceiling, same floor, same windows, same view out the window.

Vikir’s brow furrowed slightly.

‘Illusion? Trap?’

Naturally, his mind flashed back to the sign he’d seen earlier.

Number 4. And number 14.

‘Did it say to take the fire escape stairs, crouch against the wall in the corner, close your eyes, and wait until dawn?’

But at the very end, in #14, it vehemently denies it.

Which option, then, should we follow, number 4 or number 14?

Vikir turns his head and sees a staircase leading to an emergency exit, illuminated by a green mana lamp.

He’s trapped in a labyrinth of corridors, so he might as well get out through the emergency exit.

Kkigigigig…

Vikir twisted the rusted handle of a door at the far end of the corridor and pushed it open.

Stairs glowing dimly in green. An eerie shadow.

Where?

The door swung open and an unexpected scene came into Vikir’s view.

There was one passenger who came before Vikir on the emergency exit stairs.

“My Lord in the heavens. Hallowed be thy name, on earth as it is in heaven, thy will be done… lead us not into temptation, but deliver us from evil…..”

The shivering woman with her eyes tightly closed is clearly Dolores, the student council president and saint.

She had been reciting the Lord’s Prayer with her forehead pressed against the wall of the emergency exit.

Vikir couldn’t help but sigh softly behind his mask.

‘…What the hell is she doing here?’

Chapter 156

How to Keep Your Night Shift Employees Safe (3)

◆

Vikir let out a light sigh.

‘…What the hell is she doing here?

St. Dolores. Wasn’t she supposed to be in the showers?

And why is she in Building 4 at this late hour? It’s a long way from the girls’ dormitories….

Vikir adjusted the mask that covered her face once more.

He prepared to modulate his voice.

He reached out a finger and tapped Dolores on the shoulder.

“And forgive us our trespasses, as we forgive those who trespass against us …, and do not lead us into temptation, but deliver us from evil… kya-ak!?”

At Vikir’s touch, Dolores jumped in surprise, almost fainting.

She squeezed her eyes shut even tighter and began to shake. She was so frightened that she didn’t even bother to open her eyes.

“Ha, our Father in heaven….”

“Stop saying the Lord’s Prayer. Just open your eyes.”

Vikir said, deliberately scratching his voice.

Dolores opened one eye from behind her clasped hands.

“Huh?”

Only then did Dolores’ expression turn to one of horror.

After staring at Vikir’s mask for a long moment, Dolores stammered.

“Nigh, Night Hound…?”

“It’s been a while.”

Vikir nodded, and Dolores looked mesmerized once more.

Finally, she managed to speak.

“It’s been a long time… to see you.”

Dolores has a million things she wants to say, but her mouth is too small.

Her heart clenches in her chest, not knowing what to say.

Why he’d disappeared without a word as soon as the plague was over, why he’d been raiding the branches of the Quovadis, where and how he’d been, and what… really was.

There were so many things I wanted to ask.

At such a young age, she had easily taken on the roles of the Academy’s third-year student council president, head of the newspaper department, and patron saint of the Quovadis family, but right now she was fidgeting like a normal seventeen-year-old girl.

Vikir, meanwhile, gets straight to the point.

“Why are you here?”

“I… That is.”

Dolores began to squirm, this time for a completely different reason.

She was recalling something that had happened only a few minutes ago.

◆

After the boys had gone back to their room, Dolores came to her senses.

“…Hot!?”

Dolores washed herself thoroughly with warm water and returned to her room to find her bedding crisp and clean.

Her roommates had already cleaned the bed.

‘I’m in trouble!’

Dolores, who was barely conscious, realized the gravity of the situation.

She had peed on herself, but her friend had taken the blame.

Even though he was the victim of her own pee!

As if apologizing wasn’t bad enough, he’d also been accused. The roles of victim and perpetrator were completely reversed.

If Dolores stays silent, Vikir will be portrayed in the worst possible light.

A freshman was accused of peeing on a senior, a student body president.

Judging by the polarity of the passionate fan clubs within the Academy who regarded Dolores’ beauty as sacred, this was a serious matter that could have resulted in threats of assassination.

‘That can’t happen! We have to fix this!’

It’s too late, but a job must be done.

Dolores walked over to the group of girls gossiping.

They were talking about the incident that had just occurred, and they were gossiping about Vikir.

“Such dignity after pissing on a saint’s belly. Don’t you think it’s kind of cool, even though he’s an asshole?”

“The sight of that unbalanced figure standing proudly even in wet pants made me feel a little heartbroken…….”

“There’s something about that nerdiness that makes me feel strangely maternal… I just want to protect him. Change his diaper. Feed him milk.”

It’s a bit of an odd direction for a conversation to take.

But Dolores didn’t hear it. So she closed her eyes tightly and told the truth.

“Girls, Vikir didn’t do anything wrong, and I peed on him!”

The girls’ eyes widened.

….

After a few moments of silence, everyone, including Bianca, sighed and tapped Dolores on the shoulder.

“Really, the president is a saint.”

“Sis, you shouldn’t have to bear the insult of being called a pisser for him.”

“Your sacrifice is admirable, and if it were me, I don’t think even my best friend would have gone that far, let alone a junior who’s not even close to me….”

No one seemed to believe Dolores.

“Oh, no! Believe me, it was really me who peed earlier, not Vikir…!”

Out of frustration, Dolores repeated the truth, but no one believed her.

Instead, they admired Dolores’ noble self-sacrifice in covering up for Vikir.

‘Aah! That’s crazy!’

Dolores decided to give up trying to explain.

Instead, she sprang into action to correct the misunderstanding.

Even if she was caught, she would go outside, meet Vikir, apologize formally, and clear up any misunderstandings.

It was late at night, but she could probably get an emergency meeting request from the supervisor and have Vikir summoned from the boys’ dormitory.

‘The sooner the better for an explanation.’

Dolores left the girls’ floor and headed straight for the boys.

She thought about thanking him for carrying her burden and apologizing for not being able to explain immediately.

And just then.

Dolores saw a strange shadow blazing across the outer wall of the dorm.

“…!”

Dolores stopped dead in her tracks as she turned to go to her tutor.

What she had just seen was surely a stork’s beak mask under the hem of a black cloak.

The mysterious creature she had been searching for, the one that had appeared so many times in her dreams.

An enigmatic creature that is both endlessly mysterious and endlessly fascinating.

The Night Hound, as he glided beneath a moon shrouded in clouds.

Dolores forgot everything she had been thinking about in a blur.

She turned on her heel and began to move in the direction of the Night Hound.

There was no thought of catching him or stopping him. Just, just….

◆

“ …I just wanted to talk to you.”

At Dolores’ words, Vikir smiled bitterly behind his mask.

He knew what she was wondering.

Why he stole a saint’s tears, and why he’s been wiping out the branches of the Quovadis.

Ko-ok.

Dolores’ hand tightened on Vikir’s collar.

Her eyes were twitching like ripples on a lake.

“Why… did you do that to me, that day, too, disappearing without a word.”

“….”

“Tell me, you didn’t do it, the branches of our family, you didn’t do it, did you? There was some misunderstanding, wasn’t there?”

“….”

“Say something, anything. Please….”

Dolores clenched her small fists around Vikir’s collar.

Then, leaning down, she pressed her forehead against Vikir’s chest and spoke in a hushed voice.

“You’re not that kind of person, the villain everyone says you are….”

Vikir didn’t know how to respond to that.

Dolores’s bite in her voice was more than trust, it was some kind of comradeship.

‘…Is it because of the ‘Red Death’ incident back in the day?’

It’s understandable that feelings of camaraderie and comradeship might have developed in the course of treating so many plague victims.

But Dolores’s feelings were much broader and deeper than Vikir had expected.

Vikir had just opened his mouth to say something.

“…!”

Vikir sensed a strange sound in his ears.

Whoosh… hook… grunt…

It sounded like the ragged breathing of a beast, mingled with the boiling of blood.

Dolores heard this ominous breath as well.

Dolores tugged at Vikir’s collar, her fingers trembling with fear.

“Did you… see the notice?”

“I saw ….”

Vikir nodded.

They were now standing on the emergency exit stairs, the location of options #4 and #14.

And this uncomfortable breathing in their ears was spontaneously reminding them of item 6 on the notice.

(6). If you’re patrolling a hallway and there’s nothing around you, and you hear something like strange breathing in your ear, immediately get low and get down on the floor.

Then crouch down and make yourself as small as possible and likewise make no sound.

If the sounds subsequently stop, call another employee to locate and clean the stain on the ceiling.

‘Ephebo’

‘Ephebo’, the first high-ranking undead guarding Quilt appeared.

Chapter 157

Familiar Face (1)

◆

[Whoosh-grrrr-]

Suspended from the ceiling with an unpleasant breath, this must be Ephebo.

He is one of the four hounds who, along with Geronto, Pedo, and Hebe, serve as Quilt’s minions.

Vikir quickly scanned Ephebo’s entire body.

‘He’s fully recovered, a demon indeed.’

No broken bones, no torn flesh, no exploded organs, all seemingly intact.

But Vikir was a veteran hound, used to fighting demons, so he wasn’t too fazed.

Vikir prepared himself for battle and calmly began to calculate his next move.

…But Dolores was not among them.

“Huh, Lord Ephebo, why are you here…?”

She looked dazed, her thinking paralyzed for a moment.

Why is the guardian knight of House Endulgentia in this place, at this time of night, looking like this?

And.

“You’ll get yourself killed if you keep bruising like that.”

Vikir advised mildly.

Quack!

With that, Ephebo, who had fallen from the ceiling, raised the large hammer he was carrying and smashed it into Vikir.

“You’ve got some serious muscle.”

Vikir stumbled backward with Dolores around his waist.

The magic sword Beelzebub was trembling.

The Quovadis’s blunt technique would be too much of a drain on his strength in a head-to-head encounter.

Vikir leaped to his feet and retreated across the hall.

There was no need for concern for terrain in this demonic labyrinth, a corridor that went on forever anyway.

Vikir set Dolores down on the floor.

“So much for wrapping. I can’t take any more.”

Dolores tried to say something, but Vikir really didn’t have time.

…Thud!

Ephebo crawled down to the ground.

[Crunch! Crunch!]

Every joint in his body was grotesquely twisted, and he had an even more grotesque appearance than when they had met before.

His arms, thick as logs, were longer than his legs, dragging on the ground, and his legs, with two or three more joints than a normal human leg, were bent in grotesque ways.

It looked like a demon.

Dolores’s eyes grew cold at the sight of him.

Although he was an Old Order figure, he had once been an ally, a member of the same Quovadis.

But the figure in front of her now was unmistakably a demon.

“…Why is a demon here?”

“It’s not a demon, it’s Lord Ephebo.”

“I mean, why would Lord Ephebo be demonized…? Are you saying he was a demon in the first place?”

Dolores stared at the figure before her in bewilderment and disbelief.

A man who had been knighted in the Quovadis Family and appointed as the guardian knight of House Indulgentia.

She had never seen his bare face, as he always wore a mask, but she had a not-so-bad image of a man who could take on any task, no matter how arduous, with grace.

‘What the hell is going on within the family?’

Dolores felt confused, but now was not the time to pry into it.

…Boom!

The Night Hound’s sword and Ephebo’s hammer clashed again.

Pfft!

Shockwaves ripped through the ceiling, walls, and floor.

Steel frames buried in the walls were bent like taffy sticks, and water was gushing out from burst water pipes.

Dolores gasped at the powerful aura Ephebo emitted.

Graduators. That’s the highest level of the Graduators.

Was Lord Ephebo that powerful?

…But there was something even more astonishing than that.

It was the blood-colored aura of the Night Hound.

…Kurrrrr!

Vikir emitted a thick, liquid, almost solid aura from the tip of his magic sword Beelzebub.

Handling it was like wielding a giant greatsword.

Crackle! Crackle! Clang!

The black aura that Ephebo emitted was torn apart by Vikir’s red aura.

It was like iron and lime colliding.

Baskerville’s seventh form.

The upper incisors, central incisors, lateral incisors, and molars.

And the wisdom teeth, premolars, and molars of the lower jaw.

A total of seven teeth fell toward Efebo, the black sack monster.

…Thud, thud, thud, thud!

The hound’s teeth punctured flesh, slicing, tearing, ripping, and crushing even the bones within.

This murderous sword technique is optimized for killing, and its sole purpose is to make the enemy suffer.

It is a legendary sword technique that only exists in the Baskerville 10th Form, and has not been reported in the literature.

Even a high-ranking member of the Baskervilles would not recognize Vikir’s current swordplay as Baskervillian.

Is that why? Dolores looked at Vikir, growing increasingly confused.

“You… have grown stronger since I last saw you, haven’t you?”

“I’ve been steadily raiding the branches of the Quovadis family.”

“What, what! How can you say that so nonchalantly… No, more than that, why?”

“Why, do you even have that question after seeing that?”

Vikir jerked at the Ephebo in front of him.

[Grunt… shrug…]

Ephebo’s entire body was covered in teeth and he was staggering around, but he was still standing without falling.

For a normal person, or even a normal Graduator, a wound of this severity would have been fatal.

…Push! …Push!

Ephebo’s tattered flesh spurted out blood as black as asphalt.

Dolores asked, not quite understanding.

“Why the hell is there a thing like that in our family?”

“What if you ask me to do your household chores.”

“You knew about it! Isn’t that why you’ve been raiding the branches all this time…!?”

But Dolores’ questions were not answered. There was a more pressing matter at hand.

Shhhh.

Ephebo began to do something unpleasant.

The black energy that emanated from his entire body turned into a chain and wrapped around Vikir.

“What a bother…”

Vikir realized that Ephebo’s purpose was to stall.

Pot!

Kicking the watery floor, Vikir stretched out the aura of Beelzebub as long as he could.

This would be the final blow.

But.

Boom.

Ephebo swung the huge hammer a few times, then picked it up and threw it.

The hammer bent like a thumb and flew toward Vikir.

With the black chains wrapped around his body, Vikir was forced to take the blow with his body.

But.

“Light of my life, flame of my life, my sin, my soul. I will break your filthy bonds!”

The holy incantation from Dolores’ mouth shattered the chains around Vikir’s entire body.

Pa’aat-.

Buff. And heal.

When the demonic debuff weighing down Vikir’s body disappeared, Vikir regained the agile movements characteristic of a Night Hound.

Jaw! Pow!

Vikir stepped on the flying hammer and leaped once more.

Using his momentum as a springboard, he swung Beelzebub horizontally.

A red crescent moon floated sideways.

…Pow!

Ephebo lost his head by just a fraction of a second.

Vikir sunk his seventh tooth into the top of Ephebo’s head, then used the remaining six teeth to tear off the flesh, tendons, and bones of Ephebo’s neck.

Kung!

Ephebo’s body crashed into the watery floor. The hammer also stopped, embedded in the wall.

Even if water wasn’t gushing out of the water pipe, it would have seemed like time had stopped.

Thud.

Vikir dropped Ephebo’s head to the floor, which was still stuck on the tip of Beelzebub.

“I’ve severed his neck completely, so I suppose not even a demon can do much about it.”

Just in case it could regenerate in some bizarre way, Vikir pulled the head away from his body and stomped on it firmly with his foot.

This is because there was a case in the past where Seth escaped with only its head remaining.

Then Dolores spoke, her voice trembling.

“I don’t know, what the hell is going on. I thought the only trouble in the family was the conflict between the Old and New Order factions, but… what the hell was lurking behind that, do you know?”

At this, Vikir shook his head.

“I don’t know. All I know is that the head of the Indulgentia family is actually a demon. That’s also at the level of a demon king.”

Dolores’s eyes widened to tears at that.

She stammered out a question.

“Ar, are you sure about that, can you say for sure?”

“Can’t you tell by looking at that?”

Vikir pointed at Ephebo’s body and then at his head.

Even at this moment, Ephebo’s body, pulsing with black blood, was still struggling to regenerate.

Dolores finally recognized the words of the Night Hound.

Paat-.

The divine white light that emanated from her body had completely destroyed Ephebo’s immune system.

In the end, Ephebo sank completely, missing even the last opportunity to regenerate.

Vikir looked at it and thought.

“…Is more useful than I thought?”

Demons’ uncommon ability to regenerate had always been a problem for Vikir.

But with Dolores by his side, it might be a different story.

Dolores, meanwhile, looked uneasy and asked Vikir again.

“If, if there were demons lurking in the back of the Old Order… then shouldn’t there be a problem with the New Order?”

“Did any of the branches I’ve raided so far belong to the New Order?”

“…Not one, that I know of.”

“Then we have our answer.”

Vikir neatly organized Dolores’s confusion.

Dolores could only stare at Vikir’s back as he walked ahead.

Then Vikir looked down at Ephebo’s head rolling on the floor.

A black leather sack, which, upon closer inspection, looked like a hood attached to the inside of a gas mask.

It, too, seemed to be an artifact of some sort, as it emitted a faint aura of magic.

I’ve thought about it before, but I had a feeling that it might be an artifact, an “OOPArt” of sorts, like Beelzebub.

I was also quite curious about the face behind the black sack mask.

Dolores was also very curious, as she had seen with her own eyes that Ephebo had used the blunt techniques of the Quovadis.

“Who the hell is… really a Quovadis?”

“You’ll know when you see his face.”

Vikir extended his hand.

With a snap, the black sack that had been wrapped around Ephebo’s face was pulled away.

Both Vikir and Dolores stared in horror.

“…!?”

Ephebo’s bare face was clearly that of someone they both knew.

Chapter 159

Familiar Faces (3)

◆

Pedo and Hebe make their appearance.

Pedo with his two heavy Jamadhars, and Hebe with a pair of huge garden scissors.

Both were wielding weapons that were not only unique, but deformed.

Bubbling, bubbling, bubbling…

A sticky liquid aura bubbled with mana and began to boil.

The two of them, shrouded in a thick vapor, looked like two Advanced Graduators.

Since there are two higher ranks, even the highest rank Vikir cannot let down his guard.

…Pow!

Vikir shot forward.

A red slash streaked horizontally from Beelzebub.

Boom!

The hallway wall broke and a loud noise erupted, but even that sound was trapped in the hallway’s labyrinth.

Pedo leaped upward and Hebe ducked downward to avoid Vikir’s blow.

At the same time.

…Boom!

Two Jamadhars and a pair of giant scissors flew toward Vikir.

The stone pillars crumbled like zucchini slices.

Puff-puff-puff-puff!

Vikir summoned his numerous teeth and tore through the rubble of the crumbling stone pillar, leaving the bodies of Hebe and Pedo beyond.

At the same time.

“Teh!”

Vikir lifted his mask slightly and spat.

The spit mixed with blood flew out and landed on the back of Pedo’s hand.

Cheeeeeesss…

The sound of flesh burning and tendons melting inside.

But Pedo doesn’t feel the pain, and he pushes in and swings his sword.

Vikir stepped back, feeling a piece of his cloak being cut away.

“Poison doesn’t work on ….”

He mixed Madam Eight-Legs’s venom into his saliva and spat it out, but the effect was minimal.

Hahaha, the undead are already moving in dead bodies, so it’s no wonder they’re less vulnerable to poison.

“Then how about this?”

Vikir stepped back, dissolving into a puff of stony smoke.

“?”

“?”

Pedo and Hebe look around for Vikir, who has vanished in an instant.

Thud.

Vikir, who had disappeared like a ghost, reappeared near the ceiling, above Pedo and Hebe’s heads.

Puff! Puff-puff-puff!

The gnashing teeth sliced into Pedo and Hebe’s bodies once more.

Having absorbed the traits of Mushuhushu’s biology, Vikir can make no sound when they move.

‘Silent heels’.

It was definitely a useful skill in this dirt.

Puck! Plop! Plop-plop!

The magic sword wielded by Vikir began to nibble away at the bodies of Pedo and Hebe little by little.

‘If it was a living opponent, I would have quickly punctured their throats or hearts, rendering them incapacitated…’

Vikir felt a little frustrated: as undead, their stabbing attacks were ineffective.

To make them incapacitated, he would have to use a wide slashing attack, which requires a lot of preparation and drains his stamina, making it difficult to deal with two of them at the same time.

Boom.

Vikir stretches out his aura.

[Grrrr!]

Suddenly, Pedo leaped forward.

Poof!

He ignored Vikir’s sword that pierced his stomach and continued to advance.

‘Oops!’

Vikir tried to retrieve his sword, but the sword was already firmly wedged between the joints of Pedo’s vertebral column (凹凸) and he was slow to pull it out.

Using his vertebrae, Pedo began to clamp down on Vikir’s sword with a firm grip.

“…?”

Vikir had no idea what Pedo wanted to achieve even by destroying most of his body.

And then.

“…!”

It wasn’t until Hebe slammed a giant pair of scissors into Pedo’s back that Vikir realized their plan.

Pfft-eog!

Hebe raised the giant scissors and sliced through Pedo’s body.

At the same time, he cut off Vikir’s body in front of him!

Uh-oh!

Vikir gritted his teeth against the two scissor blades pressing against his body.

Pedo’s body in front of him was almost cut in half.

It hadn’t split in two because of his strong spine, but the scissors had cut through all the flesh on his sides and clamped down on the bones inside.

Thanks to this, Vikir had barely escaped being sliced in two as well.

Kugugukuk…

Both of Vikir’s shoulders and forearms are tattered.

The flesh was torn, the bones were popping, and blood was flowing.

In that state.

…Puck!

Vikir raised his leg and kicked Pedo in the stomach.

Crunch! Crunch!

The sound of friction between the spine and scissor blade was heard, and Pedo’s body was pushed back a bit.

At the same time, the pressure of the scissors digging into Vikir’s arms loosened slightly.

…Puck!

Vikir kicked Pedo’s body with his foot again.

As Pedo’s body is pushed a little further into the space between the scissor blades, the scissor blades spread further apart and the force that restrains Vikir also becomes looser.

…Puck! …puck! …puck! …puck! …puck! …puck! …puck! …puck! …puck!

Vikir continued to pound the puck into Pedo’s torso.

Pedo struggled, but he couldn’t help but be pushed further and further back.

Finally.

Poof!

The scissor blades snapped the worn spine, cutting Pedo’s torso in two.

At the same time, the scissors crossed at a terrifying speed.

…Pow!

They clashed together in one place.

Of course, Vikir had leaped upward and dodged the blades just before Pedo’s vertebrae were severed.

“Fuck you.”

Vikir swung his hand, sending out a sharp, skewered blow.

…Poof!

It tore a gaping hole in Hebe’s neck in the blink of an eye, sending him flying several meters backwards.

Thud!

Vikir and Hebe fell out at the same time, both of their bodies covered in blood and tattered.

…At that very moment.

“That’s it, Night Hound!”

Saint Dolores shouted.

It takes a long time, but the effect is certain. The holy words of the Demon Sealing spell have been manifested in the flesh after a long prayer.

“Light of my life, flame of my life, my sins, my soul. Let the little things make me feel the weight of their karma suddenly…!”

The prayer that Dolores has been reciting over a long period of time gains power in itself and exerts coercive physical force on beings such as the undead at the border between matter and antimatter.

Boom!

The divine light of the runes burst forth and crushed Pedo and Hebe.

Pedo, who was still trying to reattach his torn body, and Hebe, who was still clutching at the gaping hole in his neck with his hands, were instantly crushed to the ground.

They could only wriggle slightly in the face of Dolores’s immense divine power.

Only then did Vikir rise from the floor.

White flesh and red wounds peeked through the torn cloak.

Dolores saw it and ran to him in horror.

“Nigh, Night Hound! Are you okay!”

It was a serious injury, a fatal injury that would be difficult to survive for more than a few minutes.

Dolores knelt down beside Vikir, her face covered in tears and snot.

“I’m sorry, I’m sorry! I took too long to cast the spell….”

But it was too late. All the skin and flesh had been torn away, and you could see bone and guts inside, and now he was about to….

“Quick, quick Heal, let’s get him out of here and get him to a medical center… huh?”

Dolores, who had been flailing about with tears in her eyes, was soon forced to open them wide.

Tsutsutsutsuts…

Vikir’s wounds were healing rapidly.

‘It’s a good thing I have the skill of the Bog Salamander.’

It didn’t take long for Vikir’s wounds to heal.

Only his torn cloak revealed his white skin and toned muscles.

As Vikir mended his clothes, he gave a brief word of advice to Dolores, who stood beside him with a blank expression on her face.

“Save your holy power. You haven’t even met a real demon yet.”

“Yeah, yeah, yeah….”

Dolores stared at Vikir’s body in awe.

He had never seen anyone heal so quickly from a wound.

‘Is it because he has divine power?’

Dolores, who had seen Vikir use some sort of divine power before, couldn’t help but think so.

And then.

‘The Night Hound was a man.’

Dolores had a sudden thought.

He had assumed it was a man, based on his build and voice.

However, he had been wrapped up in a mask or cloak, so she hadn’t really thought of him as a man until now.

But this time, when she saw his white, toned body peeking through the torn hem of his clothes, she knew for sure.

His gender was male and his age was considerably younger.

Suddenly, Dolores’s face flushed, even if only slightly.

It was the first time she’d ever seen a man’s naked body at such close range.

‘Oh, don’t be fooled.’

She’d seen it countless times with her patients, but she’d never considered their gender in the first place, so it shouldn’t count.

Dolores turned her head slightly again.

The Night Hound was adjusting his mask and cloak.

After seeing the body under the cloak, Dolores was naturally curious about the face under the mask.

‘…I wonder what the face is like under that mask?’

Would it be a terrifying face? Or a surprisingly normal face? What does he look like?

While Dolores was wondering all these things.

“Are you curious?”

Vikir asked.

Dolores turned her head in surprise.

“Yes, yes!?”

“I asked if you were curious.”

“What, about what?”

Vikir replied, as if asking the obvious.

“The face behind the mask.”

“…!”

Dolores’s body stiffened.

“What am I supposed to say? How am I supposed to answer….?”

After a long pause, Dolores closes her eyes tightly and nods.

“Yes, I want to know!”

Vikir nodded in agreement.

“Yeah. I was curious too.”

“…?”

Dolores opened her mouth in confusion.

Vikir turned and walked a few steps away, completely ignoring Dolores’ attitude.

He walked right up to where Pedo and Hebe were struggling.

Boom!

Vikir slit the two undead’s throats in an instant, ripping off the black leather sacks they were wearing.

‘…Ah, I thought you were talking about your masks.’

Dolores walked away, looking slightly disappointed.

But only for a moment, as the revealed identities of Pedo and Hebe hardened her expression.

“One of them is from Donquixote.”

Hebe’s body was covered in tattoos symbolizing Donquixote, the spearman.

Vikir also recognized the tattoo because he had Tudor, from Donquixote, as a friend.

“I’ll have to see if there’s a young man from the Donquixote family who’s gone missing recently. Hmm, I don’t know where the other one came from.”

Then. Vikir answered Dolores’s question.

“…Baskerville.”

Dolores had to gasp when she heard that.

“Iron Blood Swordsman Baskerville? How do you know that?”

“….”

Vikir didn’t answer.

He simply looked at the face that was revealed when the black sack was removed.

It was a face that melted quickly upon exposure to air, but Vikir remembered it clearly.

‘…Were you Staffordshire Baskerville of the Knights of Pitbull?’

Unlike a member of the Baskerville family, he was quite sly and affable, and was a hound that served well as a guide dog for training young hound.

When Seth Le Baskerville’s purges had taken out so many people, Vikir had heard that he’d been dismissed and sent somewhere, but he hadn’t expected to find himself here as an undead.

‘…I don’t have a good feeling about this.’

It’s ominous to see so many familiar faces as undead.

And then.

There was a presence that amplified Vikir’s anxiety even further.

Gooooooooooo…

A pulsating wave of mana drew Vikir and Dolores’ attention.

Up ahead, Building One.

A woman stood at the front door of the main lobby, looking this way.

A mage-type undead with a breathtaking display of magic.

Geronto.

The most troublesome of Quilt’s four minions.

Chapter 161

Sin and Punishment (1)

◆

And thus I clothe my naked villainy with old odd ends stolen forth from holy writ And seem a saint when most I play the devil.

You cover your naked wickedness with a few worn-out words stolen from the Bible, so you look like a saint even when you’re doing devilish things.

◆

Quilt.

The patriarch of House Indulgentia, an affiliated family of the faithful Quovadis.

A faithful follower of the Rune religion, an ardent preacher, an honorary mayor of the Imperial family, and a benevolent orphanage director who lovingly cares for children with nowhere else to go.

But it was all just a mask, and behind it lurked an ugly demonic face.

Quilt looked down at Geronto’s corpse with a friendly smile.

“Ho-ho-ho-ho, that was a good harpoon.”

His gaze shifted to the four black sacks poking out of Vikir’s cloak.

They belonged to Ephebo, Hebe, Pedo, and Geronto, who wore them over their faces.

Quilt grunted as if he was about to be troubled.

“Are all four of them ruined? I borrowed them from ‘that bitch,’ and I’ll have to give them back someday, but I’m in big trouble, and I wonder what kind of trouble that damned bitch will get into….”

His gestures and tone were dramatic, as if he were a theater actor on stage alone, delivering a monologue.

Meanwhile.

Dolores, seeing Quilt’s easy-going smile, was enraged and stepped forward.

“You! How dare you wear the mantle of a saint and do such an ugly thing, bringing the demon into the orphanage! What the hell are you thinking!”

“‘Ho, ho, ho! What are you doing? Haven’t you seen for yourself what has been found beneath the grounds of every orphanage, monastery, and hospital under the Quovadis name?”

Dolores shook her head, not understanding Quilt’s words for a moment.

Then she realized. She realized what Quilt was saying.

“Bones! Human skeletons!”

That’s right.

Demons do eat humans, but only the fluid ones, the very young ones.

Quilt smirked, his mouth watering.

“I guess humans are best when they’re young. They’re delicious.”

It was a clear provocation.

Dolores stared at Quilt with a mixture of horror and anger.

“Cannibal! Cannibal! Yes, you really are a demon…!”

“I’ve done some cannibalism, so it’s a bit unfair to label me a demon, but I’m not the only one who eats, you know, people in high places.”

“What, what!”

Dolores opens her mouth in disbelief.

But Quilt remained impassive.

“When you’ve been up high and seen all the delicacies, you’re naturally interested in things you’ve never eaten before, and once you introduce them to a few people, they catch on.”

“Bullshit! There’s no way anyone would do that!”

“Ho, ho, ho. Why not, there are so many of you Quovadis alone.”

“…!”

Dolores staggered once, as if genuinely shocked.

Quilt chuckled and continued.

“Well, I understand. I know it’s a shock to you, Saint. Humans often have many faces. A man may be a pious priest in front of you, but you never know what he’s like behind closed doors.”

“Bullshit!”

“Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho. Bullshit. Can you say that you, too, live with one face all the time, that you have never worn a face of shame, that you have never made an ugly face behind the mask of hypocrisy?”

Dolores’s pupils dilate at those words.

I have.

He had done something shameful once recently.

Vikir. A boy from the same academy, in the same club.

He’s older than her, but two grades below her.

Recently, Dolores drank too much while playing a board game and wet Vikir’s pants.

To get out of the situation, she committed the dishonorable act of framing Vikir (albeit unintentionally).

Is that all?

On the small scale, the peeing incident is one example; on the large scale, there are many.

A saint who is supposed to love and embrace all people.

A candidate for householder to live up to family expectations.

A New Order leader who must stand up to the Old Order.

A model student who must be the pride of the school.

A student council president who should set an example for the younger students,

A newspaper editor who should always be fair and just.

.

.

After all, she, too, had many faces, and with them all sorts of anguish, burdens, inferiority complexes, hatred, laziness, and other needs.

So Dolores stood still for a moment, speechless.

Then.

…A tug!

There was a hand on her shoulder.

Rough and crude, but warm.

The Night Hound was standing right next to Dolores.

His gravelly voice tickled her ear.

“We can make mistakes. That’s what makes us human.”

A moment. Dolores felt the pressure that had been pressing down on her entire body release at once.

It wasn’t just the pressure of facing the demon.

It was as if all the pressures she had felt throughout her life as a saint, student council president, and other positions of great responsibility had somehow been lifted.

It was like a small salvation. I felt like I was being comforted.

“…Is that true?”

Dolores asked with a lot of emotion.

Vikir nodded silently.

Of course, it was an act done without much intention.

‘If a person is in a hurry, he might pee.’

Vikir was only referring to drinking and peeing his pants.

But Dolores seemed comforted in more ways than one.

The moment.

“…Oops! It can’t be released!”

Dolores reached out and cupped his cheek.

I was somehow relieved to hear that the Night Hound was okay.

Even surprised myself.

Dolores realized how much she had been leaning on the Night Hound, and she braced herself.

“I’m a saint, and a candidate for the head of the Quovadis family. I’m supposed to be someone’s shoulder to lean on, not the other way around!”

But even with these resolutions, she couldn’t help but stare at the broad back of the Night Hound.

…Meanwhile.

Quilt narrowed his eyes and looked at Vikir.

The Saint of the Quovadis was a woman of great potential and talent, but she was still so young and inexperienced that she could be roasted with just three tongues.

However, the unexpected arrival of an unplanned visitor interrupted the plans to shake the saint’s mentality.

Quilt looked at Vikir with a smirk on his lips, but eyes that weren’t smiling.

“Who the hell are you anyway, the one who’s been raiding the branches of my organization lately? You must be the one Ephebo said he owed me the other day.”

“Why do you keep asking me questions when you know the answer?”

Quilt smirked at Vikir’s growling reply.

“Okay. I’m tired of this middle-aged actor’s face anyway. I wanted another young, pretty face. I have a hobby of collecting really pretty faces when I see them. Like yours.”

With his unique ability to relate to faces and masks, Quilt was able to see through the face of Vikir’s plague doctor mask.

Hearing this, Dolores looked back at Vikir, her eyes slightly wide.

‘…Mr. Night Hound is handsome, unexpectedly.’

She can’t see Vikir’s face behind his mask, so she can only guess based on Quilt’s words.

‘Is this the kind of beauty that even the demon covets?’

Dolores knows that she shouldn’t be doing this, but she can’t help but be tempted by Quilt’s words.

Meanwhile. Quilt continued to babble.

“Ho-ho-ho-ho! I’ve always wanted the skin of your face, St. Dolores, and now I’ve got an even prettier face, so what the hell. Two new faces will be added to my collection today…!?”

But he couldn’t get the line out.

“Gap.”

Vikir’s voice cut short.

Tsk-tsk.

Quilt’s head snapped in two in a single blow.

“……?”

Quilt’s skull split in two on both the left and right sides.

Vikir landed lightly on the back of Quilt, who was spewing black blood.

Brawl. A series of extremely honed footwork, sword strikes, and leading swords.

As Vikir pushed himself up onto the steep railing.

…Thud!

Quilt plummeted down the railing, falling to his death.

Seeing this, Dolores wore a dazed expression.

“?”

This is how it ends?

It was an incredibly futile end for a final boss.

…In fact, rather than Quilt dying in vain, it was more likely that Vikir hadn’t been able to fully reveal his true abilities until now, but Dolores wasn’t going to know that.

And.

“Of course this is not the end.”

Vikir warned Dolores.

“Be prepared. The ‘real’ stuff is coming.”

And as if to prove Vikir’s point, Quilt picked himself up off the floor.

His mouth split in two as he spoke.

[What……is that?]

Quilt’s eyes were red and bloodshot, as if they didn’t belong to a normal living being.

He could smell Vikir now.

The scent of a demon hunter, as only a demon could feel.

It was a scent that had remained hidden beneath the mask and black robes.

Vikir was beginning to show his true colors.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts…

Black and red auras swirled ferociously around Vikir’s entire body.

At the same time as the hidden power and aura exploded, the soul of the hound that had raced across countless battlefields bared its teeth.

Naturally, the smell of the countless drops of blood on its teeth also began to emanate.

Demon blood. And the most recent of them all.

It belonged to Andromalius the 10th!

The dying breath of a Demon of the highest order left a deep mark on Vikir’s soul, a mark that would become his karma for life, making his soul and body even more fierce and hardy.

And there was no way Quilt could not smell it.

Finally, the smile completely disappeared from his lips.

[Could it be that Andromalius has been……out of touch lately…?]

Vikir didn’t answer.

Instead, he exploded his hidden aura even more strongly, and as he did so, the scent of Andromalius’ blood grew stronger.

Realizing that Andromalius had been killed by Vikir in front of him, Quilt let out a pitiful sigh.

[Oooooh! It would take the combined power of ten Demon Kings to open the gate to the Demon Realm, and now that……one is gone, the burden on the remaining nine will only increase! Andromalius, you fool!]

Quilt’s appearance began to change as his voice grew more and more distorted.

[Unforgivable! The Great Work……has been put off for another decade!]

Wailing, wailing, wailing.

The voice was so terrible that it made one’s stomach churn and vomit just to hear it.

Puddeudeudeuk!

It was then that Quilt shed his human cloak and began to reveal the true nature of his existence in the Demon Realm.

“Huh?”

Dolores gulped and stepped back.

But.

“….”

Vikir hadn’t taken a step back, watching it all with a nonchalant demeanor.

‘Finally.’

‘Dantalian’, the ninth of the ten corpses!

This was the opponent Vikir had been searching for.

Chapter 162

Sin and Punishment (2)

◆

<Dantalian of the ‘Ninth Corpses’

Danger Rating : S

Size : ?

Found in: ‘Serpent’s Womb’, deep within the Doomed Gate

-Known as the Ninth Corpse.

One of the Ten Calamities, natural enemies of mankind, inscrutable and unkillable.

“Because of the disease, boils will be rampant.”

– The Book of the Ten Commandments 10: 1.

Puddeudeudeuk!

The human’s mask shattered, and his demonic form burst forth from within.

Vikir watched it all with a calm demeanor.

‘…At last.’

Dantalian. The Nine corpse.

Old, young, child, woman, man, handsome, beautiful, ugly, pretty, fat, thin, black, white, yellow, noble, slave, rich, beggar, hero, villain…

With 36 heads, faces, and identities, this demon has a humanoid body and a grim-looking suit.

Each of its thirty-six faces had a purple tongue that could be extended to any length, and the tip was sharper than a blade.

Vikir was able to recall the past from the appearance of this demon, which was as grotesque as ever, with only the shape of the faces differing.

‘Dantalian, the ‘Thousand Faces’. The one who killed the most of my companions.’

Before his regression, Vikir had lost countless allies to the demon before him.

Vikir had lost countless companions to this demon before his eyes, and so had he, for Dantalian has the ability to steal the faces of those he kills.

Mother, father, older brother, younger brother, older sister, older sister, grandmother, grandfather, best friend, respected teacher, beloved student, childhood friend, fiancé, fiancee, first love, unrequited love, etc…… In addition, any comrades who hesitated or hesitated even for a moment against Dantalian, who had all kinds of faces, would inevitably be pierced to death by his blade-like tongue.

And it was Dantalian who, with the face he had stolen, killed his comrades, his family, and his lovers, over and over again.

Therefore, as Vikir, who had the experience of losing countless comrades to the bastard, he had no choice but to evaluate Dantalian this way.

‘A demon that must be killed early on.’

Regardless of his strength, he will cause the most damage to the Human Alliance in the future, so it would be beneficial to eliminate him early on.

Right then.

Tsutsutsutsutsuts…

The smell of rotting flesh washed over them, along with a disgusting aura.

Vikir quickly stepped back.

Dantalian was a demon with countless faces, but he was also known as a plague-bringer.

It was perfect for a fake cleric who could create plagues and reap them, all the while putting on a gentle face.

But in this case, it was a good thing.

For now, Vikir had Dolores behind him.

…Pow!

Dolores emitted a divine light that blocked the Dantalian plague fog.

She opened her mouth with a stern expression.

“…Why?”

[Ho-ho-ho-ho- why? What reason?]

Dolores’ throat tightened at Dantalian’s question.

“Why would you come to the human realm and do this, why would you do this in the orphanage…!”

Then the thirty-six faces staring down at Dolores smirked in unison.

He doesn’t say anything about the ‘gate’ that the ten demons are trying to open, other than his original lament, of course.

He did, however, readily reveal the reason he was keeping another chick in the orphanage.

[It’s a kind of “farm” operation].

“What?”

Dolores asked, and Dantalian replied, still with a frown.

[See this?]

He held up a golden necklace in his hand.

Dolores could only frown as she realized that it was something that some of the children in the orphanage wore around their necks.

Then, Dantalian said.

[This means ‘meat for breeding’].

“…!”

Dantalian’s next words stiffened Dolores’ expression even more.

[We demons live off of humans, just like you humans live off of beasts, so I’ve had a change of heart. Rather than hunt them down every time, I’d rather make them into farms and raise them like livestock, like dogs and pigs.]

“What, what?”

[“Let them breed in here, increase their population, take care of their meat, and then eat them when they reach a certain age. How efficient is that? It’s a win-win situation.]”

“Crazy! How is that a win-win!”

[It’s a win-win. The orphans in the orphanage here were destined to never be born, die at birth, or end up on the streets at a young age, but thanks to me, they’re here, and they’re safe and sound until they’re in their late teens. Of course, after a certain age, their meat becomes tough and tasteless, so we have to eat them before then. Ho-ho-ho-ho!“]”

“Ughhhh…, how dare you do this behind the name of a religious hymn! You will be punished, you demon!”

Dolores shouted in fury.

But when Dantalian heard the word ‘punishment’, his seventy-two eyes widened in confusion.

[Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho- Heavenly punishment? I’m not guilty of anything!]

A passing dog would laugh at the idea that a demon who lured and ate poor children was innocent.

But Dantalian seemed to really think so.

Because.

[I have these things].

Next, Dantalian pulled a bundle of scraps of paper from his arms.

I recognized them as bills, but they were a bit smaller than that.

Dantalian scattered them into the air.

The red writing and seal on the white paper looked like a kind of pagan talisman.

“This is ….”

Dolores stared at the fluttering white bits of paper, dumbfounded.

‘All sins of this faithful church member are forgiven.’

– This indulgence was issued and guaranteed by the Old Order and counterfeiting can result in punishment. –

‘All penalties of this faithful church member are forgiven.’

– This indulgence was issued and guaranteed by the Old Order and counterfeiting can result in punishment. –

?

This ‘indulgence’, stamped with a cardinal’s seal, is a verified and guaranteed assurance by the Order of Runes that the penitent’s sins and punishments have been forgiven.

Dantalian had many such indulgences and pardons in his possession.

[“Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho! I paid a hefty tribute and received these certificates, so I’m not guilty of anything, by your standards.”]

It is the way of the world that if you commit a sin, you must be punished.

However, it is also possible to be exempt from punishment, or even to be pardoned for the sin in the first place.

It was a law that the Quovadis of the Faith recognized, creating an ironic situation in which the source of sin, the demon, was acquitted.

Shocked and at a loss for words, Dolores turned to Dantalian.

[Oh, by the way, the man who issued me these deeds is your father].

“…!?”

[Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho! As I piled up the gold chests like a mountain, they got so loud that they stamped them all over my head.]

Dolores’ father is Cardinal Humbert, who is known as an iconic figure of the Old Order and a hard-nosed principalist… who unconditionally upholds classical law.

However, he was an ambitious man who tried to take over the family by amassing a lot of wealth in return for selling indulgences behind the scenes.

As a result, even the sins of the demon that could never be forgiven were forgiven.

“….”

Dolores staggered back in shock at the realization of her father’s identity.

It could not be easily accused of being a heresy or a cult.

It was as if a sore within the family had festered and grown into a terrifying tumor.

[Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho! And I am innocent, for I have received a pardon for all my sins directly from your Rune Order… Huh!?]

But Dantalian could no longer smirk at Dolores.

For a single blade tore open two of his flapping mouths in quick succession.

“ …When dealing with demons.”

Night Hound. Vikir plucked a long tongue from the mouth of Dantalian’s third face and held it in his hand.

“Don’t play with the tongue.”

At the same time, Vikir yanked the tongue out and slashed it across the Third Face’s face with an awl.

[Ouch!]

Dantalian screamed again.

It gaped at the remaining faces.

The tongues, stained purple, were sharp as blades.

However, the speed at which Vikir wielded the magic sword Beelzebub was much faster.

…Clang, clang, clang!

The sword, quenched with malice and forged with hatred, spewed out a red-hot trail.

Dantalian cried out in horror as faces exploded one after another.

[You, you wretch, how dare you point your sword at me!]

Then, the first face that Dantalian recognized turned to look at Vikir.

It was an old woman with a gentle, warm smile.

Who says you can’t spit on a face that smiles in its sleep?

But.

…Boom!

Vikir sliced the old woman’s face in two with a relentless blow.

The grandfather’s face followed suit.

[What a bastard!]

Dantalian gritted his teeth and pulled out a new face.

It was the face of a pretty woman, a young actress whose stock was rising these days.

However.

…Boom!

Vikir swung his sword relentlessly this time.

No matter what face appeared behind him, the result was the same.

…Clang! …clang! …clang! …clang! …clang! …clang! …clang! …clang!

A bright child, a sexy woman, an old, helpless man…, all of their faces had become a side dish for the sword.

At this point, Dantalian is rather bewildered.

His faces are skinned from the faces of real people, and he can recreate their expressions and voices.

How is it that this creature in front of him can’t even be moved like a grain of rice?

[You inhuman creature, I am more human than you!]

“….”

Vikir ignored Dantalian’s words and struck again.

…Pfft!

Blood splashed in a sickening black-green color, and Dantalian staggered backward.

The spears of his tongue, his primary weapon, were much reduced in number.

New faces were regenerating, but Vikir was much faster at destroying them.

‘I had enough of them before the regression. I’m not going to get the same amount of them twice.’

The Face of a Thousand Faces The faces and voices of Dantalian mimics are nothing but mimics.

In his previous life, Vikir realized this only after losing many of his comrades.

So there was no reason or room for guilt at this moment.

“Keep your neck open.”

Vikir stepped forward, brushing the foul blood from his sword.

Then a sickening grin crossed the rest of the Dantalian’s faces.

[Ho ho ho! So this is a fellow who doesn’t care much for others, then how about this?]

Suddenly, all of Dantalian’s faces began to change in unison.

They belonged to boys and girls under the age of thirteen.

They were the faces of the children of the orphanage.

Vikir replied in a dry voice.

“I’ve smashed the faces of many children before, do you think I’ll do it again now?”

[Ho ho ho! Of course it won’t work on you].

“…!”

The words stopped Vikir in his tracks for a moment.

That’s right.

Dantalian wasn’t messing with Vikir’s mind right now, but with the mind of Dolores behind him.

St. Dolores had been volunteering here for years now, caring for many children.

Some of them she’d bonded with, others she’d adopted to good homes and never saw again.

…But it wasn’t.

None of those kids went to a good place.

Because they were all ‘here’.

[Awww! Sis! I missed you!]

[Sis! Help me! It hurts so much!]

[Sis! Sis! Sis! Sis! Get me out of here!]

[It hurts, sis! Hmph – ugh – I was wrong!]

Countless faces bloomed over Dantalian’s body like a bouquet of flowers in a vase.

The children from the orphanage that Dolores had met every weekend since she was a freshman in her first year at the academy until she became the student council president in her third year.

As they groaned and cried out in unison, Vikir was silent for a moment.

She was sure she wouldn’t fall for this kind of emotional manipulation.

But Dolores, saint of the Rune Order, paragon of all, lover of all the less fortunate?

Vikir shifted, feeling a vague sense of unease.

And jerked his head back.

“…!”

Behind the mask, Vikir’s eyes widened slightly.

Then a dry voice scratched his throat.

“…Indeed. A hero is a hero.”

At the same time.

…Pow!

An intense flash of white light pierced him in the eye.

[Kkeuheug!?]

Dantalian stumbled backwards as the heat scorched his body.

Cheeeeeeeek……

Burning black smoke rose from the body exposed to the bright light.

Then, Dolores’s voice drifted out of the white haze of light.

Extremely calm, yet bubbling with anger hotter than lava.

“…You touched something you shouldn’t have.”

That was the voice.

And the moment he heard her ‘awakened’ voice.

…Creepy!

Vikir felt a weak shudder.

The battlefield before the regression, when all was lost.

The last spark of hope, the ray of light that always managed to pull off a miraculous reversal, even in the midst of despair when the odds seemed tilted against them.

For a brief moment, I felt a nostalgic sense of the second coming of Dolores, the Saint of Steel, humanity’s last hero.

Chapter 163

Sin and Punishment (3)

◆

[Aaah! Sis! I’m scared!]

[Brother! Help me!]

[Someone help me!]

The crying faces of the children.

Dantalian must have collected the faces of the children as they tried to escape the orphanage.

Vikir remembered a strange code of conduct he’d seen a while back.

It was probably meant to frighten the children to prevent them from running away, and to ensure that no one would reach out to the children who did.

And knowing all of this, Dolores was able to summon up an intensity of holy fire that she had never been able to muster before.

…Grumble!

A pure white flame began to engulf Dantalian’s entire body.

[Aaah!?]

Dantalian writhed as his flesh burned.

However, Dolores was unable to see the scene.

“Bad… of all evil… you bastard!”

There’s not much swearing she can do.

Her vision is blurred by the tears streaming from her eyes.

She lowered her head, unable to meet the eyes of the children suffering in the flames.

Her innate divine power was immense, but she hadn’t yet acquired the practical experience to manifest it efficiently.

…But there was a veteran hand to make up for it.

Bam!

Vikir. The Night Hound bared its razor-sharp teeth again, slicing through a chunk of Dantalian flesh.

‘This is an opportunity.’

Dantalian is engulfed in Dolores’ flames, and the pain of the burning is terrible.

At this moment, if he slowly sliced through Dantalian’s body, he had a chance.

…Whoosh!

A fiery aura exploded from the tip of Vikir’s sword.

The sticky liquid aura that symbolized the Gradient Superlative had now become almost solid.

[Hmph!? How dare you on a mortal being!]

Dantalian stood up, his body burning with white flames, and drew out his purple tongues.

Boom! Clang! Clang!

Vikir’s sword and Dantalian’s tongues clashed fiercely.

Dozens of blows were exchanged in the blink of an eye.

But the skilled Vikir was no match for Dantalian’s demonic speed, and he continued to attack.

Ta-ang!

Vikir felt his knuckles crack as Dantalian’s tongue slammed down on his back.

‘…Surely stronger than Andromalius.’

Andromalius, who was in the body of Seth Le Baskerville, was also a very high level demon of the Demon King class.

The difference was that back then, the knights of the House Baskerville had fought together, and Hugo Le Baskerville had been the one to finish him off.

However, Vikir, who was now fighting Dantalian one-on-one, had a reliable ally.

“Night Hound, please step aside!”

Dolores formed a barrier of white flames in her hands.

Vikir, who had swung his sword without blinking or taking a breath during the high-speed exchange of blows, was able to step back behind the barrier and recover.

Sizzle, sizzle, sizzle…

A white heat that consumed the darkness, sending Dantalian into the distance.

But Dantalian was in no mood for impatience.

[Ho, ho, ho! No human has ever pushed me like this before. Interesting, indeed].

“Interesting? Let’s see if you can say that before you get fucked.”

[Fucked? You mean you’re going to kill me now? Ho, ho, ho. That’s a lot of balls. Yeah.]

Dantalian pulled one of the gentleman’s mustachioed faces forward, and then said softly.

[Aye. All humans believe they are special. Chosen. Unique. A hero who can kill demons and bring peace to the world. A protagonist. Something like that.]

His face soon changes into that of a seductive woman.

Then it changed to that of an innocent child, then that of a stubborn man, then that of a fierce old man.

A thousand faces. It was indeed a transformation worthy of Dantalian’s face.

[But no, everyone in the world is special. Everyone is a hero, a lover, a fool, a villain. They’re all protagonists, and they all have their own stories to tell].

At the same time, Dantalian exhaled a thick black mist from his mouth.

The mist filled the entire room in an instant, like smoke from a fire.

Flutter.

Three unpleasant objects fell in front of Vikir and Dolores, who stepped back.

They were dull leather sacks, similar to the ones that Ephebo, Hebe, Pedo, and Geronto had once worn over their faces.

The leftmost sack wriggled.

…Gasp!

Black blood stirred on the surface of the thin leather sack.

And then.

…Thud! … thud! … thud!

The three leather sacks began their mad rampage.

Their ominous flailing was like the sacks covering a condemned man’s face as he wriggles on the brink of death.

Dantalian smiled with satisfaction, as if he had already seen inside the sack.

[…Now, shall we hear your story?]

◆

In the dense fog.

Dolores looked around for Dantalian, who had disappeared behind the fog.

“What is this fog? It doesn’t disappear even with divine power.”

“…Be careful.”

Vikir had faced Dantalian before.

His attack patterns were somewhat predictable.

Then, he saw one of the three black sacks floating in the air open wide.

Vikir spoke in a dry voice.

“That is the ‘Sack of Shame’ carried by Dantalian the Face Collector.”

“…?”

Dolores scratched her head.

The sack of shame turned toward Dolores and pulled something out of it.

Dolores’s expression instantly turned to horror as she saw what was inside.

“Ouch! What?”

It was Dolores herself who emerged from the sack.

[….]

The fake Dolores looks at him with an expressionless face.

Vikir calmly explained.

“The Sack of Shame causes the target to make a face of shame. It’s a mental attack by bringing their most shameful memories to life.”

So what I’m about to see is a recreation of one of Dolores’ most humiliating memories in her life.

It’s a terrifying technique that not only breaks down the bond between colleagues in an instant, but also makes you lose your composure.

…But?

Shhh-

After walking out of the sack of shame, Dolores didn’t do much.

The only thing she did was pee her pants ….

“….”

“….”

Vikir and Dolores shut their mouths at the same time, as if they had made a pact.

“I’m dead!”

Dolores immediately unleashed a burst of white flames that blew away the sack of shame.

[Ack!? What the hell, how did you overcome the face of shame so easily?!!]

Dantalian’s bewildered cry could be heard from beyond the fog.

Apparently, overcoming this illusion would damage the demon beyond.

And then. The next sack came to life and opened its gaping mouth at Dolores.

Vikir’s expression hardened.

“Next, the ‘Sack of Fear’. It causes the opponent to make a face of fear.”

In other words, you bring out the face that scares them the most.

The thing that emerged from the sack of fear stood before Dolores.

It was a middle-aged man with a stern expression.

Vikir recognized his face at once.

“Cardinal Humbert!”

The godfather of the Old Order and Dolores’s biological father.

Dolores’ expression stiffened as Humbert’s face appeared.

“Oh, my father…”

He was so flustered, he couldn’t even speak.

[Dolores, why are you out here at this hour? Have you done your homework?]

Cardinal Humbert stares down at Dolores in a commanding manner.

The whip in his hand was making her pupils dilate uncontrollably.

“That, that….”

Dolores breaks out in a cold sweat, but she can’t meet Humbert’s gaze.

Just then.

A snap.

There was a blow that blew Cardinal Humbert’s head off.

Vikir. He had intervened in Dolores’s memory.

“…The illusion is only an illusion. There is nothing to fear.”

At the sound of Vikir’s voice, Dolores let out the breath she’d been holding.

A cold sweat trickled down her cheeks and onto her chin.

“S-sorry. I don’t have a good relationship with my father. For a moment, I forgot that it was an illusion.”

“…Understands.”

Vikir nodded, not asking any further questions.

There was only one sack left.

“…That is the Sack of Love.”

Dolores nodded at Vikir’s words.

At this point, I know what to expect. Perhaps the face of his beloved.

But even for Dolores, it was hard to predict exactly what face she would find.

She couldn’t remember a time in her life when she could say with confidence that she had ever loved someone.

Sure, he’d been guided by the Rune Order’s law of “love your neighbor,” but Dantalian’s “love” wouldn’t be that “love.”

And then.

Tsutsutsutsuts…

What emerged from the sack of love began to take shape.

It was a man dressed in some sort of black robe.

A black cloak covered his body, a top hat covered his head, and a grotesque mask shaped like a stork’s beak covered his face.

It was the Night Hound.

“….”

“….”

For a moment, there was an awkward silence between Vikir and Dolores.

“Is this …?”

“Oh, no, that sack is weird, it drives people crazy!”

Vikir slowly turned his head, and Dolores threw up her hands in frustration.

Just then, from beyond the fog, Dantalian’s sneer could be heard.

[Ho-ho-ho! My sack is honest, even more so than yours, and will pick up on the smallest emotion you have hidden in the deepest recesses of your heart and bring it out, even if you didn’t know it!]

Dolores’s face turned bright red at those words, like a confirmation.

“Wait! You’re wrong, I swear! …No, not really, but anyway, I never thought of that…!”

“….”

Once again, Vikir said nothing.

He simply drew his sword and engaged the Night Hound before him.

Bang, bang, bang!

Backed by the holy flame of a saint, Vikir easily drove his sword into the Night Hound’s body, dispersing it into a handful of mist.

“Fortunately, it doesn’t seem to be able to replicate the power of its body.”

That was probably because Dantalian hadn’t yet drawn on his magic reserves.

For when they had met in the Age of Destruction, before the regression, Dantalian had been able to recreate his opponent’s face in his memory, and even his strength.

Vikir felt fortunate to have found Dantalian so soon.

Meanwhile.

“….”

St. Dolores stirred, unable to speak.

Vikir pondered for a moment what he should say to her.

…Clunk!

The three sacks began to move again.

[Ho-ho-ho-ho I didn’t really expect much from a saint, I mean, what kind of a punk would have a past like that].

“….”

[However, I do expect something from you,]]

Dantalian’s words were aimed squarely at Vikir.

A demonic technique that could draw out and manifest a target’s shameful memories, fears, and love ones.

It was now unfolding against Vikir.

Coming up.

Tsutsutsutsuts…

The first, the Sack of Shame, has begun to sift through Vikir’s memories and recreate them in the present.

Next.

Landscapes and objects began to materialize in the mist.

“…Huck!?”

It was enough to make Dolores gasp.

[…Er?]

Even Dantalian, the creator of the illusion, was at a loss for words.

A sky stained black. A mountain of corpses. Rivers of blood.

The center of a world where everything has been destroyed.

A single tall pillar stood above the horrifyingly barren ground.

Dolores’s gaze naturally traveled to the top of the pillar.

And soon, the ‘something’ at the top of the pillar imprinted itself deeply on her retinas.

A head.

A severed head, laid out in a grotesque display.

Chapter 167

Sin and Punishment (8)

◆

The Old Order priests protest to Dolores.

“Saint, did you even realize what you were doing?”

“The deceased Quilt was a devout member of this Church, how dare you read from his letters during his lifetime!”

“It is even a conversation with Cardinal Humbert, and it is confidential, confidential!”

“How dare you release such a thing to the public…!?”

They seemed afraid of losing the credit to the New Order priests.

They say that a crisis is an opportunity, and in a situation like this, healing the sick and comforting the victims is a way to strengthen an image.

So the Old Order priests were eager to get to work on disaster recovery.

This is why Dolores, Mozgus, and other New Order priests complained that they were being prevented from doing so.

…But their complaints were short-lived.

“Quiet.”

They froze in their seats as Dolores’s cold gaze met theirs.

It was the first time they had ever seen such a cold, piercing gaze from the normally warm and compassionate woman.

It was frightening to see someone so gentle when they were angry.

Dolores’s single line brought the Old Order priests to a standstill.

And her next recitation had them all turning blue in the face.

“Baron Gorg, murder of a groom who resisted while exercising his right to first night, subsequent suicide of the bride, heavily punishment of the family, resulting in the destruction of the family, pardoned by the payment of a billion gold in donation!”

“Viscountess Moscoe, fraudulently getting her sons hired at the Imperial Central Bank and promoting them up the ranks, resulting in many job candidates with passing grades being rejected due to her sons rushing in! Pardoned with a 200 million gold donation per son!”

“Mr. Guerrasso! Embezzlement, dishonesty, and manipulation of the stock price to the detriment of shareholders to the tune of nearly 20 billion gold! Pardoned with a 50 million gold donation!”

“Madame Pierre! Kidnapping and imprisoning underage boys with nowhere else to go, sexually exploiting them, and forcing them into illegal labor! Pardoned with an donation of 15 million gold!”

“Cult leader Manimani! Intentionally spreading the plague to all corners of the country and paralyzing the local economy! Pardoned with 100 million gold in donations!”

.

.

The full extent of Quilt’s indulgence was revealed.

A long list of grave sins that could never be forgiven as they were.

And the sums paid for them were often paltry and inadequate to the crime.

Inquisition.

How can someone wear the clothes of a saint while wearing a human mask and forgive something like this?

Even the protesting Old Order priests could hardly believe their ears.

“He sold indulgences to demons like that?”

“For that price? No way. There must have been four or five zeros missing.”

“Especially cult leader Manimani, who deserves to be burned at the stake.”

“I can’t believe Cardinal Humbert and Lord Quilt could do such a despicable thing! There is such a thing as an indulgence!”

“Ha, but the seal on that letter must be….”

The chatter wasn’t just coming from the Old Order priests.

The agitation spread beyond the people of the Quovadis to the general public.

“How could the Quovadis do this!”

“What a corruption of devotional chant!”

“Calm down! That’s an Old Order problem! It has nothing to do with the New Order priests!”

“Don’t lump the Old Order priests in with this! It’s only a problem with a few of them!”

The chatter intensifies.

The priests were about to get into a fistfight among themselves.

In the midst of the chaos, Dolores finished reading the materials the Night Hound had delivered.

It detailed the dealings of Quilt and Humbert, the ugly realities of what was supposed to be society’s leadership, how the offerings to the gods had been used as investments, how they had been siphoned off for political funding and illegal lobbying, and even how they had colluded with local cults.

There was also evidence of the sale of farming tools such as pitchforks, wood chips, sticks, and even pig bones as holy relics.

The number of holy relics sold had already exceeded 30,000, with propaganda and plans to exempt one year of purgatory for each relic.

The public was shocked to learn about all of this.

“….”

The Academy’s boy and girl reporters also stopped taking notes and looked dumbfounded.

The horrific molestation of the Faithful Quovadis had been revealed by a young saint from the same Quovadis family.

In response, Dolores launches into a retort that has kept her up all night.

“I, Dolores of the New Order, reply to these atrocities of the Old Order as follows!”

Once again, the pens of the crowd straightened.

Whispers echoed through the notepads.

Screenshots of mana floated around the room, their flashes popping.

Dolores began her speech in a steady voice.

“First, when our Lord and Teacher, Rune, says ‘repent,’ he means that the entire life of the faithful must be repented! Second, these words cannot be understood as sacramental penance to Rune, that is, confession and absolution performed by the priest in his office. … Fifth, the Pope has neither the power nor the will to pardon any punishment other than that imposed by his office or by the authority of canon law. The Pope has no power to pardon any sin except by declaring or acknowledging that it has been pardoned by Rune. … Twenty-seventh: ‘It is only a human theory that the soul is released from purgatory as soon as the money thrown into the almanac makes a clinking sound.’ … Forty-fifth: The Runic religion must be taught that anyone who sees a poor person and passes him by, offering money for indulgences, is not buying a pardon from the Pope, but rather the wrath of Rune! Forty-sixth: Teach the Runes that those who do not have the luxury of abundant wealth are obligated to save what they need for their families and should never squander it on indulgences! …Fifty-first: Teach the Runes that to the many people who have been robbed of their money by certain indulgence preachers, the Pope must pay them back, even if it means selling all the churches of the Order! … Ninety-ninth, to suppress the objections enumerated by the common man, without addressing them with sound reason, but merely by force, is to make the Pope a mockery, and the Runes unhappy! … Ninety-fifth, to make the Runes have more confidence in entering the kingdom of heaven through many sufferings than by comfort!”

She read the rebuttal, which was as many as 95 articles, fluidly and without stuttering a single word.

Her determination was such that even her opponents, the Old Order priests, were moved to silence for a moment.

At the same time, Dolores felt her legs relax.

She was thankful that the flowing white skirt of her priestly robes hid the tremor.

Mozgus, who was beside her, supported her.

“That was an excellent rebuttal, Sister. You’re absolutely right! This Mozgus is deeply moved.”

“…I’m out of my mind.”

Dolores thought of what had happened last night, or rather, this morning.

After the Night Hound’s departure, the energy that had made her body so hard and strong had vanished like a lie.

She spoke cheerfully, recalling her overflowing strength, but in truth it was only a psychological factor; the strength itself had long since disappeared.

‘The Pope once said. A saint can only be awakened when she finds a true soul mate.’

The resonance of the soul, the assimilation of emotions, the resulting explosion of divine power.

In other words, this means that you gain the ability to multiply your power.

How do we make this ‘awakening’ more than a temporary thing, but a permanent one?

Now that the Night Hound is gone, there’s no one to ask and no one to test.

‘The older classical saints often spoke of awakening in the past, and I wish I had listened to them a little more, instead of dismissing them as empty words.’

Dolores still hadn’t figured out why the Night Hound could be her resonance, her ‘awakening condition’.

There is no way for her to know that this is because Vikir is the only veteran who came from the Age of Destruction and knows the true ‘Destruction’.

…Whatever.

The man chosen by Rune.

At this point, only he is worthy of being her ‘soul mate’.

Dolores raised her head once more at this.

Then he spoke in a low voice.

“‘The Night Hound’. I must see him again.”

At that moment.

…Poof! … poof! … poof!

The sound of a mana screenshot exploding behind her.

Dolores spun around in surprise to find a crowd of reporters who had somehow gotten this close.

The reporters rushed forward and spoke in unison.

“The Holy Lady has declared a ‘holy war’ against the Night Hound!”

Chapter 169

Adorable Pet (2)

◆

“….”

Vikir closed his eyes.

He remembered a former enemy he had once fought for his life.

Danger Rating : S

Size: ?

Found in: Le Rouge Et Le Noir Mountain, 10th Ridge

-Nicknamed ‘Madame of the Depth’. Her full species name is unknown.

In the distant past, the most terrible beings that inhabited the depths of the Oil Pole Hell were spiders of immense size, and it is believed that Madam Eight-Legs is a distant descendant that retains the form of those giant spiders that lived in the ancient past.

The inside of its body is filled with disgusting poison, and its mesh, which is stronger than steel, cannot be cut by anything except the hellfire of the world.

It is a dangerous, supremely powerful beast that has nearly killed Vikir himself several times in battle.

This giant queen spider found it difficult to deal with even the ancient demons that ruled Hell, so they secured an independent space for them to live in a corner of the depths of the abyss.

…And now, before Vikir’s eyes, is the last descendant of that dreadful spider…

[Kwi-ing- kyung-]

Vikir’s hand rubs against his cheek, a round ball of dust.

It sits or walks on two legs that sprout from its shaggy fur like crude doodles.

‘Madame’s… cub?’

Madame’s cub, or Baby Madam.

The tiny, insignificant creature was currently nuzzling the back of Vikir’s hand, smearing white saliva on it.

The way he was acting, he looked like a puppy.

“…Is it because the wolf carried it when it was an egg?”

This is why they say prenatal care is so important.

I could understand, at least a little bit, why pregnant women are given foreign language lessons and classical music while their babies are still in the womb.

Then.

Sticky.

Vikir noticed something strange.

A white, sticky mucus had begun to form where the cub had just licked.

As it touched the air, it quickly hardened into a fine thread.

“…Is that spider silk? It’s incredibly hard.”

Vikir stretched the silk that the cub spewed from its mouth.

Ordinary spider silk has a much higher tensile strength than the same amount of steel and superior elasticity.

Moreover, this little Madame was the descendant of Madam Eight-Legs, and the web it spewed was the strongest wire ever.

…Boom!

The threads barely snapped after Vikir pulled on them with a considerable amount of aura.

That was the small amount of thread that was pulled out.

“Its elasticity and strength are both dozens of times greater than steel, and it even has adhesive properties….”

It’s also extremely resistant to flame, unlike ordinary spider silk, which would melt helplessly in a fire.

‘I know. I wouldn’t have been able to break this web without Cerberus’s hellfire either.’

Vikir thought, remembering his battle with Madam Eight-Legs.

[Kkiing- kkuing- hegheg!]

Meanwhile, the cub continues to nuzzle against the back of Vikir’s hand.

Maybe it’s because its mother isn’t around, but it seems to be craving affection from someone it hasn’t seen before.

Vikir suddenly felt sorry for the little one.

‘Your mother was a terrifying creature.’

The thought of that voracious appetite for the eggs she had laid made him realize that it would be far better for the cub to be separated from its mother.

…Whatever.

Because of the first impression, the cub follows Vikir the first time it wakes up from the egg.

Then.

Khororok.

The cub laid down on the back of Vikir’s hand with a sullen expression.

“…Are you hungry?”

[Haeg-haeg-haeg-]

A puff of black dust, sulking.

It looks like a baker’s accidentally burnt choux.

‘What should I feed him, anyway?’

Should I feed him insects? Or meat?

Vikir pulled a few biscuits from a drawer, a chunk of salted ham, and a slice of spinach pie that had gone cold.

They were all things Pigi had bought for a midnight snack and shared with Vikir.

But.

[Omnomnomnom…]

The cub hadn’t really enjoyed the biscuits and ham.

It was just a polite nibble out of courtesy.

Even the spinach pie was gagged and spit out as soon as I put it in its mouth.

“…That’s a picky eater.”

Vikir made the pup climb onto the back of his left hand.

Boom!

It perched itself on the back of Vikir’s hand like a wristwatch.

Two legs wrapped around his wrist and held him there, like an impermanent watch.

“Good. Let’s go find your prey.”

Vikir immediately set out to visit the dormitories.

But there weren’t many places to go.

First, the library. A good place to get information.

Vikir left the dormitory and headed across the field to the library.

Passing through the large, park-like main entrance of the library and entering the lobby, he was immediately drawn to the vast stacks of books that Colosseo Academy boasts.

Endless rows of tall bookshelves were densely packed with books of all kinds.

Vikir went to the Nature, Creatures, and Monsters section and started looking for a book.

“Spiders… spiders… a g….”

As Vikir scanned the shelves one by one.

“Aah! Vikir!”

He sees two round eyes peeking through the gap in the opposite bookshelf.

He turns his head to see what it is, and sees a white-haired girl looking back at him, smiling brightly.

Sinclaire.

She strode forward, rounded the corner of the bookcase, and walked toward Vikir.

She looked like an innocent puppy, and if she had a tail, it would be wagging furiously by now.

“I’ve never seen you come to the library before.”

“Mmm. I come often. Though this is the first time I’ve met you.”

“Are you here to study or check out books?”

Sinclaire wore a badge on her chest that identified her as a librarian.

Vikir was pleased.

“Do you happen to have any books on spiders?”

“Oh, you want to know how to kill a spider? That’s what comes up when you search for pest extermination! What, there’s a spider in your room?”

Hmm. Spiders do come up, but….

Just then, Vikir felt his left wrist twitch.

[Arring…… ]

The cub’s eyebrows were furrowed in a crudely drawn scrawl, giving it an angry look.

It even made a sound to make itself seem threatening.

Vikir corrected her question with a flick of his wrist.

“I’m trying to figure out how to breed spiders, not exterminate them.”

“Oh, spider breeding? There are books on the subject. Do you want to get one? Do you like spiders?”

“I don’t really like them….”

Vikir was about to reply nonchalantly, but stopped and looked down at his left wrist for a moment.

There, he sees a burnt piece of bread looking up at him with pleading eyes.

“…But I think it’s about to get better.”

“Really? You like spiders, brother… that’s interesting.”

Sinclaire looks back at Vikir with a curious expression.

Her questioning continued until she found a book on how to raise spiders.

“Why do you like spiders? Because they have hair? Because they have legs? Because they have eyes? What about centipedes and millipedes and grimas and scorpions? What about beetles? Do you like all kinds of insects? Oh, no, spiders aren’t insects.”

What a curious girl, Vikir thought.

‘I don’t think she’s always been this chatty.’

It was a bit of a surprise, as she was usually a quiet, studious person.

Soon, Vikir borrowed a few books and went out to a quiet place.

“…Let’s see. How to raise spiders.”

Vikir slowly flipped through the pages.

“Temperature and moisture control is important… they are sensitive to mold… they need no light… be careful when taking off their shedding skin… molting time varies from individual to individual… toilet training requires patience and repetition… they are easily influenced by their surroundings, so take care of them from the time they are eggs… for larger spiders, it is good manners to wear a muzzle when walking….”

It’s all very common sense and common knowledge.

“Hmmm. If it says to give small insects or pieces of meat for baby food, why isn’t this one eating?”

Vikir looked down at the cub on his left wrist and scratched his head.

Tsk-tsk.

Even now, the cub was slumped in a sullen pose.

Then.

Vikir turned the page of the last book and saw something.

Some ‘extraordinary’ spiders, the stuff of mythology, were raised on ‘poison’ during their infancy.

“…Eating poison?”

Vikir flipped to the back page.

For young spiders with great blood, the outcome depends on what poison they’ve ingested throughout their lives.

Only a large and varied intake of strong poisons can lead to a great adult spider.

On the other hand, if only weak poisons or poisons of limited variety are consumed consistently, there seems to be a limit to how large one can grow no matter how much he or she consumes.

“I wonder if it feeds on poison.”

Vikir jumped into action.

He bites down on his pinky finger to draw blood, and black droplets ooze out.

It was blood laced with the powerful poison of Madam Eight-Legs.

However.

[Ex-whack-]

The Baby Madam, who had a drop of blood in its mouth, trembled and fell to the side again.

“You bastard. What’s wrong this time?”

Vikir turned the pages of the book again.

However, when the hatchlings have just emerged from the egg, they should be given the weakest poison first.

As the spider grows older and larger and ingests stronger and more varied poisons, it develops a poison that combines the strengths of many poisons into one, and it soon reigns supreme in its local ecosystem.

“…Yes, the mother’s poison is strong.”

Madam Eight-Legs’ poison was certainly unlike anything I’d ever seen before.

It was a powerful acid that contained all the worst qualities of neurotoxins, hemorrhagic, dermal, muscular, gastrointestinal, stinking, painful, respiratory, and protoplasmic poisons.

The poison was certainly too much for the hatchling to digest.

“I see. I’ll get you a milder poison, but until then, you’ll have to eat an insect.”

Vikir catches one of the butterflies in the air, and the hatchling pops it into its mouth, whimpering.

Although it was given to by the master, it’s obvious that it’s unappetizing.

Just then.

“Vikir! Are you here!?”

Pigi’s voice came from far away.

Vikir looked up and saw Pigi running towards him.

Pigi had a newspaper in his hand.

“Vikir, you’re in trouble!”

“How did you know I was here?”

“How could I? You’re always in your dorm, classroom, club room, library, cafeteria, and gym, but that’s not the point… Did you see this!?”

Pigi cleared his throat and shoved the newspaper article in front of Vikir’s eyes.

“You’re a fucking star now!”

Chapter 171

The Anti-Columnist (2)

◆

[Exclusive] Evil beyond measure, ‘Night Hound’ / Views: 3,872

-The Hound of the Night has crossed the line. The crimes against the imperial family and the Seven Houses have reached the heavens… Turning yourself in right now and waiting to be hanged may be your last chance for a peaceful end!

?(Hot Class 1st year student): The country is going well….

??(Cold Class 1st year student): ?? I think we need to arrest the Night Hound quickly? What is the imperial family doing?

??(Cold Class 2nd year student): How busy must you be in this time? What is the imperial family? Is it your friend’s house? These days, things are getting out of hand.

??(Hot Class 4th year student): Both,, my,, classmates,,, hate,, the,, night,, hound,, this,,!

??(Cold Class 4th year student): That’s right~~^^*

??(Hot Class 1st year student): Ugh, the comment box smells like an old man;;;

??(Cold Class 3rd year student): Good article,, spreads~~^^ always~~happy~~?

??(Hot Class 1st year student): By the way, who wrote this column, did you see the Night Hound yourself?

.

.

Vikir was a little surprised when he saw the newspaper this morning.

‘I can’t believe they actually published that column.’

Vikir was a little surprised to see the column in the paper this morning.

I was surprised that it got a lot of views and comments.

‘…The fear of the Night Hound is spreading, isn’t it?’

I’ve heard that in the Imperial Capital these days, many parents say, “If you keep crying, the Night Hound will bite you!” when soothing their crying children.

Apparently, he’s established himself as a villain who terrorizes the empire.

‘I’ll have to be more careful when I go demon hunting in the future.’

It would be troublesome to run into the Imperial Knights while wandering outside the Academy.

Vikir was thinking about his future plans.

“Vikir.”

A cold voice called out.

Vikir looks up, and Professor Banshee Morgue’s dark-circled gaze follows him.

“Did you close your eyes again today, lost in thought, and not just focus?”

“Yes. Yes.”

“Still brazen, I see. I’ll have to see if you have what it takes.”

Professor Banshee, as always, did not like Vikir.

So he threw in a few petty offenses, like giving him a pun question that he purposely twisted so that he couldn’t solve it, or a super-difficult question that was beyond the grasp of an undergraduate.

“The Imperial Army has been plagued by a massive outbreak of super-sized pinworms during the rainy season on the Western Front. Tell me how to deal with the smaller ones, which are less than a meter long, and the larger ones, which are more than 10 meters long.”

“Travelers are being attacked by goblins. Goblins are small, weak creatures, but their swarming behavior makes them a threat to those without access to mana. Discuss a realistic plan to prevent travelers from being attacked by goblins at the gates of the Imperial Capital.”

“The monster that currently causes the most damage to the knights and mages guarding the highland fortress is the wyvern, but it is also quite true that it is the opposite of impossible to say that it is not.What do you think?”

…The problem is that Vikir has never been wrong about such things.

“Smaller species, less than a meter long, can be mortally wounded by a sprinkling of salt, sugar, or carbonic acid, while larger ones can be easily repelled by shooting copper arrows.”

“Goblins have a sensitive sense of smell and are weak to bad smells. If a ginkgo tree planted as a street tree drops fruit, rather than throwing it away, it would be a good idea to collect it and provide a bag each to travelers leaving the Imperial Capital. If you throw ginkgo nuts at a goblin, most of them will lose their will to fight and run away due to the bad smell.”

“Yes.”

Vikir answered, always nonchalant in the face of Professor Banshee’s aggressive barrage of questions.

There were two reasons for this. The first was that Professor Banshee’s major classes were always related to actual monster strategy. This was Vikir’s specialty for the past several decades, so he couldn’t be wrong.

Therefore, it is possible that he could come up with groundbreaking strategies that would complement or even replace decades of outdated research.

The second was Prof. Banshee’s questioning style.

While Vikir’s attention-seeking personality would allow him to get away with whatever he wanted, Professor Banshee would deduct the entire department’s attitude points for students who failed to answer his questions or got them wrong.

In other words, since Vikir was targeted by Professor Banshee, he had to keep fending off his attacks for the sake of the attitude score of the entire Cold Class.

Vikir decided that solving the problem well and earning extra points toward his overall attitude score would make him less noticeable to other students, because people remember grudges long and forget favors quickly.

This is because people remember the punishment they receive from others for a long time, but the reward they receive from others is quickly forgotten.

Meanwhile.

“….”

Prof. Banshee couldn’t help but feel angry that his questioning attack had been cut short.

Vikir’s answers were the sort of thing that only a war veteran who had spent decades on the battlefield could give, so he couldn’t be too quick to point them out.

How could a mere 18-year-old freshman know things that even he, a professor at the academy, could only theoretically understand from his desk in the lab?

And not just like that.

Professor Banshee couldn’t help but frown even more as some of the answers Vikir had just given included strategies and theories that had never been discovered before.

‘Keu…… It was like that in the past during the Venompion incident.’

A giant scorpion-like demon living in the desert.

Who knew it had a second, hidden stinger.

Professor Banshee had once sent a sample of the Venompion to the Royal Institute of Magical Creatures to determine whether or not Vikir’s claims were true, and it had all turned out to be true.

He waved off the flood of interview requests.

‘It wasn’t my research, it was my student’s research. Phew!’

Ever since then, Prof. Banshee has been watching Vikir with interest.

In the end, Professor Banshee had no choice but to recognize Vikir’s intelligence.

“You’re so good, you’re so good, you know enough theory that you could stand here and teach your classmates, your seniors, … maybe even me.”

“Not quite.”

Professor Banshee’s expression twists once more at Vikir’s short answer.

Finally, he growled.

“I hope you go to graduate school someday, and if you do, you’ll come under my wing….”

For the first time, Vikir felt a chill at those words.

The Academy’s graduate school had a reputation for being insanely rigorous.

There is even a rumor that prisoners of war from other countries who lost the war and became slaves feel sorry for the academy’s graduate students.

The first-year students, however, don’t know that yet, and their eyes widen as they look back at Vikir.

Not only was he recognized for his theory by Professor Banshee, but he was even recommended to go to graduate school!

That was harder than getting a camel to go through the eye of a needle.

“….”

Sinclaire, the head of the Hot Class, who had been sitting in the front row, was now staring at Vikir openly, not even hiding.

His eyes glowed with curiosity.

◆

After class.

Vikir joined the crowd of students grabbing their backpacks and heading to their next class or dorm.

But there was one person who stood in his way.

Professor Banshee Morgue, the professor of Practical Monster Strategy.

“Vikir.”

He called out to Vikir in a hard voice, with just the slightest hint of displeasure in his tone.

When Vikir turned his head, he strode over and spoke with a gnarled, twisted mouth.

“Your last column, I mean. In the newspaper.”

Professor Banshee is an advisor to the newspaper.

He was the one who had published Vikir’s commentary on The Night Hound in the paper.

Prof. Banshee asked, genuinely curious.

“Did you really see the Night Hound yourself during your volunteer work?”

“It’s exactly as I told you last time. I was walking down the hallway at night, and I just happened to catch a glimpse, a quick glimpse.”

“So you really don’t know its face or voice or anything like that?” …

“Yes.”

“I see, then.”

Professor Banshee frowned and quietly muttered, ‘It’s because things like flies keep sticking to me.’

Then he looked at Vikir and continued.

“If any of the outside reporters are bothering you with requests for interviews, tell them to tell me. I have a duty to protect the students of the Academy’s newspaper.”

“Yes.”

Professor Banshee nodded at Vikir’s short answer.

“…Ah, wait.”

Just as he was about to turn away, Professor Banshee turned his head as if he’d just remembered something.

“Well, if you were doing community service, that would have been during sleeping hours and curfew, so why were you walking down the hallway at night, and that’s not in the direction of the restrooms or water dispensers.”

“I’m sorry.”

“…Sorry, is that it?”

“Yes.”

Vikir replied, still keeping it short.

Professor Banshee frowned.

“ …Well, I do know that it’s customary for boys and girls to get together for a drinking party on the last day of service.”

“Is that so?”

“Yes. But it doesn’t oblige me to condone such things, does it?”

“I see.”

Professor Banshee held up the ledger with a stern gesture and deducted one point from Vikir’s attitude score.

“ …From now on, do not roam at night.”

No more roaming around at night for the Night Hound.

Vikir nodded half-heartedly, and Professor Banshee then snorted happily and turned and went on his way.

Only then did the friends who had been watching from afar approach.

Pigi was the first to approach.

“Vikir, did you just lose an attitude point? Why?”

“For breaking the night curfew on the last day of volunteering.”

“Ugh! You’re crazy! Did you really tell me that? You’re lying! If you get another demerit here, you’ll have to do community service again, but this time it’ll be on campus….”

Nowadays, the academy’s principal has decided not to send students to community service because of the current situation.

Instead, they would be put in the unfortunate position of having to do in-school service during the golden festival after the midterms.

That’s what Pigi was feeling right now.

Tudor and Sancho came up behind him.

“Hey, Vikir, what did Professor Banshee say?”

“At least there would have been an argument.”

They were on the same newspaper staff as Vikir, and they already knew that the column was written by Vikir.

Tudor opened his mouth.

“Hey, Vikir. Did you really see the Night Hound that time?”

“Yes.”

“Dude, why didn’t you tell me about it? You were so serious the whole way back that day.”

Tudor stepped forward with a serious expression and patted Vikir on the shoulder.

“You must have been terrified to meet that vile villain, and I was hoping it was because you kept falling behind on your way back to the Academy on your last day of service, and you peed yourself because you were thinking too much.”

“If that happens in the future, you should come to us with your problems.”

Sancho nodded as he stood next to Vikir.

Meanwhile, his friends asked Vikir.

They wanted to know what the Night Hound looked like and how terrifying it was.

Vikir gave a quick answer.

“It’s very tall and well-built. His face is masked and his entire body is covered in a black cloak. His voice was hoarse. It was hard to hear because he was so far away….”

At that, Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi brushed away the goosebumps on their arms.

“Wow, you must have seen it in real life, that must have been really scary!”

“I don’t think I’d have been able to move from the spot, you’ve got a lot of nerve.”

“The Night Hound is supposed to be at least a Graduator, so how strong is it? Does it outrank the professors, or is it not that strong?”

The day pups were still fluffing up their fur as they howled at each other that they were going to catch the Night Hound.

Vikir watched the scene with a certain amount of fondness.

Just then.

“Look who’s here, aren’t you the idiots from Cold Class?”

Another fluffy one-day puppy steps in front of Vikir.

A handsome man, with a cold face beneath his jet-black hair.

He wears a small snake-like badge on his chest patch.

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi stiffen slightly at the sight of his face.

“…Granola.”

Granola de Leviathan.

A member of House Leviathan, one of the seven most powerful families in the Empire.

It was the appearance of the first-year vice head of the Hot Class and an extremely arrogant first-year student.

Chapter 173

The Anti-Columnist (4)

◆

Dolores.

She read the article in the newspaper, and once again Vikir was in her mind.

The Night Hound crossed the line.

-The Night Hound has crossed the line. Your crimes against the imperial family and the Seven Houses have reached the skies… and your only chance for a peaceful end is to turn yourself in now and be hanged by the neck!

To be honest, it didn’t feel good to see the harsh criticism being thrown at the Night Hounds.

And that bad feeling was made worse when I realized that Vikir, who had taken the time to come and see me, was once again criticizing the Night Hound.

“A villain like the Night Hound will be punished one day.”

Dolores felt a stabbing pain in her chest as she listened to Vikir and the others.

It was even more sad and miserable than when she heard the insults herself.

‘…You’re insulting him because you don’t know what you’re talking about.’

Ordinary people cursing a hero, but I know I can’t blame them.

Like the great prophet Rune, who was crowned with thorns and carried on a stake by the citizens of long ago, the Night Hound also makes this noble sacrifice even at the risk of becoming the target of everyone’s misunderstanding and hostility.

‘It was said that true heroes do not force blood on the public.’

Dolores bit her lip tightly.

Although she could use this opportunity to berate her juniors and proclaim the innocence of the Night Hound, … that would not be what he wanted.

‘It’s okay, not everyone knows the sacrifice of the Night Hound, just me. I just need to be the only one who knows and remembers his sacrifice.’

A gifted genius, a prophet the world doesn’t understand.

Dolores felt something akin to a sense of duty at the realization that only she could understand him.

The ordinary citizen. As the unknowing public disliked, hated, feared, and abhorred the Night Hound.

Dolores’ feelings for the Night Hounds have evolved into affection, respect, longing, and a heartbreaking emotion that even she can’t quite define.

These unexplained feelings grew more and more intense with each passing day, until she was unable to sleep at night.

These days, every day is unfamiliar with emotions she have felt for the first time in her life.

“….”

Dolores let go of the railing and turned around.

She’d come here to see Vikir, but she couldn’t speak to him now because the look on his face would make her angry.

And she’s not even in a position to be angry.

It was not a good time for conversation, so she turned her back on him.

◆

Back in her dorm room, Dolores took a shower and sat down at her desk.

‘Still, Vikir, I have to talk to him.’

Vikir was the only one of the Academy’s students who had seen the Night Hound with his own eyes.

So it was absolutely necessary to hear what he saw that day.

And then another.

“ …I also need to apologize for the pissing incident.”

Vikir is Dolores’s saving grace.

Dolores had made a drunken mistake, and Vikir had taken on the stigma of peeing on her behalf.

It must have been hard for him to say that he was the one who peed in front of everyone.

Although it’s unclear what Vikir was thinking when he sacrificed himself in that situation, he hasn’t asked for anything in return since, so we can only assume it was purely out of the goodness of his heart.

“…Haah, as long as you don’t insult Night Hound, you’re a really good junior.”

Dolores had mixed feelings about Vikir.

At first, he was an arrogant junior that I wasn’t interested in at all, or even hated.

I had thought he was a bit of an oddball when he sang a military song at the freshman talent show and made the old professors cry, but… after that, his image gradually deteriorated due to his frequent tardiness and detentions.

He was warned several times for his seemingly casual approach to rules, such as falling asleep in class and wandering into prohibited areas.

<Vikir-Life Attitude Score (Demerit Factor)

-1 point for using the emergency exit on the 3rd floor of the dormitory building

-1 point for entering the 4th grade private area of the performance hall

-1 point for using the central staircase on the 1st floor of the blind reading lab building

-1 point for entering the control area of ??the experimental monster breeding facility

-1 point for using the central staircase on the 6th floor of the Faculty Research Center

-1 point for using the central staircase on the 3rd floor of the Hot lab.

-1 point for entering the fitness center after hours

-1 point for entering the restricted area next to the cafeteria food warehouse.

.

.

Looking back at Vikir’s demerit list, I was stunned.

How could he have racked up such numbers as soon as he started school?

It was unthinkable to Dolores, who had always been a regular and well-behaved girl.

‘Especially in the case of the monster breeding farm control area, the penalty point was 3 points…….’

Did you say that your arms are bent inward?

Since he was a junior in the club, Dolores overlooked it to a certain extent and adjusted the demerit to one point.

However, as the penalty points continued even after that, Vikir’s image was completely branded as a delinquent student.

…But.

‘He did too much volunteer work to be labeled a delinquent.’

During his volunteer work at the orphanage, Vikir worked silently and diligently in the restrooms, cafeteria, plumbing room, laundry room, playroom, and playground.

The work was hard, tiring, and unnoticed.

He was the odd one out, the one who did the work of five or six people by himself when the rest of the students at the academy, who had grown up so fine and unused to hard work, couldn’t do a single one, and yet he didn’t show any signs of it and didn’t ask for any recognition.

At the last minute, he even threw himself down to retrieve a child’s toy that had fallen into a dirty pit.

The way he returned the ball to the children even though it was dripping with filth was the epitome of selflessness.

Who else would be so willing to jump into a pool of filth for the sake of others?

And this act of abandoning oneself for the sake of others was not a one-time occurrence.

‘A man can drink and make mistakes.’

That’s what Vikir said when he took the fall for the peeing Dolores.

Vikir’s words must have been directed at Dolores, at her.

Dolores’ face flushes red again as she recalls the moment.

“No matter how much I tried to explain after that, it didn’t work.”

Dolores says she’s said several times that she was the one who peed, but everyone laughed it off as impossible.

Instead, they praised him for making the sacrifice on Vikir’s behalf.

After that, Vikir’s image at school got worse and worse, and Dolores’ image got better and better, and Dolores felt so bad about it.

Hah-

Dolores sighed deeply.

I should apologize and thank Vikir for taking such good care of the children at the orphanage, and for bearing the nickname ‘pisser’ for me.

But aside from that, she couldn’t help but feel angry every time Vikir insulted the Night Hound.

Because the Night Hound is one of the most noble and sublime beings she’s ever known.

“Phew…… But that doesn’t mean you can’t defend the Night Hound in front of someone who doesn’t know anything. Maybe this is a good thing.”

Dolores placed her hand on her forehead.

She thought for a moment, then came to a conclusion.

Regardless of the Night Hound, we must apologize and thank Vikir.

She should also ask for information about the Night Hounds.

“Okay. Let’s distinguish between public and private matters. Just apologize for what you need to apologize for and be thankful for what you need to be thankful for.”

Dolores left the dormitory in search of Vikir.

“You can’t apologize and thank at the same time. Besides, I have to ask for information about the Night Hound, Vikir… What does he need?”

Dolores felt sorry for herself in more ways than one.

She had never been in debt to anyone in her life, and this was very awkward.

Then. A familiar face appeared in front of her.

A chubby body and a cute face.

It was a junior named Pigi, who was always with Vikir.

“Hey, Pigi, do you know where Vikir is now?”

“Old? Aah! Hello, Ms. President! Vikir is probably practicing for the practical evaluation in the performance hall right now! What are you doing…?”

“Uh, just. I thought I’d take care of the juniors in the club before the exam. You should take this.”

It was a set of genealogical notes Dolores had written in her freshman year about the written test.

Pigi took it and looked thrilled.

“I’ll take it with Vikir, thank you!”

“Uh, no, you can give them to Vikir separately. I have a lot of copies.”

“Oh, right, then, just past this forest path and over the hill, there’s a practice range where Vikir practices!”

That’s where the archery class was meeting, and at this time of day, the students would be free to practice.

‘Vikir used a bow.’

Dolores nodded and headed for the practice field.

She thought hard about what she would say to Vikir first.

Chapter 174

The 99 Hits With 100 Shots (1)

◆

A vast training ground.

The sound of arrows hitting the bull’s-eye in the distance is loud.

…Puck! …Puck! …Puck!

Students from the Colosseo Academy who use bows gather here to practice.

It was mainly used by the archery students of the Cold Class, and on rare occasions, the ranged magic students of the Hot Class, who had unusually long ranges.

For the rest of the students, it was a place they didn’t need to come to as much, because they only used bows in general education classes.

Among the few students who came here, Bianca was one of the most accomplished archers.

She was also the head of the Cold Class and was very good at shooting a bow as she came from the Usher family, also known as the Divine Archer Family.

…Puck!

Bianca’s arrow hit the bull’s-eye a hundred meters away without using a single handful of mana.

A white circle, a black circle, a blue circle, a red circle, a yellow circle.

All of Bianca’s arrows were densely packed into that yellow circle.

“Wow, did you see that? Another 10.”

“This is awesome. She’s in a different league.”

“That’s enough to get a perfect score on her midterm.”

“…She’s like a hunting goddess.”

The other students around her are in awe of this almost godlike archery skill.

But.

‘There are two 9 points mixed up. The wind is not good today and my conditions are not good…….’

In fact, Bianca herself was not satisfied, even though she had managed to put all her arrows in the smallest circle.

A perfectionist, she was unhappy that she couldn’t get all her arrows into the center, the smallest yellow circle.

Normally, she might have been satisfied with the fact that out of the ten arrows she had just shot, she had scored 8 out of 10 and 2 out of 9, giving her a score of 98 out of 100.

But.

“…I don’t like it.”

Her almost paranoid score obsession was getting worse by the day.

Poof!

It was a dull noise coming from the firing line next to her.

…Puff, puff, puff!

One after another, without a pause.

One arrow would fly and hit the bull’s-eye, and before the sound could die down, the next arrow would fly right next to it and hit the bull’s-eye.

This happened ten times in a row.

10 out of 10 arrows, 10 arrows worth 100 points.

“…Oh, ten arrows.”

Bianca hung up her bow in protest and frowned.

She glanced over and saw the man standing in the next lane.

He had shaggy bangs that covered nearly half his face, fair skin, and plain clothes.

Slightly shorter and skinnier than the average 18 year old boy.

Vikir. Classmate of Usher Bianca’s in the same Cold Class B section.

Always expressionless, today he stood in the lodge with a practice bow and arrow.

Kiririk.

Vikir feeds an arrow into the bow.

The target is a hundred meters away.

A yellow circle with a diameter of 12.2 centimeters. It sits 1.3 meters off the ground and looks like a needle’s eye.

Ting-.

Vikir released the arrow.

Pow!

He scores 10 points, the highest score a single arrow can achieve.

The students practicing arrows around him stopped what they were doing and gathered around to watch Vikir’s archery skills.

“Wow, he’s a really good archer.”

“Do you see that over there?”

“I just see a yellow dot….”

“Isn’t he Vikir? He’s got the best handwriting.”

“Oh, is that the handsome kid? I can’t see him through his bangs.”

“Oh, that’s the archer. He’s got a low mana reserve for some reason.”

“Well, archers don’t mind having a little less mana.”

Meanwhile, Bianca, who was shooting a bow in the next lane, was in a strange situation.

Usher Bianca of the Divine Archers is an honor student with a reputation for archery prowess within the Academy.

This means that when she stands on the stage, the eyes of the crowd must be directed in her direction.

But she doesn’t like the idea of people watching her shoot.

She says it makes her feel like a clown.

…But what about now?

All eyes are not on her, but on Vikir next to her.

It’s not that she’s disappointed in the lack of attention, but it’s that the public seems to be implicitly judging Vikir’s skills as better than her own.

“….”

Bianca turned her head to steal a glance at Vikir’s archery stance.

…The conclusion was a mess.

Vikir’s stance could not be called good, even if it were an empty word.

Nocking, Grip, Hooking, Set up, Drawing, Anchor, Full Draw, Release, Fallow through … Nothing was quite right.

But.

Ting-.

As soon as Vikir released the cue.

Pow!

The arrow flies and hits the mark.

‘How the hell does he shoot, I can’t even tell from watching.’

Vikir’s posture is so relaxed, it’s as if he has no structure or form.

It looked like a bow wielded by a barbarian in the forest.

‘Shooting like that usually results in blind arrows, so how on earth did that one hit the bullseye?’

Bianca wrinkled her brow and glared at Vikir.

She too fiercely parried the shot.

…Puck!

An arrow that hit the 10-point mark.

Bianca was doing just as well, placing each shot in the center of the bull’s-eye.

Except for one thing: Vikir’s arrow was a little different.

…Puck! …puck! …puck!

Puff-puff-puff-puff-puck!

The speed of the shot was different.

While Bianca fired one focused shot, Vikir was firing five or six in quick succession.

While their scores were trending in the same direction, the speed at which they were using up their arrows was making a huge difference.

“Iig! You think you’re fast!?”

Bianca bit her lip.

Contrary to her claims, Vikir was not only fast.

His arrows were both fast and accurate, and he went on a 10-shot streak.

On the other hand, Bianca, who shot two 9-point shots due to poor concentration in the early part, was definitely 2 points behind Vikir.

‘Don’t miss a single shot from now on!’

A small difference in the first half of the match turns into a huge gap in the second half.

This is a common occurrence in the shooting trajectory.

So Bianca was even more focused than she had been in practice, more so than ever.

Finally, her last arrow from the demonstration hit the bull’s-eye.

…Puck!

But it was an unfortunate result.

Bianca’s thumb had slipped from her sweaty grip, and her arrow had lodged in the 9-point space.

‘Damn it!’

Bianca wanted to throw down her bow and run for the hills.

But there are a lot of eyes watching, and you can’t lose your cool here.

As calmly as possible.

‘You can’t lower the honor of a Divine Archer!

If the eldest daughter of the Usher family, known for their divine archery skills, were to be outclassed by the base archery skills of a commoner with no genealogy, it would certainly be a laughing stock throughout the world.

Kirik.

Bianca tugged on her quiver, aware that Vikir in the next lane had stopped shooting at some point.

All eyes are on the end of the dot, on a single shot.

And then.

Pfft.

The arrow flies through several layers of overlapping walls of atmosphere.

It goes.

…Pow!

It hits the center of the bull’s-eye, ten spaces away.

Ouch.

It snapped the first arrow in half.

“That’s it!”

Bianca called out in triumph.

141 10-point shots, 3 9-point shots.

In addition, she had two shots at the fingernail-sized X10 target, splitting the first in half and hitting the second.

In total, Bianca shot 144 arrows and scored 1437 out of 1440.

This was an unusually good performance for Bianca, considering her scores usually hover between 1433 and 1435.

The presence of her pacesetter and competitor, Vikir, next to her, helped her maintain a high level of concentration in the second half.

Meanwhile, onlookers were in awe.

“This is amazing. She’s a goddess.”

“That’s right. The shot hits the center of the foot.”

“ …! By the way, Vikir is also amazing!”

Everyone’s eyes are once again drawn to the side lane where Vikir is.

When Bianca finished shooting her arrows, she too turned to look at Vikir.

‘What is he doing?’

Bianca tilted her head slightly.

Vikir had shot all 143 arrows and was holding the last one for a long time.

The pinch.

The tension that sustains a shot cannot be ignored, no matter how large and muscular the man is.

Especially when you’re not spending mana.

Yet despite this, Vikir stands motionless with his bow taut.

This is completely different from shooting arrows at a tremendous speed until now.

“…Why, why don’t you shoot?”

“I don’t know, man. Maybe he’s trying to concentrate.”

“What do you think he’s trying to do at the end?”

“Isn’t 10 points the end anyway? There’s no higher score than that.”

“Yeah, I’ll just do what I’ve been doing and get a 10.”

“Wow, so if you get a 10 this time, you’ll get a 1440 out of 1440, which is awesome, I’ve never seen that before!”

“Isn’t the Academy’s official highest score up to now 1,439 points? When you didn’t spend any mana on the 100 meter distance?”

“That’s right. The current Lord of the Usher family set the official record when he was a student at the Academy, about 30 years ago.”

“Gosh, it’s a shame it’s an unofficial record. This could have been a historic record-breaking moment.”

The students who were watching also swallowed dryly.

“….”

Bianca from the next row did the same.

The tension in my gut.

And then.

Poof!

Vikir’s bow spat out an arrow from the tip of his quiver.

The arrow flew to the bull’s-eye and hit the target with a thud.

“…!”

Everyone, including Bianca, had to open their eyes wide.

Chapter 175

The 99 Hits With 100 Shots (2)

◆

In a tense atmosphere.

With all eyes on them.

Boom!

Vikir’s bow released an arrow.

It flew in a near-straight parabolic arc, and soon hit the target.

…Pow!

The sound of it hitting is a little strange.

Bianca narrowed her eyes in disbelief.

“…6 points?”

The words came out of her mouth in surprise.

Bianca’s face flushed red as she realized that she had been thinking of Vikir the whole time.

Luckily, she didn’t get caught, as everyone else in the crowd had a similar reaction.

“Eh? What, did you miss?”

“Well… 6 points is still a point….”

“Oh, that’s too bad, you must have made a mistake!”

“Aww, this could’ve been a record-breaker, but you screwed up at the last second.”

Everyone chattered in unison.

Vikir quietly lays down his bow, seemingly not paying attention.

There’s no need to retrieve the arrows; there will be someone to collect them later, when night falls.

That’s it.

Beep.

Vikir’s record is displayed in real time on the mana board in front of me.

143 10-point shots and one 6-point shot at the very end.

This brings Vikir’s total to 144 arrows and his score to 1436 out of 1440.

This was only one point less than Bianca’s score of 1437, which included 141 10-point shots and three 9-point shots.

After winning by one point, Bianca was more dumbfounded than happy.

‘What’s with the 6 at the end? He’s been shooting 10s the whole time, what happened at the end? Did he get distracted?’

Honestly, even when I shot the last X10, I didn’t think I had a chance to win.

Vikir’s momentum was just too much.

But after such a hollow victory, it only raised my doubts.

The crowd dispersed as easily as it had gathered.

“Come on, it’s getting cold. Let’s go practice.”

“Still, that’s quite a feat for a commoner.”

“But a record is hard to break.”

“Wasn’t he just lucky in the first place? The bull’s-eye was a little closer.”

People who don’t know much about bows pick them up and go their separate ways.

But.

“….”

Bianca waited patiently until Vikir was gone, and until all the curious onlookers were gone.

Then, when all eyes were on her, she moved to the end of the lane, where there was no one around.

She could see the bull’s-eye targets were littered with numerous arrows. They were supposed to be picked up by the staff after curfew every night.

Bianca looked at Vikir’s bullseye and stuck her tongue out.

“ …I was just wondering how he got into the Academy with such a small mana pool.”

They say a slug can roll, and Vikir certainly wasn’t a scribe.

However, Bianca did not harbor the jealousy or envy typical of nobles over the fact that people from commoners achieved as much success as a noble.

It only fuels her pride and competitive spirit.

‘Hey, when I saw you take off your clothes after Naphtali, your muscles were so taut, It’s a sign of harsh training.’

When it comes to bows, this is a method that allows you to fully demonstrate your skills even with a small amount of mana.

As long as you can at least distribute your mana well, you’ll be able to do a lot of good for your allies.

‘Well, I’m not into guys, but… he’s definitely a bit unusual.’

Bianca set her jaw and analyzed the arrows in the bull’s-eye.

A single, thick pillar rose from the center of Vikir’s bullseye.

It only looked like a pillar because so many arrows were packed tightly together in one place.

All arrows are stuck within 10 points.

Several of them were splintered into pieces by arrows from behind.

But they weren’t Bianca’s concern.

Just one misfire.

Bianca focused on the single arrow lodged in the blue line near the edge of Vikir’s bullseye.

The last 6-point shot. Because of this, Vikir lost as many as 4 points and cost him the match by one point.

Of course, he didn’t seem to mind, but Bianca couldn’t help but wonder.

‘Why did he shoot a 6 point at the end?’

She doubted it was a lapse in concentration or stamina. His previous scores had been so good.

“I mean, I know bows are supposed to be split-second weapons… but still, that’s a bit much at the end, isn’t it?”

But that doesn’t explain it.

The only explanation is that Vikir’s concentration and stamina didn’t hold up until the very end.

“Sheesh, it ended on a dull note. He was a pretty good opponent.”

Bianca clicked her tongue and turned away.

…If it weren’t for something that caught her eye just before she turned around.

“Huh?”

Bianca, who had good eyesight, stopped dead in her tracks just before she took her gaze off Vikir’s bullseye.

It was the last arrow Vikir had shot, a six-pointed arrow, lodged in the blue line.

Bianca’s gaze lingers on the tip of the arrow and she shudders.

A small solid line sticking out of the hole made by the arrow.

It was clearly the leg of an insect, a tiny, tiny bug like a mosquito.

‘…This can’t be it. It can’t be?’

Bianca’s throat burned.

Her eyes were alternately focused on the group of arrows that were stuck in the 10-point box of the area, forming a thick pillar, and on the single arrow that had fallen out of the group and was stuck in the 6-point area.

A single, isolated misfire.

Is it a coincidence that there is a dead mosquito in that spot?

◆

As soon as Vikir finished firing his arrows, he left the training grounds.

‘Physical training without using mana is real.’

His entire upper body was stiff from the constant use of his arm muscles.

The archery skills he had learned from Ballak’s warriors were improving day by day.

He hadn’t stopped practicing since leaving the depths.

‘You can’t go anywhere and get pushed around with a bow.’

Even if the opponent was a powerful late-stage member of the Divine Archer Family.

That’s what it takes to uphold the pride of the warrior tribe of Ballak, even in a foreign land.

Vikir had come from the hunting grounds of the Ballak.

‘So, how’s everyone doing?’

I’ve heard rumors that the Ballak have abandoned their original base and moved deeper into the depths.

I had heard of the Ballak through Cindywendy recently, but it had been several months.

I felt refreshed after shooting my bow for the first time in a while.

Chief Akwilla the night fox, Ahun the ever-grumpy one, his adorable little sister Aheul, and Bakira, now a father….

It’s a night when I miss my native friends, the ones I’ve spent the last two years sleeping, crying, and laughing with.

‘And one more.’

Vikir’s mind naturally flashes back to that rainy night.

‘…See you.’

The Imperial language that I still had difficulty understanding..

Aiyen. The woman who’d kissed him the day he’d left the jungle, right after she’d punched him in the stomach.

Vikir stroked the choker around her neck.

The tough collar she’d stuffed herself, made from the hide of the first oxbear Vikir and Aiyen had hunted together.

Then.

Vikir smiled faintly as he recalled the nostalgic faces in his mind, then froze in place.

Thud, thud, thud.

Footsteps in front of him.

Vikir, whose senses were exceptionally sensitive, recognized with a haunting certainty that it was Dolores.

‘You’re bothering me.’

Dolores doesn’t like him much. If she saw him, there was a risk of nagging me about various things.

There wasn’t much of a place to hide on the trail, which was lined with nothing but tall ash trees.

Vikir paused for a moment to consider his options. Vikir searched his pack.

/ Mask

-Fratricide (同族相殘) +0

-Human Face – Beast Heart (人面獸心) -Off

A bandana that looks like the skin of a black dog.

Vikir pulled it over his head.

A moment.

Tsutsutsutsuts…

Vikir’s body transformed into a dog.

A black puppy, not quite big enough for his age.

Hack, hack, hack.

Tucking his tattered clothes roughly into the bushes, Vikir sat still on the ground and waited for Dolores to pass by on the mountain path.

Finally, Dolores appeared from across the path.

Vikir realized what was going on, and with a brisk pace, Dolores was walking diligently towards the archery range.

‘Is there business at the training grounds? There are few people there.’

As far as Vikir could recall, there weren’t many people left at the training grounds, and even fewer of them that Dolores would be looking for.

Bianca, perhaps?

‘Yes. You’re going to see Bianca. Hurry up.’

Vikir remained meekly on the floor, clicking his tongue that kept slipping out of his mouth.

It’s a similar reaction to the Baby Madam who left it in the room.

At that very moment.

“What?”

Dolores stopped in her tracks.

She looks down, her almost innocent eyes opening even more innocently.

It was the floor, where Vikir was lying face down.

“My dear. Who are you?”

Dolores’s affectionate call startled Vikir slightly.

Is that why? Even the ever-quick Vikir was not prepared for Dolores’ surprise touch.

“Wow, look at your soft fur. Ooohhhh!”

Dolores stroked Vikir’s head with her hand and scratched his cheek and chin.

With her other hand, she massaged Vikir’s back and buttocks.

“Wow, really… you’re shockingly cute, I’ve never seen anyone as cute as you. What’s your name, where are you from, and if you don’t have anyone else living with you, do you want to come live with sis?”

‘….’

Before Vikir could react, Dolores reached out and slipped her hands under both of Vikir’s armpits and lifted him up.

“Youngcha~ Huh? I see it’s (noona) the older sister, not (unnie) the older sister?”

‘….’

The moment.

Vikir felt an unexplained sense of shame that he had never felt before, not even during the Age of Destruction.

Dolores, despite her meek and sweet exterior, was actually quite the dog lover.

I’d heard that she donated money out of her meager income to a shelter for stray dogs and cats every year and volunteered every other month.

Then.

A truly horrifying statement came out of Dolores’ mouth.

“Oh, by the way. If you’re going to live with your sister, you’re going to have to be neutered….”

Vikir realized that there was no reason for him to stay and listen to this creepy remark, so he made a quick getaway.

Hodadak-

A black fur ball that quickly escapes from Dolores’ arms.

His pink tongue hanging out of his mouth.

“‘C’mon, cutie, come with me, I’ll buy you some pork cutlets, chocolate!”

Dolores gave him a wistful look, calling him by the name he’d already made up, but Vikir didn’t look back for a second.

Chapter 176

The 99 Hits With 100 Shots (3)

◆

The Academy’s indoor training center.

There are many advanced training devices here.

There are all kinds of exercise equipment, as well as rooms that create holograms of virtual dungeons and monsters, rooms that measure the magic power in your body, rooms that quantify the damage done, and so on. ….

But the best piece of technology is the room called the ‘Gravity Room’.

In this room, you can adjust the amount of gravity applied to you at will, and it will keep a record of how long you last at that level.

Of course, if you push yourself too hard, the gravity in the gravity room will randomly disappear and your record will be reset.

And now.

…Push!

The door to the first-year gravity room opened, and a sweaty man walked out.

A well-trained, muscular, black-haired boy.

He was ‘Granola des Leviathans’, the third son of the Leviathan family.

“Wow. After all, seven times the gravity without using mana is tough. It’s like the weight of destiny that noble people carry from birth…”

Granola smirked, enjoying the stares of awe around him.

Considering that most students struggled to withstand even six times the force of gravity, withstanding seven times the force of gravity for over half an hour was definitely a record.

Granola felt like he might throw up a little, but he swallowed hard and wiped the sweat off his face in a nonchalant manner.

…But?

The looks of admiration and envy directed at him seemed a little off.

‘Not me?’

Granola shifted his gaze to where the other students in the weight room were staring in unison.

There it was.

“…!?”

There was a sight that made Granola’s eyes widen.

It was the instrument panel of the other gravity room right next door.

Gravity Room F-2

.

.

A whopping 8x gravity.

And an almost hour-long entry time.

Records that are still being updated even at this very moment.

‘No way!’

Granola’s mouth dropped open.

Half an hour in 7x gravity was enough to make him dizzy and nauseous.

But who on earth could survive an hour in eight times the force of gravity?

‘If the user’s condition becomes severe, the gravity will dissipate on its own and the records will be reset. Does that mean that the person in here… is actually withstanding this gravity?’

There are very few people who can withstand a gravity field of 8x without using mana, not even in the first year, but in the senior class.

And that’s only for about an hour….

Then.

Pause.

The gravity chamber has stopped working.

Only at exactly one hour did the door open and a thick steam burst out from inside.

‘Who is it, the one who can withstand 8x gravity?’

Granola peeked inside in a cold sweat.

There are few monsters at the Academy who can withstand this much gravity.

‘Not in the Hot Class, maybe a Tudor or Sancho in the Cold Class.’

Granola finished his thoughts with a shit-faced expression.

But. It was a different face that emerged from the gravity room.

Vikir.

A commoner schoolboy who always wore an expressionless face.

Granola’s face twisted at the sight of him.

“No, how can that weakling withstand eight times the force? Isn’t there something wrong with the record… huck?”

But Granola didn’t finish his sentence.

As the steam cleared, the body underneath Vikir’s face began to show.

His body, which had always looked skinny and thin under his clothes, was now fully exposed.

His muscles are trained to the extreme, and there is no flab at all, making them look even more prominent.

The lines of the cut muscles were so sharp that it felt like a cutting.

Granola swallowed hard at the sight of a body that didn’t look like it belonged to someone his age.

“That’s right, with a body like that, it’s possible to do 8x if you manage to squeeze it, yes. But it would be impossible to go any further than this without using mana. That’s the inherent limitation of a guy with poor mana reserves…… uh?”

Granola’s voice trailed off this time.

Crackle-.

As soon as Vikir exited the gravity room, he went to the instrument panel and adjusted the gravity coefficient upwards.

Gravity Room F-2

.

With that, Vikir returned to the gravity room and began to withstand 9x gravity.

“This is ridiculous. He won’t last even a minute like that!”

Everyone, including Granola, thought the same thing.

Inside, however, Vikir didn’t seem to mind the strain on his body.

‘Mana is more active in a healthy body, so you should train your pure physical body without using as much mana as possible.’

Vikir was still an adolescent, so his height was short and his muscles and skeleton were not fully formed.

Normally, it would have been impossible for him to withstand this much gravity.

But the seven minutes he spent in the Styx River at birth, his grueling childhood training, and the strong survival instincts he developed in the depth have made him a force to be reckoned with beyond his weight class.

Furthermore, the three wraiths of high-level monsters imprisoned within the magic sword Beelzebub were tempering Vikir’s body to become even stronger and tougher, and the karma he had earned from slaying demons so far had hardened his soul.

Thud, thud, thud, thud.

Muscles and bones screamed from every part of his body, but they were instantly restored by a level of regeneration that transcended humans.

The muscles tear, heal, tear again, and tear again, until they are even more stretched and torn.

Vikir finally makes it through another hour and steps out of the gravity room.

Push-ups.

Every time Vikir endure it, he can feel his muscle mass increasing.

Outside, the students, who had been watching Vikir’s gravity room time steadily increase, are now giving him openly surprised looks.

“Wow, look at your body, I didn’t realize it when you were wearing clothes….”

“Indeed, without using any mana and based on purely physical strength, he must be the strongest in the first grade.”

“What’s a freshman, I will rub it in with the third year seniors as well. No, maybe even to the graduating seniors.”

“But what’s the point, he’s a mana pool after all.”

“That’s right, it’s all about mana. The concentration of mana.”

“That’s too bad. If only he had a better family and better support, he’d be at…. by now.”

While everyone admired Vikir’s record, they also felt a certain amount of disrespect, jealousy, and condescension.

However, the students’ views are shaken by Vikir’s next move.

Geek-

Gravity Room F-2

.

.

Vikir has increased gravity again.

◆

When Vikir exited the gravity room, he found Tudor and Sancho in the fitness room.

“Holy shit, Vikir. Did you just go through 12x gravity and survive? Is it possible to do that without a mana boost?”

“You’re insane. I can’t do that even when I’m hitting 1000 on 3. No warrior among my peers in the North has ever been able to withstand 12x gravity with their bare bodies. What is your secret, and if you set the gravity that high, won’t you lose muscle?”

Vikir nodded, accepting the towel from Tudor and the protein supplement from Sancho.

Tudor chuckled.

“Granola’s asshole watched you defy gravity and then ran off at 10x. That was hilarious, that asshole.”

Unconcerned with the judgment of those around him, Vikir merely nodded silently this time.

Then.

“Vikir! Vikir, are you here?”

The door to the fitness room swung open and someone walked in.

It was Bianca, who rarely comes here.

She turned and stared at Vikir in the middle of a group of surprised boys.

She blurted out.

“Mosquitoes!”

Bianca’s shout made everyone in the gym turn their heads.

Bianca shouted again.

“That mosquito, you knew about it, didn’t you?”

No one understood why she would come out of the blue and say something like this when they rarely talked.

Not even Vikir himself.

“…?”

Bianca repeated in frustration when Vikir just shook his head.

“And again, aren’t you the one who was on the roof on Freshman Welcome Day, smelling that rum!”

“Hey, stop it and get out of here, this is the men’s area, why did you come here and not the women’s area?”

“Because I’m not interested in you!”

“You think I’m interested in you? I heard you just got a part-time job at a cafe. Get a part-time job, moron.”

“Why do you know I got a part-time job at a cafe, you crazy bastard?”

“Let’s get this straight. I only heard about it because Sinclaire started working part-time at a cafe, so I asked and heard that?”

Tudor stops Bianca in her tracks and sends her away with a wave of his hand.

Sancho, meanwhile, was watching the scene, sharing a protein supplement with Vikir.

“Vikir. Don’t you think they look good together?”

Vikir shook his head at Sancho’s question.

“Nope. They look like enemies.”

“Yeah, but they’re always interested in each other, even when they’re bickering.”

“Isn’t that because they hate each other?”

“…Hmm. Maybe, but I keep having a hunch otherwise.”

Sancho looked at Tudor and Bianca with a wry smile on his face.

‘You’ve got a sixth sense.’

Vikir put down the barbell he was holding and thought back to his memories before the regression.

Clearly, Tudor and Bianca would grow to love each other in the future.

Their love story, which had been a constant battle since they were childhood friends, was the kind of small talk that spreads to the battlefield and becomes the kind of thing that everyone knows about, and everyone cheers for, except for Tudor and Bianca.

I’d been wondering about it, because there was no sign of it at all once they were back together, but Sancho, who was close to Tudor, seemed to see something in his eyes.

“I know. I’m not very good at this sort of thing.”

Vikir thought to himself as he pulled out some clothes from the cabinet.

Burr-

As he was putting on the shirt, Vikir suddenly felt a slight twitch in his left wrist.

Baby Madam can be seen sitting on Vikir’s wrist, looking up at him with a sullen expression.

[Haeghaeg-]

The cub rubs its stomach with its two legs as if it were hungry.

It seems to have digested the poison that Granola had sprinkled on it.

“Hang in there, little one. I’ll make sure you’re full for tomorrow’s midterm practical.”

Vikir patted Baby Madam’s head and said,

Tomorrow, in just twelve hours, the midterms would begin.

Before going on a demon hunt, Vikir was making plans for tomorrow.

No matter how fake my identity was, since I was a student, exams were important.

Chapter 177

Midterm Random Defense (1)

◆

It’s midterm season.

At Colosseo Academy, there are two types of exams: final exams and midterms.

The final exam is a competition between students and basically follows the format of a tournament-style martial arts competition.

However, in order to account for the different levels of students, it introduces the concept of “tiers,” which means that students of similar levels are grouped together to compete.

In order to determine the tiers for the final exam, it was necessary to validate the student’s skills in various ways, which was done through the midterm exam.

The midterm exam consists of three main tests

Defense&Attack.

There is a group test for ‘defense’, an individual test for ‘offense’, and a normal written test.

The written portion of the test is actually not very important, only about 10% of the total score, but the Defense and Attack portion is 50% and 40% respectively.

Whether it’s a defense or offense test, all students have to fight a battle against a monster.

In this case, the dummy is a clay golem made by the professors of Hot Class, which only the monster’s appearance is covered with a hologram.

However, these golems are controlled by the professors themselves, who carefully mimic the movements of the monster, so it is almost like a real battle with a wild monster.

In the defense test, students are placed in an arena in groups of four, and a huge area of hologram magic creates the illusion of being in a real dungeon or monster field.

(In this case, spectators watching from outside the arena can only see a 100-meter diameter circular arena).

Students participate in the game wearing black tights that cover their entire bodies, and when they receive a certain amount of shock from magic tools, these tights are quantified on a distant instrument panel.

Students are given “hit points” (HP), which are deducted from them each time they are hit by a monster.

A hard hit takes away a lot of HP, a light hit takes away less. The same goes for being hit in the face.

If this HP reaches zero, they are automatically eliminated, so they had to be careful when dealing with monsters.

Students had to enter the dungeon in groups of four and defend against waves of monsters, and how long they could hold out against these waves would determine their grades.

For example, Dolores, the third-year student council president, formed a party with three classmates to enter the virtual reality dungeon and managed to fend off waves of “killer ants” for most of the first, second, and third phases.

They lasted 20 minutes for Phase 1, 20 minutes for Phase 2, and 18 minutes for Phase 3, for a total of one hour.

They would have gotten a perfect score if they had lasted two more minutes, but they were still the longest of the third years, which is quite an accomplishment.

The second-year vice student council president also faced the “killer ants” in a four-person team and managed to defeat the first and second phases before being retired at the beginning of the third phase.

The time taken was 20 minutes for Phase 1, 20 minutes for Phase 2, and 1 minute for Phase 3, totaling 41 minutes.

This was the best time for a second year.

Most third-years made it through Phase 3 without incident, and most second-years made it through Phase 2 without incident.

And now it was the turn of the freshmen.

◆

Thousands of people gathered on the sidelines of the arena.

At Colosseo Academy, the midterm and final exams are like a festival for the entire Imperial Capital, attracting even ordinary people from the outskirts.

“Dolores! You’re doing great this year!”

“Cheer up! Colosseo! Pride of Imperial Capital!”

“Wow! Mage Tower’s midterms, Varangian’s midterms, and Temisquira Women’s College’s midterms are all a mess, but Colosseo’s midterms are the best!”

“I’m looking forward to this ‘National University League’ too!”

Spectators gathered near the stadium in cloud-like crowds, each calling out the names of their favorite students.

Meanwhile, professors, including the principal, were also watching the game.

Several of the Ministry’s magical professors, specializing in the summoning of golems and their precise control, were on hand.

Screech!

The muddy golem rose to its feet.

Three crude spheres joined together as a head, chest, and stomach to form a body, with six legs attached to each side.

Tsutsutsutsu…

This lump of clay was coated with illusionary magic.

From a crude lump of clay, it soon took the shape of a killer ant with a sharp exoskeleton, sharp jaws, legs, and stingers.

With a snap of the professors’ fingers, these Killer ant-like golems crawled around, biting stones with their jaws to crush them or shooting their stingers into the ground.

Each time the fake ants made a stinging motion, a small amount of the poison provided by the Monster Research Institute would spew out, making the battle feel real.

“Wow, it looks like a real monster.”

“So, those are all dummy controlled by the professors?”

“All we have to do is stop them, I’m confident!”

The first-year students were giddy with excitement about their first big test.

They had just watched the third- and second-year seniors perform admirably.

Then, a large hologram window appeared in front of the first-year students.

-Join forces with your teammates to defend against the swarming Killer ants!

HP: 100/100

Kill point: ? point

Assist point: ? point

The real midterms have begun.

◆

Pigi was furiously writing down notes outside the arena.

It was the test scores of the second and third year students from last time.

Since fourth-year seniors don’t take midterms or finals, it’s actually the third-year students who perform best.

And among those third years, it’s Dolores, the student council president, who remains at the top of the list.

She had assembled a solid party of healers, buffers, supporters, and defensive, offensive, and hybrid mages, and the result was a 58-minute run across three phases.

Pigi analyzed the seniors’ performance data.

“Usually third-year students make it to Phase 3 and sophomores make it to Phase 2, so freshmen only need to make it through 20 minutes of Phase 1. Even if they can only last 10 minutes, they’re halfway there.”

Pigi was strong on the written portion of the entrance exam, ranking third in the class, but not so strong on the practical portion.

Also, Pigi doesn’t have the connections to form a group.

The best friends form groups with people they know, or people with whom they have a mutual interest, but none of them needed Pigi.

‘…What should I do?’

Pigi was fiddling in his mind.

Tuck!

A hand tapped Pigi on the shoulder.

“Hey, don’t just go halfway. If you’re going to take the test, you should see the end.”

It was Tudor. Next to him, Sancho stood with his arms crossed.

Then Pigi said in a creepy voice.

“You’re Tudor, and you’re so good at it, you could probably last the whole 20 minutes… but I’m not like that, I’m a real jam. So I don’t even know who I’m gonna line up with, actually. I’m wondering if there’s a group of kids who would be willing to take me on….”

“What, you mean?”

Tudor’s eyes widened at Pigi’s words.

“I thought you were already in our group?”

“Huh?”

“What do you mean, were you trying to be disloyal and get into a group with the other kids?”

Tudor chuckled, and Pigi’s dazed expression instantly turned to tears.

“My, I was afraid I’d be a nuisance… I’m weak and….”

“There’s no such thing as that, friends, is there, Sancho?”

“Well, of course, and you’re smarter than us. Everyone has their strengths and weaknesses.”

Tudor and Sancho nodded in agreement. Pigi quickly pulled out a handkerchief and dabbed at his eyes.

Tudor turned his head to look at him.

“No. But where the hell did he go? We need to get some breakfast.”

He looked for Vikir.

But Vikir was somewhere else, a little farther away.

@@@@@Party Member Wanted@@@@@Expert Advanced/Shield Warrior@@@@@

Looking for two [fire, poison] mages##### Current party members (2/4)#####

Party Wanted))) I’m an Expert Advanced Melee Dealer~~!! I’ll carry you~~!!

Tank one person please~~!!!! Expert Intermediate and above~~!!! Current party members (3/4)

~~~1 Healer on a first-come, first-served basis~~~(Female only)

.

.

Vikir walks leisurely through the outskirts of the stadium, past numerous signs.

Spotting Vikir walking across the field, Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi walked toward him and clapped their hands together.

“Hey, Vikir, come on, let’s get a group together, it’s almost time for registration!”

But a similar shout came from their side.

“Hey, Vikir, does anyone want to join us for the group test?”

Waving was Sinclaire, the head of the Hot Class. Next to him was Bianca, whom he’d gotten to know quickly.

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi. And Sinclaire and Bianca.

Divided into groups, they fight over Vikir.

This was especially true for Tudor and Bianca, who are usually at odds with each other.

“Vikir is in the same group as us.”

“What do you mean, he’s been walking around on his own ever since I saw him, so I’m guessing you guys picked him.”

“What are you talking about? Of course Vikir is with us. He’s our best friend, he’s been with us the longest, he’s got the best hands and feet.”

“I’m not hand-in-hand with weaklings. He’s an archer, so we have chemistry.”

“Two archers in one party? You don’t even know the divisions of the party?”

“I’m playing. If there are two archers of his level and me, we can easily combine them.”

They chatted for a while, then turned to Vikir.

“Vikir, which group are you going to join?”

But.

“I’m sorry, but I’ve already decided on the group I’ll be in. I have a prior agreement.”

Vikir’s answer was unexpected.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire all narrowed their eyes.

They hadn’t seen Vikir with anyone but them since they enrolled.

Just then.

Three faces popped out from behind Vikir.

“Why, do you have a problem?”

“Do you have a problem?”

“Do you?”

Three men with cynical questions directed at Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and Sinclaire.

Highbro, Middlebro, Lowbro.

The triplets infamously known in the Cold Class as the “Trident of Baskerville”.

Chapter 179

Midterm Random Defense (3)

◆

Beep-.

[First year group 69! The four members of first year group 69 will please come up to the arena now!]

It was the turn of Vikir’s group.

The Baskerville triplets led the way, with Vikir following close behind, carrying their unwieldy baggage.

“Go, Highbro, you look handsome!”

“Baskerville is the best!”

“Show me your trident charisma!”

The popularity of Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro was immense, both inside and outside the Academy.

Powerful skills, noble bloodlines, tall stature, broad shoulders, stern faces, and the unusual trait of being triplets.

He had all the ingredients to be a star.

In addition to the girls at the academy, there were many fans from outside the academy.

Even the Mage Tower, Varangian, and Temisquira Women’s College, the four major academies in the empire along with Colosseo Academy, came to see the Baskerville triplets.

Meanwhile.

“Come on, Vikir!”

“We’re here for you!”

“Go big brother!”

There were also those who cheered for Vikir. Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Sinclaire, and Bianca.

At Dolores’ urging, they were currently in separate groups, as first-years are encouraged to split up their cold and Hot Class as much as possible.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca made up the 108 group, and Sinclaire was the only Hot Class, so she was in the other group.

“Hmmm. C’mon, commoner, thank me for taking you in.”

Next to Sinclaire stood a blushing Granola.

They were currently in the same group, but it didn’t mean much if they weren’t in the same group as Vikir and Bianca, so as soon as Sinclaire posted “Party Wanted@@@@{Earth+Gold}Mage$$$$Head of Hot Class####” on the public board, Granola contacted her immediately.

That’s why Granola is so excited about the group.

Whatever.

Vikir and the Baskervilles’ triplets stepped onto an amphitheater a hundred meters in diameter.

In the huge Colosseum surrounding them, countless people stamp their feet, cheer, and watch the test taking place in the training hall.

It was like watching an ancient gladiator match.

Tsutsutsutsuts…

Soon, the scene in the arena changes.

Vikir and the triplets’ view is suddenly transformed into a deep, abyssal crypt.

Soon, countless ‘killer ants’ began to swarm around them.

Waaaaaah!

The crowd roared.

To the audience, it would appear to be just a bunch of golems crawling like ants around the circular arena, approaching in a clockwise direction.

Vikir and the triplets must intercept and hunt them down before they reach the center of the arena.

Phase 1, 20 minutes. If you can last just 20 minutes against this army of ants, you get a perfect score.

But the average first year student will only last 17 or 18 minutes at best, and 19 minutes will probably put them in the top spot.

“….”

Vikir looked around.

The Filthy Spawning Grounds, deep within a nest of killer ants.

A terrifying dungeon that most people would never visit in their entire lives.

But Vikir had been here dozens, perhaps hundreds, of times already.

Not in virtual reality, but in real life.

‘I almost died so many times back then, not every day, but every second.’

Vikir frowned at the lingering nightmare.

The darkness, the damp grave smell, the wrinkled earthen walls, the slime dripping down like a veil, the piles of eggs squirming on the floor and walls, the swarms of ants the size of men crawling out from between them….

The average freshman would be horrified by the appearance of the barren dungeon in front of them.

‘Hoh. They did a pretty good job recreating it.’

For Vikir, it was like being in the cradle of a child’s play.

With that, Vikir drew his bow and let fly.

Puck! Pow! Pow!

The exoskeleton of a killer ant is hard.

Their shield-like heads are an excellent defense, deflecting most impacts.

So Vikir only targets the ants’ front leg joints and antennae.

…Poof!

An ant with a broken front leg falls to the ground and is crushed by the ants behind it.

The dead body becomes an obstacle for the other ants, slowing their advance.

Dengue.

Ants with severed antennae are also disoriented and scorch the walls or ceiling.

Sometimes they would run backwards, disrupting the line behind them.

The slowed-down ants were then slaughtered by the Baskervilles’ triplets.

Pow!

Sword Expert Advanced. At the age of 19, they had reached the peak of Expert level and began to slice and cut through the ants, emitting a red aura that was as thick as water vapor between gas and liquid.

Puck! Puff! Puff, puff, puff, Crackling!

The ants’ heads and everything else were sliced off.

Baskerville’s trident began to push the ant army backwards.

-Let’s join forces with our allies and stop the onslaught of killer ants!

Time remaining until the end of Phase 1: 14 minutes, 58 seconds

1. Highbro Le Baskerville

HP: 91/100

Kill point: 49 points

Assist point: 23 points

2. Middlebro Le Baskerville

HP: 87/100

Kill point: 45 points

Assist point: 26 points

3. Lowbro Le Baskerville

HP: 86/100

Kill point: 41 points

Assist point: 29 points

4. Vikir

HP: 100/100

Kill point: 2 points

Assist point: 38

As the game progressed, the scores continued to climb.

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro were working hard on the front lines, and their HP was slowly dropping.

Meanwhile, Vikir was working diligently in the back under their protection, shooting down ants with his arrows, and while he wasn’t racking up many kill points, he was racking up some solid assist points.

After focusing on the Baskerville triplets’ spectacular individual performances at the beginning of the match, the crowd slowly began to pay attention to Vikir, who was steadily making assists from the back.

“But who is he, Vikir? He doesn’t have a last name, so he must be a commoner.”

“Ah, Vikir, the one with the top marks? He’s an archer? I didn’t know that. He seemed to have a low mana pool for some reason.”

“He’s pretty good with a bow, for a guy who’s supposed to be an academy student.”

“But wasn’t there a bit of a buzz about him being handsome? I don’t think so.”

“No, he looks great without his glasses. Want me to show you? Where it was?”

Many eyes in the stands lingered on Vikir for a moment, but the interest quickly faded as he barely moved from his spot and drew his bow.

Only the cheering of Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Sinclaire, and Bianca is steady.

“Come on, buddy, we’re rooting for you!”

“Hey, Vikir. You’re building up a nice stack of assists. You’re going to get a good score at this rate.”

“Wow, Vikir, your bow skills are impressive! You may not be able to see it, but you’re definitely disrupting the ants’ momentum!”

“Too bad. Me and my hyung would have really hit it off if we were in the same group.”

“Nonsense. An archer knows an archer’s heart. He would have doubled his score with me.”

Whether or not he realizes that his friends are cheering him on, Vikir remains silent, fending off the wave of ants.

Tsk, tsk, tsk!

The ants rubbed their exoskeletons together, making unpleasant noises and occasionally lifting their antennae upward like scorpions to spray venom.

Sting-.

The pale paralyzing venom flew a long distance, shooting out like a squirt.

Vikir watched it and thought.

‘The ants are just holographic magic overlaid on a clay figure, but… the poison is real.’

The Introduction to Golems explains the various ways to store things inside a golem.

The professors here have built an ant-shaped golem and filled it with diluted poison supplied by the Monster Research Institute.

Meanwhile, the triplets of House Baskerville would bend low whenever the ants spewed their venom, allowing it to splash toward Vikir.

This was exactly what Vikir had ordered them to do.

Thwack!

A thick poisonous fog rises. This was actually happening inside the arena.

(A thick wall of magic surrounds the arena, preventing the poison from reaching the stands.)

There was only one reason why Vikir would want to be this close to the poison.

[Omnomnomnomnomnom…]

Madame cub.

This thing attached to my left wrist was sucking in poisonous fog as if possessed.

The paralyzing venom of the killer ants is just the right meal for this one.

It’s amazing how a creature smaller than the palm of your hand can store all that poison.

“You know how spiders eat a lot at once and go a long time without eating?”

For her, it’s a 20-minute all-you-can-eat poison buffet. So I thought it would be a good idea to feed her a lot now.

For more information, visit ….

-Join forces with your allies to defend against the onslaught of killer ants!

Time remaining until the end of Phase 1: 1 minute 07 seconds

1. Highbro Le Baskerville

HP: 2/100

Kill point: 228 point

Assist point: 80 point

2. Middlebro Le Baskerville

HP: 1/100

Kill point: 208 point

Assist point: 96 point

3. Lowbro Le Baskerville

HP: 1/100

Kill point: 199 point

Assist point: 102 point

4. Vikir

HP: 47/100

Kill point: 16 point

Assist point: 134 point

Wave time is almost over.

Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro reached 0 HP almost simultaneously and slaughtered countless ants until the very end.

After the trio retired to 0 HP, it was Vikir’s turn.

At the end of the trial, the total score was 308 for the Highbro, 304 for the Middlebro, 301 for the Lowbro, and 150 for Vikir.

They lasted a whopping 19 minutes and 50 seconds, with only 10 seconds left in the first phase.

If you add up all of their kill points and assist points, they totaled 1063 points, and if you convert the 19 minutes and 50 seconds that you lasted into 1 point per second, it’s a total of 1,190 points.

Vikir’s team totaled 2253 points, the highest among the first years.

A new record for first place!

The Baskerville triplets walked out of the arena, smiling broadly as the cheers erupted.

Next up was the ever-expressive Vikir.

Vikir was just about to step out of the arena’s magic wall.

“…?”

For some reason, my left arm felt a little heavy.

I turned my head and saw that the Madame cub had stuck a thin web on the arena floor, refusing to leave.

It looked like it wanted to eat more of the remaining poison.

“Can you eat that much and still go in? But no. It’s time to go.”

[Grunting].

“Then you live in the arena. I’m going home.”

[Kkuing-kkuing…]

“Sssh-”

Vikir picked up the refusing cub and tucked it into the cuff of his left hand.

To anyone else, it would have looked like he was just picking up a wristwatch from the floor.

As Vikir exited the stadium, he could hear the crowd appraising him.

“Wow, Vikir or something, that guy is completely on board.”

“Yeah, well, according to the score, the triplets from Baskerville did it all.”

“I thought the three of them were there to bully the little bastard, but it turns out the three of them were there to serve the little bastard.”

“Lucky commoner. How did you get into that group?”

“Well, being number one in handwriting, I guess he was trying to use his brain.”

“But he’s pretty good at stopping monsters with his arrows. 150 points isn’t exactly a stellar score, but it’s a good one.”

“I saw him shoot a bow with no mana the other day and it was amazing. He has the basics, right?”

“Oh, yeah, I saw that, too. Wasn’t he almost as good as Bianca from Usher’s?”

“Oh, a close one, ain’t it? He lost by one point because of his last shot. In archery, a one-point difference is huge. It’s almost a division. If there is a difference of 2 points, the difference in skill level is impossible to compare.”

“Still, he’s kind of helpful. We should try to get him in the same group next time.”

“That’s right, he’s a commoner, and he’s the highest scoring arrow shooter.”

At first, there was a lot of negativity about Vikir being taken advantage of by the Baskerville triplets, but that was slowly changing.

Of course, Vikir himself didn’t care about the comments, but there were others… who did.

“Hahaha, it makes me proud to see my friend being recognized.”

“With that kind of score and integrity, he deserves to be recognized everywhere.”

“Yes, Vikir is more than just brains. I’m glad everyone seems to have discovered a new side of him.”

“You look great. Hehe.”

“…Well, it does shoot a little. He’d score better if he had more mana.”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Sinclaire, and Bianca.

They’d watched Vikir’s group of 69 take first place in first year, and they were fired up.

“Let’s see if we can beat that! Go Group 108!”

“We can’t lose to Baskerville’s Trident.”

“I’ll do my best, I’ve been analyzing killer ants all night!”

“Just keep your distance and I’ll carry, don’t let the mob get to me.”

This was Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca, chattering away in cheerful tones.

Meanwhile.

“Whoa, whoa, whoa, commoner. Let’s do our part.”

“….”

“What is it, commoner, are you deaf, hmmmmm, can’t you hear me?”

Group 203, to which Granola and Sinclaire belonged, was also preparing for the test.

Next up.

Group 108, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca, was called.

Beep.

[First-year 108, the four members of the first-year group 108, please come up to the arena now!]

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca rush onto the arena, excited to get their turn.

…And the same time.

Vikir, who had come to the side of the arena to watch his friends play, noticed something strange.

‘…What’s wrong?’

An unexplained feeling of anxiety overtook him.

Soon, Vikir realized what it was.

‘Ouch!’

He realized that his left hand had felt strangely light.

Vikir quickly looked into the cuff of his left hand.

There, he could see the cub sitting in an unusually quiet position.

But then.

A rustle.

Vikir takes his hand away, and the cub crumbles to dust.

Nothing but an empty shell in his hand.

That’s right.

The guy had just shed his skin.

Chapter 180

Midterm Random Defense (4)

◆

Tudor recalled the fight with Highbro that had nearly turned into a duel not long ago.

“Asshole. I’ll see you someday in Naphtali, and I’ll kick your ass again.”

“Wow, you sounded like a real third-rate villain.”

Bianca jerked a thumbs up at Tudor.

It was quite a surprise to see Tudor and Bianca in the same group, as they were always arguing.

“…Will we be okay?”

“…Mmm.”

Pigi and Sancho looked at them, uneasy.

Beep-!

[First year group 108, the four members of the first year group 108, please come up to the stadium now].

But it was an unnecessary worry.

“Now then, please cover me as a range dealer from behind, Ms. B.”

“Don’t worry about it, Mr. T.”

Because as soon as the exam started, Tudor and Bianca completely put aside their personal feelings and became businesslike party members.

Tsutsutsuts…

Before my eyes I was summoned to a dank darkness, to a dank crypt, to gloomy molds and foul slime, and to a mass of eggs and eggshells that stirred unpleasantly.

Dgldgldgldgldgl…

And among them, countless armies of ants began to swarm.

A monster wave! A monster wave! It soon rushed towards the four examinees, almost overwhelming them.

-Tingling!

A magical status board appeared in front of everyone’s eyes.

<Map: Killer Ant Colony ‘Filthy Spawning Grounds’

-Let’s join forces with our allies and fend off the murderous ants!

Time remaining until the end of Phase 1: 19 minutes, 59 seconds

1. Tudor Donquixote

HP: 100/100

Kill point: 0 points

Assist point: 0 points

2. Sancho Panza Barataria

HP: 100/100

Kill point: 0 points

Assist point: 0 points

3. Usher Pou Bianca

HP: 100/100

Kill point: 0 points

Assist point: 0 points

4. Pigi

HP: 100/100

Kill point: 0 points

Assist point: 0 points

“Alright, let’s set a new record!”

Tudor, the most promising young man in the Donquixote family of spearmen, lunged forward, holding a large spear.

…Whoosh!

A steamy aura of blue light emanated from the spear, indicative of an Expert rank.

Although it is weaker in hardness and density than the liquid aura of a Graduator or the solid aura of a Swordmaster, the expert’s gas aura is still the lightest in weight.

…That means it’s easy to swing!

Puff-puff-puff!

The ants in front of him got caught in the storm of auras from the spear and were torn apart like paper.

Bianca snorted at the sight.

“Do you really need to tear them to pieces? It’s inefficient to waste energy you don’t have to use.”

“What? Fine, then you can try it.”

“I’m sure I can, just watch.”

Bianca let go of the demonstration as she spoke.

Poof!

An arrow, imbued with mana flew in a bluish trajectory.

It pierced the brow of the ant crawling in front of her.

It flew all the way back, lodging itself halfway in the brow of the ant behind it before exerting its full force.

Bianca killed the ants one by one, using minimal effort.

Bianca’s arrows hit just the right spot, wounding the ant just enough to kill it.

Her penetrating shots, imbued with the unique gas aura of an Expert, leave the ants lined up and dying.

“Oh-so arrogant.”

“Do you get it now, ho-ho-ho-”

Tudor and Bianca smirked at each other. They were bad friends who got along well together.

Just then, ants fell from the ceiling toward Bianca.

They opened their big, sharp jaws and aimed for her head.

“Where!”

“How dare they!”

A huge axe and a sharp longsword blow the ants’ heads off.

Sancho and Pigi were now at Bianca’s side, playing tank.

Puck! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!

Sancho swings his two axes with tremendous force, chopping up the ants.

Pigi swung his longsword and slashed at the ants, all the while barking orders.

“Tudor! I think it would be more effective to get to the corner and deliver the blow when the line of ants breaks; Sancho, let’s try to draw them in a little further rather than blocking them from the center straight; Bianca, if you can, aim for the middle row of ants, preferably at the front leg joints so you don’t have to kill them.”

Pigi’s orders were so precise and sharp that even Bianca, who didn’t like to be told what to do, looked surprised and moved accordingly.

“…You’re really good, aren’t you?”

“Hehe, thanks. I didn’t want to embarrass you, so I studied a lot!”

Pigi may not have the combat prowess of the other three, but he was just as intelligent and dedicated.

Because of this, Tudor, Sancho, and Bianca were able to hunt more efficiently than ever before.

“See! I told you Pigi was good!”

“I don’t think anyone ever refuted that. Hehe!”

Tudor’s spear smashed through the ants in front of him, while Sancho’s double axe sliced through the ones coming out of the side.

“I think our combination is pretty good?”

Bianca was firing well-timed arrows that were causing the ants to tangle in their ranks, noticeably slowing down the monster wave.

“Thanks for believing in my order, I’ll be right there, Tudor, just a little more distance, your spear skills are amazing, maybe you can expand your area a little more, ah! Same goes for Sancho, you’re doing a great job as it is, but I think you’ll be much more efficient if you fight in the corners a little more, and Bianca’s doing so well right now that I think we can just keep going as it is, go, guys!”

And it’s all done under Pigi’s orders.

As Tudor crushed the ants’ heads, dodging the venom that poured down the back of his head, he exclaimed.

“Man, this is good, and if I do it right, I’ll break Vikir’s record!”

Then Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca joined in.

“We can do it! Break the record!”

“Huh… this is really hard. I wonder if Vikir had it this hard?”

“The Baskervilles’ dogs are so strong and stubborn, it must have been hard.”

Everyone feels sorry for Vikir, who was with the Baskervilles’ triplets.

They talk about things that Vikir would have loved to hear.

Time passes.

Countless ants have died and piled up, and Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi, who had been on the front lines, are exhausted.

Everyone’s HP was so low that Bianca, who was now an range dealer, had to step forward and stand upright.

And finally.

<Map: Killer Ant Colony ‘Filthy Spawning Grounds’

-Together with your allies, let’s defend against the onslaught of killer ants!

Time remaining until the end of Phase 1: 0 minutes, 08 seconds

1. Tudor Donquixote

HP: 0/100

Kill point: 231

Assist point: 81

2. Sancho Panza Barataria

HP: 0/100

Kill point: 189

Assist point: 94

3. Usher Pou Bianca

HP: 0/100

Kill point: 156

Assist point: 179

4. Pigi

HP: 0/100

Kill point: 58

Assist point: 89

Eight seconds left!

We beat the record set by the Baskerville triplets by two seconds.

The total score at the end of the trial is 312 for Tudor, 283 for Sancho, 335 for Bianca, and 147 for Pigi.

Kills and assists totaled 1077 points, and if you add in the 19 minutes and 52 seconds they lasted, at a rate of one point per second, they totaled 1192 points.

That’s a total of 2269 points, 16 points ahead of the original first-place record of 2253 points.

The first place record has been broken!

Looking at the status window, Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca, with their HP-recording suits half off, shouted.

“We’re in first place! Yay!”

“Well done, everyone.”

“Really? We’re in first place? Hooray!”

“Good job.”

Tudor, who killed the most ants up front, Sancho, who killed the next most ants, Bianca, who had the highest score for kills and assists combined, and finally Pigi, the unseen hero who gave orders at just the right time.

Their synergy set a new record in spectacular style, and there’s not a group in sight that can top it.

Tudor looked down at his suit’s HP log and breathed a sigh of relief.

“I’m glad impacts are quantified in HP, because if this was real life, it would have meant death, right?”

With that, everyone realizes the horror of the real thing.

They look back at the number of monsters they’ve defeated and realize their capabilities, limitations, and potential for improvement.

“Now, let’s get out of here!”

Pigi shouted, and everyone nodded.

First year students only have to complete one phase of the test.

In the second year, they’ll have to endure another twenty minutes of Phase 2, and in the third year, they’ll have to endure another twenty minutes of Phase 3.

Bianca muttered.

“One day I’ll be a warrior like Ms. Dolores who can last an hour.”

Tudor, Sancho, and Pigi nodded in agreement.

They headed for the dungeon’s entrance.

Soon, the holographic spell would lift and they would be back in the real world.

The illusory anthill would disappear, the real arena would appear, and the magic wall would be lifted.

Then you will hear the thunderous roar of the crowd.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca walked on, wondering how they would respond to the cheers.

…But.

“Huh?”

“What?”

“Huh?”

“Why isn’t it over?”

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca’s faces are colored with puzzlement.

Despite the end of the first-year-only Phase 1, the illusion of the anthill still hadn’t faded.

Everyone looks back at the status window in confusion.

1. Tudor Donquixote

HP: 0/100

2. Sancho Panza Barataria

HP: 0/100

3. Usher Pou Bianca

HP: 0/100

4. Pigi

Pigi: 0/100

Everyone’s HP remains the same. A power retirement signaling the end of the test.

Just then.

Rumbling, rumbling……

Behind the last of the ants, another huge swarm of ants began to swarm.

“What the hell!?”

“Why are they swarming again?”

“I thought we were done!”

“Open the door!”

Everyone panicked and banged on the magic wall behind them, but there was no response from the outside.

Instead, what flashed before their eyes was.

-Ting!

.

<Page 2 has begun

.

.

.

This time, it’s not just worker ants.

They were swarming with giant-sized army ants.

They were enormous in size, and their entire bodies were coated with an exoskeleton like an iron shield.

“ …X that.”

The blood began to drain from the faces of Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca.

Chapter 183

Midterm Random Defense (7)

◆

In the darkness.

A child stood alone.

‘Get out.’

The voice of a middle-aged man.

A memory from a distant past he didn’t even recognize.

‘This scum is not my blood.’

The voice was bitterly cold.

It is followed by the sobs of a mother.

‘You lowly thing, you don’t even know what you’re talking about.’

‘Get him out of here now.

‘……Get rid of him.

The sobs are followed by a chorus of chatter around the room.

The child’s vision shifts several times after that.

A fleeing mother, forests and mountains, pursuers, steep cliffs, raging rivers, hungry wolves, and the startled faces of passing merchants and mercenaries.

Time passes, and so do memories.

His mother, who never smiled and always looked at him with a sad expression.

The stepfather who was always there to comfort and support him, and to give his son the love he deserved.

In the face of my father’s dedicated efforts, my mother was gradually able to smile.

The house, which had always been narrow, dark, and musty, slowly became wider, brighter, and warmer.

The things that went into his mouth gradually changed from harsh things with a sour smell to sweet and soft things.

And so began a life worth envying.

A mother’s pride, a father’s hope.

Now, for the sake of his mother’s newfound happiness, and to repay his father’s dedication, the child chose a challenge of his own.

Enrollment in the Colosseo Academy.

It was the result of his own hard work, combined with his father’s life’s savings.

His mother was nervous that he would be enrolled in a school that attracted only the best and brightest in the Empire.

His father smiled from ear to ear as he spent his life’s savings on a life of luxury.

He thought, ‘I’m going to make my parents happy by being a good student here.’

He wanted to show his mother, who was full of misery, and his father, who had dedicated his life to making her happy.

But things didn’t go so well.

At his first school, he was bullied. This was due to his timid nature.

When he went to a regular school outside, he was a leader, active, and achieved excellent results in various sports, but here in Colosseo, where only the most talented people in the empire gather, he was just an inferior student.

His brilliant mind and relatively weak body have failed him in tests.

Even now, he was in danger of losing his life.

And now, pushed to the limit, his mind is replaying the earliest sights and sounds he can remember.

‘Get out. This scum is not my blood.’

Flashlight.

With his body and mind pushed to the limit, the child struggles, barely holding on to a sense of identity that is about to explode.

Just then.

‘It’s okay now.’

A voice came out of nowhere.

It had a greater effect than any other magic in the world, instantly dissipating the child’s physical and emotional pain.

No more birth anxiety, no more guilt for his parents, no more sense of duty as a child, no more studying, no more loneliness for not being able to make friends, no more physical pain, just one word to relieve it all.

It was the consolation of a friend.

“…Uh!?”

The child opened his eyes.

The first thing he saw were three faces.

“Hey, Pigi! Are you okay! Breathe, Pigi! Breathe! Come on, breathe, don’t die!”

“Okay, he’s breathing again, my northern warrior CPR is working…!”

“Hey, shut up and pump his chest, now, and you get to massaging his limbs!”

Tudor, Sancho, and Bianca. I can see my friends looking down at me, their faces covered in tears and snot.

Tudor’s emotions are always high, but I’m surprised to see even Sancho and Bianca crying.

Pigi woke up with a groan.

His ribs were cracked. Maybe even broken.

But even through the pain, Pigi moved to find someone.

“Vikir! Vikir! Vikir!”

Tudor, Sancho, and Bianca’s expressions changed strangely.

Suddenly, the eyes of the four friends focused on one place.

And there it was.

Pow! Puff! Puff-puff-puff-puff!

You see the back of Vikir, who is furiously shooting ants with his bow.

◆

‘Hmm. At this rate, I should be able to catch them even if I’m only using the strength of an Expert level.’

Vikir thought as he pierced the skull of one of the soldier ants with a single shot.

He didn’t even need to pull out his Graduator Aura.

Because….

‘I’ve got a knack for killing ants anyway.’

Vikir knows all of the strategies for killing ants that are currently unknown.

Giggle- giggle- giggle-

A swarm of killer ants swarms around Vikir and targets him.

But Vikir stays calm and shoots an arrow into the ant’s thoracic plate, the area between its head and chest.

Surprisingly, the destroyed ants begin to move backwards instead of forwards.

The ants that had been swarming forward began to walk backward, causing great confusion in the swarm.

As Vikir watched, he realized that the golem was an exquisite imitation of a real killer ant.

It must have been created by a skilled mage.

‘Killer ants have a bio-compass right here. If it breaks, it’s over.’

This is a method of dealing with monsters that humans don’t know about now, and won’t be discovered for another 20 years.

Before Vikir’s return, humanity was puzzling over how the killer ants could find their way back home from so long a distance.

If they could figure it out, it would be a great way to bring back warriors who had fallen in the fight against demons.

And after countless years of tireless research, humans eventually figured it out.

Killer ants were known to find their way around by spraying pheromones or memorizing the shape of major landforms, but that didn’t explain their ability to find their way home after a storm washed away the pheromones or an earthquake altered the landscape.

It has now been confirmed that even baby ants that have just left the nest for the first time are able to find their way home.

In fact, the killer ants’ ability to navigate so precisely is due to a magnetic field compass built into their bodies.

No matter where they are, they can calculate exactly where they stand, where they want to go, and how many steps they need to take by integrating a complex function of mana along the way.

This extremely precise bio-compass, which can even detect polarization – the rotation of the direction of the force field when sunlight hits it – keeps the killer ants pointed in the right direction at all times.

And then.

Poof! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!

Vikir wasn’t killing the ants, he was just picking out and destroying their bio-compasses.

The killer ants, with their broken sense of direction, ran backwards, blocking the path of those behind them, and were crushed to death.

“What’s next… Is it a soldier?”

Vikir lifted his head and stared at the giant ants in front of him.

How could he forget those murderous, heavily armored creatures?

The Battle of the Basin in the Great Colony, with so many casualties. That nightmare in the anthill.

The monsters that had exploited the worker ants’ weaknesses and turned the tide of battle in an instant, baffling the victorious Allied forces.

‘If you go down into the depths of the anthill, into the Catacombs, they scurry around like normal ants, though I don’t know if they even exist today.’

The soldier ant is a dangerous creature, similar in danger rating to the hellhounds you’ve faced before.

It’s so strong that even elite warriors at the upper ranks of the Sword Expert can’t fight it 1:1.

But of course, even such a beast has its weaknesses.

Just as you can trap a hellhound with chocolate, you can trap a soldier ant with a trick.

“You just have to find the right point.”

Vikir focused his attention on the arrow.

He needed to concentrate even more since he only had to use the aura of an intermediate to advanced Sword Expert.

Of course, the gas aura used by the Sword Expert and the gas aura used by the Graduator are on a different level in terms of their proficiency.

The same bread knife wielded by a child and an experienced chef will produce different results.

Shhh-

Vikir’s gas aura flies in a dark red trajectory, like a cherry at the end of an arrow.

And it goes.

Peo-eog!

It pierced right through the center of the soldier ant’s head, instantly knocking the giant monster to the ground.

‘The soldier ants are so realistic.’

Vikir smiled faintly at the sight of his single arrow.

‘Their strength is their skull, which is broad and flat like a shield, and specialized for headbutting.

Everyone knows this.

But paradoxically, few realize that the creature’s weakness lies in its skull.

This sneaky ant hides its weaknesses in what should be its greatest strength.

“The powerful skull encloses the left and right brains, separately. The only weaknesses are the connecting hippocampus and the cartilages that cover it.”

The skull of the soldier ant is divided into two pieces, with the connecting link at the bottom of the center.

That soft carapace, about half the size of your little fingernail, is the vital area.

An ant that is pierced in this place collapses the coordination system between the left and right brains and dies, literally ‘splitting in half’.

The body is still intact, but the neural and sensory networks have been destroyed, and the ant just lies there, unable to move.

Vikir stepped over the dead soldier ants and continued to fire arrows at them.

If there is an ant that breaks through the defense line and approaches, it mercilessly cuts off its neck with the dagger on its thigh.

His appearance was that of a veteran soldier who had spent decades on the battlefield, and with the mana of a Sword Expert, he was truly a military god.

…Puck! …Puck! …Puck!

The ants continue to die from the flying arrows.

By now, far more were being crushed by their fellows than by Vikir’s arrows.

With their bio-compasses broken, the ants are starting to run backwards, and with the corpses of the giant troopers in the way, the monster waves can’t really get going.

Furthermore, the paralyzing poison that the ants spewed was being inhaled by the cubs, so it’s no wonder that the poisonous fog was concentrated around Vikir.

Vikir climbed up the carcasses of the troopers as a rampart, wiping out the ants in front of him, and when he ran out of arrows, he moved forward to retrieve the ones in front of him.

He would then climb up the body of a soldier ant further in front of him and kill another, and another, and another.

Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, and Bianca, who were watching from the rear, muttered in a daze.

“…This isn’t a dream, is it?”

The third phase, the one that even third-year seniors struggle with, had already passed.

…But.

-Join forces with your teammates to defend against the onslaught of killer ants!

Time remaining until the end of Phase 3: 0 minutes, 0 seconds.

1. Vikir

HP: 100/100

Kill point: 968

Assist point: 5,321

Vikir isn’t just holding his own, he’s pushing back the line itself!

Chapter 184

Aftermath (1)

◆

It was only later that Professor Sadi, who had the magic wall B key, was discovered.

She had been found in a drunken state in a back alley bar outside the academy, only because the barkeep had reported her for vandalism and disturbing the peace.

Professor Banshee Morgue looked down in disgust at Professor Sadi who was being carried in drunkenly.

“Retrieve the keys at once. And open the magic wall.”

And with that, the situation was finally under control.

The rescue took 42 minutes and 13 seconds.

By the time the magic wall was dissolved and the professors rushed inside, it was all over.

The professors didn’t want the outside world to know that they were late because of jurisdictional and liability issues, so they exaggerated Vikir’s heroism even more.

The story of what could have been a catastrophe was dropped and all the focus was on the fact that the academy had the most heroic first-year student in its history.

Meanwhile, Vikir responded briefly to the flood of interview requests.

“It was a team effort, a group of friends.”

Due to the toxic fog that filled the stadium, people were unable to see the details of what was happening inside.

But we do know that Tudor, Sancho, Pigi, Bianca, and others who were later rescued spoke out about Vikir’s heroism.

Meanwhile.

Vikir’s ability to reach Sword Expert rank caused a stir around the school.

Attention was also drawn to how he had managed to ace the defense game with this power, which was strong enough for an 18-year-old, but still insufficient to kill a large number of worker ants and soldier ants.

Vikir readily shared the secret.

“I think you can find it in my midterm exam written answer sheet.”

The midterms are divided into a practical and a written portion, with the practical consisting of defense and attack, and the written portion consisting of free research and an essay.

For his free-research paper, Vikir chose the topic of killer ant strategies, and he had written about the weaknesses of worker ants and soldier ants in his report.

The worker ant’s bio-compass, which detects magic fields, and a vital point in the skull of a soldier ant.

This information would have been incredibly helpful to Imperial armies out in the wilderness slaying monsters.

It’s a treasure chest of tactics that can dramatically reduce the casualty rate of common soldiers and mercenaries, especially those without mana.

A new strategy for the low- to mid-tier monsters that caused the most damage to humanity.

After this was announced, not only the Academy, but the entire Capital, and even the entire Empire, began to tremble.

The result.

“Who is Vikir? The Commander wants to see you.”

“His Highness the Crown Prince has sent a letter of commendation.”

“The head of the Magical Research Institute wants to meet him….”

At least within the Academy, there were almost no people who didn’t know Vikir.

◆

Night sky. The rooftop of a dormitory on a quiet night.

[Exclusive] Hot Star of the Year – Vikir, who is he!? / Views: 129,872

-A boy’s performance at the Cold Warrior Class’s practical evaluation at around 11 a.m. yesterday became the talk of the town… The person who received the award was a freshman Vikir (18), who just entered the school this year… He dug a tunnel and jumped into the poisonous fog to help his four friends in crisis… He set an example for the others by being a man of action… and by discovering a strategy for the ‘Killer Ant’ that was previously unknown… Meanwhile, Vikir’s performance was recognized with a whopping 9,889 points in the practical evaluation, a new record in the academy’s history, given that it was set by a single person…

?(Cold Class 1st year): Wow;; I thought Vikir was just good at studying, but he’s an excellent student. ???

??(Hot Class 2nd year): I was there too. But I barely saw it because of the poisonous fog. ??

??(Hot Class 1st year): Wow, that’s too much exaggeration~~^^ Typical star making~~

???(Cold Class 1st year): If I didn’t see it myself, I would have said ??

???(Hot Class 1st year): Even His Highness the crown prince would look for it, but this…?

??? (Cold Class 1st year): He’s just a commoner, what kind of star is he?

???(Cold Class 1st year): Rumor has it that there’s a royal among the 20th class…?

???(Hot Class 1st year): No way 22222222…

???(Cold Class 2nd year): No way33333333…

??(Cold Class 1st year): Isn’t 9889 points a true story??? That’s a record he set alone????

???(Cold Class 1st year): I thought you knew the strategy.

??? (Hot Class 3rd year): But no matter what, that’s just too good;;;;

???(Cold Class 3rd year): I wonder if that score is possible even with a 4-person graduating class….

??? (Hot Class 4th year): Yes, it is possible. Now I know that strategy haha.

???(Hot Class 3rd year): You don’t know Columbus’s egg? It’s hard at first, but after that it’s easy~

??(Cold Class 1st year): He’s going to be a superstar from tomorrow ??? I should get his autograph already.

.

.

.

Vikir crumpled the newspaper.

“…Yikes.”

In a matter of minutes, he had become a school celebrity.

Somehow, it was getting farther and farther away from Vikir’s intentions.

“This is all because of you.”

Vikir frowned at the young madam, who was hanging from the roof railing, knitting.

[Hack-hack-hack-]

But the cub, who had just finished eating to the point of bursting at the seams, laid down on its belly in front of Vikir’s face as if it was happy.

Vikir sighed and scratched the cub’s belly.

Then.

Pudeudeog-

The thing he’d been waiting for had arrived.

A white owl flew across the night sky and perched on the railing in front of Vikir.

It was a letter from Cindywendy, arriving just in time for the appointment.

Fluttering-

Vikir plucked the letter from the owl’s leg and read it.

The letter is encrypted and cannot be decrypted except by Vikir.

1. 10th Commandment. Information obtained. Time needed to analyze. A month.

2. The Night Hound. Two impersonators appear. One for praise. The other, purpose unknown.

3. Osiris of the House of Baskerville. Family crest emptied. Supposedly headed to the ecliptic Imperial Capital.

After interpreting the keywords, we see that there are three pieces of information listed in order of importance.

The first was about the ten demons (now eight) that Vikir was chasing.

Cindywendy thought she had a clue about the third demon that Vikir would be hunting.

‘However, since I am a very cautious person, it seems like it will take a month to determine whether it is true or not.’

But the information was reliable enough.

Vikir decided to wait patiently.

After all, the last Dantalian hunt had taught him that taking on a demon of Demon King class one-on-one would be too much for him.

‘Until then, I must diligently develop my skills.’

Vikir realized that he needed to extend his time as a Night Hound.

There is nothing better than actual practice to develop your skills.

…But.

‘A copycat?’

The second piece of information took a moment.

Apparently, there are two copycats of the Night Hound.

This was something that Vikir had more or less guessed.

It was a newspaper article from a while back.

[Exclusive] The Night Hound Strikes Again!? / Views: 74,609

-At around 1 a.m. yesterday morning, the Night Hound began to terrorize again.

The place that was destroyed was the ‘Central Clock Tower’, a landmark of the ecliptic. This building, which boasts a long history, is a symbol of imperial power and at the same time contains the legacy of the previous emperor, Peha, who wanted to present the standards of imperial order…… Meanwhile, the number of deaths due to this terrorist attack is…… The imperial family declared that they would put this rare and heinous criminal to death by any means necessary……

[HBO] The worst villain, the Night Hound, how far does his evil go? / Views: 89,269

-The Hound of the Night has struck again.

After destroying the Central Clock Tower at around 1:00am, the Night Hound ravaged the Royal Cemetery at around 4:00am.

The Royal Cemetery is a sanctuary where the brave and fierce generals of the previous era who unified the empire rest, so the fact that they attacked this place was a heinous act that was tantamount to a declaration of war against the entire empire, and indeed the entire human race…… Meanwhile, the number of remains damaged or lost due to this terrorist attack is enormous, and the exact damage has not yet been calculated……

Note that the times mentioned in the article were all around the time Vikir was writing his report for his midterm.

What Vikir didn’t do was blamed on the Night Hound.

“…It’s a copycat.”

A copycat is a criminal who copies a criminal’s behavior when they become famous.

The reasons for copying vary from praise, sympathy, support, rivalry, and cover-ups, but even Cindywendy hadn’t quite figured out the needs of copycats yet.

“One is praising the Night Hound,… and the other is aimless. Hmmm.”

Vikir stroked his chin with his hand.

It was to be expected that the Night Hound would become so infamous that there would be copycats.

Most of the copycats were quickly arrested, so he hadn’t given it much thought.

However, the two copycats mentioned in the newspaper article and Cindywendy’s letter are different.

The force they had seemed to be considerable, and so was their deliberate action.

It was clear that the two copycats mentioned by Cindywendy were probably the same as the real criminals pointed out in this newspaper article.

It was not very pleasing to Vikir that two strong and cunning villains appeared at the same time

Not only would it raise the imperial alarm, but it could also lead to overlapping activity.

“…I’ll have to take a look at the site, see what they’re like.”

Vikir finished reading the letter.

The rest of the letter was of little interest to Vikir, such as the fact that Osiris Le Baskerville, the head of the Baskerville family and Hugo’s eldest son, was away from home.

Vikir burned the letter with an aura on the tip of his fingernail and sent the ashes into the wind.

Just then.

A voice caught Vikir’s attention as he leaned against the rooftop railing, reading the newspaper.

“…?”

Vikir slowly turned his head.

A familiar short cut hair, silver hair blowing in the night breeze, shining brightly under the Milky Way.

Sinclaire, head of the Hot Class.

Considering the place and time, it was a somewhat unexpected meeting.

Chapter 185

Aftermath (2)

◆

“…?”

A pale face with no makeup, short silver hair that hadn’t dried, and the faint scent of shampoo still lingering in the air.

Sinclaire, a commoner with no last name, just a first name. However, she is the one who holds the top spot in the Hot Class with overwhelming grades.

“….”

Vikir didn’t answer, just twitched one eyebrow.

It was a rather unexpected encounter, considering the time and place.

Why would she be here, at this time, in this place?

The question was soon revealed.

“You know too, hyung? This is a famous spot for the Milky Way.”

Sinclaire smiled broadly and held out something to Vikir. It was a small can of beer.

Phew.

Sinclaire opened the beer and quickly brought the foam to her lips.

Sinclaire, whose white beard suddenly grew, grinned and handed Vikir a beer as well.

“Two cans, but I’ll get you a special one.”

“…Thanks.”

Vikir hesitated for a moment before accepting the beer.

“I didn’t expect to see you here at this time of night. I thought I had the place to myself. I always come here when I’m in a bad mood and look at the Milky Way.”

Sinclaire suddenly seemed to be in a better mood.

Something had happened, it seemed.

But Vikir had something else on his mind.

‘…This was a dangerous place. I think I’ll have to change my meeting point with Cindywendy.’

From now on, she thinks, ‘If I come to this place, I might run into him from time to time.’

And the man thinking, ‘I should never come to this place again.’

It was a rather ironic dream.

Just then, Sinclaire put down her beer can and took an interest in the owl sitting next to Vikir.

“An owl? How cute. Did you get a letter?”

[All-pam].

“Ahahaha, that’s an unusual cry.”

Sinclaire gently stroked the owl’s round head.

Then she looked back at Vikir.

“Did you get a letter?”

“Mmm.”

“To whom?”

“….”

Not knowing what else to call her, Vikir remained silent.

Then Sinclaire’s eyes narrowed.

“You’re a girl?”

The owl’s head had a greenish-gold ribbon in it, the color of Cindywendy’s hair.

Vikir nodded silently, knowing that it was indeed a girl.

Sinclaire’s expression hardened slightly.

“Wow~ I see a relationship on academy, hyung. You’re confident that your grades won’t drop while dating, right? Is it good to do CC? Well, who among freshmen doesn’t have a dream of becoming a CC? ….”

“It’s not like that.”

Vikir briefly dismissed Sinclaire’s comment.

Vikir’s adamant denial of a romantic relationship caused Sinclaire to pause for a moment, then exhale.

It was an oddly relieved sigh.

“Hyung, if… this is a secret relationship and you’re hiding it from me, I’m really disappointed. We’re supposed to be able to talk about things like this between us, we’re best friends. If that’s the case, do you need to tell me? Really!”

…Best friends? Vikir didn’t understand, but didn’t bother to ask.

After that, Sinclaire chattered and told many different stories to himself.

Vikir was a little surprised, as she wasn’t usually this talkative at school.

Sinclaire waved her half-finished beer wistfully, then spoke up as if she’d had an idea.

“Oh. Hyung, what is your relationship with the president?”

When Sinclaire said President, she meant Student Council President Dolores.

If asked what his relationship with Dolores was, Vikir could confidently answer with one word.

“Nothing.”

“I didn’t think so?”

Sinclaire narrowed her eyes and elbowed Vikir in the side.

“If it’s no relationship, why has the chairman been looking for you like that for the past few days?”

“?”

Vikir’s eyes widened as if he’d never heard of it before.

Why is Dolores looking for him?

He’s had too many meetings lately.

To the principal, to the president, to the ledger, to the director, to the president, to the so-and-so, to the so-and-so…… I was just getting stressed out about why so many people were looking for it.

Even the crown prince said he would give me a commendation.

“…I don’t have time to study, let alone assassinate.”

Cindywendy’s comment that it would take a month to analyze the information was almost considered good news.

Sinclaire shrugged.

“I don’t know. Anyway, President Dolores has been secretly looking for you lately.”

“Then that’s why she came to the archery range, to find me.”

“Eh? Why didn’t you see her?”

“…We crossed paths.”

I can’t tell her that I turned into a dog, hid, and then ran away to avoid being neutered, so I give her a quick aside.

Sinclaire nodded and drained the rest of the beer.

Phew.

The burnt barley scent of the black beer spreads across the night sky.

She leaned against the railing, propping her chin with her hand, looking somewhat helpless.

“I envy you.”

“?”

Vikir folds his arms and shakes his head.

Sinclaire smirked, wiping the beer foam from the corner of her mouth with her thumb.

“Hyung, you’re always like that.”

“?”

“Not asking first. It’s my style.”

Vikir laughed softly at Sinclaire’s comment.

Born to be a hound, bred to be a hound, Vikir is not used to questioning anyone.

It was a hound’s virtue to stand still and wait for his master to speak first.

Are you tired of people always approaching you first and making noise?

Perhaps Vikir’s attitude struck a different chord with Sinclaire.

“The reason I said I was jealous…… I just said that because I was jealous of my hyung.”

“Is that so?”

“Yeah. We’re in the same class and there’s a huge gap between us.”

Sinclaire looked back at Vikir with a puzzled gaze.

A first-year student who ranked first in his class and had already published three or four research papers that would shake up the academic world.

A monstrous irregular, far beyond the level of a typical undergraduate.

For example, the level of a first-year undergraduate student is as follows.

-Professor: Today’s lecture is on how to eat salmon deliciously~.

-First-year undergraduate student 1: Wow, what’s wrong with salmon?

-First-year undergraduate student 2: Is salmon edible or not?

-First-year undergraduate student 3: What is flounder for?

And then by the end of the fourth year, it’s a little different.

-Professor: Today I’m going to lecture you on how to eat salmon deliciously~.

-Fourth-year undergraduate student 1: ….

-Professor: ….

-Fourth-year undergraduate student 1: ….

-Professor: What are you doing, you’re not going to catch salmon.

First and fourth years are worlds apart in terms of the depth of subject matter covered.

But Vikir was already far beyond the level of even this fourth-year student, and had reached the level of a graduate student, or even a professor.

And what about his practical grades?

Vikir, who had been suspected of being a Beginner, let alone an Expert, revealed his hidden Expert level skills.

It was a level that was unimaginable for someone from a commoner’s background, one that was on par with, and perhaps even better than, the great late-period experts of the Seven Families.

“Written and practical. You’re a man to be reckoned with, hyung.”

“….”

“I hear you’ve already been meeting with celebrities a generation or two above you. Everyone’s jealous.”

Vikir was annoyed by it, but to others, it seemed like it was something they needed and wanted.

But Vikir knew better.

“….”

Money? Power? Honor? All of those things will be worthless rubbish when the Age of Destruction begins.

When that happens, all existing order will crumble and all values will be overturned.

As a great writer once said, ‘an era in which survival becomes a cheap joke’ will soon arrive.

“It’s all for nothing.”

At Vikir’s words, Sinclaire shakes her head again.

“You’re not of this world, sometimes.”

The words made Vikir’s chest heat up a little.

Sinclaire smiled again.

“The way you talk, you sound so old – no one would ever think you’re 18! Then, why don’t you leave this world and go into hiding somewhere?”

With a clink, the empty beer can crunches.

Sinclaire placed it in the palm of her hand and drew on her mana.

Crunch!

A white-hot flame bursts forth, melting the beer can.

It soon takes on a new appearance thanks to the mana of the iron attribute.

A rabbit with a pocket watch, an elaborate metal figurine, rests in Sinclaire’s palm.

“By the way, did you hear the rumor?”

Sinclaire said, fingering the rabbit.

“This time, I mean, among the classmates of the class of 20, a royal family member whose identity was hidden entered the school.”

“Isn’t that just gossip circulating in the stock market?”

“…Hmmm, well, what do you think?”

Sinclaire replied in a somewhat questioning tone.

“If it’s imperial blood, it’s probably not normal talent, since it’s descended from the first emperor who was a great prophet, right?”

“….”

“You shouldn’t stand out too much at the beginning of the semester, so you’ll have to keep your talents hidden, so it’s worth it to get in. Perhaps you’re looking to recruit someone to work with you? I think so.”

“….”

“But you wouldn’t be able to hide your skills until the moment of truth, like if your close friends were in danger during a test.”

“Enough.”

Vikir dismissed Sinclaire’s words again.

“I’m not royalty.”

“…I never said you were royalty.”

“?”

Vikir scratched his head.

Sinclaire merely smirked.

It reminded Vikir of a certain scene.

‘Come to think of it, Sinclaire, this woman was a mystery to me before.’

Vikir remembered before the regression.

After graduating from the Academy, Sinclaire lost contact with all of her classmates and predecessors.

She disappears from the world, from history, forever.

Before the regression, the Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro, who had grown quite a bit older since graduating from the Academy, would often have conversations about “what Sinclaire is doing now?” and “she’s probably doing well somewhere, since she didn’t miss out on being Head of the Hot Class for four years,” and “where did she come from and where did she go?”.

We would reminisce about the amazing grades and records she had set when she was a student at the academy.

…When Vikir was thinking about this.

“Hey. What are you doing after midterms this time?”

Sinclaire asked again.

“We have a week off after midterms. Do you have any plans then?”

“I do.”

“Like what?”

“Back and lower body, and archery training.”

“…Not workouts and training.”

Sinclaire stuck out her lips with a sullen expression.

Then she spoke.

“Come over to my place when you’re free. Let’s have a meal.”

Sinclaire’s invitation was a bit of a surprise.

Vikir raised one eyebrow.

Come to think of it, Sinclaire had made a similar offer to Vikir once before.

It was back when he was volunteering at an orphanage.

Dantalian’s act of collecting donations for the parentless children, and Sinclaire and Vikir’s conversation went something like this, with Sinclaire asking him if he didn’t want to donate.

“Hyung. You don’t donate?”

‘…I don’t have any money.’

He said he didn’t really have any.

Vikir had decided not to accept any support from the Baskervilles.

However, it was not currently receiving financial support from Cindywendy.

He didn’t want to arouse any unnecessary suspicion with his cover as a commoner.

Anyway. Sinclaire was a bit puzzled at the time.

‘Money? Why don’t you have any money? You’re a student at the Academy, aren’t you being a bit harsh? The poor kids here don’t have parents, and we should be helping them.’

‘There is no need for parents.’

“Huh?”

“They have to navigate the world on their own. Parents are only functional during childhood, when help from others is essential, but otherwise they are unnecessary.”

Vikir’s thoughts were the same then as they are now.

Why do I feel sorry for children in orphanages?

They have everything they need to survive, except that their parents have been replaced by state institutions.

They get the nutrients they need and the education they deserve.

It’s a much happier and more comfortable life than being raised as a hound in Baskerville.

The world is full of pain, something to be fought and overcome, and parents are just the initial guides to help with the first tutorials in that long fight.

Vikir sees parents as merely functional, and that’s a natural value in the Baskervilles, where he’s lived his entire life, and in the Age of Destruction, where he’s lived half his life.

But those who have lived through war and those who have not cannot understand each other.

Vikir realized that he might seem a bit strange to those who had not yet lived through the Age of Destruction.

So he had no expectations.

…However.

“You have to come, okay?”

Sinclaire looked at Vikir with a seriousness he hadn’t seen before.

Instead of her usual curious and bubbly demeanor, it was heavy and wistful.

She was looking at Vikir as if she understood and empathized with him.

As she had in the past.

“Now, if you’ll excuse me, it’s almost time for my shift!”

Sinclaire dropped something in front of Vikir and walked toward the rooftop exit.

‘She’s got a part-time job, at this hour?’

Vikir tilted his head.

But Sinclaire just smirked and waved.

And then.

…Bang!

The rooftop door slammed shut.

“….”

Vikir turned his head to look at the object Sinclaire had set down in front of him.

There was a rabbit with a pocket watch, scurrying about in a hurry, staring at him.

Chapter 186

Aftermath (3)

◆

The midterm exam period, which felt long, is already halfway over.

And one quiet afternoon, on the sunny terrace of a cafe.

“I hear you’ve been very busy lately.”

“It’s kind of like that.”

Dolores, the student council president, and Vikir, a first-year student, were having a conversation.

As the head of the newspaper club, Dolores took advantage of this opportunity to honestly say things she had not been able to say before.

“I’m really sorry about the pissing… incident, and I didn’t explain it in time and it got out of hand. And I’m so grateful that you stood up for me.”

“We can make mistakes, that’s what makes us human.”

Vikir nodded without thinking.

Just then.

“…!”

Dolores froze for a moment when she heard Vikir’s response.

Suddenly, a voice echoed in her ears.

‘We can make mistakes. That’s what makes us human.’

To her surprise, it was the comforting voice of the Night Hound she had heard that night.

The same comfort for the same worry, but from a different person. Could this be a coincidence?

‘…Sure, it’s a coincidence.’

Dolores laughed a little at the ridiculousness of her own fleeting thought.

It’s a comforting thought. It could happen to anyone, she thought.

Whatever.

Dolores had organized this to help the juniors in the club before their upcoming attack test.

Vikir tilted his head.

“The genealogy you passed on to me through Pigi the other day has helped me prepare well for the written test. Thank you.”

Since strategies for ‘killer ants’ often come up in the notes, and studying them can be used as a secondary skill in defense games, it’s a good idea to research killer ants when choosing a topic for free research in the first place.

It saves you from having to study them twice.

But Dolores shook her head with a faint smile.

“Genealogy. Every other third year has one. Mine is just a little more organized than the others, nothing special, and I admire you for doing legendary research with it.”

“Yeah. You’re like that too.”

“…You’re being honest, too.”

Dolores smirked at Vikir’s casual admission.

It was starting to look like this new kid’s cockiness was coming into its own.

“Anyway, I called you here because I wanted to give you some advice for your upcoming attack test. I don’t think you’ll need it, seeing as how you’re shooting a bow in your defense test, but just in case.”

Once again, Dolores explained the structure of the midterm.

“Like I said, the midterm is 10% written, 50% defense, and 40% attack.”

As of yesterday, the 10% written portion of the midterm and the 50% defense portion of the midterm were completed, leaving only the 40% attack portion of the midterm.

The written portion of the exam is actually not that important, only about 10% of the total score, but the defense and attack portions are 50% and 40% respectively.

While the defense test is played in teams of four, the attack test is solely solo performance.

The structure of the attack test is very simple.

It’s a one-on-one, “professor vs. student” match.

The rules of the test are also much simpler than the defense test: you fight a golem controlled by a professor and win.

The test golem is a typical entry-level stone golem with one head, one body, two large arms, and two legs.

What makes it special is that the professors, who are experts in combat, control the golems with their own bodies.

The golem mimics the movements of the professor from a distance.

When a student faces a golem that moves in exactly the same way, at the same speed, and with the same combat style as the professor, they can’t help but feel like they’re fighting the professor directly.

However, since the opponent is a golem, the student is able to deploy the best kills he or she can, and the significance of this is that the student’s true combat power can be measured.

Students have to fight against the professor, who is a master of combat, but they can feel the realism of real life through a confrontation with a strong opponent.

The rules were designed to minimize the number of casualties, as the professors would be unable to respond to the many variables created by so many students.

Dolores held up her index and middle fingers in a serious manner.

“First of all, there are two problems with your attack test.”

Dolores folded her index finger.

“First, archers are at a disadvantage when facing a golem one-on-one.”

In the defense game, archers have an advantage.

They can stand at a distance and score points while their teammates’ tanks either catch most of them or only occasionally miss.

But in attack, it’s different.

Since it’s a 1v1 match, there are no tanks to line up in front of you, so you’re on your own.

The moment you give the golem any distance, it’s over.

Furthermore, the professor controlling the golem won’t be hurting himself, so he’ll just charge at you and you won’t be able to inflict any pain, so there’s no point in hitting him.

This means that the only way for the archer to deal a fatal blow to the golem is to run here and there, creating distance and unleashing powerful arrows from time to time, which is impossible if they can’t keep up with the professor’s speed.

So what archers gain on the defense test, they lose on the attack test, and that’s how the whole thing balances out.

…But Dolores wasn’t done worrying yet.

She raised her middle finger, still looking serious.

“Second. The professor who will be in charge of you is… that ‘Professor Sadi’.”

Vikir’s eyes narrowed at that.

Professor Sadi.

His full name was Donatien Alphonse Fran?ois Sadi de Sade.

“You mean the pathetic professor who disappeared with the B-key to the Magic Wall and was found high and dry?”

“…Yes.”

Dolores nodded with a deep sigh at Vikir’s question.

Professor Sadi. She’s technically a ‘parachute’ figure.

The last lineage of the Marquis de Sade, who fell due to an unpleasant incident in the distant past and is now almost extinct.

Unable to watch the descendants of a once noble nobleman become miserable, she was transferred from a lowly position in the imperial palace to a professorship at the academy, which is probably similar to the practice of giving honorary honors to nobles.

Dolores shook her head.

“She’s got a weird personality and a terrible work ethic, which makes her the number one professor to avoid among students. In fact, most of her classes are canceled for lack of interest. I’ve been in a few of her classes, and nine times out of ten she cancels them without warning, and that’s first period in the morning. Oh, and the one time she did cancel, she did it with notice, so I never got to attend.”

When the good and gentle Dolores says something like this, it really says it all.

In fact, Vikir also occasionally heard Professor Banshee and other professors badmouth Professor Sadi.

She didn’t seem to have a very good reputation, even among the professors themselves.

But Dolores, being the nice person that she is, had a few nice things to say about Professor Sadi.

“But one thing is for sure, she’s good at what she does. In addition to teaching at the Academy, she’s an advisor to the Imperial Guard on arrests and torture, and I hear she’s recently been helping the military track down criminals.”

“ …Tracking criminals?”

“Who else?”

At Dolores’ words, Vikir nodded.

“A criminal of extraordinary proportions who has shaken the entire empire. A villain so vicious that even the Empire’s military was mobilized.”

I speak of the Night Hound.

‘……I guess there’s a tracer who looks like an idiot.’

Vikir thought for a moment, then shook his head.

From the sounds of it, Professor Sadi was a lazy person who was very dissatisfied with life.

Why would a drunkard like that, who lives her life by getting drunk and letting things slide, be so eager to capture the Night Hound?

Vikir quickly pushed the thought of Professor Sadi out of his mind.

Dolores, however, was not to be deterred and continued her warning.

“Professor Sadi has one nasty habit: whenever she sees a talented student, she tries to ruin their path.”

“In what way?”

“Well, she beats them so badly in the name of dueling that they become crippled… or she leaves them with severe ‘post-traumatic stress disorder’… This is a rumor, but there are also rumors that she sexually traumatizes them, male or female. You should be careful.”

“Sexually?”

“…Well, not the scores. Sexual stuff.”

“Why would she do that?”

“I don’t know. They say it’s because she’s the last of a fallen marquise, so she has an inferiority complex about the descendants of the now successful family, but only she knows if that’s true.”

Professor Sadi is notorious for bullying students who are talented, come from noble families, pretty, handsome, or just plain good.

Now that Vikir had performed so well in his defense and written exams, it was likely that Professor Sadi would target him.

That worried Dolores to no end.

Just then.

“Good morning, it’s a beautiful day, isn’t it? Here’s your parfait and espresso!”

A cheerful voice broke in between Vikir and Dolores.

…Clink!

Cold and hot cups were placed on the table.

And the part-time worker who brought them smiled broadly at Vikir and Dolores.

She was Sinclaire.

Dolores’s eyes widened and she asked.

“Sinclaire, do you work here?”

“Yes, Ms. President, only on weekend mornings! I was a replacement last night and this afternoon.”

Beside Sinclaire, who answered cheerfully, was Bianca, who looked pale.

Dolores asked them both.

“Why are you two working here?”

“Because tuition is coming up soon! I need to earn money for school, hehe. The first year scholarship doesn’t cover 100%, and I wanted to get some part-time cafe experience while I’m in school….”

Sinclaire was still a cheerful high school student (苦学生).

Bianca, on the other hand, had a simple reason.

“I like their uniforms.”

Vikir scratched his head at that, but Dolores nodded in understanding.

Meanwhile, Sinclaire set down the unordered biscuits and pies on the table.

“This is a service under my authority! Hyung, do you like sweets?”

“No, I don’t.”

“I’ll keep that in mind next time!”

Sinclaire was still cheerful.

She turned to Vikir as if she’d just remembered something.

“Oh, by the way. Did hyung-ah pay his school fees this time?”

“No.”

“When are you going to pay it?”

“Hmm.”

Vikir stroked his chin.

He’d been so busy lately, he hadn’t thought about tuition.

I’ve decided not to seek assistance from the Baskervilles, and it’ll be a while before I can contact the Cindywendy, who have entered the Red and Black Depth to trade with the Ballak.

Much of the cost would be covered by the scholarship anyway, so the immediate out-of-pocket expenses weren’t too great.

So Vikir asked Sinclaire a question.

“I have a question about this cafe.”

Vikir rarely asks a question first, so not only Sinclaire but also Dolores and Bianca turn to look at him.

Finally, under the three women’s gaze, Vikir spoke briefly.

“Do you have any men’s jobs?”

Chapter 188

Attack Land (1)

◆

The final exam of the midterms had begun.

Students and golems faced each other in a large, circular arena.

On the opposite side of the arena, the professor stood alone.

The student’s opponent, the golem, copies the professor’s movements.

Whiz-pop!

Clank… thunk!

When the professor swings his right arm, the golem swings its right arm, and when the professor leaps, the golem leaps.

The professor has to control his “avatar” golem from a distance to take on the student, but in this case, the sense of distance becomes a handicap.

Then it was time for the real thing, and the students on the stage faced off against the golem.

The students had to use all their strength against the golem, which mimicked the professor’s body movements.

Meanwhile, the attack test was divided into sections based on the order of the attendance list, with a specific professor in charge of sections A through B, and one professor facing about a hundred students.

Naturally, with different professors controlling the golems, the golems’ fighting styles would also vary.

A professor with a generally gentle personality moves the golem in a defensive manner, while a professor with an impatient and aggressive personality uses the golem offensively.

Therefore, students had to memorize where their name was located in the attendance list and identify their professor in advance to study his/her fighting style.

This was a test designed by the academy’s first principal, who believed that education is more effective when you know and analyze the person who will teach you before you learn.

Meanwhile.

“Iyab!”

Tudor, who was being tested for the first time, was holding a spear and fighting hard.

…Pow!

The tip of the spear exploded with a powerful aura.

If it was a real man-to-man duel, no matter how strong the professor was, he wouldn’t have been able to unleash such a lively attack.

But the opponent was a golem, and the real Professor was moving safely at a distance.

So without hesitation, Tudor plunged his spear into it.

Boom, boom, boom!

The golem, which was radiating magic, was knocked back by Tudor’s aura.

However.

[Not yet].

A familiar voice spoke from the golem’s mouth.

Professor Banshee Morgue. The Academy’s leading candidate for Vice Principal.

Even though he was on the far side of the training grounds, he knew exactly how far away Tudor was.

Chaaaah!

The golem snaps its fingers, forming a bond, and thorny vines grow around Tudor’s body.

“Huh!”

Tudor ducks his head.

[The vines are fake].

The golem, controlled by Professor Banshee, immediately throws a giant punch.

Tudor barely twisted his waist to avoid it.

[Fist is also fake.]

There was no way to avoid the sole of the golem’s foot as it launched a back kick.

…Pow!

Tudor was knocked off his feet.

The golem’s shadow casts an eerie shadow over Tudor, who is covered in dirt and thrown out of the field.

The click of Professor Banshee’s tongue comes through the golem’s mouth.

[Did you think that because I’m a mage I wouldn’t use my fists and feet?]

“Ugh… Yeah.”

[The purpose of battle is to win. Just because you’re a mage doesn’t mean you have to use magic to win. You have to use whatever you have to win. Whether that be fists, kicks, teeth, or whatever].

“Thank you for your teaching.”

Professor Banshee was a hated human being, but he was a great teacher.

Tudor bowed politely and exited the arena.

-Ring!

.

Tudor’s score was then displayed in a magical status window.

.

-Effective hits: 12 (1 point each)

-Effective dodges: 20 times (1 point each)

-Effective Defense: 3 (1 point each)

-Critical hits: 0 (10 points each)

=Total Score: 35 points

A total score of 35 points. By far the highest score of any first year student.

“Good!”

Tudor threw his hands in the air and called out in triumph.

He succeeded in delivering 12 effective hits to the golem controlled by professor Banshee, successfully evaded the golem’s attacks 20 times, and properly blocked the golem’s attacks 3 times.

I didn’t manage to land a critical hit against the skillfully maneuvered Banshee’s golem, but it didn’t matter.

Professors, masters of combat, would never allow a critical hit against a student.

Tudor nodded to Dolores, the student council president, who was watching from a distance.

It helped that Dolores had given him a heads-up on the fighting style of Professor Banshee, who was now in charge of Tudor.

Though he hadn’t expected to use his feet at the end.

“At least you scored better than those triplets from Baskerville.”

Tudor smirked as he looked to the other side of the arena.

There, he could see three people standing arm-in-arm: Highbro, Middlebro, and Lowbro.

Highbro had a score of 34, Middlebro and Lowbro both had a score of 33, and they were in first and second place until Tudor showed up.

Tudor taunted the triplets with a nasty look.

“Hey, how’s that for being a dick to your friends?”

But.

“….”

“….”

“….”

Somehow, the Baskerville triplets didn’t respond to Tudor’s taunt.

They just stood there like carved wooden chickens.

Tudor, who had just taunted his dumbfounded classmates, stuck his tongue back in his cheek.

“What is it with them, always picking fights, and now they won’t take a fight at all?”

Tudor wasn’t sure why the Baskervilles’ triplets had suddenly become like that, but he thought it was a good thing.

Tudor’s taunt fell on the wrong person.

“Damn, I’m pissed at that Tudor asshole!”

Bianca, stomping her foot at Tudor.

.

-Effective hits: 7 (1 point each)

-Effective dodges: 24 times (1 point each)

-Effective Defense: 0 (1 point each)

-Critical hits: 0 (10 points each)

=Total score: 31 points

Bianca is an archer, which puts her at a disadvantage in 1v1s like this.

Especially against a golem that knows no pain.

“Ahhh, I can’t believe I lost to Tudor! It’s all because of the weird test structure. It’s disadvantageous for archers, the balance sucks!”

“You know, I don’t remember you mentioning balance once when you were raking in the points on the Defense exam.”

“Why would you bring up the defense exam if you had nothing to say?”

“Of course you’re bringing it up so you don’t have anything to say.”

Tudor and Bianca started fussing over the scores again.

And then I said.

“Uhahahaha! How’s that, you foolish things!”

Granola, the second in charge of the Hot Class, finished the test with a victorious smile.

.

-Effective hits: 11 (1 point each)

-Effective dodges: 22 times (1 point each)

-Effective Defense: 2 (1 point each)

-Critical hits: 0 (10 points each)

=Total score: 35 points

He finished the exam with the same score as Tudor, the head of the Cold Class.

Apparently, his original advisor, Professor Banshee, became the one in charge of the exam, and he scored better than expected.

In other words, he was pretty lucky.

Granola looked over at Tudor, who was cheered on by his fellow Cold Class.

“Is this a tie? I think you and I will have almost the same midterm scores, right?”

“Don’t rub it in, we broke the class record on the defense test.”

“Our individual scores were tie, and let’s not forget that I have a higher written score than you!”

Tudor smirked at Granola’s arrogance, as if he wasn’t worth the trouble.

“I don’t know what you’re talking about. The Cold Class hasn’t released the final weapon for the attack test yet.”

“What? Isn’t the final weapon yours or Bianca’s? You’re tied with me, and Bianca’s dead.”

“What!? Who wants to die? I’m going to tear that gloomy bastard up and put it on top of my porridge…… !?”

Granola’s answer made Bianca behind him jump, but she was quickly silenced by Tudor’s urging.

Tudor smirked and looked at Granola.

“1:1 strongest. Even in a one-on-one fight against a golem, there’s someone much stronger than me.”

“…!”

Granola’s expression hardened at that.

Yes, even the arrogant Granola was wary of Tudor and Bianca.

In fact, there was someone even more threatening than Tudor and Bianca.

Sancho Barataria of the Class A Cold Warriors.

Tudor exclaimed triumphantly.

“Sancho is a northern warrior who can beat a bear with his bare hands without a handful of mana! Moreover, if it were an attack test with unlimited mana and unlimited number of kills, what would the result be?” “It will be on a different level from when Naphtali was doing it!”

At that, Granola and the other Hot Class students grunted and averted their gazes.

They admit it.

Of all the students in both the cold and Hot Class, it was Sancho who was expected to score the highest on the attack test.

“Sancho must be number one in the Cold Warrior Class, right?”

“That’s right. Have you seen his size? His fist is bigger than my head.”

“Doesn’t he just rip apart golems with his strength?”

“Maybe he’ll set an all-time record for individual scores.”

All the students were chattering the same thing.

But.

What happened next sent all the students, cold and hot, into a panic.

…Thud!

Sancho, covered in blood, fell helplessly to his knees.

On top of him, a status window reflected the cold reality.

.

-Effective hits: 8 (1 point each)

-Effective dodges: 9 (1 point each)

-Effective Defense: 0 (1 point each)

-Critical hits: 0 (10 points each)

=Total score: 17 points

That’s a ridiculous score.

He only managed to land 8 effective hits and 9 dodges.

He even had zero effective defenses, meaning he was hit by almost every attack.

A score of 17 is not even mediocre.

It was truly a shock that Sancho, who can score high scores in the late 30s, barely received this score.

Even worse, Sancho collapsed in a heap as soon as he finished the test.

The gaping wounds and dripping blood made the atmosphere in the testing room even more gruesome.

“Sancho!”

Dolores rushed over to the injured junior.

Dolores helped Sancho stagger to his feet and heal him.

Soon, a crowd of students gathered around Sancho and Dolores.

At the front of the line was their roommate and best friend, Tudor.

“Hey, Sancho, are you okay?”

“…The president heal me, so I’m fine.”

Sancho’s deep sigh shows his self-destruction for failing the exam.

I also feel sorry for not being able to establish the prestige of Cold Warrior Class.

“….”

A vein appeared on Dolores’ forehead.

She patted Sancho on the back a few times, then stood up and glared at the professor standing on the other side of the arena.

The pilot of the golem that had been in charge of Sancho just moments ago.

“Hohoho- boring.”

It’s a laugh that seems to tickle, but underneath it all, there’s a deep sense of extreme boredom and pessimism.

Sadi de Sade, aka Ms. Sadi.

A young female professor who was considered the worst disgrace of the Colosseo Academy.

Chapter 190

Attack Land (3)

◆

“….”

Vikir stood there, his face still expressionless.

And behind him, a female student with white hair walked out.

Sinclaire, a head of the Hot Class.

She walked toward the stage, as if sensing it was her turn.

“Class A, Hot Mages. Number 69. Are you Sinclaire?”

By this time, she heard Professor Sadi’s voice calling out Sinclaire’s name.

It was a line of genuine interest.

Despite being from a commoner’s background, Sinclaire’s performance in practical and written exams is better than anyone else’s.

Not only that, but she has a reputation as an alpha girl who takes multiple general education classes, clubs, volunteer work, and a part-time job in her spare time.

In fact, Sinclaire’s name is known to students, professors, and even some of the most polarizing parents who are interested in the inner goings-on at the academy.

…Is that why? Professor Sadi had her eye on Sinclaire.

Dolores stepped up to Sinclaire’s side, looking concerned.

“Sinclaire, you might as well drop out of the exam. In addition to being a professor at the Academy, Professor Sadi is an advisor to the Imperial Guard’s Arrest and Torture Unit, which means she’s very capable, and she’s just as likely to do you harm as she is to be a cranky professor who’ll try to bully you if she sees a talented student.”

But. Sinclaire shook his head, looking more determined than ever.

“I was expecting that.”

“…What?”

“I’ve been expecting it, more or less, since my proctor became Professor Sadi.”

Sinclaire lifted her head. Her sparkling gaze was fixed on Dolores.

“I appreciate your concern, Ms. President. But I need to do well on these exams so I can get a scholarship to pay for my tuition.”

“…I see what you’re saying, but Professor Sadi’s case isn’t typical. Even if you fail this exam, I’m sure your professors in other subjects will make up for it somehow, whether it’s by giving you extra credit or extra points or whatever.”

“…But.”

Sinclaire turned her head.

She could see a number of students lying there, groaning.

The damage was especially severe among the Hot Class, who had relatively little stamina compared to the Cold Class.

Seeing this, Sinclaire bit her lip tightly.

“I can’t hide from the person who made my friends look like that.”

“….”

“I want to take the test on the same terms as my friends, Ms. President.”

Sinclaire’s desperation was enough to get through to Dolores.

Why don’t I know, Dolores had been a freshman herself, when her friendships with her classmates were strong.

“…Yes. There is such a thing as comradeship and country love.”

“Thank you, Ms. President!”

“No problem. But if you’re in any real danger, you should give up the test and run right to me. I’ll heal you.”

“Yes!”

Sinclaire replied with a flourish, and leaped up onto the stage.

Now, Professor Sadi’s curious gaze is on Sinclaire.

The innocent look of a child looking down at an insect to tear apart.

“Oh, so you’re ‘the’ Sinclaire, the one with the good grades, the great combat skills, the sweet personality, the good nature, and all the classes, volunteer work, and clubs?”

“Thank you. You’re flattering me.”

“Wow, you have a nice voice. You have a pretty face, too….”

Professor Sadi began to ramble on.

“It must be worth ruining.”

The atmosphere would have been quite warm if it weren’t for that last comment.

Tsutsutsutsuts…

At this point, Professor Sadi’s aura began to radiate.

Professor Sadi’s avatar, a mud golem that closely resembled her figure, stood up on its slender legs.

In its hand it held a long vine whip.

The golem’s mouth moved to convey Professor Sadi’s voice.

[There’s been a ridiculous rumor going around the school lately… that I’m bullying a talented student?]

Sinclaire cringes at the words.

Rumors? Surely Professor Sadi’s true intentions were not jealousy or inferiority complex?

Sinclaire was confused for a moment, wondering if she had misunderstood.

But Professor Sadi’s next words were certainly more insane.

[That must be a real misunderstanding, because… I bully everyone, talented or not, hohohoho!]

At the same time, the golem’s whip flew out.

Crack-

With a loud crack, the stone floor cracked.

Sinclaire ducked and dodged, but the whip moved as if it were alive, chasing after Sinclaire’s feet.

Kiririk-

With a vicious motion, like a salmosa…

[Except that the talented ones struggle a little longer, so they’re unusually full of it. Hohoho!]

“….”

[Was that Sancho back there? I guess he had some expectations, but the academy’s standards have dropped a lot, and such a lump of lousy talent is the ace in the hole for Cold Class. I’m disappointed, I’m disappointed].

Professor Sadi licks her dry lips with her tongue and continues to flick it into thin air.

[How about you? Try acting like an ace in the Hot Class game~]

At the same time, the whip makes countless bends and knots, bursting the air around it.

Puff-puff-puff! Crack, crack, crack, crack!

The surrounding cobblestones explode.

Sinclaire cast a wind spell on her body to help her move faster.

“Haste!”

With a quickened movement, Sinclaire dodged the noose created by the whip and moved to the edge of the training grounds.

Speed like the wind, indeed.

But.

[Haste? That’s how fast you can move with a haste? Kid, if you do that in real life, you’ll die right away~]

Professor Sadi’s golem caught up with Sinclaire’s movements far too easily.

“Huh!”

This gasp came not only from Sinclaire’s mouth, but also from the mouths of all the students and professors watching the test.

Sadi piloted the golem with such ease that even the professors were amazed at her godlike skill.

Ordinary professors, no matter how skilled in combat they were, could not control a golem from a distance so perfectly.

A body synchronized to a golem has a slight slowdown when moving, and the golem also has a momentary synchronization delay when it is avatarized.

Additionally, the distance jamming would be more challenging as you would be trying to intercept a distant opponent, and you would be unable to calculate the difference in length or thickness between your limbs and the golem’s limbs, which would introduce small errors.

But.

[Hohohoho- you don’t get points for running away, do you?]

Professor Sadi had none of that.

Her incredible focus and physicality flowed like water as if she was actually fighting the student in front of her.

It’s as if she’s actually in close combat with the person in front of her.

“That’s right. I don’t get points for running away, so thanks for the advice!”

Sinclaire stood firm and cast a spell.

A multiple spell cast.

Three circles, three layers, nine mana circles in all.

Quack, quack, quack, quack!

A whopping three Class 3 magic spells exploded out.

A song of fire, ice, and wind.

A tremendous talent rarely seen at her age. In terms of mana affinity alone, she could match or surpass the mages of House Morgue.

However.

[Hohohoho-]

Seeing the spears of fire, ice, and wind, Professor Sadi could only chuckle softly.

[Hohohoho- The Aces of the Hot Class are nothing special, either. I would rather be bothered by the big guys from Varangian…… ]

Professor Sadi muttered, her interest waning.

And then.

Pfft!

With a single kick, all of Sinclaire’s magic was destroyed.

“Kuck!”

Mana flowed back as the spells were forcibly canceled.

Sinclaire stumbled backwards, blood pouring from her eyes, nose, mouth, and ears.

Above her head, the golem’s fists and kicks began to rain down.

Quack, quack, quack, quack!

The physicality of Professor Sadi’s golems was astonishing.

The amount of mana that can be injected into the golem is obviously limited, but Professor Sadi chooses the moves that are most efficient with that limited amount of mana.

This, coupled with the unparalleled physicality of the explosive bursts of mana, results in an unbelievable level of control over the golem.

Insanely flexible, bizarrely contorted, incomprehensibly bent, and monstrously fast.

It’s as if its entire body is one long whip.

“Kyaaaagh!”

Sinclaire couldn’t help but scream.

Sinclaire stumbles backwards, frantically dodging the golem’s fists and kicks.

And then she hears the voice of the Grim Reaper in her ear.

[Oh, no, my dear, there’s something else you’ve forgotten. Have you forgotten my whip?]

The golem’s fists and kicks are so fearsome that she forgets for a moment.

Professor Sadi’s primary weapon is a whip.

“…!?”

Sinclaire snapped out of her reverie, and she could see the whip stalks sprawling around her body like some kind of bird.

…Snap!

The noose tightened in an instant, binding Sinclaire’s entire body in a single bound.

“…! …! …! …!”

Unable to move, Sinclaire turned her head.

Killheel’s pointed heel came so close that it almost touched the surface of Sinclaire’s eyeball.

Seupas!

Sinclaire quickly jerked his head back to avoid Professor Sadi’s kick, but not the second one that followed.

…Pow!

A heavy middle kick.

Sinclaire didn’t need to see it to know that all of her ribs were broken, piercing her internal organ.

Sinclaire was sent flying through the air.

Like a kite with a broken string, she tumbled out of the arena.

At the same time, a status window popped up.

.

-Effective hits: 3 (1 point each)

-Effective dodges: 16 (1 point each)

-Effective Defense: 0 (1 point each)

-Critical hits: 0 (10 points each)

=Total score: 19 points

Top of the class. Never missing out on first place in any test, her total score was only 19 points.

Barely above average.

“Sinclaire!?”

A startled Dolores picked up the falling Sinclaire.

Heal Magic was cast on Sinclaire, who coughed up blood.

The professors rushed over and began to heal her.

Meanwhile, Sinclaire looked up at Dolores and smiled faintly.

“I’m sorry, Ms. President….”

“Don’t talk, Sinclaire, it takes time for your internals to heal!”

“Cough! Cough! I guess I won’t get the scholarship….”

At that, Dolores cried and held Sinclaire’s hand tightly.

For all we know, Dolores could pay Sinclaire’s tuition.

She was quite wealthy, coming from the prestigious Quovadis family.

But that wasn’t what mattered now.

It was about doing things on her own, whether it was exams or tuition, without anyone else’s help.

That’s what mattered to Sinclaire.

Then.

“Hohohoho-”

Laughter pierced the silence.

Professor Sadi. She was smiling broadly at Sinclaire’s tears.

“Are you crying because you didn’t get the scholarship, honey, I’ll pay for it, don’t cry about it, you’re not a beggar.”

Not an unknowing remark, but a knowing one. It made Sinclaire’s stomach flip twice.

Students and professors alike stiffen at Prof. Sadi’s words, like thorns on a tongue.

…But.

There was one person whose face didn’t change at all.

“….”

Vikir. He just stares at Professor Sadi with his usual expressionless face.

But.

Professor Sadi opened her mouth to speak, and Vikir’s expression finally broke through.

“Okay, let’s get right to it. Next on the agenda is class B of the Cold Warriors….”

Her flesh-colored eyes snapped open and rolled in Vikir’s direction.

Then her lips curved in a soft arc, crimson against her pale skin.

“Pigi. Come up?”